Right, that's it. So, yeah, I just want
one of these people to meet me today and
that's it. Simple. I just want one of
these people to meet me today and that's
it. And show me what they're about, bro.
Show me what they're [ __ ] about.
Because let me tell you something, bro.
I'm I'll I'll tell you exactly what I'm
going to do if one of these people don't
meet me today. If one of these people
don't meet me today, I'm going to tell
you exactly what I'm going to do, and
you're not going to like it as well.
Yeah. the next time I'm out this week,
next week, whatever. So, I'm gonna make
sure, bro, just just just do yourself a
favor. Yeah, please. You've been winding
people up now for years. Meet me one of
you today. Cuz if you don't meet me,
what if you don't meet what if one of
you don't meet me today, the next time I
argue with a woman, I'm going to put it
all over YouTube and it ain't going to
be nice and it's going to be an innocent
person. So, you pick. Want to use meet
me today? one of you meet me today or
the next woman I come across as a [ __ ]
I will bully the [ __ ] out of her, bro,
and make her cry. So, it's it's up to
you people. It's up to one of you
people, bro. You can either meet me and
not be cowards and we can sort this out
or the next woman I come across that's a
[ __ ] which will either be this week or
next week. I'm I'm going to bully the
[ __ ] out of them. So, it's it's it's up
to you really, bro. You either want to
do it the normal way or we can do it dirty. Simple.
and I will absolutely humiliate them
worse than the worse than the park one.
So, it's up to you really
and I will make you so mad that you're
gonna want to meet me, bro. So, it's
it's it's either it's either one of them
to be honest. You know, you you can either pick
[ __ ] little nerd. So, it's either you
meet me or that's what's going to happen
next time I Yeah. got
And I will do it, mate. And I will and I
will make one of you people meet me. I
because the police are not going to be
interested in your [ __ ] Yeah, just one
of you people. One of you people.
Obviously, we've got favorites. Yeah,
we've got favorites about like who we go
for and that miners fantasy stories
every day of the [ __ ] week, bro. If
one of these people do not meet me,
Grezy, the next woman I come across, I'm
going to absolutely bully the [ __ ] out
of her. I am going to absolutely bully
the [ __ ] out of her, the living [ __ ] out
of her, and it's going to make one of
these people meet me. So, it's either
it's either you meet me and we'll do it
normal or we do it dirty. Simple. So, if
anyone of these people not willing to
meet me today, the next video of a
woman, I'm going to humiliate her, bro.
So, at the end of the day, bro, it's up
to you. You either want to meet me and I
get one of you people, you know, or you
know what I'm saying?
or if you don't meet me, the next woman
I come across that's a [ __ ] I'm going
to [ __ ] put her in her place and I'm
going to scare the [ __ ] out of her and
there's not going to be no biasess. So,
it's up to you, bro. I want to do it in
a normal way. And that's how much I hate
these people. That's like that's the
that's the that's the lengths I'm going
through to meet one of you people. You
understand me, bro? Do you really understand me?
That's it. So, it's up to you what you
want to do. It's up to you completely
what you want to do, you know?
You going to meet me today? You just
said I'm skinn. Apparently, I've got £30
to last me a month. Okay, that's news to
me. I'm skinn. Okay, so come and meet me
today in London then. You're only 25
minutes away. You're the outskirts of
London. We're not asking for a [ __ ]
stone at your ass. So, if you're really
this big man, come and meet me then.
Simple. And if you don't meet me, I'm
just going to wind you up. I'm going to
wind you up with women bullying content.
And I'm going to avoid every man. And
this is what I'm going to do, Reeves.
I'm going to avoid I'm going to avoid
every man and go for women just to piss
them off, you know? Like, trust me, I'll
be a [ __ ] I'll be a nasty [ __ ] If you
don't want to meet me, I'll be a nasty
[ __ ] Simple. So, it's up to you, bro.
I'll piss in one of their face, bro, if
I have to. Like, trust me. Yeah. No, I'm
sick of it, Greg. I went on your video
and and these little comments by these
little nerds, bro. These little little
wet wipe little nerds living in their
mommy's basement in their 40s. Fat ugly
people that ain't got no [ __ ] life.
30 quid a month. Why are you talking
about 30 pounds a month? You must be
self-projecting. What the [ __ ] Where
are these people? Don't pee in their
face. I will do what I [ __ ] want to
do. I will do what the [ __ ] I want. I
will [ __ ] in their face. I just went
downstairs and said to my mom, I'll [ __ ]
in their face. So if you don't meet me,
So if you don't meet me, that's what's
going to happen.
I'm going to affect you by the videos
that I put up. with the videos that I
put up, I will affect you with with the
videos and I will make you want to meet
me. So, it's up to you really. So, you
know, if it has to be that way, it has
to be that way.
Yeah. I don't give a [ __ ] I don't give
Yeah. Shut up, you fat old man. Gona.
Gona in the kitty. Shut the [ __ ] up, you
Welsh monk. By the way, I'll be in
Cardiff New Year's Eve, by the way. Uh,
everyone knows that. So, we'll see what
you're really about, fat man. In the
Caliban caught up with the shagger and
the sheep. Make sure you're not shagging
the sheep, mate. When I'm there, please.
Please, mate. Make sure you're not
[ __ ] shagging sheeps, you [ __ ]
Welsh sheep shagger. When I [ __ ] when
I [ __ ] come there New Year's Eve.
Yeah, bro. I'm coming New Year's Eve.
I'm coming New Year's Eve. And you know
how I know that you people are [ __ ]
right? Because how long have you been
arguing with me? Right. Yeah. Listen,
listen, listen. How long have you people
been arguing with me, right? Before I
rearrange this, right? Let me let me let
me let me let me just say something,
right? This is how you know these people
on here are [ __ ] Grezy, how long,
right, have we been arguing with these
people? And the only people that have
left their area is me and London Taylor.
And I don't even like [ __ ] London
Taylor. But we're the only Have you
noticed that we're the only people that
have left our area.
See, but none of these people have Kevin
Gona because they're all [ __ ] It's
the same thing as it's because they're
all [ __ ] It's the same as Kevin
Murphy. They're all soft little [ __ ]
you know? They could never took it upon
themselves to leave their area and try
to meet other people. So yeah, we should meet uh 400 p.m.
I'll [ __ ] whoop your ass. I'll whoop
your ass and then uh yeah, that's that.
And then I'll get on with what I'm
doing. So yeah, lovely 400 p.m. So it's
funny how you go and Kevin and all these
other people can't even leave your [ __ ] area.
Yeah. People from London are [ __ ]
The people from London are [ __ ] Yep.
Yep. And then we'll move over to a
field. Bro, you're not going to beat me.
You're a fat old man. Please stop it.
You're a fat old man. Yeah. Yeah, I
agree. Yeah. Yeah. New Year's Eve.
Yeah. So, why is it that none of you
mongos have left your area anyways?
Why? Why have none of you No, no, let me
let me tell Let me ask you this
question. Let me ask you this question,
big man. because we've already arranged
this now. I'm coming now. Why is it that
none of you people have left your area
to come on someone's door yet you state
that you got a problem with someone?
Answer this. Answer this. Answer this.
Answer this. Answer me this question,
bro. You say about how people have been
there and they ain't called you out.
Like, you've got the same excuses. Nah,
you got the same excuses, bro. Over and
over again. Over again. But bro, you
ain't ever been on anyone's door, bro.
You've never been on anyone's door, bro.
Like, I lived by myself for 8 months.
You knew it. Where was you, bro? Where
was I'm I'm just putting this out there.
I'm not trying to get out of anything.
I'm putting this out there. How [ __ ]
you people are. Yeah, LJ flew flew to
another country and he done absolutely
nothing. We're not going to get into
that again. We're not going to get into
that LJ thing again. That is a weak
excuse, right? Wales is barely another
country. You're a train ride away. So if
you really knew someone lived by themsel
like I did, bro, you would have come.
You would have come. You're about
nothing. And it's going to be and it's
going to be proven New Year's Eve that
you're about nothing.
You know, I'm not going to explain the
neighbor thing again. I've already
explained it. I've already explained the
neighbor thing again. Look, see, I've
already explained these things. You're
bringing up people and I've already
explained it. You're just using other
people to get out of it.
So you you bro, the only reason I've not
done anything to the neighbor is because
my mom lives here, you [ __ ] idiot. My
mom lives here, [ __ ] Yeah, my mom,
not me, lives here, [ __ ] So if I
was to fight anyone, she's she's going
to lose the [ __ ] house. You [ __ ]
stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah, you you
this is what I mean. You people are full
of excuses. Excuses. Excuses. Excuses.
Yeah. And what about that bouncer that
shot himself? And what about them four
people that shot himself?
Bro, if it was my house, then I would
Yeah, I stuck it on two gay people
before when I lived at the old house cuz
it was my house. You understand? Dick
head. Yeah. Anyways, we'll see what
you're about New Year's Eve anyways, you [ __ ] idiot.
Yeah, but you make excuses, bro. You
knew where I lived. You knew I lived by
myself and you didn't do anything.
You're a [ __ ] You've got more anxiety
than anyone. You Kevin, do you know what
I'm saying, bro? Like, you're you're uh
I just don't like these people in this
community ghosted. I just don't like these people.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's not what
happened though, was it, Gona? I told
them to [ __ ] But listen, Gona,
I told them to [ __ ] back to Newcastle
and they didn't even stand up.
I told them to [ __ ] off back to
Newcastle and they didn't even stand up. That happened.
>> This is what I mean. You're constantly
full of excuses. This is what I mean, bro.
Definitely not what happened. I told
them to well I man [ __ ] off back to
Newcastle and I told them that my train
is worth more than that outfit. Goona,
that's not what happened. That's not
what happened. Take your bias goggles
off. You kitty jagging gallivan man.
Bro, stop it. That's not what's
happened. I told them to [ __ ] off back
to where they come from, Newcastle, and
to mind their own [ __ ] business. But
you make up stuff, bro. If they were any
man, they would have stood up, bro. They
made I told them to [ __ ] off and call
them an ugly [ __ ] I done nothing. I
done nothing. I said that you're an ugly
[ __ ] and my trainers are worth more than
your whole outfit. I said that you're an
ugly [ __ ] What do you mean I done
nothing? What do you mean I done
nothing? Goona, you're so full of [ __ ]
You're so full of [ __ ] It's so obvious
now that you're trying to reflect. Bro,
you didn't come to London once when I
lived by myself. Bro, you're not about
that life, old man. Yeah, [ __ ] Laney.
[ __ ] other people. I was living by
myself for 9 months. Where was you?
You're not about that life. Anything
that you say is embarrassing now, bro.
You're a train away from Mryland
station. Where was you, big man? Where
was you, big man? You was nowhere. So,
no one can take you seriously, mate. [ __ ] idiot.
Bro, why are you licking LT's ass,
Smokeoky B? Anyways, are you meeting me
today or what? Anyways, [ __ ] all this.
Are you meeting me today or not?
about I done nothing. I said that
they're an ugly [ __ ] and to [ __ ] off
back to Newcastle. Excuses after excuses
after excuses after excuses after
excuses after excuses after excuses
after excuses. That's what it is with
you people. Even when you're proven
wrong. Well, like I said, if none of you
meet me today, I'm going to the next
woman I come across that's a [ __ ] I'm
going to absolutely humiliate her. I'm
going to humiliate her so badly that
you're going to want to meet me. So,
like I said, bro, back to the original
thing of today. If none of you little
nerds want to meet me, you spend enough
time on YouTube doing what you do. If
none of you want to meet me today, the
next [ __ ] woman I come across, I'm going
to absolutely bully that woman. And I'm
going to make you meet me, bro. It's
going to be so disturbing that it's
going to want to make you meet me. So,
at the end of the day, right, bro, no
woman bullied me on the train. I said
that she looks like a crackhead, mate.
Again, get your bias goggles off. I said
that she looks like a crackhead. a
clapped ugly crackhead. Again, Smokey B
making up stuff. Yeah.
Uh Doing, have you ignored all the
things they've done to me? Again, Grezy,
this is where you come into this. This
is the whole part of dismissing
struggles. Uh this is the whole part of
people dismissing struggles now, Grezy.
Um we need your presence. I know you
don't like me, you know, bringing you up
and stuff, but this is where people
dismiss people's struggles. the whole
part of and I know Triple H is a brother
and I know Triple H is a cool guy but he
is guilty of dismissing people's struggles.
Oh, you haven't seen what they've done.
Well, do you know what, bro? If you're
that ignorant that you didn't watch the
videos, then I'm not going to explain it
to you. Well, if you're ignorant, I'm
not I'm not going to sit here and
explain it to you because you know what
they've done. You know what they're
like. Why am I going to sit here and
start explaining it to you when we all
know you've seen the videos? So anyways,
um but yeah, when I come across a woman
again that's a [ __ ] there's no there's
not going to be no holding back, bro.
There's not going to be no holding back. Yeah.
Okay. So, you didn't see all the
screenshots. So, you didn't see all the
approaches. You didn't see all the
[ __ ] that have got attitude. Really?
I find that hard to believe. Over all of
these years, you didn't see any of that,
bro. You didn't see any of that stuff. Really?
talk about dismissing people's
struggles, but the next woman I come
across, we're going to see who the bully
is Smokey Me. We're going to see the
bully and you're going to do nothing.
So, at the end of the day, bro, your
your um your uh you're not going to meet
me and you're thinking that you've won,
but this the next video that I put out
is going to be so disturbing that you're
going to want to meet me. It's going to
be worse than the one in the park. It's
going to be worse than the one in the park.
And it's going to be worse than that
woman in a part. I'm going to bully the
[ __ ] out of her and no man's going to do
nothing. Yeah. Simple. Yeah. Simple.
That's all right, bro.
You know. Yeah. I'm overweight.
Definitely not overweight. Definitely
don't drink alone. Uh Goona, talking
about yourself there, bro. Hold on. Hold
on. Hold on one second. Bro, you're
calling me overweight.
You're calling me overweight, bro. Put
yourself on camera. One second. One
second. One second. One second. Hold on
a minute. One second. You're calling me
over. Wait, bro. Put yourself on camera
right now and show everyone what you
look like. One second. One second. No
one talk, please. One second. One
second. One second.
One second. You're You're calling me
overweight. Okay. Let me put Let me put
a link up. Right. Let this guy join. One
sec, bro. Hold [snorts] on. One second.
You're You're calling me overweight, Una.
Let's try and get this live stream up.
And you say that you don't project.
Right. Trying to hang out right now.
Trying to hang out right now and show
everybody what you look like. [gasps]
Right. Didn't own a woman on a train.
Anyways, Kevin, when are you coming to
London, [ __ ] boy? Like me and LT went
to [ __ ] Liverpool multiple times and
we went to Manchester multiple times.
When when is when is it your turn to
come to London? One second. Just chill,
bro. Anyways, Luna, come in the hangouts
and show your face. Come in your
hangout. Come in the hangouts and show your face.
Show what you look like. Don't Don't
type. Show what you look like. Come on.
Come on. Come on. You've just said that
I'm overweight. Okay. Come in and show
yourself and prove that you're not
projecting, mate. I've already had the
balls to come to you, you little bongo,
and you shat your pants just like
everyone else in Liverpool. I came to
you and you shat your pants. I traveled
250 mi there, 250 mi back, and you shat
your pants. You all shut the [ __ ] up.
You ran away. Me and LT owned the whole
of Liverpool. What are you talking
about? Me and LT went to Liverpool
around the same time and we all had you
running, you [ __ ] stealth prick. And
you still haven't been to London. You
still have not been to London. And I
don't even like London Taylor. But here
we go. Bro, we went to you and you shat your pants.
You shat your [ __ ] knick-knocks. You cheeky sod.
Yeah. 30 to last me to Christmas. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. That's that that's news to
me. Even though I get money every week.
Yeah. I got 30 to last me to Christmas.
Smokey be talking about himself again, people.
He's self projected again. I think he's
done his bollocks in you know.
Kevin, when are you coming to London?
We've already been to Liverpool. Come
on, man. We went We've already been to
Liverpool. Why don't you come to London,
man? Mate, how can I have 30 to last me
a month? If I got money every week, it
wouldn't even be possible. Even if I d
my balls and you I think you're talking
about yourself. Anyways, are you coming
to London today? Well, like I said, if
none of you meet me, if none of you meet
the next woman I come across, it's going
to be a banging video. It is going to be
a banger. It is going to be a banger. 10
times worse than Timmy's. So, you either
meet me, you either meet me or the next
woman I come across, I'm going to bully
the [ __ ] out of her. So, it's I I'm I'm
giving this a fair offer. I'm giving
this a fair offer, bro. I'm wanting to
meet any man today on this community.
I'm I'm making it a good offer, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. But Oh, but it's okay when
other people ghosting to do it, don't
they? I What about all of the people
I've tried to meet before? Biasness
again. Biasness again. Listen, bro. I
told you where I'm going to be today. We
all know a lot of you people live in
London. And there's no reason why you
can't come to London. There's no reason
why Smoky B can't come to London.
So if you don't uh if you don't meet me
today, the next woman I come across,
she's getting bullied. So it's it's straight.
But yeah, I I'm saying that I want to
fight you. Yeah. Yeah. I know. I know.
But I'm saying I want to fight you. But
I want to fight you. Yeah. I want to
fight you. You little fat ugly little
nerds. You fat ugly little disabled
virgins that can't get off YouTube. I
want to fight you. I want to fight you.
That's my wish for Christmas. I want to
fight you. And guess what? If none of
you meet me, I'm going to bully the next
woman that I meet and I'm going to scare
the [ __ ] out of her. So don't say I
didn't warn you. Don't say I didn't warn
you, bro. Don't say I didn't warn you.
You either meet me or the next woman I'm
going to bully the [ __ ] out of and
degrade her. So it I'm giving you the
option. I am giving you the option right
here, right now. You either meet me or
the next woman is getting bullied and
I'm going to make her cry and I'm going
to talk about her vagina, how she needs
to get this. Bro, just meet me. Trust
me, it ain't going to be nice. Yeah,
simple. It ain't gonna be nice. So
that's that. Yeah, because the last time
I went to Milton Kings, you didn't show up. So yeah.
So if you don't meet me, that's what's
going to happen. That's the end of that.
That's the end of that, basically.
So, that's the end of that. Anyways, so
don't say I didn't warn you. It's not
very hard to get into these uh situations.
I just don't like these people in this
community, bro. I don't gamble. I don't
I don't lost money. I didn't lose money.
I haven't even left the [ __ ] house.
Barely even check. I just don't like
these people in this community. I just
don't like these people of this community.
I just don't like these people in this community.
I don't like any of them on this
community. And you need to ask yourself
this question. Why didn't Kevin Murphy
come to London? That was after I'm pretty sure.
When did L come? Yeah, it was the same
round time about Liverpool, wasn't it?
That this was before L J went to the
door. But guess what? But guess what?
Kevin Murphy didn't come to London. Guan
didn't come to London even before that
Lord J thing. So it's like, bro, you
ain't even got any balls in this
community. You're just little weasels.
You're just little weasels. That's all
you are. You're just little weasels, you
know, because we all know that if you
people was about anything, you'd have
the same mind as me. And I don't even
claim to be about much. And you haven't
even been to London. So, it's just
embarrassing. It's just [ __ ]
embarrassing. And this was all before
the LJ thing. This was all before the LJ
thing, you know. And LJ didn't even do
anything when he came. He just he done
nothing but shut himself and stood
behind a gate, mate. So, it's all
excuses with you people. It's all
excuses with you little mongrels. We've
heard it for years now. We've heard it
for years. We've heard it for years with
you disabled autistic people. We've
heard it for years now, bro. Years.
What? Did you play Frankie today or
something, Kevin? You must be self
projecting. I don't I haven't played
Frankie for a very very long time. I
don't know what you're talking about.
You must be talking about yourself. You
people on here really talk about
yourself, lad. You people on here really
do talk about yourselves. The [ __ ] that
you come out with, the [ __ ] that you
come out with is insane.
The shite that you come out with, man,
is is madness. 30 to last summer of the
month. The [ __ ] that you come out with.
Jesus Christ. It just goes to show how
disabled you are really. Is it? It just
goes to show how disabled you are.
It just goes to show how disabled you
people really, really, really are.
disabled skinned people when we all know
that you are the ones that are skinned
because if you weren't skinned why
haven't you come to London and just
squash the whole thing lad
yeah you people don't bully no one yeah
you people don't I mean you can't even
meet me you can't even meet me bully me
you can't even meet me you can't even
[ __ ] meet me I mean bro you don't bully no
Yeah, you bully me. Did you bully me
when I was in Liverpool, Kevin?
Did you bully me when I was in
Liverpool, you scouse [ __ ] Did you
bully me when I was in your city, you
scouse [ __ ] and you ran away and I made
you run away and LT had you making
excuses? Did you bully me when I went to
your city and you done nothing? 250 mi.
No, you didn't, you scout [ __ ] Did you
bully me when I was in Manchester a
million times, which is only 40 minutes
away from you? No, you didn't. You scout
[ __ ] So, I think you've got you've
definitely got it like mixed up, lad. So, yeah.
So, yeah. Anyways, so why didn't you
come out when I was in Liverpool anyways, lad?
You [ __ ] prick. You [ __ ] prick.
Sucking a dick when you're [ __ ]
talking. sucking a dick when you're
talking. You're [ __ ] prick. Come to
Liverpool. And then when somebody comes
to Liverpool, you [ __ ] yourself. You
done it when I went there and you done
it when LT went there. You both You all
done it, mate. Everyone saw it. Everyone
remembers that January. Everybody
remembers that January, mate, when
nothing was going on
and you was nowhere to be seen. You was
nowhere to be seen. You was nowhere to
be seen. But you know what? It's okay
now because like I said, I'm going to do
that video now. None of you people are
meeting me. None of you people are
meeting me. So, I'm going to do that
woman video the next time I come across
one. And whenever you people get doxed,
I will just wait now. I will just sit
there and I'll wait until one of you get
doxed. I will wait until one of you get
doxed. Oh, it's going to happen. It is
going to happen. It is definitely
definitely definitely going to happen.
It is definitely definitely no friends,
no house, no car, no assets. It's not
nice to talk about yourself like that.
Big cheese. It's not nice to put
yourself down like that talking about
yourselves. Like, bro, just cut the cat.
We all know that you're talking about
yourselves. This is why you spend all
your lives on YouTube because those are
all the things that you don't have.
That's your life. That's your projection
life. No friends, no job. That's you.
That's you skin people. And there's
evidence of it because you're on YouTube
every day. That's you people. That's
self-proing. Because anybody that's got
a life and got all of these things don't
sit on YouTube every day. That's
yourselves you're talking about. That's
why you're on here every day. Like how
how well I don't go on certain channels
anymore, right? But how many times do
you come on here? Yeah. Saying that
saying that um you've got this, you've
got that. If you had all these things,
bro, you wouldn't be on here. That [ __ ]
everything up. If you had all of this
money, you wouldn't be sat on YouTube
being a little nerd every day and nerd
behind the screen. Everyone knows it,
bro. It's It's trying to lie now is just
embarrassing. Trying to lie now is just completely embarrassing.
You've got all of this money, but you're
sat on YouTube every day. Make it make
sense because it doesn't. It really,
really doesn't. You come on here saying
that you've got a life, this, that, and
the other, bro, but you're sat on
YouTube every day. Make it make sense.
And it's also, well, it's what you do on
here as well. It's not just that you're
on here. It's what you actually do on
here. You're on here every single day,
bro, in your 30s, 40s hating on people
that you don't know. But you've got all
of this money and life, bro. Make it
make sense. Just make the Just make the
thing make sense when you're saying it.
Then people will be more inclined to
believe it. You people are fat, ugly,
skint nerds. And that's why you don't
put your cameras on. And listen, I've
got no problem. Listen, let hear me out.
I've got no problem showing proof of
purchase because you tried to say that I
get my stuff from Colano and this place
and that place and this place. You tried
to say that I I um I I get I pay
monthly. I can show you purchases. Not a
problem. When you show your face and you
prove that you're not an ugly [ __ ] and
what I'm saying about you is wrong, I'll
gladly prove anything you want. I'll
show money. I'll show proof. I'll show
proof of all of the things that I
bought. But you can't do that because
you're fat and ugly. And it's the truth.
What I'm saying about you is the truth.
You knows that you're fat and ugly. You
know that you're little mongos. That's
why you can't come on the hangouts. and
why you can't talk cuz you're fat ugly
nerds. And it hits a no, I'll gladly
show you stuff that you want to see.
Bro, if you come on the Hangouts and you
show your face and prove that you're not
an ugly [ __ ] and Peter Bell is wrong
about you, bro, that's fine. [snorts]
Yeah, but it's okay for what women do.
So, ghosting, it's okay for women to be
toxic. It's okay for women to have
attitude. And it's okay for women to
lead people on. But you don't see any
problem with that? Really?
I [snorts] don't think me and you are
going to get on too well, bro.
Hate to break it to you. I'm not going
to start calling you out or anything,
but but you don't think any of the stuff
that they do is wrong, but you think a
verbal thing is wrong. What they do is
disgusting. But again, we're not You're
probably one of these people that are
just going to dismiss people's struggles
no matter what people show you. We
stopped doing this, bro, ages ago.
You think that's disgusting?
You think that's disgusting, but you
don't think any of the things that they
do is disgusting and vile and toxic?
Really, bro? Really? Really, bro?
Toxic is a word. Really?
Yeah. Well, if if normal people had the
experiences that I had, they would.
Yeah. Women are not normal, but women
are not normal. So, you're saying about
normal people, women are not normal.
They lead people on. They're toxic.
They're horrible. Women are not normal.
So if I wish stuff on people that are
not normal, I mean normal people. Women
are not normal. So I don't know what
people that you're referring to.
You know, someone tells me that you're a
little white knight thinking that you're
going to get laid cuz they're the only
Okay, let me Okay, let me Okay, let me
give you an example, right? Let me give
you an example. Let me give you an
example. Ghost, right? Did you hear that
man on the train? He got his head he he
got his head crossed in the door. He
defended that woman just for being a
woman. No other reason. Even though we
was both as bad as each other. We was
both as bad as each other. He defended
that woman just for having a [ __ ] in
between her legs. No other reason. No
other no other reason because he thought
that the woman was going to like him. It's pathetic.
So anyways, Ghost, no opinions on them
leading people on being toxic. No, just
just dismiss it. Yeah, just dismiss it.
Yeah. Just just dismiss it. Yeah. Women
are innocent. Women are perfect, aren't
they? Yeah. Yeah. Women are perfect.
Hey, I didn't need to do nothing. He got
his head crushed in the door, mate. He's
got He got his head crossed in the door, [laughter]
mate. His head got crushed in the door.
I didn't need to do anything. Palmer got
him. Palmer [ __ ] got him,
mate. He's got He's got his head crushed
in the door. Everyone's laughing at him.
I didn't need to do anything. As he went
to walk out the train, he got his head
crushed in the door like a spaz. I
didn't need to do anything.
Willow, they don't find you attractive
either, you little virgin. They hate you
as well. You know what the maddest thing
is, right? All of these people that are
trying to defend women, women hate them.
They're still virgins. But where they're
so autistic, I'm not lying. He literally
got his head crushed in the door. I'm
pretty sure if you can actually watch
it, you would actually hear his head got
crushed in the door. Mate, his head got
crushed in the door like a spaz. I don't
care what he done. That would teach him
for defending somebody for just having a
[ __ ] bro. That's Do you not believe in
karma, bro? He got his head crushed in
for defending somebody for having a
[ __ ] He deserved it. You know what I'm
saying? You know, Juno, when you come in
and show us your face, I'll answer you,
right? You said I was overweight. If you
come in and show us your face and show
us your weight, I'll answer any question
that you want.
Jesus. No, he didn't. But he didn't owe
I I said I'll talk to her how I want. He
owed me. I said no, I will say what I
want. I said I will say what I want. No,
he didn't. I said that I will say what I
want. Listen to it properly. Do I need
to get back on the TV again? I said that
I will say what I want. If somebody
talks to me like that, I will say what I
want. I answered back. I was arguing
with two people. I will say what I want
and that's exactly what I said and I
will say what I want. So
anyways, back to you
ghosting. What about them leading people
on and being toxic? Is that not vile and disgusting?
What about what women do? Let's talk
about what they do for a change. You
know, I'm not answering you. When you
come in and you show us your fat belly
and your fat old man face, then you can
come in and ask me questions.
When you come in and you show your fat
ugly face and your fat belly, then you
can start coming in and show me asking
me questions. Until then, bar off, you
little [ __ ] spaz. Right. So, anyways,
yeah, she offered me a fight. Huh? Nice
one. Anyways, so what I'm saying,
Ghosting, you're saying about what I'm
saying is disgusting, but I'm asking
you, what about all of the things that
they do that I've just listed?
Leading on, being toxic, being nasty.
I'll give you a story, ghost him. Right?
I'll give you a story, lad. And this
wasn't even about me, by the way. Right?
And I can I can tell you a few more
stories, right? Just listen to me if you
want. Right now, I'm pretty sure I told
you this before. Maybe I didn't tell you
this before. Listen. Listen. And this
weren't even about me.
No, I think it was the second last time.
I think it was near Halloween. I can't
remember exactly. It was about a month
and a half. It was month It was a month
and a half ago. And I approached this
woman with this guy. She turned around
and said he needs to fix his fat
forehead before going and approaching
women. Now, you just said that wishing
the R word on people is disgusting. And
that weren't even about me. And I just
stopped talking to the whole group. When
she said that, when she said that, when
she said that ghosting, I just left
them, bro. I was like, "Nah, bro." Even
though it weren't about me, it was about
this other guy. Now, you're saying, One
second. One second. You're sat there and
saying that if somebody wants to wish
the Rword on someone, that's disgusting.
But it's okay for women to try to bully
people that they don't know. Make it
make sense. Yeah. And it weren't even
about me, bro. And that I swear on my
dead dad, that wasn't even about me.
I've never been told about a forehead in
my life. But that's okay. It's okay for
a woman to bully someone that they don't
know. But as soon as you swap the women,
disgusting by you, make it make sense,
bro. Yeah. Make it make sense. And it
weren't even about me, bro. It wasn't
even about me. It wasn't even about me.
Well, what they do is disgusting. And
what they do is disgusting. Yeah. So you
think it's okay. So what would how would
you feel? Right. Okay. Okay. So how
would you feel? How would you feel, bro?
How would you feel if I went on the
street today and said, "This woman is a
fat ugly pig for no reason." Yeah. No,
it wasn't about me. Bro, stop avoiding.
Stop avoiding. So it's okay for a woman
to be a bully [ __ ] but you're not
allowed to say anything back to them.
Bro, you don't make the rules. You don't
make the rules. She said that this guy
had a fat forehead and needs to sort his
forehead before talking to women. Don't
even try to defend them. The fact that
there's there's people out there like
that, right? No, bro. It's comparable
because they're nasty little [ __ ]
Because they're nasty, dirty bully
little [ __ ] So, whatever is said back
to them, don't start playing the victim.
Don't start playing the victim. You
know, it's like me being on It's like me
going on the street and being racist and
then moaning that I got stabbed. Oh, you
took it a bit too far. You stabbed me.
No, bro. It is comparable.
So, anything about that woman talking
about that guy's forehead and it weren't
about me. Trust me, it weren't about me.
Because if it was about me, you would
have known about it. No problem. No
problem at all. Is that completely fine?
Is that completely fine? So, is that
completely fine then? Women to go around
with attitude and you can't say anything
back because let's let's put let's put
it this way, Ro. It's not about rape, is
it? It's It's not about rape. If anyone
said anything, you'd be defending them.
So, I don't know why we we're going back
to rape because rape is not the problem.
Even if somebody never said rape, even
if someone never said rape, you'd still
be defending them. So, the rape thing is
just I don't even know why we're talking
about that because even if you said that
they're an ugly [ __ ] that deserves to
die, you'd be like, "Oh, you're saying
to a woman." So, I mean, the rape thing
is irrelevant. [laughter]
So, do you know what I'm saying?
So you're dismissing you're dismissing
about the women TALKING ABOUT PEOPLE'S
WHY DO YOU keep dismissing what women do
you people on here
Joe why do you keep dismissing all the
bad things they do can I ask you a
serious question now no overalking why
do you keep dismissing all what they do
and then when someone says back you have
a [ __ ] you you know you you get your
knickers in a twist why do you do that
I'm I'm asking you generally why you're
doing it you know I' i'm i'm asking you
a podcast. I I'm thinking of starting a
podcast. I want to know why you keep
defending these women. Like nothing
about my experiences. I want to know why
you keep doing it. I'm asking I'm asking
you why you keep defending them for just
being a woman. What is your what is the
what is the end goal here? I'm asking
you I'm asking you why you're doing it. Huh?
What are you talking about, Joe?
Me and this guy approached this woman
and she turned around and said that I'm
handsome and he's ugly. He's got a big
ugly forehead and he needs to stop
speaking to women um before he before he
sorts his forehead out. So what is it
okay for women to bully people but you
can't say anything back? [ __ ] the rape
[ __ ] Is is that your logic then? Like
I'm trying to understand. I'm trying to
understand. I'm I'm understand. No no no
no no no. But the difference is no no no
no no. The difference is it's somebody
that you don't know. It's somebody that
you don't know. You know, it's somebody
that you don't know. So again, you're
dismissing everything that women do. As
per usual, this is what I mean with
these people. You dismiss everything
that they do. You love defending women.
And I don't know why you do it. They
don't like you. They're never going to
sleep with you. Why are you doing it?
Why are you doing it? Why are you doing
it? Why do you continuously defend and
simp over women? I'm asking you to I'm
asking you, Joe, why you're doing it.
Why are you doing it?
Okay, then. Okay. Right. Right. So, if I
go to the mall Okay. Okay. Okay. One
second. Okay. Right. Right. So, if I go
to a mall today and I start picking on
women, no one's going to have a problem
with it then. Okay. Yeah. Some of
Because they're entitled to Okay. Okay.
Okay. So, if I go in the mall today and
I start picking on women, you're not
going to have a problem with it. No.
You're not going to have a problem with
it. So, you're not going to have a
problem. I mean, they're not telling
somebody to sod off. They're insulting
them. I mean, they're insulting them.
Don't act like you're stupid, mate.
You're not as stupid as you look.
They're not telling them to sod off.
They are insulting them. They are
insulting them. Let's see if I go around
the shopping mall today and I start and
I haven't gambled.
If I gambled, I would have told you that I gambled.
You know, you love women because you
don't get women. The only people that
sit there and say they love women is
people that don't get women. That's what
I'm trying to say. It's the people
that's never had a woman. It's so
[ __ ] obvious. It's so because I
wouldn't say this stuff. I've had more
women than everyone on this community.
And I believe what I say and I've never
had to suck up to them ever. But they're
not telling. So anyways, Joe, if I go
around, it is 100% true. 1 million%. I
have had more women than people in this
community. And it is absolutely true.
The way these people sit there and
defend women, it's obvious they've never
had women. It's so obvious. It's so
obvious. It is so obvious. Speaking from
someone that's traveled up and down the country, right?
It's so obvious. It is so obvious. It's
so obvious that these people don't get
women. The way they defend them. And
that's and I was saying to my boy as
well earlier is that simp is not going
to get you laid. I don't know how many
times you have to tell these people
defending them they don't like you.
They're not going to sleep with you.
They're not going to like you. And no
matter how many times you tell them,
they still seem to do it.
So at the end of the day, I don't know,
bro. It's it's crazy. It's actually
madness. They defend them. And the irony
is they've had less than you. people.
Real men don't simp over no [ __ ]
women, mate. I was I was saying this to
Oreo man. I was saying this to Oreo man.
Not all women aren't the same. Yes, they
are all the same. All women are 100% the
same. 1 million% they are the same. They
are 100% the same. And I will prove my
life on it. And I will and I will bet my
life on it. I will bet my life on it
that they are 100% the same. It's so
obvious. It's so obvious. Act the same.
Say the same stuff. same attitude 1
million% O'Reilly they are wall the same
thing and you're not going to and and
the thing is what I say Joe is anyways
what what I'm saying Joe yes they are w
evil yes they are w evil and again I've
given them the benefit of the doubt to
prove me wrong and they haven't so again
whatever you say or whatever you
whatever you say whatever you say and
whatever you say and no matter what I
say it's irrelevant I've gave them the
benefit of the doubt so whatever you say
I'm not interested cuz I've given them
time and time and time and time and time
through their wrong.
So [snorts] what's it go? If a woman
wants to abuse you after be okay. So can
I go and abuse them then? Okay. So can I
Right. About women aren't all the same.
Women are 100 million% all the same.
It's so obvious. People that are not the
same don't act say and do the same
things. Mate, I've met more women than
you ghosting. Believe you me, mate. I'm
telling you right now that I have met
more women than you and they are exactly
truly the same. And that's why I don't
bother with them because they're all the
same. Why would you bother with people
that are all the [ __ ] same
it's it's madness.
Okay. All right. Okay. So, it's okay to
ins So, your logic, Joe, then if
somebody approaches you first, you can insult them.
Really? Nah, you're trying [ __ ] You're
trolling it. So your logic is that if
somebody So you can actually insult them.
So you can insult them and that's fine.
Really, bro? Really?
Really? Is that really what you're
saying? You've got friends. I've got
into relationships. Good for them, bro.
Good for them, man. That's nice for you.
I'm I'm I'm not saying that you need to
meet other women. I'm telling you I'm
telling you that I have met loads and
loads and loads of women and they are
exactly all the same. I have a boyfriend
I'm not interested or people that lead
you on and people that's got attitude.
There's nothing ever any different. They
are all the same.
What's the day today? Monday. Yeah. So
yeah, they are literally literally all
the same. They are literally all the
same. They are literally all the same.
They do and say and act exactly the same
way. It's too obvious. They're all the same.
Games, mind games, attitude. No, they're
100% all the same. 100% all the same.
They're NPCs. It's so obvious. They're
NPCs. They're non-playing characters.
They're completely non-playing characters.
Why do some No, no, no, no. Okay. Well,
I would explain it to you. Okay. I would
explain it to you. Why do they give Why
do some num Why do they give numbers and
some don't? Okay. So, what do they do
when they give their number? Goona.
Okay. Goona. So, what do they do when
they give their number? Okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. So, what do they
do? Right. So, what do they do when they
give their number? What do they all do
when they give their number? You know,
with these women that give us their
numbers, do you want me to tell you what
they all do? They play toxic mind games
and lead people on. They are all the
same. They are all the same. You know,
that just goes to show that they are all
the [ __ ] same.
And men are not the same as them.
Because if if it weren't just women, men
would be doing the same thing. So, at
the end of the day, Yeah. Okay. They
give their number. What do they do when
they give their number, bro? What do
they do when they give their number?
What do they do when they give their
number, Gona? They do exactly the same
old [ __ ] They are all the same. I've
literally got messages that are the same
as another message from a different
person. They are literally all the same.
So, um yeah, that's it. So many white
knights on here. So many simps. I really
hope that you people are just trolling
me, bro. Cuz there's no way these people
can sit here and keep defending women
and women don't like them and they're
virgins and they still defend them.
Maybe it's the way they were brought up
by their dad. Who [ __ ] knows, lad.
You It's not different outcomes. It's
the same. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's not different outcomes. It's the
same outcome. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. It's not
different outcomes. It's the same
outcome. You only get numbers when
they're in bars and clubs. So, no.
So, yeah. So at the end of the day, um,
no, you get numbers in bars and clubs.
Yeah. And they all do the same thing. So
they are all the same. If they weren't
all the same, they wouldn't do all the same stuff.
So that's that.
Oh, I've already explained this to you.
Oh my god. I've already explained this
to you. Oh my god. I've already
explained this to you, bro, a million
times. You're making me tired. Oh,
okay. What do these people say? when you
approach them in public. Okay, let let
me All right. Okay. Okay. So, what do
these women do when you approach them in
public? Pretend they've got a boyfriend,
give you attitude, I'll [ __ ] you.
They are all the same. They say the same
stuff. Why are so many people saying the
same stuff that are apparently
different? Because they are all the
same. I put it like this. If anyone was
any anything like me, I'd be very, very,
very concerned. acted the same way, said
the same stuff. I would be very, very
concerned. But yet, you've got all of
these women acting the same way, doing
the same stuff, saying the same stuff,
but they're not all the same. Get out of
here, bro. Get out of here. Get out of
here. But anyways, you little white
knights and you little simps, you have
your opinion on what you want. Keep
being virgins. Keep thinking that it's
going to get you laid. Um, that's your
life. Like I said, I'm not here to to
convince anyone anything, you know.
So, we're moving on from this now.
Anyways, I don't know why the thing the
whole thing is going this whole
conversation is weird because I've
proved I've given them proved. Sorry.
I've given them the benefit of the doubt
a million times. So, what you're saying
is nonsense. What you're saying is completely nonsense.
Yeah. And I've gave them the benefit of
the doubt for years, Ghosting. And
that's what makes me think they're all
the same. So, again, we're moving on
from this now. I'm not talking about
this now. So no one wants to meet me.
Okay. So when I get into it again,
there's no holding back. Simple.
Right. Anyways, moving on from this now.
So I've given them the benefit of the
doubt a million times. So whatever you
say is irrelevant. So moving on now. Um
when someone does start again, which it
won't be it won't be long. I'm not
holding back. So don't say I didn't warn
you. You're saying something could doing another.
Okay. We're moving on from this now. Anyways,
anyways, we're moving on from this now. Anyways,
yeah, we're moving on from this. Anyways,
anyways, moving on now.
I need to get a new charger.
Right. Ban all these little mongos now.
Anyways, little tastics.
You're saying one thing, but they're proving another.
So, I don't understand the whole point
of this. We got white knights trying to
tell you to think different.
But women prove they're all the same.
So, whatever they say, you're saying one
thing, they're proving another. You know,
it's mad. You just They dismiss people's
struggles, Douglas. They literally
dismiss people's struggles. I think
they've got autism. I generally think
that these people on here have got autism.
It's got to be autism, bro. It's got to
be autism. So maybe autism is probably
like more common than they say. They've
got Why? I would love to know. Uh
I would love to know. Yeah, I would love
to know where it comes from. People sat
there that have to defend women. Where
does the desire come from to defend
women that don't like you?
Where it comes from to people that
defend women that hate them. I've never
I've never understood it. I would I
don't think I ever will to be honest
with you. They don't get women. They've
had less women than you, but they still
sit there and defend them.
Maybe upbringing maybe from their dad
maybe. I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know what it is. It seems strange.
It does seem weird. I'm I don't know.
Maybe Maybe I should do like a podcast
and ask, you know,
why? I don't know why. Why they do it?
Why? Why they defend women that don't
want them? I don't know. I don't I don't
think we'll ever ever know. They will
sit there. It's like that man on the
train defending a woman just for having
a [ __ ] and yet the women don't like him
and will never sleep with him.
They hate you. They don't want you. Like
I was watching Savvy Guy earlier. Yeah.
And he was like, "Oh, the only thing
that works is being a millionaire and
sing." Being a millionaire might work,
but sing will never get you laid ever.
I've never had to s a day in my life.
Madness. Absolute madness.
I've never had a good relationship, bro.
What are you talking about? I've never
had a good relationship. You your your
family is different. You know, your mom
and your sister, you can't compare them
to normal women because they're your
family. So, that's a bit biased. So, um
I have a good I have a good relationship
with my sister and my mom. Very much so,
actually. Very much so.
I don't compare myself to other people.
And he was already with Natalie. And oh,
I'll answer your question. Uh, he was
already with Natalie. He was already
Rice was already with Kaye. Uh, they're
losers. They're fat, ugly losers, and
they were already with them. Yes. Do you
think that man on the train got [ __ ]
after after getting almost his head
crossed through the door? No. No. I
mean, they were already with these loser
fat women. You you explained to me when
one man has said, "Oh, you can't say
that to a woman. You can't say that to a
woman." And then a woman jumped in bed
with him. It's never happened. So, I
have explained it. Yeah. They were
already with them and they're fat, ugly
losers. That would go with anyone. That
would go with [ __ ] anyone.
How many people have been singing over
Natalie for years? And how many how many
guys has she been with on this
community? How many guys has she been
with on this [ __ ] community?
How many guys has she been with? How
many guys has she [ __ ] been with? How
many guys has she been with on this
community that have sed less than 1%.
Why don't you explain that one then?
I've explained one to you. So why don't
you explain one to me then, [ __ ] idiot.
And you know the maddest thing is
Douglas, I'm completely unbiased. I've
gone out, I've met women, I've been with
women and they are absolute [ __ ] And
I've given them the benefit of the doubt
more times than I should have. And then
you still have these people defending
them. I don't I would love to know why
they do it. Autism thinking the women's
going to sleep. Why? Why do they do it?
Why did she choose Monty? I I don't know
why she ch Why did she choose money
Mike? You know, I I don't know. She's
desperate. I mean, she's desperate,
isn't she? Look at that guy in the train
defending a woman just fing a [ __ ] in
between her legs.
And I told him I'll talk to who I want
when I want. I literally, that is
literally what I [ __ ] said. People
that have to defend people, right?
People that have to defend people by
having a [ __ ] in between their legs.
Like they're they're the lowest of the
low, bro. They think women like them and
they women hate them.
B. Listen, bro. When I get your when I
get your address, I'll be the first one
on your [ __ ] door, you little [ __ ]
So, just wait for it, mate. I'll be like
that person in the shop. I'll wait, bro.
When you get docked, I'm coming on your
door, mate. So, you'll have everything
to say when I'm when I'm at your front
door, you little keyboard warrior. And
that's the best way with these little
keyboard warriors. Just sit there and
wait until they get doxed. Pick your
moment and wait until they get doxed.
And then we just go in their door then.
Then we'll just go in their door and
smash the [ __ ] face. And simple. See
what they're about then it when
someone's on their front [ __ ] door.
Madness, bro. [ __ ] madness.
Mad, isn't it? Why are these people sit
there and defend women for just having a
[ __ ] is mad, bro?
Mad. And they and they think women are
going to sleep with them. It's mad. And
what is it with you people in this
community always twisting things? I beat
a bouncer. Oh, he can't eat you. He's at
work. Okay, so I stuck it on two people.
Oh, well, they owned you. Okay, then we
own two women. Yeah, you always make
excuses. And this is what I mean. I
can't wait to get one of you's
addresses, bro. I can't wait to get one
of your addresses. Oh, boy. I can't wait
to get one of your addresses, bro. Trust me.
Any of your addresses that's been
bothering people. I'll be I'll be the
one on your door, mate. I'll be the one
on your door and I'll risk everything. I
don't give a [ __ ]
I stayed up all night the other day just
so you didn't get the last laugh. Not
because I needed £110. Not because I
needed £110. Just I went through all of
that just so you didn't get the last
laugh. Does that not tell you how much I
hate these people on here?
Does that not tell you how much I hate
you people on here? Haters. The haters.
Not all of you. The haters.
That's not his address. And you can [ __ ]
off. That's not That's not his address.
I want that fantasy stories and that's
not Lord J's address cuz people would
have been on his address by now
and I will go one of your doors. I will
go on one of your doors, bro. You think
it's a joke, I will go one of your
doors. Whatever. You can keep making
excuses. I don't give a [ __ ]
And next time now when a woman starts or
she gives attitude, I'm not holding back
this time. I'm not holding back this
time. I would normally because I don't
give a [ __ ] But I'm not going to hold
back this time just to piss you people
off now. just to annoy you. People
didn't want to meet me. You didn't want
to meet me. Okay, that's fine. You
didn't want to meet me. So, I'm I'm not
going to hold back now. I'm not going to hold back.
I'm not going to hold back and I'm just
going to terrorize you even more that
way. So, you asked for it. You could
have been a man and met me today, but
you don't want to do it. So, that's
that. But, I don't know why Ario man
says about being a s.
I got I commented on his video. I got 25 thumbs up.
I got 25 thumbs up. It's not going to
work being a s. Look at that man on the
train. He s and he got his head crushed
in the door, bro. He got his head
crushed in the door. His head got
crushed in the door. Joseph Ferrar all
for defending someone just cuz they had a vagina.
She knows how much I hate these people.
Yeah. No, I hate these people. I [ __ ]
hate these people, bro. I hate these people.
No, I know what you're saying. I hate
these people, bro. This is what I mean.
I hate these people. I I want one of
these people to get docks, bro. Even if
I need to pay £1,000, I don't I don't
mind. I hate these haters on here. I
hate these biased people. I hate
everything about this the people in this community,
you know. Triple H, I don't mind.
Greasy, I like a few people here. I I
hate most of these people.
Kieran, I don't mind.
I want one of these people, bro. I want
I want that Fantasy Stories, bro.
Because he annoyed me, bro. He annoyed
me because he annoyed me because of the
whole Pat Mustard thing. Um, and then he
thinks he can come on here giving it the
[ __ ] big with his Northern Irish
[ __ ] gay accent.
Yeah, I want that [ __ ] more than anyone,
bro. More than anyone. So, I will hire a
private investigator. I don't mind
paying £1,000, whatever it is. It's not
a problem, but I want one of these
people bad, bro. Bad. I want I want to
shut the whole community down as well.
like these little nerdy little geeky
little [ __ ] idiots thinking that they
can come on here every day. Bro, it's
annoying, bro. It's annoying. And if I
get one of these people, that's fine. I
don't need it anymore. Just one of them.
The Irish are [ __ ] I don't want it
to be an Irish person as well. I want it
Yeah, but he didn't do Yeah, but he
found it. Yeah. Yeah, he did find it.
Yeah. So, I'll just wait. I'll just sit
there and wait, bro. That's the best
because they will get doxed eventually,
bro. They will get doxed eventually. B. Yeah.
I hate these [clears throat] people,
bro. Fantasy stories, these little bully
victim, little narcissist. I hate them,
bro. Hate them. You don't understand,
bro. Worse worse than LT. Trust me, I
do, bro. I do.
And even if it's like Smokey B, anyone
else, bro, I'll get them as well. It's
It's not a problem.
We all know these people not about it,
Douglas. How long have they known where
I've lived, bro? Not to not to keep
bringing this up, but how long have they
know where I've lived despite me going
to their city? Why they been? Why they
been? You know, I've traveled miles and
miles and don't use LJ as an excuse. Lj
done nothing. And it's been going on
before the whole LJ thing. Yeah. It's
been going on before the whole LJ thing.
It's because you ain't about that life.
Yeah, that's what it is. You're not
about that life. Stop sugar coating it.
You know, I hate these [ __ ] people on here, bro.
And when I get hold of one of them, bro,
it's not going to be a prime thing. It's
going to be, you know, it's going to be something different. You know,
if I could get two people, I think it
would be Fantasy Stories and Prime. Them
two or them two. I want them two, bro.
And do you know what I would do? I would
tie them up, bro. And I, bro, you don't
know what I would do, bro. You don't
know what I would do. I would tie them
up and make them my [ __ ] I would make
them my assistant for the day, bro.
Yeah. I would make them my assistant for
the [ __ ] day, bro. Yeah. I make them
my little [ __ ] Trust me. Yeah.
Yeah. It doesn't matter though, does it?
Because he's been to places like I have,
hasn't he? So, at the end of the day,
bro, you can say what you want about
him. I don't even like him. But we're
the only ones that seem to have left our city,
you know? We're we're the only ones that
seem to have left our city, though, haven't we?
The maddest the maddest thing is is when
Tiger has done more than these people.
That's the most embarrassing thing. When
Tiger of all people have done more than
these people. [snorts] Tiger done more
than these people. And look at the size of him.
Look at the [ __ ] size of him.
Tiger of all people done more than any
of these people. It's like Smokey B,
right? He knew where I lived for eight
months, right? Eight months. It's very
easy to get to Maryland from, you know,
uh, Houston, right? Uh, and he didn't
come on the door. Now, this guy is
saying that he's bullies people, right?
Yeah. He's only probably about 35
minutes away from me. Why isn't this guy
come on my door or even tried to call me
out when he was in London? Because he's
not about it. They're middle-aged sad
virgins with no life.
Yeah, that's him. Yeah.
So, yeah. Watch when one of you people
get docked. Anyways, I'm coming on your
[ __ ] door, bro. I swear that I am.
That Northern Irish accent. I want to
beat him so bad he can't even talk
again, bro. I want to beat him so badly
that he can't even talk again.
little [ __ ] mongos on here, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. It's weird how you have no problem ghosting uh
um they're not even trolls. They're just
little spastics. Can you not call them
trolls, bro? Cuz they're not trolls.
I think it's
just can't believe people like you
ghosting think that women can't do no
wrong. I feel bad for you. I really,
really feel bad for you. How you seem to
think that women can't do no wrong.
Wow. And then when you give it back to
them, you're a bully. It's a sad life
that we It's a sad world that we live
in. It really is a sad world. You know,
it's okay for them to insult people,
lead people on, be [ __ ] but as
soon as somebody gets agitated and
wishes them things, oh, oh, oh, you
can't say that about women. You can't
say that about women. You can't say that
See, this is what I mean with you people.
I do feel bad for you. I feel bad for
people that think women can't do no
wrong. I feel bad. I do really, really
I really, really, really feel bad. I
mean, okay. Why do you think I don't go
out and approach anymore?
What I mean, why do you I don't think
men deserve to be led on, but again, we
we're just going to keep going round and
round in circles. But the point is, why
do you think I don't go out anymore? I
think that tells you everything you need to know.
Well, it clearly aren't good, bro, when
you're defending women for the sake of
defending women like that man on the train.
Defending women for just having a [ __ ]
in between their legs. Mad.
Absolutely mad. And you know, the only
reason why I put it up is cuz Greavves
was like, "Oh, just put it up." I was
like, "Fuck it. Might as well." But we
don't you clowns are like on here
anyway. She just twist wings. Even when
you beat a man, even when you stick it
on a grown man, Douglas, they will still
say, "Oh, well, he can't hit you cuz
he's that work." Bro, they always make
excuses. They make tons and tons of
excuses on this community. They even
done it with the with the four people
that I clearly stuck it on and they was
like, "Nah, nah, they stuck it on you."
That's what they're like on this little
community, bro. Just wait until one of
these people get doxed. Wait until one
of these people get doxed. I'll be
banging on that door, mate. And I'll be
live streaming as well. And we'll see.
We'll see, bro. Yeah. Simple. That's it.
No, you can defend who you want, but
it's just you're defending them just cuz
they're winning. I mean, that's the
problem. It's not that you can You're
defending them just because they've got
a [ __ ] in between their legs. I think
that's where the problem lies. Um they uh they
mean the problem is when you're defending people that
have a [ __ ] in between their legs and
that's the reason why you're doing it.
You're not doing it for the right
reasons. Just like this guy on the train
defending them because they got a [ __ ]
in between their legs.
What if I had a knife on me and I went
and stabbed the guy? They don't know who
they're [ __ ] with. All for defending
someone just for having a [ __ ] in
between their legs.
Yeah, bro. You know what these little s
little white knights are like? They're
never going to change, bro. They're
never ever ever going to change. They'll
keep defending women. Women still hate
them, right? You're listing your bad
experiences whilst having more women
than these people. where you're
listening your bad experiences with
these people having had more women than
these people and they still defend the
women like you're the virgin. It's It's
weird. They're [ __ ] in their head,
bro. They're [ __ ] in their head,
you know? They are literally [ __ ] in
their head, bro. Well, women hate all
men. They [ __ ] do. They [ __ ] do.
Well, when you're single again, why
don't you go out and approach women?
Women do hate you. They hate you. They
hate me. They hate all of they hate most
men. They do [ __ ] hate us and they
hate you as well. So, I don't know why
you keep defending them. Of course, they
hate you, bro. Go out and speak to some
women when you're single again and
record it and see what you get. You're
no exception, bro.
You're no exception. Trust me, you're no
I don't know what it is, Douglas. I
think it's where my dad died. He didn't
teach me to lick women's asses for just
being a woman. I think it's father
figure, but the father figure is the
wrong way. They're learn they're being
taught the wrong way, but it is the way
that they're brought up. I think that's
what it it's got to be that it's got to
be. I was thinking about this the other
day. Why do these men continuously
defend women when women hate them? And I
I don't know what. And and I'm thinking
it's got to be the way that they were
brought up by their father.
It's got to be, bro. It's got to be the
way that they're brought up, but they're
being brought up the wrong way
because with me, um, I learned myself
because I had my own experiences. My I
didn't get obviously I got brought up,
but like I I went around and saw the
world for what it was. I've seen the
world for what it was, Douglas.
I've seen the world for what it was. I
learned for myself.
So, I don't I don't know why they do it.
I don't know.
I think you're deluded as well. Um,
thinking that it's okay for women to
lead people on and make up stories about
them and give them false hope and give
them attitude. I think you're completely
I think you're completely wrong and
deluded that you think that's okay. I
mean, and then when you say something in
retaliation, oh, it's disgusting. Oh,
it's disgusting. I mean, it's words at
the end of the day. They do actions. I
said words, they do actions. What they
do is worse. they're evil. So yeah, and
that's my personal experience and I will
say what I want
and other men have been through the
stuff that I have because most men
struggle. So considering most men
struggle, how does most men not go
through what I considering most men struggle?
>> But it's okay for them to leave people
on and be rude. No problem with that.
That you keep dismissing. See, this is
what I mean with you people. All you do
is dismiss stuff because you're white
knights. You just miss things cuz you're
white nights and you think women don't
hate you. But ghosting, trust me, women
do hate you. Women are not going to
sleep with you. If you was to ever be
single again, believe you me, being a s,
women don't like you. Trust me, I'm
telling you right now, you can go into a
pub and defend a woman and they're not
going to [ __ ] you. They're not going to
sleep with you. You're wasting your
time, bro. You know,
bro, there's there's loads and loads and
loads and loads of single people out
there. There's loads and loads of single
people out there.
I mean, there's loads and loads and
loads of single people out there. Most
people I know are single. So, more men
struggle than don't struggle. So, your
whole your whole logic is flawed with
that one because most people struggle
and don't struggle. So, that [ __ ] your
logic up with what you're trying to say
when you're trying to make it seem like
a personal problem. Yeah, there's people
in relationships. Why are people in relationships?
Loads of different reasons. They might
have got lucky on a dating app. They
might have met someone through work.
They might have met someone through
school. They might have met someone two
years ago. They might have met someone,
you know, I don't know, [ __ ] uh they
might have met someone, you know, before
social media. There's different reasons
why people in relationships all have got
nothing to do with me and it almost
being 2026. And there's loads and loads
and loads of people that are single.
Most of the people I know are single,
even women. So obviously I know people
in relationships but most of the people
I know are single.
What do you mean bro? What you what you
just because they met someone doesn't
mean we are ghosting. What are you
talking about? So I don't know what the
statistics [ __ ] are, bro. But I know
there's loads and loads and loads and
loads and loads of
It isn't hard to meet a woman.
It's not [laughter]
Wait a second. It's not hard to meet a
woman really, bro. [laughter]
I mean, are do you mean technically or
do you mean like generally? Cuz if you
mean technically, I mean, I mean, no,
it's not hard. You just go and speak to
someone. But you mean like getting into a relationship?
Really, bro? Well, me and Douglas would
love to know these undercover secrets. I
mean, the dating apps don't work. I
mean, if you try to speak to a woman, she's rude
or she'll pretend she's got a boyfriend
or lead you on. Doesn't seem easy to me,
but you know, anyone can have their own opinions.
Yeah. I mean, Yeah. I mean, some people
I mean, like there's there's different
reasons why people have met someone. I
mean, I could have been with I could
have been in multiple relationships
years ago. years ago but I never you
know you know that Douglas so it's like
it doesn't matter about people have met
people through different ways different
reasons people got lucky people met
people before [ __ ] you know there's
there's several different reasons
really I think you need to watch my
approaching videos again ghosting really
I don't believe you.
I'm starting to think now that you're a
virgin, bro. No offense, but
I don't know, bro. I I might be only 28,
but I've got a lot of life experience. [snorts]
I don't think you've got much experience
with women, bro.
Not not not to be a hate or anything,
bro, but saying stuff like that.
[sighs] Ah, I don't know, bro. I don't
think I believe you, man. Right.
There's no getting through to these
white knights, Douglas. In their head,
right? In their head, Douglas, women are
innocent. Women can't do no wrong. Just
leave them to it, bro. Just just just
just leave just leave these people to it. You know,
I was thinking of going to Manchester
again at some point. I don't know why.
What do you think is going to happen
when I go to Manchester?
What do you think's going to happen when
I go to Manchester and I approach?
What do you think's going to happen?
Yeah. These people have got their way of
thinking and that's it. Yep.
And when you approach them, they've all
got attitude problems.
There was this guy on Reddit, Douglas.
He said that he's had hundreds of one night stands. Huh?
Hundreds of one night stands, he said,
and he was in his 20s. Hundreds. Now, I
have banged escorts
a lot of [ __ ] times, bro. And even
that wasn't hundreds.
Even that wasn't hundreds.
That was I don't know how many there
are, but they're not hundreds. But this
guy said that he's had hundreds of one
night stands. I'm starting to think
these people are lying, bro. Seriously.
Yeah. I don't know why they lie on Reddit.
I don't know, bro. That's I mean I've
been with a lot of escorts and I don't
know how many I've been with. I've been
with a lot and I don't even think it's
100. I don't even think it's 100. I
don't know how many it is but it's a
lot. I don't [ __ ] know.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. You're
You're trying to tell me one thing and
my videos are showing another. That's
that's that's my problem. You're saying
one thing, my videos are showing another
in 3D. So, I mean
I mean there's videos out there that you
keep dismissing. I mean, I can put them
up again if you want, but we know that
you just got to dismiss them again. So,
you're saying one thing,
but these videos are showing another.
And this is being completely unbiased.
So you can understand why someone
doesn't agree with you when someone has
given the women the benefit of the doubt
for years and they prove they're all the
same. At this point, it doesn't matter
what anyone says, does it? This is my
whole point. You're saying that women
aren't this, they're not that, but your
experiences would always show that they
are all the same, which is why I gave up.
I gave up for the best. I'm dreading
going out next week drinking. I don't
want to go out next week, but I planned
it with my sister and I have to go. So,
I can't let her down again. So, would I
go if I wasn't? [ __ ] no. Would I? I'd
stay in bed, stack up money, leave.
Dumb. I'd stack up money and I'd leave.
I don't know, bro. I don't know. Five
grand. I don't know. A lot.
Cuz it's addictive.
But I don't use escorts now. I don't
care about sex. So, I don't give a [ __ ]
about that. I don't use escorts anymore. So,
ghosting, you're saying about having
different opinions, but my videos back
up my claim. They back up my what I'm
saying about women
being [ __ ] being evil, leading
people on. I don't want to be with
people like that. I don't want to be
with people like that. I don't want to
be with evil people. That's why I do my
own thing. You can say they're not all
evil, but it shows otherwise. I can tell
you. Oh, I can tell you another thing, Ghosting.
There was this woman that come on my um
phone and [ __ ] with me the other day.
She [ __ ] with me the other uh other
day, month, a few months ago. Um she
purposely unblocked me and [ __ ] with
me. Um but you're not allowed to say
that they can go and get you know what,
but they're okay to do whatever they
want to do.
They can do whatever they want to do and
be devils, but you can't say anything
back to them. I've even got the
messages, by the way. She was messaging
me trying to be a [ __ ] and then I had
to tell her and the guy that she was
with about herself, I think it was her
friend. So, it seems very mad that they
can do anything and everything they want
to do. Oh, it's not we're not talking
about rape. We're talking about
anything. It seems a bit weird how they
can do and say and act exactly how they
want to, but no one's allowed to say
anything back to them. I mean, look at a
train. Look at the train situation.
She was giving it back as much as I was.
But Superman wanted to defend someone
for having a vagina in between their legs. So, you know,
it's not about the R word. It's not
about the R word. You would defend them
no matter what. You know, you would
defend these [ __ ] no matter what they do. Madness.
madness. So, it looks like I don't have autism.
I was half asleep in that video as well.
I was half asleep. I said, "No, I'll say
what I want." You know, if see if she
You know what I'm saying? I'm arguing
with two people. I'm half asleep.
So, it's like why?
That's what I'm going to ask next time.
I'm going to ask them why they do it.
I'm not going to be violent. I'm not
going to I'm just going to ask them why.
I'm going to be like they're not going
to let you hit dog. So why do you keep
defending them? Why do you keep sticking
up for them? They're not going to let
you hit it. They're not going to let you
hit it, dog.
So why do you keep defending these
women? You know, it's different. If it's
someone's mother or someone's sister,
then it's completely different. It's
completely different, you know, or their
wife or their mom, then it's a
completely different story, you know.
But these men go out their way defending
people that they don't know simply for
having a [ __ ] not knowing what somebody
could be carrying on them. I could have
been carrying a knife. What if I was
carrying a knife and I put it through
that cunt's heart?
You know, it's you know what I'm saying, bro?
It's mad. There's so many [ __ ] in
this country. So many [ __ ] in this
country, bro. I had it a lot when I was
working as well. You never get it with
Asian people, though. You never get it
with Asian people. Never get it with
Asian people. That's how you know it is
a westernized problem. Asian people are
the most loveliest people you ever meet,
bro. Mind their own business. They're so
nice. They do anything to help people.
And these westernized [ __ ] these
[ __ ] here, bro. Like tell so many
stories. It was annoying me the other
day, bro. I was in Liverpool Street.
This guy rode on a bike and he's like,
"Red light, red light, mate. Red light, mate."
And I'm thinking, bro, if the guy
literally parks up the bike and he calls
you out, you're going to [ __ ] it. So,
what's the point with the sly comments?
What's the point with the sly comments?
Like, I don't understand it. Like,
they're so ent
because they're so entitled. They think
the world revolves around them. They're
so entitled that they think they can say
what they want and then they get [ __ ]
and then they're surprised when someone
says something back to them. Red light,
mate. Red light, mate. I mean, the They
weren't almost hitting you, mate. So,
why are you They just It's just a
country full of [ __ ] bro. This is
a [ __ ] country. That's what it is.
And the mad thing is, whenever you stand
up to them, they never do anything.
[ __ ] Absolute [ __ ] in this
country, bro. It is a country designed
to annoy you. It's a [ __ ] country,
bro. [ __ ] country. Why do you think
everyone's going to Asia now? Yeah,
but that guy on the train, he wasn't
being a s. The other one, he was said,
"I'm sick of you and I'm sick of her."
And then he said, "Be the bigger
person." That's what you want to hear.
That's what you call unbiased. That's
what you call someone not being a s cuz
he told her, "Stop. Stop." And then he
said, "I've had enough of you as well."
Yeah, that's fair. Yeah. Yeah. But he,
an unbiased person would say, "Both of
you, shut the [ __ ] up." and then just
say to one of you be the bigger person,
but they're not. They're defending them
for just having a [ __ ] in between their legs.
That's what the pro that's where the problem lies.
You understand? That's where the problem
lies is when they're defending people
just for having a [ __ ] in between their
legs. No other reason.
Madness, bro. Pier really needs to start
driving I think after this.
So what about Elephant and Castle
Douglas? Why the [ __ ] does this Uber
kept sending me to Elephant and Castle?
[ __ ] elephant and castle, bro.
Yeah, but the bike kept Yeah, but the
bike kept taking me to elephant and castle. M zed
[sighs and gasps]
elephant and castle.
You lasted long, didn't you? Joseph Fra.
But it's quite simple, is it? Just don't
show these people content ever again. I
only done it cuz Greavvesy was begging me.
I mean, you should know what they're
like on it, bro. They call you virgins
even though you prove you've had sex.
Even when you prove you had sex, they
still call you a virgin. I mean, Jesus Christ, bro.
But then they defend they defend the
[ __ ] the Allington virgin mad.
You [clears throat] need to take a closer look.
You don't need You need to take a closer
look at what the M does and says this is
nothing compared to See, they they're on
here every day, right? Writing stuff,
but they'll never meet anyone.
It makes you die, doesn't it? Like they
they they fully know where you live.
But all they do is write stuff. It's
it's it's crazy, isn't it?
But it's all right because one of these
people are going to get doxed
eventually. So yeah. And I'm still doing
that woman thing as well, by the way. [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] on here, bro. Watch. Watch
when I find out where one of these live.
They're getting it, mate. [ __ ] getting it.
I hate them on here, Douglas. You
should. So, I stayed up all night just
to get that £110.
Yeah, because they're disabled. Because
they're disabled, bro.
They do it because they're just [ __ ]
Because they're disabled little nerds.
Disabled little nerdy [ __ ]
They ain't got no insults. They got no
insults, bro. They're [ __ ] disabled.
They're [ __ ] disabled, bro.
Disabled fat, ugly mongs with autism.
And then they wonder who killed the
community. Someone said the other day,
"Who's killed the community?" "Uh, you
repeating bastards have killed the community."
By the way, apparently I'm over
apparently I'm overweight, said
Gonachan. but he can't come in and show
his face. A lot of this on this
community, bro, is to do with jealousy.
You know that you're younger than them,
you're better looking than them. I know
I need a haircut, by the way. But this
is what it comes to with these people,
Douglas, is because they know that their
lives are over. They're bitter, old,
fat, ugly people, lad.
These people these people killed it
because they're constant repeaters.
They're constantly repeating the same
old [ __ ] They killed the community,
bro. They're repeating your [ __ ]
The [ __ ] They're weirdos, bro. Madness.
Yeah, I'm dreading [ __ ] next
Saturday, Douglas. Going out drinking.
I'm I'm dreading it, bro.
That's how you know you're properly
done, bro. I haven't approached for ages.
Because once you've met one, you've met them all.
Why is this not working?
Oh, here we go.
There we go. See,
apparently I'm overweight. Coming from a
man who's obese
coming from a man who's obese. No thanks.
Just through takeaways. Just through
Yeah, just takeaways and stuff.
Yeah, just takeaways and [ __ ] mate.
Takeaways. I'm not dealing with their
[ __ ] ever again, bro. [ __ ] that.
They say in life, Douglas, what do they
say in life? That having a having a
partner is supposed to be a bonus. They
say that it's supposed to be a bonus
having a partner, right? Have you heard
that saying before? Life is what you make it.
You can be happy by yourself and having
a part a partner is a bonus. Now
a bonus doesn't mean sat there
all day going out approaching dealing
with toxic lying [ __ ] women. You know
what I'm saying?
I've got only 30 tomas. I don't know why
you keep making stuff up.
30 into Xmas. You must be talking about
yourselves, bro. These people must these
skinned people must have done their
bollocks or something, bro.
Where the [ __ ] do they come out with
these things from Douglas?
Strong [snorts] self projecting 30 until
into until Xmmith. Why do you keep projecting, bro?
Oh, you know around this time, Douglas,
as well, you know these ugly people,
right? You know these ugly people on
here around Christmas time, they get
really hateful because they know they're
alone. Christmas is lonely for them sat
on YouTube. So, you'll notice that the
hat is going to be getting more and more
and more this this uh year. It happens
every year uh this month. It happens
every year. They're fat, ugly, lonesome
people with no money and they know
Christmas is coming, so they're going to
try and ruin your Christmas by
projecting to the max. So, yeah, just be
aware of that. That that does happen. It
used to happen with the bomb as well.
They're going to be like skin lonely
Christmas because they know that it's
their lives that they're talking about
on here. skin, lonely, fat, ugly, no
this, no that. They're talking about
themselves, so the hate is going to get
strong, bro. Don't say I don't warn you.
It happens every uh every year in December.
Yeah. Sat lonely with nobody.
I think I was live Christmas last year
and people was on on online.
People was on here Christmas.
£30 to last a month. What the [ __ ] are
these people talking about?
I showed 110 the other day. No one
showed me 2 uh 220. Huh? Well,
I don't know why these people keep
asking people to show money. Every time
people show money, they run away. I
don't know why they keep asking people
to show their money. They get show
money, they run away every time.
I mean, are they still doing this [ __ ]
[ __ ] hell, bro.
No, but they done it before that as
well. No, no, they do it every year.
They do it every year, lad. They do it
every year. They hate in December every
year. December the community becomes
live again with haters.
No, no, no, no, no. They they done it
before that as well. They done it before
last year. They do it they've done it
before last year.
Um they done it every December. You will
see that these hateful, ugly skinned
people go mad because they know what's
coming. So they come on your live
streams and project. It was before last
year as well. They've done it before
last year as well. So all these little
lonely skinned people that can't get off
of YouTube because that's all they have.
Just like fatty
ga in the calaban in my
bro. How can someone even take someone
with an accent like that seriously? [ __ ] hell. Yep.
Kitty in the gallivant.
Yeah. Do you know what I find weird
about Reddit as well, Douglas, is these
women are such snakes. They're so fake
that they'll speak to you normally one
day and then the next day they switch.
Have you noticed that with these women, Douglas? Yeah.
Have you Have you That's what they do.
They switch cuz they're so fake and
phony. They can't even keep it up longer
than a day cuz they're fake and phony. Yeah.
You've met one, you've met them all.
There's nothing Asian about these women.
lack of education, mate. You're not even
using correct punctuation.
So, uh you might want to use correct
punctuation um before trying to tell
someone else that they're not using uh
uh yeah, before telling people they've
got a lack of education.
I mean, I'm clearly more educated than
you will ever be. So, yeah.
Reddit mods ban me, bro. I'm giving up
with it now. Anyways, you know,
[clears throat] you're using incorrect
punctuation and you're telling me that
I'm not educated. Please, bro. Please, please,
please, mate. Please. Please. Yep.
They tell people to go on dating apps. I
see. They say go on the apps.
You know what's so mad is I've met more
women in Gona.
I've literally met more women in Gona
and he's older than me. How mad is that?
I've probably met more women than
probably 90% of the population. So, I'm
in a 10% minority,
but they still try and tell me what
women are like. [snorts]
I don't know.
They still try and tell me, but I'm in
the 10% minority [sighs]
weird, isn't it?
Uh, I have had a relationship and again,
let me explain this to you because
you're clearly low IQ.
um you know you know relationship is um
with um is with one person. A
relationship is with one person. So let
me explain this to you again cuz you're
low IQ mate. Even if someone had two
relationships and somebody that met
million [ __ ] millions of women had no
relationship, they would know more about
women than the people that were in
relationships. A relationship is with individual women.
They are individual women. They are
individual women. You don't need to be
in a relationship to know about women.
Why do you think that? Is that is that
the way your brain works?
You don't need to be in a relationship
with one to suddenly know all about
women. I told non-legs this multiple
times. Just because you've been in a
relationship with a disabled woman, you know,
I don't want to keep them. They're
[ __ ] stinking little [ __ ] toxic
liars. [ __ ] [ __ ] I don't want
nothing to do with them. And the next
one I come across, they're getting it good.
I'm not holding back this time. I'm not
[ __ ] holding back this time. You
know, I'm going to I'm not holding back
this time, big man. So, don't don't cry.
And I'm doing it just for YouTube as
well. I'll be doing it just for YouTube.
Not cuz I even care about it, but I'll
do I'll do it just for YouTube. So,
you think people that are in a
relationship with a woman knows more
about women? What about people that have
got sisters? What about people that's
got a mother? Do they not know anything?
Do would they wouldn't that maybe think
that they know about women now? No. No.
No. No. No. Of course not. [ __ ]
idiot. You [ __ ] absolute clown.
You're an absolute [ __ ] idiot, mate.
You're an absolute [ __ ] idiot.
So yeah, basically it's too toxic
basically, Douglas. That's why I'm not
ever dealing with it ever again.
[ __ ] dealing with that [ __ ] You must
have no respect for yourself to deal
with them [ __ ] Them rude stuck up little [ __ ]
Yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah, you keep telling
yourself that even though I've met more
women than you and probably been with
more women than you, even though you're
older than me. I know. Mad in it. Okay, bro.
Okay. Whatever you say. 37 years. Nah. Really? Yeah.
So, Douglas, why do these people not
mention about the women that have got
attitude and lead me on? They never
mention them women, Douglas. Why is
that? They never really pay attention to
those things that they do.
They never really focus on that
about the leading on the toxicness.
Mad, isn't it? I wish I was born with a [ __ ]
I've never proven I've had sex.
I mean, done a video having a [ __ ]
Was in a woman's bed in Manchester. Was
in a woman's bed in Nottingham. Was in a
woman's bed in South London. I went into
a hotel room with a 19year-old that
admit to sucking my dick.
Really, bro? Really?
I mean, I've been in several different
women's beds in different cities,
but I haven't proved I've had sex. I
mean, I've literally been naked next to
a woman in her bed.
What the [ __ ] are you talking about?
[ __ ] But yeah, Nons is definitely
not a virgin because he's got a disabled
girlfriend. Oh, the biasness, Douglas.
Oh, the biasness.
Oh, the biasness. I have proved I've had
sex more. See, I'm unbiased. I know you.
This is what you think in your head,
Gona, that anyone that doesn't lick
women's asses have got to be a virgin.
If you walked into a Rolex shop,
I mean, if you was out the Rolex shop
with it on your [ __ ] wrist, then
Yeah. I I I would say it's your Rolex.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Nice try
though, Duda. Nice try. Nice try, matey.
They seem to think anyone that defends w
that don't defend women is a virgin.
They must think that as opposed to
somebody just being completely unbiased
like me. I'm completely unbiased.
That's what I am. I'm unbiased. I've
been with more women than Ant-Man.
Well, at the later stages. Yeah. And I
completely hate them.
And I have no reason to lie. I
absolutely hate them. And I'm going by
my experiences. I hate them. I'm not a
virgin. I've been with women. I've had sex.
So, I'm completely bi I'm biased when
I'm when I'm saying this. I've got no
reason to lie. They are absolute [ __ ]
And I um and I uh
um I'm an incel. Why? Because I'm not
licking women's asses. Because I'm not
saying all women are perfect. All women
are great. Why? Because I'm not sucking
up to women.
So, anyone that doesn't suck up to women
is an incel. Get a grit, mate. It's
boring now. Very, very boring. So,
anyone that doesn't suck up to evil
women just for having a [ __ ] in between
their legs, that makes them an incel.
That That makes you an incel because I'm
not going to be bullied into being a s
or a white knight like you. Oh, women
are great. Women are great. Yet, these
people don't get women. Don't have
women. I mean, for [ __ ] sake, bro.
Look at Pat Bustard. Look at his [ __ ]
misses. Do you remember for years when
he was saying women are great, great
people? And have you seen the state of
his misses, mate? Have you seen the
state of that [ __ ] Jesus Christ. So
your definition of an incel is somebody
that doesn't that doesn't lick women's
asses, bro. That's your definition.
So if you don't lick women's asses,
you're an incel. We don't have to be
bullied into thinking your biased way,
your little white knight way. My way is
the white is is the right way because
I'm I'm biased. I'm completely unbiased.
I don't dismiss people's struggles like
you do. [ __ ] completely dismissing people's struggles. Again,
dismissing people's struggles,
right? Again, dismissing people's
struggles. I have put so many videos out
there where women have been [ __ ]
Again, dismissing my struggles. This was
the whole point of the thing. This was
Yeah. There we go. There we go. I won't
be trying to put I don't want nothing to
do with them evil little rat [ __ ] I
don't want nothing to do with them.
No. No. My experiences was negative with
women. My experiences with them as a
28-year-old man. My experiences with
them were negative. Hence my opinion of
them. I am going by my experiences with
women, my experiences with them. USA is
the people that I've approached. The bad
experiences with women make you
negative. It's the bad experiences.
Again, same conversation over and over
and over again. The bad experiences with
women make you feel that way and that's
why you're the way you are. Not an
incel, an unbiased person. Jesus Christ.
No, you're like that when you've had
your experiences with women. That's what
makes you like that. And you're entitled
to be like that because they're your experiences.
So, yeah. I mean,
what about what about the women that were rude?
Why do you keep You're dismissing my
struggles cuz you know I'm right. You
keep dismissing my struggles because you
know I'm right. You know, you know I'm
right. That's why he's dismissing my
struggles cuz he knows I'm right. He's
not talking about the approaching
videos, the ones where they've led me
on. He knows I'm right. Gona knows I'm
right. He knows I'm right, bro. That's
why he's making up stuff. He knows I'm
right. I've hit the jackpot. As soon as
someone has to start making up stuff and
dismissing people's struggles, you know
that they know you're right. You know
that. You know, I know I'm right. I'm
right. I'm right. Yes, I knew it. I knew
it. I knew it, mate.
I mean, I've I've got plenty of videos
where women have been rude and led me
on. But now you're talking about my
[ __ ] sisters. You're wrong and you
know it. Yeah, you're wrong and you know
it. You know, just because someone don't
suck up to evil women, [ __ ] women,
it doesn't mean they're an insult. How
about someone that's sick of their [ __ ]
Ga? How about being in the middle and
just being sick of their [ __ ] Nah. Nah.
How about just being sick of their [ __ ] for once?
What about that, bro? What about that?
What about that? What about
that, bro? What about being in the
middle and just simply being sick of
their [ __ ] Sick of their toxic [ __ ] for
a change? No. Doesn't Doesn't occur to
you? No, no, no, no. Just an incel.
Yeah. Just a virgin incel. Yeah. So, no
one So, Goon's logic is that no one can
be tired of them and their games and
their toxic [ __ ] [snorts] without being
an I quote incel. Yeah. This guy's is
apparently educated people. This guy is
is he he you know what I'm saying?
You've not seen women bleeding me on.
While there's plenty there's plenty of
evidence. If you took your simp goggles
off, you would see it. You would
literally you would see it. If you took
if you took your not if you took your
simp goggles off, you would see it. You
would see it. But again, making up stuff
because you know that I'm right. You
You've not seen evidence of women
leading me on. Even though I've showed
plenty of evidence, there's no getting
through to these white knight virgins.
There's no getting through to these virgins. people.
So, I'm not even going to waste my time
explaining it. You're an idiot, bro.
You're an absolute idiot. You're an
absolute [ __ ] idiot. Making excuses
for women. Loser. Goon is a loser. He's
a [ __ ] loser. Loser. Loser. Loser.
Loser. Loser. Yep. I'm an incel because
I don't lick women's asses. Make
everyone make Gona Chan right. By the
way, I'm not I'm an incel because I
don't suck up to women for just having a
[ __ ] because I don't have autism. And
I'm not going to defend women that are
wrong. I'm an incel. Oh, poor me. Oh,
poor me, mate. Can I get my candy floss?
You're an idiot, mate. People that don't
suck up to women does not make them an
incel. You're making excuses for women.
Shut up. You're making excuses. You're
on my channel [ __ ] probably
constantly. Everyone's seen the videos
that I put up and you're still denying
it. You are a white knight virgin. You
don't even have a daughter. Because if
anyone had a daughter, they wouldn't be
defending women the way that you do.
Shut the [ __ ] up, bro. You're defending
women because you've never had a woman.
You've never had one in your life.
I mean, I've put I've put I mean, I've
put approaches up that you keep
dismissing. Women having attitude
problems, people women being [ __ ]
but you keep dismissing it, which proves
you're wrong. When you dismiss people's
struggles, I have shown women that have
had nasty attitudes, but you ain't said
anything about it, because you know
you're wrong. That's why you keep
dismissing it. No, you're not banned.
No, you're not banned. No
[ __ ] I mean I've shown women being
rude, but you've got no problem because
they've got a [ __ ] in between their legs
and anyone that speaks out about it is
an incel. You know what? I'm going to do
a video about this. We need to stop over
We need to stop this word incel now for
people that are not actual incelss, you know.
No, no. You've seen it where women lie
that they've got boyfriends and have
attitude problems. No, no, no, no, no.
You've seen it when they've had attitude
problems and pretend they have
boyfriends. Don't twist things now.
You've seen it where they politely be bullshitt.
And also where they've been rude. They
didn't even say they've got boyfriends.
Where they've been [ __ ]
Yeah. Where they've been [ __ ]
So shut the [ __ ] up. You've seen them
when they've been [ __ ] with [ __ ]
attitudes and pretending they've got
boyfriends cuz they're a [ __ ] Where
nine times out of 10, Gona, they don't.
They're just a [ __ ] It's like what
Antman said, they're [ __ ] Because nine
times out of 10, when they say that they
don't because they're [ __ ]
and you've also seen where people have
led me on. You've also seen where people
have said straight away not interested.
You have seen their [ __ ] behavior. And
you're only saying that you ain't seen
it. You know what I'm saying?
You know, mate, we're not getting into
this boring argument again. We're not
getting into this boring argument again.
How do I know they don't? I'm not
entertaining it. It's boring. We've been
over this multiple times, mate. We're
not getting into this. You'd clearly
defend women cuz they've got a [ __ ] I
wish you well. Women don't like you, GA.
Women are never going to sleep with you.
So, good luck in whatever you do in the
future. They don't like you. Like,
you're going to be in your bed. Yeah,
you're going to be in your bed an old
man thinking all of that defending women
and they never liked you, defending them
for just having a [ __ ] and they don't
like you. They don't like you. Women
don't like you. So why do you keep
defending them? They don't want you.
They're never going to sleep with you.
You're putting all this time in
defending them. But yet I've had more
women than you and women don't like you
regardless of what I've had. Women don't
like you. They don't want you. They
don't find you attractive. Stop defending them.
You've never seen I've been led on. Okay. Well,
you apparently Douglas Gona Douglas
Apparently Goon has never seen me been led on. [laughter]
He said that he's never seen me been led
on. Good one, bro. I mean, that's got to
be the funniest joke of 2020 by You
never seen me been led on. [laughter]
He says that he's never seen me been led on.
Oh, Jesus Christ. Dismissing struggles
as usual. He's never He's never seen me
been dead le on.
Oh, [clears throat] Gona, you really are funny, bro.
You've never seen me been led on. Yeah,
he watches me all the time.
They're only dismissing their my
struggles because they've got a [ __ ] in
between their legs. If I was a gay if I
was a gay guy, they'd have no problems.
They're only defending them because
they've got a vagina in between their legs. Jesus Christ.
Defending women just for having a [ __ ]
in between their legs. Sad.
Even Virgin Boy does it. He's 31 and
he's still a virgin. And he well he's
he's 31 in February, right? Douglas and
he will still defend women despite not
getting laid. Never been with a woman,
you know, never been with a woman. Women
don't like him. Virgin. And he still
defends women. Like he's had more women
than me, but he is autistic. I mean, he
actually is autistic, but I mean still
defends women that women don't like him.
Maybe it's ingrained at them at a very young age.
You know, I mean, he was put into care
at a very young age because of it. You know,
he was put into care at a very young
age. So, he didn't even get brought up
by his dad. So, I'm not sure what the
[ __ ] is that all about. He was put into
care at a very young age.
A very young age because of it.
a very young age because of it.
Madness. [ __ ] madness. Absolute madness.
Yeah. He He has a relationship with a
disabled He has a He has a relationship
with a disabled girl. Yeah. Yeah. But
the thing is, I win because every single
woman I've been with, he's tried to get
him with and they've rejected him. So, I
think you find that I win because he's
the one that's still pulling my sloppy
seconds. So, I think you find that I
win. I think you find that I win, lad.
He goes on about me every single day
because he's upset and jealous of me.
Dennis of all of the women that I've
been with. I think you find that I win,
mate. I think you find that I win. Yeah. Yep.
disabilities. You know, you're disabled
yourself. How do you know I don't work?
How do you know that I don't work? How
do you know I weren't at work today?
Since you don't Okay. How do you know I
wasn't at work today? Since you know so
much about me. How do you know I didn't work today?
One second. One second. One second. How
do you know I'm not I didn't go to work
today? This is what makes me laugh, bro.
That you're sat on there calling people
disabled. Like you called Timmy
disabled, but bro, you're you're
disabled yourself. You're [ __ ]
disabled your [ __ ] self. You're
trying to make fun out of [ __ ] people
being disabled, bro. You're disabled
yourself, mate. You're you're you're
disabled yourself. Maybe I went to work
today. You never know. You never know. I
could I could have been at work today.
How do you know? Was you with me today?
No, you wasn't. I could have been at work today.
Mate, you're disabled yourself, which
makes me laugh when you're trying to
talk about other people. You're [ __ ]
disabled yourself. And you're trying to
talk about other [ __ ] people.
You're [ __ ] disabled yourself.
And you're trying to talk about the
[ __ ] You're trying to talk about the
[ __ ] Eldridge, mate. You're [ __ ] disabled yourself.
You're [ __ ] disabled your [ __ ]
self, bro. You know, but the thing is
though is that someone that rides a bike
around is earning more money than you.
Someone that's riding a bike around in
London in in London is earning more
money than you. That's the sad thing
about it. That's the sad thing about it.
They're earning more money than you,
bro. Cuz I mean, it's London, isn't it?
So, I mean, they're earning more money
than you, you little sheep shagger.
You [ __ ] sheep shagging [ __ ]
you know? So [ __ ] sheep shagger, you know. Yeah. [ __ ] mong.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean that was one. Yeah. I
mean you can earn 200 pound a day
easily. You could earn 200 pound a day Sad it
[ __ ] sad, eh? [ __ ] sad.
Maybe in 18 years I'll be your stepdad.
I'll be your stepson. Um, I'll be your
sorry I'll be your son-in-law, Guna.
Maybe in 18 years I could, you know,
your I could be your uh daughter's um
I can be your your daughter's boyfriend. Imagine that.
Yeah. In 18 years, maybe 10 years,
depends how old she is.
And you'll be calling I'll be your son-in-law.
I like that one. You know, yeah.
I will be alive, mate. I [ __ ] will
be. But bro, you're a fat old man. Why
are you trying to flex when you're a fat
old man, bro? Yeah,
you're a fat old man. Struggle dismisser.
He's a struggle dismisser.
Struggle is missad.
No, a lot of English people do it. A lot
of white people do it. There's there's
channels where people do [ __ ] Uber.
So, I don't know what you're talking
about. There's there's loads of white
people that do it. As you know, Douglas,
as you know, there's loads of white
people that do it. English people.
You dismiss people's struggles with
women. Yeah, you do. Yeah, you [ __ ]
I mean, there's white English people
that do it.
So, what are you talking about, bro?
I don't I am happy single. I just
[ __ ] hate women. I never said I'm not
happy single. I just hate women. I think
they're [ __ ] That's my that's that
that's my opinion after my experiences.
I can say and think what I want and
nothing's going to change that. Well,
they can change it, but I mean, I've
given them the benefit of doubt for
years, so they're all the same. And
that's me wanting to give up. I want to
give up. Women are all the same. And
that's me. There's there's nothing left
to say. So, I haven't been out now for 3 weeks.
So, going out next week cuz I'm going
out with someone. And yeah, that's that. Yeah,
that's that's that's on me. It they are
all the same. Clearly all the same
in my hygiene. Yeah. Making up excuses
again. My hygiene. Yeah. Everyone see me
looks maxed. Everyone see me hygienic
again. Making up stuff. Now you're just
making up stuff now.
Now you're just making up stuff.
I'm going to try and get out of going
out next week to be honest with you,
Dusty. I don't want to deal with women
and I know what I'm like when I'm drunk.
But I can't let my sister down. That's
the problem, bro. I don't really want to
go. I'd rather just not.
I'd rather not, bro. That's how bad it
is now. They've even put me off wanting
to go out.
Yeah, I'm going to try and get out of
it. I think
I think I'm going to try and get out of
it, bro. I don't think it's good. I
don't think it's good, lad.
Bad dental hygiene. [ __ ] Go to the
go to the dentist all the time. You
don't know anything about me, Goon.
You're just making up stuff to try and
simp women. You don't know anything
about me. You don't know anything about me, mate.
So, stop making excuses for women.
Everyone has seen what I'd look like
when I've gone out. Stop making excuses
for women being [ __ ] It won't get you
anywhere in life.
You'll be in bed a 90-year-old man
thinking that you've defended women all
your life for no reason and they still
don't like you, you know.
So that's that.
Just making excuses for women. Making
excuses for women. Oh, it's pathetic.
Making excuses for women.
[ __ ] pathetic. Trying to talk about
my hygiene now. Any excuse to defend
women. I've heard your excuses, bro.
They're getting boring now.
Boring now. It's getting boring now.
It's getting boring now, bro. It's
getting boring now. It's getting boring
now. Everyone has seen me going out.
Looks Max, stop defending women. Come
on. It's pathetic. Come on, Gona. It's
Professor. Well, no. I pretended to be a
woman as an experiment. Goona,
I was a woman that complained about men
and then I was a man that complained
about women. And the answers were a lot
different. Ga, the answers were a lot
They were a lot different. I'll tell you
that they were a lot different. I didn't
get called an incel when I was a woman
moaning about men. I got sympathy. That
tells you that it's a gender issue. It's
not a you issue. It's very much a gender
It's a gender issue. H It's a It's not a
I mean, the replies were so different.
The replies were so different.
It tells you that it's a uh
apparently not Tiger Tiger. Apparently
my experiences don't count.
Apparently my experiences don't count.
So, I mean, you're wasting your You're
wasting your time, bro.
I just wanted to know if it was a gender
thing or not. I just wanted to see if it
was me being wrong or was it because I
was a man. And it proved that it was cuz
I was a man.
I just wanted to make sure if it was a
gender thing or it was a me thing. And
yeah, it's uh it's a gender thing.
Definitely a gender thing.
Yeah, it's a gender thing sadly.
I wish it wasn't, but it is mad. [ __ ] mad.
But you know, the thing is, Dusty, they
don't actually have options, though.
Because the options that they have are
weirdos that won't even meet them, like
simps, not men that are like willing to
be with them and stay with them. So, the
only options, they have options for
weirdos that want sex, but they don't
actually have genuine options.
I just want to know why they're sexist.
Uh, city, I like that. I like that name.
I just want to know why they're so sexist.
Bit rude, isn't it? I want to know why they're sexist
and they blame men for just being men.
That's what I'd like to know.
I just want to know why why they why
they do that
then. But no, they don't have they don't
have genuine options, Dusty. They just
have simps and [ __ ] They don't have genuine options.
And it doesn't matter what options they
have because they always go for the same stereotypical
woman abuser, drug dealer, [ __ ]
scumbag. They always go for the same
kind of man. So, you know,
never ever go they never go they always
go for the same stereotypical kind of
guy and claim they don't know what
they're like. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Cuz if that was the case, you'd be
getting laid all the time. You'd be
getting dates all the time
if what they're saying was true. Their
[ __ ] is they know exactly these men
are no good.
Then they moan about men. Mad.
Then they complain about men.
Complaining about [ __ ] men, bro. What
the [ __ ] man?
Why do they moan about men? I don't get it.
No, they do. They go for the same man
that's like a drug dealer that's a
scumbag and then they moan about all
men. No, no, I've seen it a million
times. It happens. I've seen it loads
and loads and loads of times.
Loads and loads and loads of times. They
go for the same stereotypical [ __ ]
and then moan that all men are the same
and then we have to hear it and then
they go back to them and then they go
back to them. I've seen it and I've
heard it but I've heard it all before.
I've heard it all before. I got called
weak because I wanted to give up with
women because they're toxic. I got called weak.
But a woman when she wants to give up
going for the same men that she keeps
going for, she's praised. She's given a [ __ ] reward. Sexist [ __ ] Uh,
women are allowed to abuse people.
They're allowed to verbally abuse
people. That's okay, man.
I don't know.
I don't know, mate.
Yeah, but I don't care about it anymore,
bro. I'm leaving. So, it doesn't it
doesn't bother me, bro. I'm leaving.
I'd rather be single than deal with them
again. That's how bad it is. I'd rather
be single than to deal with them again.
Like what they say in life, it's a
bonus. That's what they say in life. No,
they say it's a bonus. So
they say it's a bonus now.
So, I'd rather be [ __ ] I' I'd rather
be single, bro. Yeah.
I probably won't even go out next week,
to be honest.
>> Yeah, I probably won't even go out to be honest, bro.
>> Yeah, the more you think about it, the
more it's just not worth it, Douglas.
The more you think about it, the the
more you just know it's not worth it
anymore. You know, [ __ ] single set,
just no [ __ ] single set. It's just
not worth it
cuz you know the result before you even
go out and try. So,
I told that Oreo man to get an escort. Yeah.
I don't [ __ ] know what people can do.
I I gave up.
So I I don't know.
Give up, go Thailand.
Give up and go Thailand. That's what
most people are doing now. Yeah.
And there's people that want
relationships there, too.
There's people that want relationships there, too.
So, it's not just about money. There's
people that want relationships there.
They're all just going to be like
Chinese is he? So
yeah, they're not bad, bro. So you might
That's That is really your You either do
that or you continuously stay in this
country dealing with their [ __ ] being
led the [ __ ] on just in hopes to find
someone. It's not worth it. You might as
well just be by yourself. And if you
want someone, just go to Thailand.
That's really your only option.
If you want children, you can go to
Thailand and stuff, you know. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Your options, man. I Yeah.
I don't know what I'm going to eat
today, bro. [ __ ]
All right, this is what this person said
on Reddit, lad.
They said the average guy is lucky to
get four dates a year, and even then
he's probably going to get friend-zoned.
Getting laid is extremely hard. um
is extremely hard for a large majority
men. Hell, these guys can't even meet
women in the first place. Then throw in
their passive nature, having zero
communication skills, can't flirt, wait
for women to make the first move, trying
to be friends first. And guys in 20 20
raised 90% of their dating culture.
average guys are getting less and less
sex while women across the board are
experience more sexual freedom every
single day. More women having sex and
amount of guys
having sex is in decline.
I don't believe
I don't know.
What do you do tiger man? I don't know
>> what what what
it is, bro. You
dating apps don't work and approach it
whether they're all stuck up and they
lead you on. So
yeah, I guess you leave the country in it.
leave your country to find love if you
want children. I think it's bad.
I think it's really bad.
I'm supposed to be going out uh this week, Tiger,
but I'm really not wanting to go out,
bro. I think I proved my point enough times.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know what the Yeah.
So, what happened in Elephant and Castle, Douglas?
Do you still have like a sex drive? I
don't have a sex drive. me.
Nah, not really. Nope.
I don't know what I'm going to eat today, bro. Probably
just eat some eggs.
Eggs and bacon, I think,
basically. Yeah. Yeah.
There's no It's like what Oreo man said.
What's the point of keep putting your
hand on a hot stove?
On a hot stove, bro. What's the point of
keep putting your hand on a hot stove?
Pretty much. Yeah.
If I need someone that bad, then I'll
just go Thailand.
So, what happened in Elephant and Castle, Douglas?
the tiger. Tiger people on Reddit say
that I'll meet someone.
What happened in elephant and castle, Douglas?
There's a lot of history for Peter. [laughter]
Yeah, but what else happened? Yeah, but
what what else happened, Douglas? >> [laughter]
>> Yeah, but what else happened?
What? Reunited and done what? >> [laughter]
>> And then and then what happened? [laughter]
Don't let these [ __ ] women win.
Don't let these [ __ ] women win it. You know,
that's the bees.
That's the be. Yeah. >> [snorts] >> Uh
yeah, I'm just going to have some eggs.
[clears throat and sighs]
>> [clears throat] >> Yeah,
I haven't had a date since April,
Douglas. I haven't had a bloody date
since April, man.
All right, Greasy, read his comment.
read the comment.
I think this is greasy.
[laughter] I think this is greasy.
I think that counts greasy, is it?
So, how does it know about the mama
thingery then? How does it know about
the mama thing and that?
So, you're definitely not getting a
takeaway today, Grezy. I fancy a takeaway.
But I might just get some. Uh,
Nah, it's you, mate. It's you. I don't
know what to get.
I was thinking of I thinking a McDonald's we
You sure on a diet? Yeah.
No, I'm just going to have some eggs. [ __ ] it.
I'll just have some eggs.
Yeah, that's good.
really greasy. What if I ate it in front of you?
So you said nothing will tempt you.
Well, what if I order it and I eat it
right in front of you?
M. That'll get Greavvesy's belly started.
What if I eat in front of you? You sure?
What if I went to a restaurant? Zy, [snorts]
why are you on a diet anyways? Are you really fat?
Yeah, I probably just eat eggs. I
haven't ate today. I probably just eat eggs. Yeah.
Eggs and tuna. Bless you.
Why are you on a diet anyways?
I'm not buying any more coke.
Yeah, I'm not buying any more coke, lad.
I'm going to put some eggs on. Oh bless.
I'm going to make myself free.
Okay with you, boss. Yeah.
Must have some boiled eggs.
I've got 30 to last me a month apparently. Grievy. Interesting.
I'm going to be doing this woman video
when I next out we
did warn people if they weren't going to
meet me today.
So, you're looking forward to that, Grezy
said, "Don't leave Peter Belly because
then Greavvesy won't have no content."
The poor [ __ ] They said, "You can't
you can't leave Greavves without any
content, the poor fucker."
I'll stick it on this [ __ ] this time. Yeah,
proper proper proper proper do it. Poor [ __ ]
I wonder who that is, bro.
You poor [ __ ] Grezy.
Maybe I'll stay just for you cuz how are
you going to get content? You poor [ __ ]
That looks like that virgin [ __ ]
Do you remember that cat looks like the virgin [ __ ]
The bird [ __ ]
do the [ __ ] experiments properly cuz
they just ban you on Reddit.
They just ban you, don't they?
They said to me they today, "Did you
gamble?" Even though I specifically told
them I rarely gamble anymore, they were
still asking me if I gambled.
Even though I said like loads and loads
of times that I don't I rarely gamble
only on the football every two weeks and
they'll ask me if I lost money. [ __ ] idiots.
A [ __ ] absolute idiot.
So, it's been boiled.
I'll wait until they've been boiled. Greasy. Look.
I'll just wait.
But I'm waiting.
I'm waiting. Greasy. Oh, [ __ ]
When I'm gone, you can go on Virgin Boy
channel. Can't you just watch the Virgin?
You don't need me. You got that virgin [ __ ] [laughter]
That virgin [ __ ]
Are you looking forward to the new year's madness?
Let you down quite a few times, haven't
I? With the new year been
gy. I've let you down a few times. I'm
sorry for going out, meeting people.
I've been a let down a few times, haven't I?
A let down.
I've been a let down a few times. [laughter]
And he was like, "Oh, not again."
You even got your McDonald's ready for
it, didn't you, Bezy?
I said I was quitting a coat, didn't I? From today,
>> I let you down. Did I [laughter] virgin [ __ ]
This is my favorite comment.
My favorite comment. [snorts] [laughter] Look,
look, we see >> [laughter]
>> Look crazy. [laughter]
Funny as [ __ ] isn't it?
Yeah, I was just talking to uh I was
Ant-Man. He said that he he was with his
girlfriend today, Dusty.
Yeah. He said he doesn't really drink
much now. He's got a girlfriend. He's in
Thailand. Is it? >> Yeah.
>> I'm just boiling my little eggs and I'm
going to have them bad himself.
Got some corn flakes to go if I get peckish.
I was supposed to be ditching the Coke
as well. It's no good for you.
I got some biscuits. Digestive biscuits.
You know, if I get if I get hungry, I'm
going to get peckish in the night. Oh, bless.
You know what you said to your bra?
Lovely. Digestive biscuits.
I think that I think Trip said about my
mama. Is it?
I think Trip said it in it, Grezy. You
met your mama. Bye-bye, weirdo. [clears throat]
Do you know what I'm saying? If I didn't
say any these things about my mama and
that, these people wouldn't have known, would they?
They wouldn't have known, would they?
They would have done, would I?
So, did I bring it on myself?
looks like some cod mama.
Taking a baby away from its mama.
Peter belly can't get attached anymore
because he already found his mama.
He already found his mama.
I said, "Why did she why didn't she tell
me?" They said they wanted she wanted to
keep it a secret.
The account replied to me saying that
she wanted to keep it a secret from Peter Benny.
Wanted to keep it secret. taking cocoa. Oh, look.
They're boiling our grapes.
They're probably eggs. Yes, sir.
Just on her own, sir.
>> You're on the street every day.
>> Behind a million and one different
account. Bless you.
Yeah, I'm having them all by themselves.
should be ready soon.
I was going to get a takeaway today, but
we usually didn't get a takeaway, so I
wanted to be a little copycat.
Is that all right if I be a little copycat today?
Didn't want to be a little copycat.
Better than saying shovel clothes
attracted to fit in. I guess at least it's food.
At least it's food. Okay. Yeah.
I'm a little copycat. Hello.
I just woke up pissed off today. I went
on your channel, Grezy.
I went on your channel.
I went on your channel, lad.
And it just pissed me off.
Piss me off, bro. just going on your channel.
>> Yeah, it just annoyed me.
They're little shitty little comments.
I can't wait until one of these people get doxed.
Oh, I get docked.
I'm going on the door. I'm going on the Yeah, bro.
Yep. Just made myself the eggs now. Lost.
Oh, bless you. If you go David lovely,
are you into comic books, crazy?
Are you into comic books?
I used to have a friend that was really
into comic books. Oh,
I like Superman.
I watched the new Superman when it come out.
I watching the super come out.
>> Yeah, it's good. Super map. Oh m
these eggs are lovely.
So I'm a prop with the end and Virgin
boys the cop with the golf thing isn't it?
We all copy in some way is it.
I guess we're all all copycats one way or another.
I've unblocked him. So, I don't know why
he doesn't type. Let's have a little
conversation. Why he copies the crowd? Yeah.
Copies the crowd.
Yeah. I didn't copy it though, did I, Grezy?
Yeah. I didn't copy that one though. I
wonder if anyone else did.
Sounds like a copycat statement. Copycat.
I called him a copycat before. He said
whatever. I said it is. You are. Yeah,
but you are you are a copycat. Why you
saying whatever you are? You want to fit
in with the crown.
Anything to fit in with the crowd.
Remember that's me. Dusty wanted to fit
in with the crowd.
Dusty this personal on Reddit said that
they recommend bars and clubs.
They said they recommend bars and clubs
for women. Dusty, they just replied. They said
that they recommend bars and clubs
or coffee shops.
What do you think about that, Dusty?
They said, what did they say clubs? They
clubs and bars and coffee shops.
Have we tried that one before? Bars and coffee shops.
Have we tried that one before,
Greavvesy? Maybe not.
What do you think, Greavvesy? A coffee
shop? A coffee shop? speaking to someone
in a coffee shop. We dusty
balls and clubs maybe
I have done it in a coffee shop. I've
got a video of me doing it in a coffee shop.
I've got a video of me doing it in a
coffee shop. Greavesy.
It was a Starbucks and I've done it. I
think I've done it three times in a coffee shop.
They weren't interested. They weren't
interested there either. Good evening.
And they're not interested there either.
Oh, I don't think I can go out this
week, Grezy. It's too depressing, lad.
I don't think I can go out this week.
It's It's too too depressing.
I'm going to have to be a let down again.
I'm going to have to be a big letdown again.
The more I think about my experiences,
the more it's just not worth it. Even 3 weeks in.
Sorry, mate. I'm going to have to be a big letdown.
I'm sorry, bro.
I don't want any more bad experiences.
No, I don't want any more bad experiences.
I think I'm just going to live off 50
pound a week and just start stacking for
like 3, four months for the lows.
Nah, no point going out. I can watch
WWE. I can watch some WWE videos. I can
go on Netflix. I don't need to go out.
There's no reason for me to go out.
You know what I'm saying? Grezy, there's
no reason for me to go out, lad.
The more I think about my bad
experiences with them, the more I don't
want to go out.
You know what I'm saying?
My life is all right the way it is. It's
good the way it is now. You know,
we're looking for the winter. Huh?
But yeah, I approached I've already
approached some coffee shops before.
One interest I've done it I don't know
how many times I've done it. I've done
it I think I've done it three times. Not interested.
Same old [ __ ] Same old attitude from
when I used to do it, but I've done it
three times. One had attitude, one gave
their number and then never replied to me. Uh,
I'm sure I've done it another time. I
can't pinpoint, but I'm sure I have. Oh,
yeah, I have. I got Instagram and then
they never replied.
So, same old negative experiences with
women. Doesn't matter where it is. So,
I don't think it's a good idea me going
out, bro. I really don't.
Cuz someone will get it and I will put
it on YouTube just to annoy these
people. Grezy, I will put it on YouTube
just to annoy them,
you know, because no one wanted to meet
me today, did they, Grezy? So I said
that the next woman and I'm going to do
it to a woman, not a guy. I'm going to
do it to a woman because
I gave them opportunity.
Nope. I'm not going out and I don't
think I'm going to go out this week either.
No, I'm good, bro. I think I'm going to
stay in now for like four months
and live off like 50 a week and then
just leave, I think. Well, I can leave
now if I wanted to, but you know. No, I
think I'm done. I'm completely done.
I don't want any more bad experiences.
So, no, I've completely given up. I best
let my sister know I'm not going to go
out this week either. Yeah.
Now it's me letting people down now.
Greavves. It used to be people letting
me down. Now I'm letting them down.
Nah, it's too depressing, bro.
Bad experiences. Bad experiences. Bad
experiences. [ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that.
Even if you paid me, I still wouldn't go
out. I don't need money. I've got my own Nah. Nope.
I'll end up on a watch list. Greasy.
I'll end up on the watch list.
Yeah, I gave these people multiple
chances today to meet me. They didn't
want to meet me. They didn't want to
meet me. So, the next woman I come
across, Dusty, they're getting it. The
next woman I come across that gives me
any kind of remote bit of attitude.
I'm literally giving it to them, bro.
They're getting it. No, man. I'm not
interested in men. I'm doing it to a woman
because that's what I warned these
people. If they didn't want to meet me
today, that's what's going to be
happening. And you know what they're
like? They're white knights and simps.
I'm going to tell them about themselves
and I'm going to get in their face. I'm
going to get in their face and I'm going
to threaten them.
Yeah. I warned these people. If they
didn't meet me today and they kept
winding me up and winding me up, winding
me up, right? That's what I'm going to
do. And I'm going to put it all over
YouTube. And I'm going to do it to a
woman. No man, a woman. Yeah. Which I
didn't want to do, but
Yeah. I don't even really care about
doing it, but just to annoy them and
they'll do absolutely nothing. So,
they're going to see it and then they'll do nothing,
bro. I'm going to get in their face. I'm
going to get in their face. It's going
to be worse than the park one. It's
going to be worse than that. That one on
the train, I was [ __ ] half asleep and
I just couldn't be bothered. I said what
I said. You look like a crackhead and
you're ugly. I didn't need to keep
saying anything else.
No, no, no. We're doing more than tell
them about the self. I'm going to get in
their face. I'm going to get in their
face and chase them. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no. I'm I'm going to get in their face.
I'm going to get in their face now.
I might even rob one if I get the
chance. I might even rob one [ __ ] blind.
be a proper [ __ ] You know what I mean?
Like a proper proper [ __ ]
and I'll be wanking off to all the [ __ ] comments.
I can't believe that ghosting today,
Greavesy, right? He thinks it's
disgusting saying that, oh, a woman
should get raped, but they've got no
problem with women insulting people
talking about their foreheads. It's okay
for women to be bullies. And it weren't
even to me either. It's okay for women
to be nasty bullies, but you're not
allowed to say they can go and get raped.
I don't know, man. That seems a bit unfair.
Rape. [ __ ] hell, bro.
But it's okay for them to go around
being bullies to people they don't know.
No problems. And it weren't even to me,
bro. That that that forehead thing
weren't even to me. If it was, I would
have told you it was.
But it's okay for them to to go around
being like that.
Madness, isn't it?
Cuz you know, if you punch one of them
in their face, they'll be knocked out.
You do realize that? One punch, they'll
be on the floor. You do realize that, Greasy. You know. No.
No. I'm not going to keep myself out of trouble.
And I'm going to show you people on
YouTube how you properly own a woman.
You want to talk about people owning
people? I will show you a proper ownage.
I will show you a proper proper ownage.
And oh, do you know what I will do next
time? I'm going to I'm going to spill
drink at them. I'm going to spill drink
on them. What I'm going to do? Oh,
that's a good idea. Next time just going
to spill drink in their face. Grezy,
I was thinking of doing that in the
weather spoon. You know, I was thinking
of doing that in the Weather Spoons.
I was actually thinking of doing that in
the weather suit. I like that. That's
what I'm going to do. I'm going to get a
load of drink and just pour it in someone's face.
[snorts] Get like an get like white
wine, Grezy. Yeah. Get like white wine
and just go and I'm going to I'm going
to look for someone that's wearing
white. I'm going to throw it at them and
I'm going to [ __ ] throw it at them. Yeah.
Just throw like red wine over white,
bro. We'll talk about ownage then,
[ __ ] Yeah, we'll talk about owners then.
Yeah. [ __ ] scumbags.
Yeah. Yeah. Like from KFC, in it. And
it's P on them. Is it
these women he telling about themsel,
mate? Proper. Proper. Yeah.
And I wouldn't do it. Like I said, I'm
not asked about this. This is just for
YouTube. Now, this is just for YouTube.
This is just for YouTube now, you know. So,
Or no, no, no. Do you know what you
should do? Get a load of piss.
Wait like 5 days and throw it on them.
No, no, no, no. That's the best thing.
Get piss, right? If you if you piss on
something and you leave it for like 3
days, it starts smelling.
Just mix it with a load of [ __ ] piss and
then just throw it on them.
Oh, that is that is vile, bro. Cuz you
know if you leave piss for like three four days,
three four [ __ ] days. Yeah. If you
leave piss for like three, four days,
it starts smelling really really bad.
Really bad. I used to piss in bottles.
So what you should do is come in it,
piss in it, and then just throw it on
them. Who's owning who now, [ __ ]
That's a proper ownage, mate. That's
what I'm going to do, I think. Bro,
I'm going to go I'm going to bring a
piss bottle with me everywhere, you know. Yeah.
Like putting their drinks or something
as well. Yeah.
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. These women need
owning, bro. Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] women are [ __ ] Grezy. They're
[ __ ] [ __ ] That's what they are.
They know in that sig. I wish I really
robbed them, bro. I wish I robbed them,
but I didn't know what. Well, Stig
didn't do anything to me, but
I wish I robbed them. Proper proper rob
Proper proper rob them.
It's good robbing a woman, you know. And
that's the lowest of the low. Somebody
that nick stuff, Greavves, is the lowest
of the low. someone that has to nick stuff.
I don't believe in thieving and nicking,
but for a woman, I would do it 100%. I would nick
I would nick their stuff.
A little thief
is a thief in it. Yeah.
But the best thing is, baby, maybe
follow a woman home and then just just
put piss on her. Just throw piss all over her. Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
See, this is what these women do. They
turn they turn a normal person into a
nasty person, but they don't think that
they're the problem.
They don't think that these women are the problem.
Yeah. Just follow a woman by herself and
then just just throw [ __ ] at her.
You know what you should do? You should
you should pick your [ __ ] up and throw
it at them. No, that's too much. No,
that's too much, bro.
Get like king's poo. Yeah. And then just
pull it in their face. Get their get
[ __ ] Yeah. And then just shove it in
their face. [ __ ] that, bro. Imagine
that. Imagine that.
Go to the Weather Spoons. If you're
arguing with a woman in a in in a place,
go to a toilet, have a [ __ ] pick up
your [ __ ] and then just put it in their face.
Shit's for [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Yeah,
creepsy. Someone's going to get
sectioned, aren't they?
These [ __ ] women need to pay.
I want to hurt one of them, bro. I swear down. Yeah.
I think the piss bottle is the best the best bet.
I did warn these people, bro. I did warn them.
Either you meet me or woman's getting
it. Simple. So
it's like blackmail in a way is it really?
Yeah. [ __ ] these women, bro. They need
to pay for all the bad experiences
they've given me over the years.
But I have spat on a woman before. I
have spouted a woman. She's being rude
to me and I spout on her.
I have actually spouted a woman before. Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
They think wishing that our word on them
is disgusting, but they don't think what
they do is disgusting.
They don't think anything that they do is disgusting.
[ __ ] off, mate.
You know, I might get the piss bottle
ready in a minute, Grezy.
You know what? I might get the piss body
bottle ready in a minute. It has to be
nice and yellow. Greavves. Yeah.
Yeah. I get a nice piss bottle ready in
a minute. I don't have a lug bottle.
I've got a coke bottle.
Got to get ready in a minute.
All the bad experiences they've given me
over the years. [ __ ] snake, rats, you know.
[ __ ] I hurt one of them, bro. I swear down.
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] You know,
don't let these [ __ ] women win,
Grezy. Is it? Huh?
They were laughing at us, Grecy. weren't they?
And I'll do a video walking around
London with a piss bottle and just throw at someone.
What do you think, Grezy?
Is that okay with you, boss?
Have to run it by you first.
No, no, no, no. I gave these people
chances to to to meet me today, Greasy.
I said, "Meet me, meet me, meet me." And
they didn't want to. So, a woman's going
to get it. [snorts] Yeah.
Oh, you virgin.
You absolute virgin.
Look at virgin boy. Yes. How he treats
women and speaks about but again
everything women do gets dismissed.
How how many how much of the population
greasy do you reckon dismisses people's struggles? 90%.
You reckon 90% do it. You're done. >> Yeah.
And then it's going to make these hate
these people hate you even more and
they're still not going to meet you.
That's the whole thing, bro. Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
The UK biggest nonser.
Yeah, I will. What? Dude, dude.
Don't let these [ __ ] women win.
Do you agree with what Joseph said? If
only she knew it's been well more than 3
days. I actually was that morning to be
honest. Eating on a train and talking
with your mouth for a burger early in
the morning train with the people just
wanted to get to work. No wonder she was
annoyed. How we can't understand that is beyond me. So
people don't eat food on the train. No.
No, he's not right.
He's not right at all because people eat
on the train all the time
and you could have moved carriages or
you could have said something politely.
So no, he's not right. And certainly sir,
It was busy enough. It was busy. It
weren't packed pack, but it was busy. It
was busy enough. It was It was like medium. Yep.
I might just do it every day. Just throw
piss on someone every day. Just to annoy
these [ __ ] Just to annoy these little
[ __ ] Just throw piss on them every day. it.
Yeah, exactly. But she was entitled and
she didn't think anyone was going to say
anything back to her.
[ __ ] [ __ ] She's like I didn't
smash her in her mouth.
Yeah. Know what I'm saying? She's lucky
I didn't [ __ ] smack her in her mouth,
mate. Everyone on that train. You got
lucky, bro. You got lucky. I was in a good mood.
You're lucky that I was in a good mood, bro.
Really, you're lucky.
Yourself lucky you didn't get your teeth
smashed out and I was half asleep and I
was in a good mood. You got lucky, man.
You got lucky. Really, you did. [ __ ] [ __ ]
I think you could tell I was [ __ ]
half asleep, to be honest.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
Yes, she was.
Why is this person saying Mont is single
for life and I love it?
Mate, you are single. You're a single
virgin that can't get off of YouTube.
Why are you Why do you keep looking in the mirror?
You are literally single yourself.
Single yourself. Ugly yourself. Scared
to leave your house yourself. You're
talking about yourselves. Why do these
people keep talking about themselves?
And then then they wonder why the
community is dead.
They wonder why the community is dead,
Grezy. They literally post up by saying
they're single ugly people that ain't
got no life talking about themselves and
then they wonder why the community is
dead. They s bro they actually post who
killed the community.
You repeating self-proing low lives
killed it with your projection every
day. These people are fat fat ugly
people that ain't got no life. Never
been no anywhere near a woman. Never had
sex. And they're talking about people
being single when they're [ __ ]
virgins. You know what I'm saying? It's
[ __ ] the projection is strong with
these people. The self projection is
really strong with these people.
And this is why I'm doing this video.
This is exactly why I'm going to be
doing this video. Um, putting piss piss
on a woman's face because if this is not
going to make someone meet me, hopefully
that does, you know.
Stop projecting, Mr. Lonely. You're
single yourself and you're a virgin
yourself. I gave these people chances
today asylum to meet me. They were
whining me up since I woke up. They were
whining me up. I gave them every
opportunity to meet me. They don't want
to meet me. Okay, then a woman's getting
at them, bro. The the the train
incident, I was in a good mood and I was half asleep.
Okay, bro. You're going to see the real
me with a piss bottle then, aren't you?
They had several chances to eat me. They
don't want to do it. No one's been
docked yet. So, a woman's getting pissed
in their mouth.
They're getting pissed. They're getting
piss in their face. A woman is getting
piss in their face to wind them up since
they don't want to meet anyone. Since
these people don't want to meet anyone,
since they don't want to, you know,
they've not been docked yet. Okay, I'll
[ __ ] I'll [ __ ] with women then. Cuz that
seems to really get them rowdy. That
really seems to wind them up. I'll just
[ __ ] with women. I'll [ __ ] with innocent
women then. Simple then. I will just
[ __ ] with I will just I will just [ __ ]
with innocent women. I'll [ __ ] with
them. [ __ ] with them. [ __ ] with them.
And get them out that way then. Simple.
And they're going to have to watch it.
So that's the way it's got to be, bro.
Yeah. So I'll go to jail then. Simple.
I don't think you're going to go to jail
for [ __ ] pissing in someone's face. But yeah,
I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't give a [ __ ] I don't give a flying [ __ ]
Or I could just spit in their face.
Either way, I've actually spit on someone before.
So yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] if they
remind me. I don't give a [ __ ] I don't
give a flying [ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ]
Listen to me when I'm saying this. I
don't give a [ __ ]
I don't I definitely don't give a [ __ ]
you know. So, that's that.
Yeah. I gave these people opportunities
to meet me. They don't want to meet me,
bro. So, yeah. Yeah.
I don't give a [ __ ] if I get them done
for. So, I don't care.
I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't care, bro.
These people are not going to meet me.
So, you know, that's that.
I'll get Red Star mad by spitting in a
woman's face and he'll go mad and there
and he can't do anything about it.
That's how you get these people. [ __ ]
with a woman, spit it up in her face,
right? Degrade a woman because, you
know, all of these white knights and
simps go mad and they'll do nothing. And
then if the police thing don't work,
they'll do nothing.
Degrade them, [ __ ] with them, mock
women. Because you know these white
knights hate it. You know these white
knights go mad when you [ __ ] with women. You know,
I don't give a [ __ ] I don't give a
Get a woman, spit in her face, and say,
"Who's owning who now?" I've just spat
in someone's face. My DNA is on their
face and they're going to do nothing.
That's what you need to do, bro. And
I'll be in a bad mood. I'll be in a
[ __ ] bad mood as well.
M single for life. I don't know why they
keep calling themselves a M. They're
ugly 40y old men that are virgins trying
to talk about me.
They're ugly 40 year old men talking
about me being single when they they
haven't even had sex. They're so fat and
ugly they can't even go out and speak to
women. These people are here right on
here. They can't even speak to a woman.
They're that ugly coming on here trying
to put other people down every day
because they're fat ugly life virgin losers.
Ugly fat virgin autistic losers. Tell
them to put their face on camera, bro.
Tell these people to put their face on camera.
Yeah, I don't care about consequences.
I'll do [snorts]
and I'll spit straight in their face. I'll do
[ __ ] and I'll teach that will teach them
a lesson, bro.
Get spat in your face talking to people
like that. I don't care about
consequences. I don't care. I'll spit
straight in their mouth, bro. I've spat
on someone before. I don't give a [ __ ]
I've spat in someone before.
I spat at them before. Not directly at
their face, but I spat at them. So yeah,
these [ __ ] little stupid [ __ ] don't
own me, bro. The next one I come across,
they're getting spat straight in their
face. I'm spitting straight in their
face and I'm putting it on camera. Yeah, 100%, bro.
These people are fat, ugly, single
people. Why are they talking about other
people? Bro, you people are single and
virgins for life and you're trying to
talk about me when you're sat on YouTube
being a virgin every day, no girlfriend,
and you're trying to talk about me.
You're trying to talk about me when your
life is a 40-year-old virgin on YouTube.
You know, I would say, bro, honestly,
90% of these people on here were virgins.
Absolute virgins. You know, simple, lad.
No, it won't be the end of me, matey.
Because when one of these people are
docked, I'm going on their door. I'm
smashing their windows, bro.
When I get someone to dress, I'm
smashing their door in just like that
fantasy stories. Give me 10 minutes with
that [ __ ] and I'll beat the Irish [ __ ]
out of him, bro. I would smack that
Irish little rejected [ __ ] right? From
one part of shitty island leprechaorn
land to another. See, what annoys me is
these little geeks, these little
virgins, right? Like bat ugly virgins.
They would never say anything to
anyone's face. This is what annoys me is
that you got these ugly washed up skint
nerds. virgins that come on here giving
it the big when bro 10 seconds I would
rearrange the whole ugly face like you
know what I'm saying bro
like there's fantasy stories you know I
would knock the Irish [ __ ] out of him
bro like it's not even a joke I would
knock the [ __ ] Irish [ __ ] out of him
you know I I would I would [ __ ] love
to go for a [ __ ] Irish person on here
bro I would love to you know that
fantasy stories I'd smack his teeth down
his throat Bro, make him swallow it.
Spit in his mouth. I would make him suck
my dick, bro. I would make him suck my
dick. The stupid Irish [ __ ] I would
make him suck my dick, bro. And I'll
piss in his mouth. Yeah. [ __ ]
Northern Irish single [ __ ] Virgin that
women hate. Virgin. Some little Northern
Irish virgin trying to talk about other
people about women hating. Women hate
you. You're a virgin. I've been on here
with more women more than you little
virgins. You little virgins have never
been seen with a woman. You little
virgins have never been laid by a woman.
You know what I'm saying, bro? You ugly
people on YouTube. And I was calling
them all out earlier, bro. Running up my
mouth. No one wants it. Nobody wants it.
This is what I'm saying, bro. Nobody on
this community wants it, bro. This is
what I mean.
I'll make him suck I I'll make him suck
my [ __ ] dick, bro. Yeah.
You [ __ ] ran away from Pat Mustard,
you little bully victim trying to come
in here say that you bully people. You
[ __ ] Irish little bully victim
running off of YouTube for [ __ ] a
year. Please, bro, when I get my hands
on one of these people, bro. When I get
my hands on one of these people. Oh, [snorts]
trust me, bro. Trust me.
>> [clears throat]
>> Please, bro. Just let this is what I
would do, bro. Like, bro, listen. This
is what I would do one of these people
when they get out there, bro. Just this, bro. Yeah.
Just start smacking them in the mouth,
bro. 10 times harder, bro. 10 times harder.
Straight on their straighten their
[ __ ] nose, bro. I swear to God when I
get my hands on one of these little
Irish little virgins,
these little [ __ ] virgins, bro, I'll
smack their teeth down their [ __ ] throat.
And we'll see if they ever come back on
here, bro. Yeah.
I want one of these little Irish virgins
that are hated by women. These little
virgins, like fantasy stories, you know?
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. I want one of
these people badly, bro. Badly, bro. Badly.
>> That's what I want for Christmas, bro.
That's my Christmas wish.
You know what I'm saying, bro? I want
that fantasy stories. The little virgin.
I want that little virgin
little all mouth. And you know what
annoys me about him? He had several
chances to meet that Pat Mustard and he
pussied out of it every time. Every
time, bro. I would have cut off my balls
to beat that pot mustard that day. And
he continu And that's what we we know
that Irish are [ __ ] Irish people are
not about it. They are not about that
life. You might hear about it, but
they're really not.
They're really not about that life.
They're really, really not about that life, bro.
They're really, really, really not about it.
Yeah. Tell him to come on this panel.
I'll [ __ ] own the [ __ ]
I'll own the [ __ ] [ __ ] here. [ __ ] Irish [ __ ] Yeah.
Don't know why they're going like Irish
people are strong and they're [ __ ]
not, mate. They're [ __ ] not strong.
They're [ __ ] well not.
Anyways, what do you think of that
meeting? Do you know what this person
said to me on Reddit? UK asylum. They
said I should meet women in bars and
clubs and coffee shops.
They said go to coffee shops. Coffee shops.
What do you think will happen if I
approach in coffee shops? UK asylum.
Coffee shops. I've done coffee shops three times.
What do you think?
No, I'm talking What do you think will
happen in a coffee shop? H
They said go to coffee shops.
I remember I approached in a coffee shop
once and I said, "Oh, where you from?"
They said, "Uh, just London." But I just
walked away. I literally just walked
away. This was years ago. I still got
the video, by the way. I was just like,
"Nope." Just walked away.
I just walked away, but I just turned my
back and walked away. Yeah. Yep.
What do you think will happen, Greavves,
if I approach in a coffee shop?
I got a number from a coffee shop, but
they never replied.
There were no good women out there.
I'm so certain of it that I'm canceling
next I'm cancelelling this Saturday.
There are no good women out there. I am
telling you, I'm not going out Saturday now. So,
I'm letting people down again once
again. I'm letting people down once
again. And if I don't go out this month,
then I'm [ __ ] because I won't be able
to go out until February.
I'm doing the right thing. I think, bro. Yeah.
There's a time when you need to learn,
bro. You need to learn. And that's the
time I I already learned. The only time
I went out was when I was extremely bored.
But no, I'd rather sit here being a bit
bored than dealing with that [ __ ]
That's completely fine. I'll stay bored.
I've been bored many times before.
So, Saturday's cancelled delayed.
Yeah, that's not what happened.
Yeah, that's not what happened though,
was it? because I told her that she was
clapped and she looks like a crackhead.
So yeah, that's not what happened. But
anyways, you keep making stuff up just
like you done with the Black Bouncer,
just like you done with them two guys.
Bro, no one cares about your opinion. We
all know that you just make up stuff.
You just make up stuff, so no one cares.
You make up stuff a million times. Yeah, bro.
Bro, listen. You make up excuses every
time. No one's interested. We've seen me
stick on a black bouncer. We've se seen
me stick on two men. You're full of
[ __ ] You're lying to yourself. And we
also started a train thing. You're lying
to yourself. Lying is bad, but lying to
yourself at this point is bad. You make
up stuff continuously.
You make up stuff continuously. No one
cares. Stop lying to yourself. Stop
lying to your [ __ ] self.
What was it with the black bouncer
again? Oh, he was at work. Oh, that was
the excuse. You need to stop lying to
yourself. It's unhealthy.
You need to stop lying to your [ __ ] self.
Stop lying to yourself. Stop lying to
I say words, bro. I told them to go [ __ ]
back to Newcastle when I called them an
ugly [ __ ] and they didn't even stand
up. Stop lying to yourself. It's
embarrassing. Stop lying to yourself.
Jesus [ __ ] Christ. It's not good. It's unhealthy.
But again, you people always make up stuff. So
that's your life, is it? Doesn't matter
who it is. You always make up stuff. You
get beaten at the money game, you
pretend you've won. People show more
women than you, you call them virgins.
Uh, people stick it on men and women.
You still pretend that I lost, bro. It's
boring now. It is boring now with you
biased people. Boring biased people.
Boring biased people. Stop it. It's
embarrassing. Stop lying to yourself, you know. So,
I think you skid people need to get a
job and get a life and get off of
YouTube. That's what I think. I think
you skinned people need to to get a life
and get off of YouTube. That's what I think.
Saturday's cancelled. Triple H.
I've already done something. I called a
woman an ugly crackhead on the train and
no one done anything about it. I told
people from Newcastle to [ __ ] off that
they're a [ __ ] and my trainers are
worth more than anything.
Yeah, you you trying to bait people to
get the police involved is not going to
is not going to work. I tell you what
though, if you want to meet me, I'll
gladly do something. You know what? If
you want to meet me, I'll gladly do something.
Yeah. You want people to like smash
someone's teeth in it on camera so you
can get the police involved. You little
nerd. You little birdie nerd. Well, I'll
tell you what though. If you meet me
tomorrow, I'll do something to you if
you want. It's a bit late now. I
understand that. I've I've been calling
people out all day. But I mean, I'll
meet you tomorrow and I'll gladly do
something to you if you want. [ __ ] idiot.
Yeah, [ __ ] the police. Well, you're all
police informants on here. Shut the [ __ ]
up about [ __ ] the police, [clears throat]
mate. You're a keyboard warrior, little
nerd. Shut up. Stop saying [ __ ] the
police, you little nerd.
I told a person on the train that they
were crackhead and that they're ugly in
front of everyone. But I got owned, bro.
I got owned. Yeah, I got owned, bro. I
got owned. Yeah. Just like the black
bouncer owned me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Only
in your little head. Yeah.
Tom Kilbin. Okay. All right. I'll come
to Kilbin tomorrow.
Yeah. Yeah. I'll come to Kilbin
tomorrow. So, can you do a video proving
that you live in Kilbin
and say the time? 400 p.m. I'll be there tomorrow.
I'm not a good little boy. [ __ ] off.
You're a good little boy. You've known
where I've lived for years and you'll do
nothing because you're a good little boy
and you do as you're told. You've known
where I've lived for years and you've
done nothing because you know what's
good for you. I don't know where you
live. I don't [ __ ] know your address.
You know where I live, but you've never
been to my address because you know
what's good for you. You know better.
You're not stupid. You know better. So [ __ ] bongos.
Yeah. What are you saying, Triple H,
bro? Um, yeah. Uh, okay.
You know, I was thinking of doing triple.
I [clears throat] was thinking of
starting on an innocent woman because
these people are not meeting me on here.
Triple H. They're not meeting me on
here. I've gave them several chances to
meet me. They want to keep talking [ __ ]
and pretending women's owe me. So, what
I want to do is I want to start on an
innocent woman and put it on YouTube
and then someone will have to meet me then.
One second, bro. Hold on. Yeah.
So then someone will have to meet me then.
Yep. Someone's going to have to meet me then.
So that's that is it.
You want the link? Yeah.
I wish I could just come across that USA
Izzy, bro. That would be the That would
be the lushest.
Who would I prefer? USA Izzy or Fantasy
Stories? I'd say USA Izzy 100%.
Would that be nice is being in London
and pop and then bumping into that [ __ ]
Yeah, I think I think I'd prefer her
than Fantasy Stories and V.
Yeah, definitely. I think
that's mad, is it, bro?
Yeah, I think I prefer that [ __ ]
I would have a good day with that [ __ ]
bro. Good [ __ ] day with that [ __ ]
Smash her in her mouth, bro. Yeah,
and it will all be on the same website.
You can watch Little Britain.
I'd drop kick hero in her [ __ ] tits.
Really? I drop kick hero in her [ __ ] tits
and hopefully she'll get you know what BC
I'm not going to say it, but you know
what I mean. Greavesy,
I'll do a [ __ ] Randy [ __ ] dropkick. Yeah.
Switching move. I'll switch in music the [ __ ]
That's what I'll do. You know that is
greasy. I'll switch in music the [ __ ] Yeah.
I like that w I like that wrestling move, you know.
Same website you can watch Dobby on, isn't it?
Yeah. I like Dobby. He's a lovely character. Grezy,
I have to be on YouTube now. I can't
leave Grezy without content. The poor [ __ ] in it.
Cuz seaside Mark's not on here anymore. Oh, [ __ ] Yeah.
Oh, I love that USA Izzy, bro. Just a
[ __ ] smash in the face. I'd be like,
"Where's your friend now? Where's your
[ __ ] friend now? Where's your [ __ ]
friend now, bro?"
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
So, we know how to trigger people on
here. We need to start on women. We need
to start on women. That's how you
trigger these people on here.
We trigger them by starting on women, Dusty.
Start on like you're at the park. Do you
know what I done in the park?
You need to do something like that, but worse.
But you need to make sure what you're
doing can't get you nicked as well
because obviously they're police boys on
here. They're little police boys, little
police informants. So, you need to do something bad.
Nope. I'm not leaving women alone. I'm
definitely not women. And And you can
blame these people on here today. I gave
them every opportunity to beat me and
they haven't. I definitely am not
leaving women alone.
I am definitely not women living leaving
women alone. 100% I am not leaving them
And you need to do something where you
can't get nicked for it as well.
You need to do something where you can't
get nicked. Then they're [ __ ] because
then they have to beat you then. Cuz you
know these little police boys on here,
these little police informants, little
police boys, they've got no shame. So yeah.
No, I'm definitely definitely not
leaving women alone. I'm giving them a
bit back of what they've gave me over the years.
Oh, there's one that said that she just
wants to be my friend. I could try and meet her. No,
maybe I'll try the steak thing with her.
Maybe that might work. Uh
yeah, yeah, yeah. Maybe, maybe. I need
to come up with a good story. I might
try and do that the same thing about the steak. Yeah.
You know what?
Let me try and message this person I met
Liverpool Street. They might be up for meeting.
Yeah, I'll just say that. Oh, I've had a
bad experience with a woman. I'm just
looking for friends now. Do you want to
meet me? And then try to try to like get
them to pay for the steak. Yes.
Yeah. I could try with a few people and
then just fill my boots. Greasy. Fill up
my boots and leave him leave him with the bill, you know.
Yeah, I think I might try this route again.
And Red Star is going to do nothing but watch it.
And obviously the police can't do
anything either, realistically. So yeah.
Yeah, I'm going to try uh
Yeah. One second. I'm going to fill my boots.
Going to go Hawks tomorrow. Going to
give them a nice 300 pound bill. Lovely. [ __ ] lovely.
I just say I want to be friends. Let's
go to a nice Let's go to a nice steak place.
That's what that was my original plan
with the first one, but she she cut on.
Yeah. And then just leave them with the
bill. Get them by the pockets. getting Yeah,
that's what I'm going to do, I think.
Yeah, I think I'm going to do that. I'll
just say, "Oh, yeah. I've just had a bad
experience. I do want to be friends and
stuff. I need some women friends." And
then just [ __ ] him over.
Maybe I'll even spill some w I'll throw
some wine at them at the restaurant
and then just walk out.
Yeah, just throw some wine. Some red
Yeah, [ __ ] [ __ ] I'm going to
try and do that. I'm going to message
them in a bit. Yeah.
You want to be a [ __ ] to me, I'll be a
[ __ ] to you. Simple.
And I'll probably think of some other ideas, too.
There's this place called Hawksmore.
It's like [ __ ] I went there. It cost
me like £120 before just for me. Had a
nice steak there. £120.
Yeah, £120 it cost me.
£120 it cost me. So, I could probably
get to like a £400 bill.
Yeah, I'll just walk off. I'll just
walk. I think I'll just I'll just get up
and walk away. Yeah.
So, I messaged this one saying like,
"Oh, do you want to come for a
restaurant to a restaurant? I need some
friends and stuff." Yeah.
I was hoping it worked with the first
person, but I had them on a on a wild goose chase.
Now these women need telling about
themselves, bro. They need telling about
himself. Good and proper, don't they agree? Yeah.
Or you could keep approaching and try
and get one pregnant and then just leave them.
But I don't want to deal with them. I
don't want any interaction with them scumbags.
You could do that. It might take like a
month and then just like [ __ ] their life
up with a baby because eventually I
think you would find someone if you
approached every day. Just [ __ ] their
life up. Just get one of them and just
[ __ ] their life up before they [ __ ]
anyone else's up. That's what you need
to do. You need to [ __ ] someone's life up.
Bit like what they've done to you over
the years. Grezy. Yeah. Yeah,
could be anyone. As long as it's a
woman, greasy. I don't give a [ __ ] As
long as it's a woman, um,
then I I'll do it to anyone. Anyone
that's a woman, I'll do it to. do this.
There is no decent birds. They're all
the same. By the time you find a decent
bird, you'll be in a you'll be in a grave.
I mean, you'll be in a you'll be in a grave.
So, there are no decent birds. They're
all the same.
So, that Yeah. So yeah,
there were no decent birds.
They're all the same. So yeah, we'll
find somebody to do this to. Yeah,
just get a free meal in it. [ __ ] it.
A free lovely meal. Yep.
And it's an exp the bill's going to be
like £400 by the way. The bill will be
like £400. Maybe I'll find like an even expensive one.
I'll probably find like a brew. I I
think Hawksmore is pretty expensive.
Yeah, Hawks Mall is pretty expensive. Greeny. Um,
yeah, that is probably your best bet, I think.
Yeah, that's And they can't get the
police involved as well. So, the people
on YouTube are just going to have to
watch it. They're just going to have to
So all they can do is watch. All they
So they're going to have to go to work
and work hard now to pay for Peter
Belly's meal and be a slave at work. And
they can't get the police involved.
Grezy. I mean they could try and call
the police, but I mean
realistically they're not going to but
so that and obviously they can't get the police involved
because they don't know the person. So
yeah, I think that's the best option.
Just do it with a couple people. But yeah,
do you believe I was going to go that
day if she was going to go to the steakhouse?
Do you believe in Grey that she was
going to she was I was going to meet?
Yeah, I was 100% I was going to meet,
mate. I was looking forward to a [ __ ] steak. Yeah.
Just get free food off the [ __ ]
Keep Peter belly in his little belly. Yeah.
Don't let these [ __ ] win, Grimy.
And I can't leave you without content.
Can I poor [ __ ]
You know, now your idols gone off YouTube.
[ __ ] [ __ ] scumbag women. Yeah,
I won't be out Saturday either. Now I
changed my mind. Yep.
Don't let these [ __ ] women win.
Do not let these [ __ ] women win in it, Grezy.
Don't let these [ __ ] women win. You
remember the one I was arguing with in
the park, Grezy? You found it funny, didn't you?
Did you like that content where I told
her about herself? Did you like that
content? And all you can see is all the
other people in the park. Grezy,
you like that little content, didn't you? [ __ ] [ __ ]
Proper, proper, proper, proper.
Could you imagine I do it to a black
woman? I'm definitely going to have LT
up my ass, bro. I'm definitely going to
have him up my ass.
Definitely. If it's a black woman, I'm
definitely have an LT up my ass, lad.
So, be prepared for it.
I want these women to pay for what they
put me through over the years.
Yeah, I just want to [ __ ] with a woman, bro, badly.
Well, he is only bothered by people's
skin because it's already been proven
with a bouncer.
I [ __ ] up, bro. I stuck it on that
bouncer and he was making excuses just
cuz the guy was black.
If it was a white guy, he would have had
no problem. Uh,
so if I do it to a sister, if I do it to
a sister, as Americans would call it,
he's definitely going to be gunning for me, mate.
But to be fair, a lot of people made
excuses, but he made excuses because the
guy was black. Oh, he can't hit you cuz
he's at work when we all know bouncers
hit people all the time. We all know
bouncers act like [ __ ] We've all
seen bouncers go around the corner and
start fighting people, mate. We've seen
it in Wales. We've seen it. We've seen
it, mate. We've all seen these bouncers
what they do, mate. Yeah, I've seen it.
You've seen it. You know, so
you got to understand that these black
people are more racist than than they
try to say other people are.
They're more racist than anyone else.
Yeah, exactly, bro.
If a bouncer ever done that to me, bro,
I would go back with a hammer, bro. I
would go back with a [ __ ] hammer. I
stuck it on a big uh Polish bouncer, you
know? Uh he was big. He was a white
Polish bouncer, bro. And I was calling
him a Polish pig. Everything, bro. I was
running up my mouth cuz if if if they
ever beat me, I'd go back with a hammer.
I would, bro. I I generally would go
back with a hammer or like get some
glass bottles and start throwing it at them.
No way is a bouncer beating me up in
front of anyone. Bro, you mad. [ __ ]
that. [ __ ] that, bro. I tell you who's
got the worst bounces. Leads. Leads.
Their bounces are disgusting, bro.
They're They're horrible, bro. Horrible.
Them bounces and leads are the worst.
They hate us, bro. They hate Southerners.
I had to stick it on one before it was
some black guy. I said, "What?" I said,
"Bro, why don't you [ __ ] off?" Yeah, you
[ __ ] [ __ ] Yo, you're you're [ __ ]
you're wearing Ralph Lauren. You're
you're [ __ ] you are you are flexing
Ralph Lauren. That just goes to show how
behind you are, bro.
I've already been to Newcastle.
Yeah, the bounces in Newcastle. All right.
Yeah, the bounces there are all right.
He was like, "Oh, I was like, bro,
you're flexing Ralph Lauren,
bro. That just goes to show you Norman behind.
It goes to show that these northerners
are [ __ ] behind
for New Year's Eve.
Could do. Yeah,
Newcastle for New Year's Eve. Yeah,
I just don't want to go out in this
country anymore. UK silent. The women
ruin it. They ruin the whole experience. They're [ __ ]
I don't really want to do anything, bro.
If I'm honest with you.
Yeah, Newcastle was a good shout though.
That is good. You know,
I just don't want to do anything, bro.
To be fair.
And I'm not even depressed. I'm not even
depressed. I just don't want to do anything.
I'd rather just sit in and just chill,
bro. Like, I'm not even depressed to be fair. No.
Yeah, I'm just looking at Newcastle. The
hotels [ __ ] expensive as [ __ ] bro.
Oh, there's that nice hotel that I was
staying in with a balcony. That's a nice
hotel. It's got a balcony.
Yeah, that hotel's lovely, bro.
That's the one that all that [ __ ]
happened with the police.
That was a lovely hotel as well.
That's when that happened with the
police and [ __ ] They come and nicked
me, bro. They're [ __ ]
That's a lovely hotel, though. It's got
a nice balcony and a bath.
But there's What they are set,
but [snorts] the
hotel is £223.
Not worth it, is it? 223 pounds. Good.
New Year's Eve.
New Year's Eve. Newcastle would be sick though.
That'll be ace.
How busy do you reckon it'll be? It'll
be [ __ ] choa, mate. Choa block.
It'll be rammed. Yeah.
No, I don't think I'm going anywhere.
I'm not doing nothing. I don't want to
do anything anymore. I just want to sit
around and just stay money.
It gets like that, Dusty. It's just pointless.
It's pointless doing anything,
you know. Might as well just save to leave. No.
Oh, look a red star shine £1,000 again. [snorts]
Look at them fingernails, bro.
Oh my god, this guy's skinned, bro. I've
just gone on his channel.
Showing a,000 power maximum. Oh my god.
Oh Jesus Christ. This is ridiculous, lad.
Uh oh. M is going to be absolutely
fuming over this. Clana for Christmas
shopping rejected by Reddit. Two skin
hack actors to fly.
So you you need to make up your mind.
Have I got bad credit or do I use clana?
Shame the mon can't ma match that. I can
match it, but I'm not showing you any
money because every time you're showing
money, you fat ugly [clears throat]
people. You fat ugly little bongos, you
run away. I can match it, but I'm not
showing you nothing. So that's that.
Bum chains. Bum chains. Look at his life
savings showing £1,000. I could easily
more than double that right here, right
now. But I'm not I'm not doing it cuz
I'm not showing
I'm not showing these little skint
self-reflecting fat ugly people
anything. You show your faces and I'll
show you money. Simple. I've said this
before and that that's it. That's what
I'm saying to you.
[ __ ] virgins. Absolutely virgins on here, bro.
Colana. Apparently I use Kana. I [ __ ]
wish. Why? Because people are not skin
like you. Look at this guy showing these
benefits off again. 10 pound notes
again. Oh my [ __ ] god, bro. Jesus Christ.
Jesus Christ. This is embarrassing, bro.
Colana. Why? So, because people are not
skin ugly and feel the powder bob boys
like you. How the [ __ ] did all of that
go to that, bro? It's embarrassing now.
It's really, really embarrassing.
You go about skin. It's cuz you skint
yourselves. Change the self-reflecting [ __ ]
change the [ __ ] self-reflecting
record, you skin bastards.
You know what I'm saying? You [ __ ]
ugly fingered benefit boy showing off
your benefits. Look at this red sauce
showing off his benefit.
Showing off £800. He's [ __ ] skinned.
This is what I mean with these people,
bro. They're [ __ ] skinned on there, Yeah.
Yeah, they would do, bro.
You know what the [ __ ] is this colada
thing? So because people are not fat,
ugly, and skin like you. You're making
up stuff. That's also what you're
resorting to making up stuff now.
Madness, bro. No one needs Colona. We're
not all skin like you. We don't live
your skin lives showing off 700 [ __ ] pound, mate.
Do you know what I'm saying, bro?
We're not [ __ ] showing off [ __ ]
£800 cuz we're skintike. You don't know
what it is with these people. Their
disabilities, bro. literally get their
mixed up with themselves. It's part of
their autism. They get themselves
confused. Bro, you just said that I've
got [ __ ] credit history.
But I'm more than happy to prove these
receipts to you. The trainers, the
jeans, show you're not an ugly fat [ __ ]
Show you're not an ugly an ugly fat
bastard. And I'll show you what you
want. But you can't because you're fat,
ugly little nerds.
Low life skin rejected people. That's
why you do it. Why? That's why you do
what you do all day. Skin ugly pack of fat nerds
showing off [ __ ] £800. What the [ __ ]
bro? [ __ ] these people truly truly asking.
I I I you know what, bro? I expect
double that last month.
These fat When are these fat ugly people
going to get off of YouTube and get a life? You know,
fat ugly skin 300 pound a month bumble
chum is going to get a life. Like you
really really need to ask yourself this
question, bro. It's [ __ ] pathetic now.
I've never used colada in my life. We're
not all you skinned people on YouTube.
You go on like you got all of this
money. Yeah, but you're on it all the
time. It's cuz you're skin. It's the
definition of skin. Well, unless you're
saving for a car. Well, unless you're
saving money for a car or I don't know
what it is you're doing, bro. You know
what I'm saying? Yeah, they would say
that because they make up stuff.
Well, yeah, they
I don't hate many people in here, but
the MTO isn't. Bro, you people are the
mons. Listen, if you hate me that much,
smog, why didn't you do anything when I
was in Newcastle?
You hate me, brother. I was in
Newcastle, another fat, ugly slob that
hid. Mate, you people are dumb bunties.
Have you seen your ugly faces? Have you
seen the state of you people? Have you
seen the state of you ugly people before
talking about other people? How can
these fat ugly single people call people
mers? These fat, ugly single people,
mind you, yet they try to talk about you
single being single. How can these fat
ugly slobs come on here and talk about
other people? these fat ugly muners
that's never been seen with a woman
because they're too ugly. Talk about
anyone, bro. Like, let's let's really
let's set the record straight, bro.
These people are the biggest monies ever.
They're the pro, bro. Listen. Like,
these people are [ __ ] disgustingly
ugly. Why do you think they don't put
their camera on, bro? They don't put
their camera on because they are [ __ ]
ugly. This is why they target people
that are younger and better looking than
it because they are [ __ ] fat and
ugly. Why do you think they sit on here
every day doing the [ __ ] that they do?
Because they're fat, ugly bully victims
in the real world. Yeah, they're [ __ ]
absolute bully victims. Too ugly. They
can't even leave their house. Every time
they try to leave their house, bro, they
probably get picked on for being so ugly
and then they come back on YouTube again. Bro,
these people on here, bro. They're fat,
ugly life losers.
Yeah. Home [ __ ] skint ugly, rejected
virgins. That's what they are. They're
And to this smog guy, right? I've been
to Newcastle three times and this guy
did not come out. I went to Newcastle
three times and this little Jordy
[ __ ] this little Jordi Manta [ __ ]
did not come out. Oh, we've heard it all
before, bro. You know what I'm saying?
We've heard it all before. What the
[ __ ] This little jewely. Well, I man
and deck [ __ ] didn't come out once.
Hate is a strong word. Hate is a very,
very strong word to use considering
somebody's traveled 300 miles and you
still didn't come out. Hate is a very,
very strong word for somebody that you
wouldn't even you wouldn't even confront.
You know what I'm saying?
You know what I'm saying, bro? Like hate
is a strong word. Is a that's a quite a
strong word, Grezy. Would you hate
somebody that you don't know but then
you run away from? These people on here
are so disabled. I'll answer your
question later why the community died
since you wanted to know so badly why
the community died. It died because of you mongos.
Because of you little mongos. It died
because of you repeated mongos. But you
want these people to answer your question
cuz are you little autistic repeating
little skin low lives that can't get up
on YouTube. So are you saving for a car?
You need to tell me exactly what are you
saving for. Are you saving for a car?
Are you saving for something like I'm
not going out because I'm saving money
cuz I can't be bothered. But that's why
I'm on YouTube. Why are you on YouTube?
You got skin ugly [ __ ] low lives.
rejected ugly people that don't fit into society, bro.
Yeah. Ugly little rejected little
keyboard warriors. And you know, every
time I say this [ __ ] it hits a nerve.
Fat, ugly, disabled, hopeless 40 year olds, wrinkly,
ugly to the core people that ain't got a life.
You know what I'm saying? [ __ ] fat,
ugly people that can't get off of YouTube.
Big fat ugly virgins. [ __ ] virgins.
Yeah, that's all I wanted to say, bro.
That's it. That's that.
People don't need People don't need to.
And look, they're still repeating
themselves, but then they're wondering
why the community is dead. They're They
literally They're asking each other,
"Why is the community dead?" Because
these disabled, brain dead people keep
repeating themselves. People are bored
of it. This is why people, bro, do you
know how many people used to be on here
compared to how many people on here now?
It's because the repeating. It's the
repeating. It's boring.
A bunch of fat, ugly, disabled people
repeating themselves. And then you
wonder why people don't And then they
wonder why people don't stay around.
They wonder why people don't stick
around. Why is the community dead,
Grezy? They asked, "Why is the community
dead?" They posted, "Why is the
community dead?" because of you disabled
fat projecting [ __ ] boring the [ __ ]
out of people, talking negatively about
yourselves, calling yourselves skin,
calling yourselves a mun, bullying
yourselves. Like, we don't want to see a
bunch of people bullying themselves
every day. A bunch of fat, ugly keyboard
warriors that bully themselves. Who
wants to watch people that bully themselves, bro?
Who wants to watch a bunch? And do you
know what the thing is, right? They call
people on here autistic, but they repeat
the same [ __ ] every day. Every single
insult is the same. It's the same old
[ __ ] It's the same old repeating
because they are autistic. Low IQ,
autistic. That is the the their favorite
word on here, bro. That's their favorite
word on here because they are autistic.
Autistic, ugly people that's got no IQ.
They can't even think of different comebacks.
[ __ ] talk about disabled for people
that keep talking about the same. They
repeat the same [ __ ] every day.
No, I'm just sick of these people,
Steven Howard. I'm just sick of these people.
I've got a low credit score, but yet I
use Colada. Make it make sense. By the
way, like I told you, I'm willing to
show these receipts. When you come on
camera and you show your face, I'll show
you anything you want. Money, receipts.
I've got email receipts of the things I
bought. I will happily when you prove
that you're not an ugly bastard in your
40s, I will gladly show you everything.
But you can't because you know you're
ugly. And this is where all of this
YouTube stuff comes from. Ugly, jealous
40 year olds. That's what they are, bro. Ugly, jealous
40year-old virgins that ain't got a
life. Look, they come here insulting
people every day. Oh, they've got this,
they've got that, but they're sat on
YouTube every day, bro. You know,
you know what I'm saying, lad? They're
[ __ ] all got all this money, but
they're sat on YouTube every day
obsessing over content, but they've got
all this money. Women life, but they're
[ __ ] sat on YouTube every day.
They're sat on YouTube every day. Lonely
lonely people talking to each other
because they're [ __ ] loners, bro.
Uh, I'm going to meet this woman and
make her pay for the steak. So,
basically, if somebody doesn't meet me,
I'm going to be I'm going to purposely
go and [ __ ] up with I'm going to [ __ ] up
a woman. I'm going to [ __ ] over a woman.
Like, I'm going to go I'm going to make
her pay for my food and then ditch her.
I'm going to purposely [ __ ] with a
woman. If none of these people meet me,
I'm doing that, bro.
Bro, but guess what? I've took a day off
of YouTube. None of you can. So, if
that's the case, Jen, how comes I can
take a day off YouTube, but you can't?
Cuz you ain't got a life. You're lonely
on here. This is what I mean. How comes
I can take a day off of YouTube, but
none of you little weasels can't? But
you got all this money and everyone else
is the ma, but you little mongos can't
take a day off of YouTube. Do you want
me to prove it again? Please don't make
me prove it again. It's because you're
fat, ugly little nerds that don't fit
into society, bro.
You're fat, ugly, little weasel, little
[ __ ] nerds. And I'll say it to your
face. The difference is I'll say this to
your face, but you can't say it to my
face. You literally are fat, ugly
people. Hopeless little losers that
don't even leave your house, right?
Trying to talk about people every day
that you don't even know, bro. Trying to
talk about people that you don't even [ __ ] know.
You can't even take a day off of YouTube
because you're that [ __ ] disabled
[ __ ] ugly people. You can't even get
off of YouTube because you're bully
victims. You're absolute bully victims
in the real world. Bully victim fat ugly
little virgins. And that's the truth.
And you know what I'm saying about you
is the truth. End the story now. We're
not going to keep going on about this. That's it.
So, no. I'm just sick of these pe I'm
just sick of these little mongos.
These ugly little bongos, bro. Yeah, I'm
a bully victim. Yeah. Okay, bro. You
keep telling yourself that, bro. The
only people that get bullied is you
people. You're little virgins. You're
little nerds. You can't get off of
YouTube and get a life. You're bully
victims in the real world. Just because
you write comments on YouTube, right? It
doesn't mean that we're bully victims
like you fat, ugly people. You can't
even take a day off of YouTube. Every
time you go outside, you get bullied for
being so ugly. You're absolute victims.
You people are absolute bully victims.
Ugly little skin bully victims. And
that's why you've been doing this year
in year out year in year out because
you're absolute bully victim. Unlovable
single depressed little virgins. Bro,
you're laugh you're laughing at someone
that's younger and better looking than
you. Someone that's younger and better
looking than you. I don't think you're
laughing at me. I think you envy anyone
that's got better looks and, you know,
younger than you. Trust me, mate. You're
old, wrinkly, ugly people. You laugh at
yourselves. You old, wrinkly, skinned
little virgins laugh at yourselves. A
bunch of old skin, wrinkly people is
laughing at someone that's younger and
better looking than you when you're in
your 40s, got no money, no life. Are you
really trying to tell me that, bro? sat
on YouTube, skinned, never had a woman,
can't get any money, and you're laughing
at someone that's younger, better
looking than you. Younger, better
looking than you. Really, bro? Yeah,
because they're monsters themselves.
Yeah, because they're mters themselves.
they're calling people a m cuz they're
mters themselves. It's what they look in
the mirror every day
because they all the monsters. I'm 28
and I've had more girlfriends than you.
Bro, you're you're repeating the same
[ __ ] brother. You're in your 40s. Yeah.
You're in your 40s and you're single.
Shut up. Stop trying to talk about other people.
Brother, you're in your 40s and you're
single. [ __ ] a 28-year-old, bro. You're
in your 40s and you're still a virgin.
And you're talking about a 28-y old.
Look closer to home. Look closer to
home. Look at your own lives, bro.
You're in your [ __ ] 40s and you're
single and you're talking about other
people. You little virgin. [ __ ] off, bro. You know
these people are in their 40s and
they're single and they're trying to
talk about other people. Bro, stop it now.
Stop it, bro.
You are in your 40s and you're single
and you're trying to talk about a
28-year-old that's better looking and
younger than you. Get a grip, bro.
to my [ __ ] I was just talking to my
mom, bro. Sorry about this. Yeah. No, I
was just talking to my mom. I said,
"Yeah, they just make up stories. No
matter what they make up stories about,
they're just fat, ugly little lowife
people that ain't got nothing in their
life." Simple as that, bro. I was just
talking to my mom about this. They're
just ugly little bitter nerds. 40y old
bitter nerds. That's what they are, bro.
They're [ __ ] old, ugly little bitter
nerds. That's what people need to think.
People need to think about that really
before reacting to these people. It's
the truth. They're ugly. They're fat.
They're worthless. They got no money.
They got no life. They're bully victims.
They're single. Why are we reacting to
these people, bro? It's the truth,
really, isn't it? It is the truth.
Yeah, sorry about that, bro. I was just
talking to someone.
Anyways, yeah, bro. They're just um
that's what they are. Yeah,
fat ugly little skint low life pathetic people
that twist [ __ ] Yeah, that's what they
do. Yeah, [ __ ] ugly people. They
ain't got a life.
All sad people that haven't got anything
in their lives.
Ugly, bitter little middle-aged people
that ain't got [ __ ] in their life. It's
laughable, bro. Laughable.
People will move on to something else now. [snorts]
>> I know the video is not getting
privatized, bro. Greavves is not
privatizing it. Grievy. Just leave it up
there, lad. Because whatever you do,
these people always twist [ __ ] and make
up stuff. You know what these little
virgins are like? These little nerds.
So, no, don't privatize it. Leave it up
there, bro. I don't need anything
deleted or anything because these people
continuously make up stuff even when
they took L's.
Just leave him, bro. Just leave them,
brother. Yeah. They're just disabled,
bitter, ugly people. They ain't got [ __ ]
all. Look at this. Triple H. You see the
same people on it for [ __ ] years, bro.
Asking why the [ __ ] community is dead.
Skid little wet wipes. Funny, bro. disabled.
Even when they took L's, they lose.
That's why Cayman doesn't come on here, bro.
Right. I'm not looking on this. No.
Anyway, it's boring, bro. It's actually
so boring. They just repeat the same [ __ ]
That's why my mom don't even look on it
anyway. They're just repeating little losers.
Yeah. Bad. Bad. All right. And you're
getting banned as well. Bye-bye, coward.
Sad little life. Pathetic ugly losers.
Ugly pathetic skint losers. They ain't
got a life. You're banned as well. You
[ __ ] virgin. Another one that that
backed out of me. Now we need to careful
who's on here now, bro. Yeah.
They need to get they need to get they
need to get a job and get a life. These
people are here.
They need to get a job and get a life, you know.
sad little middle-aged losers. They got
a pot to piss in. I'm going to do a
video later on and screenshot this, you
know, and I'm going to do a video later
on these little nerds, these little
single nerds. What makes me laugh is
they try to criticize other people.
Yeah. But they're sat there lonely on
YouTube. You're lonely people. And every
time you hit a nerve, you you know what
you're saying about them is the truth.
Terry, another one, single, ugly,
[ __ ] Is it mad how they're jealous of
anyone that's younger and better looking
at them? Did you know this is what it
comes to with these people? It comes to
jealousy with these fat, ugly nerds.
That's why you need to really swallow
the pill that is jealousy with these
people. Think about it, bro. These
people late 30s, 40s, 50s, no money, no
looks, no future, they're depressed,
bro. Depressed, ugly people that come
onto YouTube every day. depressed, ugly
people. This is why they do this.
They're hopeless little losers.
Hopeless little nerds that say they've
got this, say they've got that, say
they've got this, but they're on YouTube
all day, every day with not a pot to
piss in. You see the the comments, right?
Go over and over, reply and over and over.
It's [ __ ] madness, bro. Madness.
sad, pathetic little virgins.
Virgin, ugly. And this is all jealousy
as well, Steven Howard. This is what it
is with these people. They hate that
you're younger and better looking.
That's why they've got a problem with
with with you. They hate the fact that
you're younger and better looking. It
kills them. And obviously, because you can't
uh because you can't meet because they
can't meet you in real life and stuff,
um it kills them that you're younger and
better looking. That's where all of this
comes from. It's jealousy, bro, with
these people. Believe you me, I've asked
these people numerous times, Stephen
Howard, to put their cameras on. Like,
as put your camera on, show what you
look like. They can't do it. They can't
do it. It proves that they're ugly,
jealous, old people.
What I'm saying, bro? It's the truth. It
is actually the truth. They hate that
you're younger and better looking. Don't
forget, the people that come on here,
bro, are losers. like their lives are
over. Sat calling people this that
[ __ ] killing the community, bro.
They're [ __ ] killing it.
These people are,
you know, just like this Smokey Bee,
he's got no life. Old, ugly, skint, and
he can show 1700 pound. He's still
[ __ ] skin, mate. You know, he he he
is there. bad skinned people that are
ugly that take out on the rest of the
world. That's why they do this, bro.
Believe you me, this is why they do
this. Because people that's got money
don't come on here. They're living their
best life. Look at all of these big
YouTubers, bro. Yeah. That do this,
that, and the other. Yeah. They're
living their best lives. These people
are living their worst lives on YouTube.
No money. Old ugly people waiting for
any bit of content. It's pathetic, bro. It's pathetic.
So yeah, Greavvesy, just leave it up,
bro. Don't don't take anything down,
you know. Do not put don't don't and and
we'll get these [ __ ] back anyways with
the poo. So it's all right, bro. I don't
want you to take anything down, bro. I
don't need anything to down
cuz these sad little virgins will always
do what they do. Sad little virgins.
That's it, bro.
Uh, I've already explained to you why
I'm on here all the time. I've already
explained it. Why are you rich people on
here all the time? Shouldn't you be out
living your best lives? No, because you
ain't got anything. And I've already
explained to you why I'm on here all the
time. Because I can't be bothered to go
out and I just want to save money. Why
are you rich people on YouTube, better
looking than everyone, got all this
money? Why are you on YouTube every day,
all day, every day, doing what you're
doing? Because you've got nothing.
because you don't have anything in your
lives. Old ugly skinned people. Not
repeating myself anymore. It's the
truth. You do what you do because you
hate that you're old and ugly and you
take it out on people that are better
looking and younger than you. Because because
one second because
um what was it again? I mean, how many
times do I get calls off that Jamie
Thompson? It's because you're younger
and better looking than him. It's a hard
pill to swallow, but that is the truth.
Jealousy is a killer, to be honest with
you. That's why they do all of this
stuff. I've noticed it. Yeah.
Oh, that's why they do all of this stuff.
Yeah. Maybe others are doing the same as
me. No, I don't think so. No, I don't
think so. Because you're on here on a
hot summer's day.
You know, you're on a hot summer, you
know, you're on YouTube. you you know
you you're you're on YouTube on a hot
summer's day. I don't think people are
saving money on a hot summer's day. So
no, it's because you people are skint
and that's why you are so obsessed with
skint people. It's cuz you skint
yourselves and you can't stop talking
about yourselves. You talk about people
being skint is cuz you are skint. I
don't know how many times I have to keep
saying it, bro. It's because you people
are ugly and skint and you can't even
get off of YouTube
because you are skinned.
Free boiled eggs, but I've got plenty of
money, plenty of hunger. Really? Yeah. I
mean, we're on a diet. I mean, me and
Greavves is on a diet. But I'm not on
here pretending I'm rich, but can't take
a day off of YouTube like some people.
Yeah. I mean, do you want me to order
takeaway? I mean, I could order a
takeaway right now and prove you wrong
yet again. But there's a problem with
that. Yeah. But there's a there's a
problem with that. I mean, I could order
a big takeaway right now. I could go to
a steakhouse if I want to. But there's a
big problem with that is I don't wake up
every morning having to prove myself to
fat ugly people. To fat, ugly, skinned
people that ain't got a life. That
that's the that's the problem with it.
And every time you have been proven
wrong in the past, you pretend that you
haven't. My life is not proven fat ugly
people that ain't got no life wrong
millions of times. So I mean I can order
a takeaway right now. I really really
really really can. You get proven wrong
a million times and then you still act like
me and Greavves is on a diet. We have
got money. We can buy whatever food we
want to but we are on a diet.
Yes. Okay. And what I can get a takeaway
whenever I want to.
This is what you people do on it. You
bounce of other people's lives cuz you
ain't got a [ __ ] life of your [ __ ]
own. That's what it is.
Uh self projected and but then you
wonder why the community is dead. But
then you wonder why the community is
dead. Yeah. Again. You're talking about
yourselves again. Skelselves
Okay, GA. How much? Okay, Gona. Okay,
how much money
How much money do I have right now? Gona, okay,
skint loser. Whatever people show you
skin people, you just call them skin. I
don't know why you do this.
It's not going to change the fact that
you're skint. The amount of times you
keep trying to call people that you
don't know skin. It's not going to
change the fact that you're skin yourselves.
I'm trying to help you here. I'm
actually trying to help, but you don't
listen to me.
One second. But didn't you say that I
But apparently I do I use Kana. But
apparently I use Kana.
But you're saying I've got bad So which
one is it? Is it Is it Kana?
Is it Kana? Oh, is it is it have I got
bad credit? Which one is it? Make up
your mind. You need to make up your
mind. Do I use Colana or have I got bad
credit? Make up your mind, bro. It's not
really making a lot of sense now. Cuz
one day you're saying one thing and then
one day you're saying another, right?
Yeah. You need to get a job. Yeah,
exactly. You get a job. Same to you,
bro. Exactly the same to you. You get a
job. You get yourself a job. Get off of YouTube.
You people get off of YouTube, get
yourselves a job, go get your ugly
selves laid, and then start talking
about other people. Yeah, bro. Yeah, you
go get yourself a job, get yourself off
benefits, and then start talking about other people.
No, no, but but people have said that
I've used Kana, so I use Colana. Oh,
make up your mind. I told you. Hey,
Duna. Guna. Bro, I've said to you, I
will happily show you anything you want.
When you show your face and you prove me
wrong that you people are not fat, ugly bums.
When you prove you're not fat and ugly,
I will show you whatever you want. But
you can't do it because I'm right about
you people. Old, fat, and hideous
looking ugly people that ain't got
nothing. Bro, I'm right about you, bro.
Show your face. Show your stomach. and
show that you're not a fat ugly [ __ ]
But you can't do it cuz I'm right about
you. I'm right about you ugly little
nerds. That's what I'm saying, bro. I'm
right about you. I'll show you receipts
if you want. I'll email I'll put them up
right here now. I've got emails, emails
with receipts of things I bought. You
show that you're not fat and ugly and
I'm wrong and I will show you anything
that you want. Money, receipts. That's
my promise to you. But you can't do it
cuz you know you're fat and ugly. You
know you're fat and ugly and I'm right
about you and it kills you. Simple.
That's that, bro. Yeah. I'll show
receipts when you come and you show your face.
Yeah. When you show your face and you
prove you're not fat and ugly, I will
show you anything you want. And I'm
going to be mentioning I'm going to be
mentioning that on the video that I do
later. Actually, when I street when I
screen record this stuff, when I screen
record this stuff, I'm going to say to
you, prove you're not fat and ugly and
I'll stop showing stuff to you.
Oh, you are fat and ugly. Oh, can we see
your fate? Okay, prove it. Prove it.
Show everyone what you look like. Show
everyone what you look like. And then
I'll start showing receipts.
£1,100. You don't know what I get, Gona.
You don't know what I get, Gona. And let
me tell you something, Gona. I've got
more I've got more disposable money than
you will ever have.
I've got more disposable money than your
Welsh ass will ever have. So, you can
keep telling people what they get a
month. I've got more disposable money
than you would ever have. Think about
that one. So, yeah.
Right. But you don't know how much money
I have. Maybe I do. Maybe I do other
things to get more money. You don't know
my life. I know what you people get.
You're on £300 a month. You got no life.
You're on universal credit. I know how
much you people get.
You're on that £300 a month benefits.
That's why you're on YouTube every day.
Skint on YouTube every day. Skint to the
eyeballs, calling other people what you
are. Yeah, you're on that universal credentials.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that.
You keep telling yourself that. When are
you people going to get a job and get a
life and get laid? When are you little
skint virgins going to get off of
YouTube and get a life and get laid? You
little skint nerds, when are you going
to get a job and get a life?
When are you little skint little nerds,
little virgins going to get off of
YouTube and get a life? Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Yeah, because
you've never been with a woman. Cuz
you've never had a girlfriend. You've
never been with a woman. You're a sad little man.
Because you're a sad little man that's
never been with a woman. But that's why
cuz you've never been with one. So
you've never ever ever had the chance
for them to even insult you.
Say nothing to the woman. I I told her
she was an ugly crackhead.
[laughter] I told her she was an ugly
ugly crackhead and she's boring me.
Okay, GA. Okay, GA. Whatever you say. I
said that she's an ugly crackhead that
needs to look in the mirror. Okay, GA.
Okay, Ga. Okay, Ga. Just like you've
known where I've lived for years, but
you ain't done nothing. Okay, GA. Okay, Ga.
Okay, Ga. Says the man that knows where
people live, but doesn't do anything.
Okay, Gona. Okay, Gona. Do you want to
Do you want to join the Do you want to
join the box?
Rob, you're a beta male, bro. You're
trying to sit there and say that I went
to Wales without calling you out, bro.
You would have went on my door. I lived
by myself for 9 months, but you didn't
do nothing. Goona, stop it. Stop it.
Goona, you knew where I lived and you
done nothing. Goona, you're not about
that life. You're really really not
about that life. Fat old man, you're not
about that life. So, I don't know why
you why you keep flexing. Bro, you said
that I went to Wales and you said I
didn't call you out. Bro, you knew where
I lived and you done nothing. knowing
where someone lives. Bro, I've told you
this earlier. How long have I wanted to
know where people have lived? You knew
my address and you done nothing. You
done absolutely nothing. And you was a
train ride away. So, stop going on like
you're some kind of big man, bro. I
could walk in a circle and you'd be out
of breath, falling to the ground. You're
a fat old man. I don't know why you're
coming on here like you're going to be
fighting people. But me and LT went to
places, didn't we? Me and LT went to
places, but you scared to go on people's
doors because you're a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Simple. Just typing [ __ ] Yeah, cuz
you're a [ __ ]
You're a [ __ ] Welsh [ __ ]
Oh yeah, the box. Sorry about that. One
second, bro. I forgot.
[ __ ] Welsh bog.
Calling people disabled, but you disabled yourself.
Yeah. Yeah, of course. Of course I did.
Anyways, GA, why didn't you come in my
address when I was living by myself for 9 months?
Come on. What's the excuse? Come on.
Don't use Lord J as an excuse. What's
the What's the excuse? Come on. Sorry
about that. You knew where I lived and
you've done nothing, but yet you think
that anyone's going to take you
seriously. [ __ ] out of here, bro. It's
embarrassing now. [ __ ] out of here. I've
even been on people's [ __ ] doors.
You'd rather be You'd rather be fat and skint.
Okay, but you are fat and skint. So why
why are you saying you'd rather be
Anyways, come in the box, bro. Come in the box.
I told that [ __ ] woman to [ __ ]
herself. She's an ugly looking
crackhead. And look in the mirror.
You're an idiot, Guda. You're a fat old
man. Shut up. You're a fat, bitter old
man. Stop it now. Yeah,
right. No, no, no, no, no. I want to
know why you didn't come on my door.
You're saying I'm a [ __ ] so why have I
traveled to places to meet people and
you haven't? I've been to Middlesbr,
bro. You couldn't even come to London.
You're not about that life. You're not
about that life. And you know you're not
about that life, bro. You're a fat old man.
You're a fat old man. And you're on
YouTube [ __ ] acting like you can
fight, bro. What could a fat old
asthmatic man do to me? Please just stop
it now. It's embarrassing.
Yeah, there you go.
You got the link by the way. You joining
or what? You said you wanted the link.
I'm doing that thing with the steak, by the way.
the way. Not a problem at all. We're
still doing that.
Yeah. You know what makes you look
stupid? Telling people to get a job when
you ain't got a job yourself, you
[ __ ] fat bum.
Telling people to get a job when you
ain't got a [ __ ] job yourself, you
[ __ ] [ __ ] But no one will tell
you that, will they? No.
Mate, you're a [ __ ] [ __ ] trying to
tell other people to get a job when you
ain't got a job yourself. You little bum
boy. You little bum boy. Do you know
what? I'm convinced. Yeah, this is like
the same four people. How many years
have you been telling people to get a
job and you ain't got a job yourself?
It's embarrassing. It is embarrassing.
Yes, I do, Guna. And you're going to do
nothing. You're going to do nothing
about it. Yeah, you got a great job. Of
course you do, mate. Wanking waiting for
your £300 a month from the benefit
system is not a job. Your little
benefits, your £300 a month benefits is
not you working, you little skint [ __ ]
If you had an amazing job, you wouldn't
be telling people to get a job every
day. You ain't got a job yourself.
You're skint. Practice what you preach.
Anyways, I'm banning some of these
people now. Anyways, bro, they're
[ __ ] boring, bro. more than spasticated people.
There you go. You got you got the link.
[ __ ] what are you people going to get a life?
Yeah, I'm so hard bullying a woman. Oh,
I'm bullying a woman now. Oh, make up your mind.
Oh, I'm bullying a woman now. Make up
your mind, you little sin. [ __ ] weirdo.
You're an absolute idiot, man.
Anyways, I'm going to I'm going to do a
video on this thing later, bro.
More than happy to to prove stuff to you
if you put your cameras on. You put your
cameras on. I'm more than happy to prove uh
Yeah. Don't go on Lord J Steven Howard.
It's just repeaters.
Yeah. And what did I call her? A
crackhead. I called her an ugly
And I called her an ugly crackhead. And
look in the mirror. I called her an ugly
clap crackhead. Yeah, you might want to
rewatch it again. Okay, whatever. Yeah.
No woman's ever bullied me, you [ __ ]
bongo. I call her an ugly crackhead.
Someone that hates crack. You might want
to listen to it again. Beautiful. You
might want to listen to it again.
No, you're not bad. Oh, you're bad, man.
Yeah, you stay banned, bro. It's just
the same repeating people. But then they
wonder why the community is dead.
Steven, but then they wonder why the
community is dead. They literally will
post asking why the community is dead.
Because they keep repeating themselves
every day and boring people off of
YouTube. That's why the community is
dead. It's because it's nothing but
repeating. Repeating by the same fat
ugly people that's been doing it for
eight years. That's why it's dead.
That's why it is dead. But because of
them. They killed the community, bro.
Okay, whatever. Yeah. Okay, bro. Was
that woman laughing at me at the park?
Was that woman laughing at me at the
park, you little [ __ ] bongo?
Yeah. Was that woman laughing at me at
the park when I made her [ __ ] herself
and run away?
Yeah. Laughed at a woman you own on a
train in a pub. In the pub. She called
the security of me. You make up excuses
every time, dude. It must be part of your autism.
Mate, I made her run away. I made the
[ __ ] [ __ ] herself and run away. Yeah.
Oh, one second. Hey, I wanted to talk to
you. Sorry, I unblocked you, by the way.
None of this [ __ ] Um, so what I
wanted to say to you is why did you say
Chev is attractive to fit in? It doesn't
make you look good. That's one of the
reasons I stopped meeting you, bro.
because I can't be with someone that's a
copycat that feels the need to copy
that copies the crowd. You know, I don't
like copycats. I know we've all been
guilty of being a copycat, you know.
Well, that woman bully me when I made
her [ __ ] herself and run out the park.
Gun Chan, [ __ ] off, bro. I mean, why why
do you do this [ __ ] bro?
Do you remember Do you remember when you
was a college student? Uh you were
studying landscaping, wasn't it?
Yeah. You was you was
landscape. Yeah. Landscaping.
You remember you was doing landscape? Yeah.
You remember you was you was you were
studying landscaping and then you
stopped going in because these two kids
were picking on you.
And he was like, "I like Cole. I'm not
gay. You little copycat. No mind of your own.
No mind of your own. Absolutely no mind
of your own. Yet you used to hate people
that used to copy each other.
You used to hate people that used to
that that that used to copy each other.
And then you're saying attractive."
You never really answered why you done
that. Why? Why? Why you copy the crowd?
Doesn't make you look good. It doesn't
make you look clever. It doesn't make
you look good. It doesn't make you look clever.
Yeah, but you had to you had to uh back
out because of the bullying.
Do you remember?
You have to back out because the
bullying, mate. Do you remember? Do you
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, [laughter]
no. You said that if you don't like her,
you're gay. No. You said that you don't
like her, you're gay. Copycat,
you're lucky, right? We didn't we didn't
make you dress up as like a fancy dress.
Yeah. And then like come and then we be
like copycat. You wanted to fit in with the crowd. Yeah.
I remember you telling me a lot about your dad. Yeah.
No, you literally said if you don't find
her attractive, you're gay. That's No,
you literally did say that. No, you
Uh yes you did. Yes you [ __ ] well
did. Anyways I remember a lot about your
dad. He was born on the 1st of September
day before before my mom's different
year. And um yeah he used to work abroad
a lot. He used to work abroad a lot. And
um yeah and you told me a lot about him.
His name was Mick. Diehard West Ham fan.
He he he was a he was a diehard West Ham
fan. I mean I mean the second time I met
you, you was wearing a West Ham t-shirt.
Yeah, Mick was a diehard West Ham fan.
He got into a uh couple of rules back in
the day over football. Isn't that right?
No, he was a he was a he was a diehard
West Ham fan. that
die hard West Ham fan. I You was
actually wearing a West Ham top when I
met you. It's the second time I met you,
I think. Yeah. You said that you like
West Ham. I said, "I'm I'm not really into football."
No. No. It was a West Ham t-shirt.
I know a lot about you, Dad. He's got a
very dark past. A very very dark past.
Quite quite scary in a lot of ways.
He's got a dark dark past.
Yeah. Well, that never happened. So
again, you're twisting things again.
Piss myself. Yeah. You keep telling yourself that. So yeah.
And your dad? Um, I know your stepdad as
well, Philip Campbell from Leeds. Nasty bastard.
Also, also known as David Campbell.
Yep. From Leeds. Your stepdad was from
He used two names.
Yep. I know all about you, mate.
I know all about you.
All about you, mate. Oh, all about you.
Oh, all about you, mate. Oh, all about
you. All All about you, mate. All about
you. All All about you.
Yeah. Well, guess what, Gona?
Well, here's here's here's what I'm
going to say back to you. How many years
did that happen after being on YouTube?
I mean, how many years does that happen
after being on YouTube? Years. That
prime thing is still very new compared
to this community. So, you just make up
stuff. You people don't meet anyone
because you ain't got balls. It's not
because of Prime. It's not because of
Law J. It's cuz you ain't got balls.
You're just keyboard warriors. You're literally
You've had strangers make fun of Again,
you're not going to get a reaction. You're boring.
We That's not what happened. That's why
I told Grezy, "Leave the video up
again." That's not what happened, Gona.
All of this typing. You could have been
in London by now, bro. All of this
typing on YouTube. You could have
actually been in London by now. You
literally could have been in London.
We've been live 4 hours, bro. But you
don't think you're a keyboard warrior.
But you don't think you're a keyboard
warrior. You've been typing away for
hours and you're still not here. I mean,
you must have been free today, Monday.
Why the [ __ ] are you not in London?
You're typing away for hours. Soon have
you been here by now?
Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah, you're
boring. That's not what happened.
That's not what happened. That's not
what happened. Anyways, stop deflecting
and come to London. Stop being a
keyboard warrior. Come to London. You've
been typing for hours all day. You could
have easily come to London, [ __ ] idiot. Nah, mate.
Do you know what though? Hopefully next
year, Virgin Boy, you might actually get
laid. I think you might get laid next year.
What? 31 and still a virgin. Nah, can't be right.
Do you remember the sex stories you made
up with Aisha that you [ __ ] her in a
park bench? You didn't [ __ ] anyone in a
on a park bench, you silly goo. Shut up.
No, you didn't. And you tried to say
that you had [ __ ] on your dick. Shut up.
You're an absolute virgin.
Them little silly stories that you made
up. There's nothing wrong with being a
virgin. Just admit it. People [ __ ]
respect you more if you just admit that
you've never had it.
You haven't lost your Valentine's card.
Valentine's card. When are you going to
lose your Valentine's card?
When are you going to lose your
Valentine's card, mate?
It's your birthday soon. Couple months.
You You're still going to be a virgin.
You're not going to die a virgin, are
you? You don't want to die one. And I
knew you was a virgin as well because
you kept dismissing the escort stories
like anyone would [ __ ] lie to some
ratfaced [ __ ] ugly virgin that
they've had to pay for [ __ ] sex. Like
someone has to lie to some [ __ ] skin
[ __ ] ratfaced looking virgin when
they paid for [ __ ] sex. You kept
dismissing the stories. Who the [ __ ]
dismisses escort stories? All cuz you're
a virgin. You don't want to feel left
out, virgin boy. [ __ ] virgin.
[ __ ] virgin. You [ __ ] virgin, mate.
What What's your What's your What's your legal name?
Nods. [ __ ] Nods. That's your name,
mate. Dods, mate. Duds, mate. Nods.
You do realize you avoided your uh you
voided a court order, by the way.
You've alreadyed a court order.
That's why they told you to [ __ ] off.
Look, I can grow a beard, but you can't.
Look, I can actually grow a beard, mate.
But you've actually you've actually
[ __ ] the order up now, mate, because
you've been at me lately, haven't you? You know,
we all we always used to like a your
name Sunday. We always used to call it
the sword Sunday,
do you know?
Yeah. Guna, why don't you come in and
show your face?
Why don't you come in and show us your face?
Good. Why don't you show us your
handsome face? Everyone wants to see it.
Let's see your face.
Talking about other men's looks, but
can't show your face. Seems a bit
ridiculous, doesn't it? [ __ ] off, you Welsh bong.
Yeah. Okay. Well, why don't you show us
your face then?
>> All the gyms. Nah, we're not fat like you people. >> No,
>> we're not fat ugly people like you.
Nah, bro. We're not fat ugly people like
you. That's why none of you people can
come on camera. Did anyone find out who
Bon was? I don't think so.
Did anyone find out his name or anything?
>> You people talk about people with looks
cuz you're ugly yourselves. Another
thing that killed the community, but
then you wonder why it's dead. [ __ ] idiots.
[ __ ] absolute idiots.
Absolute [ __ ] idiots. Hello.
I need to go to the barbers, but I can't be bothered.
Yeah, good for you, bro. You've got a
million chins and a fat belly. No one
cares about you fat, ugly people that self project.
Yeah, Kevin, do you want to come in and
show your face? Do you want to come in
and show your face?
The nose. Oh, it's so boring now. Oh,
the nose thing is so boring. Stop
repeating. Come up with something
original. Well, listen. Listen. I'm
going to I'm going to make it easy for
you. There you go.
Think of something original. My nose is not big.
You need to think of something original.
Uh Kevin, it's boring. Boring. Now,
think of something unique, something
original. Stop repeating.
None of you people can show your face.
So anyways, when are you going to lose it?
But guess what, Guda? You can't show
your face. You people can't show your
faces cuz you're ugly. You're ugly
bastards. You talk about men's looks
that are better looking than you because
you're ugly yourselves. You're writing,
but you're not showing your face.
Kevin Murphy, bro, come in and show your
face. You scouse [ __ ] You [ __ ]
beatle scouse liver puddling little
[ __ ] boy who let me come to his city
and he done nothing about it cuz he's a
good boy. You let me You let this travel
250 miles but you done nothing about it
because the scouts are [ __ ] You're a
[ __ ] click. You're a [ __ ] click.
You're a [ __ ] click. No, no, no, no,
no. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. Only people
that are not ugly can show their faces.
No, no. The only people that don't show
their faces or ugly people.
Ugly people with something to hide. Only
ugly people. Because, bro, you know,
savvy guy doesn't know what I look like.
Sab boy. Sab boy. If they said show your
face, I would say, "Yeah, you don't show
your faces cuz you're ugly. That's why
you don't show your faces. It's nothing
else cuz you're ugly. No, no, no, no.
But if they if they turn around and said
show your face, I would show my face.
But you don't show your faces cuz you're
ugly. And then you try and say, "Oh,
we're smart and we've got an IQ." Now
you say, Okay. Okay, bro. Okay, cool.
Cool. Cool. Right. You're saying that
people are spastics, bro. Listen, listen
to me. You're saying that people are
spastics, right? Hear me out. Yeah. How
long have you been coming on here repeating yourselves
over and over and over again? One
second. And you say that people don't
that don't show themselves or spastics.
So why do you come on here continuously
repeating yourselves from the time you
wake up to the time that you go to bed
if you're not [ __ ] and you're smart?
Answer me that question. You don't show
your face cuz you're smart. Okay, you're
smart people. You've got an IQ. Okay,
whatever. So why do you continuously
come on here and repeat yourselves from
the time you wake up to the time you go to bed?
I'm I'm all ears, bro. [ __ ] anyone else.
Like, would have you thought of
different comebacks by now? You're
killing the community. You're killing
the bloody community. I mean, most
people on here repeat themselves every
day. I can assure you they're anything
but smart. You don't show your faces on
here. It's cuz quite simply you're ugly.
That's that. Like that's that's why you
That's why you don't show your faces cuz
you're ugly. It's not cuz you're smart.
If you were smart, you wouldn't repeat
yourselves every day. Simple.
Yeah, whatever you say, Kevin. And guess
what? I've had more [ __ ] than you will
ever have. And And I've had more [ __ ]
than you will ever have.
I don't give a [ __ ] if anyone hates me.
They won't do anything. Yeah, everyone
can hate me all they want, but they
won't do anything. So why do I give a [ __ ]
Kevin, I've had more [ __ ] than you. You
[ __ ] scouse ugly [ __ ] Why don't you
come in and show your face,
bro? You keep calling me ugly. is not
going to change the fact I'm better
looking than you. Don't regret that [ __ ]
on your deathbed,
bro. I'm better looking than you. You
can't even show your ugly scouse face,
you scouse [ __ ] You little [ __ ]
reject, you little mong. You're the
[ __ ] [ __ ] Come Liverpool. Come
Liverpool. I go to Liverpool. You're
nowhere to be seen. LT goes to
Liverpool. You pretend you're in Wales.
Give it up now, kid. Give it up now.
Yeah, I don't want to be loved by you
[ __ ] ugly bongos. [ __ ] off. [ __ ] hell. New people.
I've done this [ __ ] you know, bro. Like
when I was 22, 23, traveled all over the
country. Kevin Murphy can't even come to
London cuz he's full of excuses. Goona
can't come to London because he's full
of excuses. Yeah, I done this at 22, 23,
24, went all over the country and you
got people that are older and they won't
even they won't even come to London.
It's embarrassing, mate. It's [ __ ]
embarrassing, kid. Absolutely embarrassing.
Absolutely [ __ ] embarrassing.
[ __ ] bad, bro. Really bad. Really,
really, really bad.
You're this big bad man, Kevin, but you
can't even come to London. It don't make
sense. Really does not make any sense.
The amount of money we've wasted on you, the bomb.
You're just [ __ ] idiots.
Where's Virgin boy? Anyways, you just
ruined the whole thing.
But I I also, you know, I've got a lot
of evidence on you, Virgin Boy. I've got
a little pack, my little evidence pack.
It's 161 pages long.
It's 161 pages long, lad.
Look how many times I've run away. Okay.
Excuses, excuses, excuses.
Uh, we're bored of these excuses now.
We're bored of these excuses.
Bored of these excuses now. It's boring
now. Very, very boring. Anyways, Virgin
Boy, like that would stop anyone who was
actually about it. Like that would stop
anyone. Yeah, but Kevin, this is all
recent stuff, Kevin. This is all recent
bro. This is all recent stuff.
Uh, you went to Southeast Asia, South America.
Yeah, that's nothing, bro. Them places
that you list is nothing.
That them places that you list is nothing.
Yeah, but them places that you list is nothing.
See, you're so focused on other people.
This is what I mean. You're absolute
nerds on here. You bounce off other
people's lives cuz you ain't got a life
of your own. You're absolute nerds. When
do you know what? Yeah. Why not make
this a a thing for you in 2026? Get off
of YouTube and get a life. Oh, can you
do you reckon you could do that 2026? Do
you reckon you can get off of YouTube
and get a life?
You reckon you can get off of YouTube
and get a life in 2026?
No. I've got evidence on you, mate. I
got evidence on you. I got evidence on
you. It's not a separate case cuz I I've
done it in retalia. I've done it in retaliation.
I've done it in retaliation, mate.
You're a nasty little [ __ ] You are
[ __ ] nasty little [ __ ] There's
people out there getting mugged, getting
stabbed, and then you got some rat
[ __ ] face with no money [ __ ]
calling you up, crying over YouTube.
You're actually crying over YouTube, you
[ __ ] [ __ ] virgin.
crying over YouTube. You're you're an
absolute loser. You are you are actually
you're a big big loser. A big big big
loser. Why do you remember your friend
Christian when you sent me a picture of
[ __ ] you and Christian saying that we
think you're gay? Two absolute virgins.
I still remember that picture of the two virgins.
You can laugh at me. Why you got to be
laughing at me? The court date's not even happening.
You little [ __ ] fat ugly bongos.
Anyways, I'm doing a videos on you
later. We have a screen recording.
We have a screen recording of you little
fat ugly nerds.
You [ __ ] fat ugly little nerds.
Little nerdy. That's why I'm calling you
fat ugly disabled little nerdicans.
Uh, sorry. I can't Do you know what? I
can't be friends with virgins,
mate. I'll I'll say your name. Come and
meet me right now. I'll say I I'll say
your name. I'll say your name. Eat the
[ __ ] virgin, can't you? Come on. Come
on, mate. I'm going to jail. Yeah, you
wish, mate. You You wish. I'm I'm going
to jail in three and a half years. Yeah.
Okay. You wish.
[ __ ] fat, ugly [ __ ]
Yeah. Well, anyways, I'm banning some of
these people now.
Where is he? Yeah, there he is.
So, um, yeah. When are you going to get
yourself a little job,
bro? Triple H, the court is, you know,
my friend. Yeah. He's in court this
month. He's in court this month from
last month, bro. No court takes three
and a half years.
No court takes three and a half years,
bro. Read between the lines. I don't
know how many people, you know, who's
been nicked and gone, but people don't
go caught in three and a half years.
They've done that for a [ __ ] reason, bro. Obviously,
you got your ass a good whoop in that
day, didn't you? With the posters and
just admit it. Oh, one second.
You got your You got your ass a good
woofing by by this base.
I stopped you going to some events for a little while.
I hand posted them.
Do you remember?
Do you remember when I when I hand posted them?
Oh, hey. I done that. I warned you to
leave me alone. You wouldn't do it.
Uh, yes I did, mate. Yes, I did. I
stopped you going to uh the late stand one
because everybody knows about your
antics. Yes, I did. You stopped coming
on YouTube for two weeks. I think I did,
mate. That was caused by me. That was caused.
Oh, that was caused by me, mate.
Yes, I did. Yes, I did. I stopped to go
to the late stone one.
You stopped going to your late stone one.
That was me done that.
I know I need a haircut and stuff, but
I'm just letting it grow cuz why not?
Yeah, look how long Monty's case. Yeah,
it wasn't three and a half years.
Yes, it wasn't three and a half years.
This has been scheduled for three and a
half years. His wasn't scheduled. They
were finding evidence on him. That's how
this is how I know you people are absolute mongos.
stamped letters. No one cares about
letters, bro. You can send as many
letters as you want. I mean, Monty, it
wasn't three and a half years, firstly.
And secondly, uh, no [ __ ] No, they
got in touch with him telling him after
that time. They told me three and a half
years. Yes. I'm not I'm not I'm not
going to prison, mate. Trust me. You
wish, mate. You fat, ugly people wish I
was going in prison.
You wish I was going prison. That never
happened, bro. Never happened.
Yeah. I mean, Mont Monty's going I mean,
you're not going to prison for calling
someone. I mean, I can still leave the
country. I can leave the country
whenever I want. I don't give a [ __ ]
The only thing they said don't do is
mention your [ __ ] virgin name.
Uh, a lot of things get to a lot of
things goes to Crown Court now. Mate,
you're not scaring me. You're just an
idiot. It just goes to show that you
don't know how the system works. You're
not scaring me. Like, I know exactly
what's going to happen. And yes, uh,
ground court cases get dropped all the
time, [ __ ] Yes, they do. Yes, they
do. You know, or they give people fines.
Yes, they do.
You know, you know, no, you can't. And
then you have
uh yes I can. I can leave the country
whenever I want to. Nothing stops me
leaving the country. Yes I can. Uh
I'll give you whatever the [ __ ] I want.
And yes they [ __ ] do. I've been
nicked more times than I've had hot
dinners. So uh uh yes the [ __ ] I do. Uh
yes uh the [ __ ] they do. And I will give
you any example that I want. Bye-bye now. go. So,
so yeah, mate, we're not even going to
give you any
sto of chance to keep running to the
police because this is your whole life.
You're a loser. You're an absolute skin
little loser. We're not even going to
give you the chance to get the police involved.
We're not even going to give you the
chance. We're not going to get have a
loser like you even get given a chance.
You know, the police told you to [ __ ]
off like two weeks ago, didn't they? Virgin,
let me tell you something, right? I'll
tell you how this whole thing has
started. Triple H. Yeah. The police.
Okay. Okay. Triple H. Do you know the
whole reason this has happened? It's cuz
he kept crying to the police, hounding
them. Crying. That's how obsessed he is
with me. crying, crying, crying cuz he's
a loser and he got owned on YouTube. The
police haven't seen all of the [ __ ] that
he has done. So when it all goes to
court, all of the stuff that he's done,
he's going to be [ __ ] He is going to
be [ __ ] Believe you me, or my dead
dad, when they see what he has been
doing, I've got a whole fold of it.
Trust me, bro. Trust me. He knows he's [ __ ]
You went to the police playing the
victim, cried to them a million times,
and I never reported you. That's the
only reason because you're so much of a
loser that you got your ass a good
whooping on YouTube and there's and
there's nothing there's nothing to be
ashamed of. You got your ass whooped on
YouTube. You couldn't handle the Peter Bear.
That's fine. But I could never be so
much of a loser that I had to go to the
police over YouTube. That's what a loser
would do because they got owned so
badly. And also this whole police thing
is also an obsession because you're
doing anything to try to get people
[ __ ] with the police. It also shows
that you're obsessed also.
It also shows that you're very very obsessed
cuz it takes time to know report things
to the police, get appointments. So the
fact that you're doing all of this, it
shows that you're obsessed.
It's another form of obsession to be
fair. It's another form of obsession.
If you didn't know. Yeah.
Yeah. You wish. Put me in the cell.
Yeah, you wish.
Yeah, you wish. Bro, stop calling
yourself ugly. I'm not the one that's
had to date disabled women. I'm not the
one that had to go with disabled girls.
I'm not the one that had to date
disabled girls. Stop calling yourself
ugly, you rat looking bastard.
Stop calling me ugly, you rat looking
bastard. Go look in the mirror and see
why you're with the disabled girl. And
you're still stalking Morgan. And you're
still stalking Izzy. You are ugly. Stop
looking in the mirror, ugly boy. I'm not
the one that has to date disabled ugly
boy that looks like a rat. Mr. Ratfaced
ugly. That's you. You're ugly with the
ugly rat face. The skin rat face. And
stop going on about this 13 grand
daddy's life savings that you showed a
year many years ago. You're skint
[ __ ] skin flin.
It's not nice to call yourself ugly.
It's not life. It's not nice to to call
your rat self ugly. We know you're ugly.
That's why you pray on the vulnerable,
you little incel. That's why you can
only get disabled girls, you little
incel. You little virgin rat face incel.
But that kills, is it? I've never in my
life had to resort to disabled. But then
again, I'm not ugly like him. I'm not an
ugly bastard like him. So I've never had
to resort to people that obviously had
had these uh you know, needs and stuff.
So I mean, we're all different. I guess
you stalk all of my sloppy seconds cuz
you're too ugly to get anything normal
yourself. You ugly self, projector. One second.
There we go.
One second. I need to add
I think your business fancies me. By the
way, Ricky says it as well.
I think when well I was going to say
have sex but you don't have sex you're
still a virgin. Um I reckon when you're
hugging and that she she's saying my
name out loud you know [ __ ] bongos.
[ __ ] disabled bongos on here. How you
can call me ugly with that [ __ ]
stinky ugly rat face is beyond me. It's classic projection.
You [ __ ] ugly rat looking [ __ ] with a
disabled gate. Can't get anything
normal. And you're jealous that I can.
That's why you're jealous of USA, is he?
Cuz you're still No, you're not blocked.
A virgin, you skinned virgin.
No, you're not blocked. Virgin boy,
ratfaced, ugly [ __ ] disabled
girlfriend. You're not [ __ ] blocked.
I've been talking to your virgin skin
ass for [ __ ] the past. Got those
allog you [ __ ] skin [ __ ] Yeah.
You're calling me ugly, but you're miss
as fancy as me. She wants a bit of Peter
Belly. She doesn't want your little
erectile dysfunction dick that can't go up.
If your dick don't work, you don't want
some ugly bastard and a little broken
dick that can't satisfy her. It's a broken relationship.
[ __ ] little mongos on here. Anyways,
I'm doing a [ __ ] video later on these [ __ ] bro. Yeah. Five.
I just got a toilet, bro.
No, you're not blocked. You [ __ ] virgin.
You skin virgin.
Virgin boy. You got unblocked for a [ __ ] reason.
Don't know why he keeps calling me ugly
when he resembles a rat. [ __ ] virgins.
Fat ugly virgins.
Same atmosphere with this community, bro.
Why don't you want to join me? These little mongos.
These little [ __ ] spasticated little
fat weirdos. Little mongos.
Ain't got a life.
I am blocked you. Where the [ __ ] are
you, Mr. Ugly virgin?
They are going through.
We can see them.
You [ __ ] skinned virgin ratfaced
[ __ ] We can see them.
Oh, we can see everyone can see your
comments. Yes, we can see him.
You [ __ ] ugly virgin. You skin
bastard. Showing dad his life savings.
You [ __ ] virgin.
You [ __ ] ugly skin rat [ __ ] who lives
in a bed.
Never [ __ ] Britney. Britney rejected
him. Still a virgin. [clears throat]
Britney never wanted his ugly ass.
Didn't want him. Didn't want to know [clears throat]
All right, Triple. Get in. Hello.
>> So, what's going on with this car, lad?
>> I'm not talking about it, bro. I've
already I've already been over it.
>> So, is he just lying in that draw then?
>> Yeah, basically.
>> [ __ ] mad, man.
>> If he Can you Can you get him laid, please? Bro,
>> he's got a girlfriend.
>> Yeah. And he and he doesn't [ __ ] her.
And that's the thing. He's got And he
doesn't even have sex with her. That's
what I don't understand. You're on
YouTube every single day, bro. At me,
you where where's where would you have
the time to have sex?
>> You know, it's crazy, mate.
>> Triple H, you reckon you could get him
laid if he comes up to Newcastle?
>> Yeah, lad. I try.
>> There you go, Trip H. Trip H will be
your big man. You can finally pop your
cherry and no longer be a virgin. There
you go. Sorted.
>> He can even come in the launch will come
in the box. Yeah, he he he needs to
[ __ ] get lagged.
>> I need to ask him a few questions about
this [ __ ] car thing.
>> Would you would you would you go would
you go would you go with his misses?
>> I wouldn't know.
>> Why? She's not your cuppper.
>> No, she's not my cup of tea. But she might [laughter]
>> Izzy's the one for you, is it?
No, that um what you call that Goon Chan
said that you um used to write poems for the Aziz. >> N
you know that Goon Chan is a sad old man.
>> N don't mind me. I think he's all right, me lad.
>> But he Do you reckon he would beat me in
the fight? Nah,
>> most probably. Yeah. Yeah, I think he would.
>> But he's an he's an old man, bro.
>> I don't know why he looks like me, lad.
No, but I'm saying Eldridge up. I put
the link up.
>> Tim Eldridge doesn't join now, does he?
>> No, I don't know why. They all go
>> should let Sean up, man. I need to ask
him a few questions to be
>> No, he's a police informant. Triple H.
She's a police boy.
>> He can go live and you can join. Yeah.
Why don't you Why don't you do that?
>> No, don't go on.
>> He's obsessed with me in it.
Someone's saying let non like let Sean
in. So [ __ ] join.
>> All right.
>> No one's trying to join. That's the link
is up, but no one joins.
>> Yeah, they try to
>> You said that they want people dead on
here, isn't it?
>> Of course they do. Yeah. [laughter]
>> No, really.
>> If the police properly looked into this
YouTube, they'd [ __ ] get a shock like
cuz it's mad on here. Especially this
Especially this community. It's [ __ ]
full of weirdos, man. You know, [laughter] >> it
>> like that crazy. I mean, not crazy. Um,
>> what do you call that phraser one said?
It's a mental health community.
>> Yeah, that that Mark's gone off the
rails, isn't it?
>> Mark Samson.
>> No, Mark.
>> Oh, Seaside. Yeah, they want him dead. >> Yeah.
>> Why would they want someone like him
dead though? I don't get it.
I see an onscella. >> No,
>> [ __ ] mong. They're [ __ ] just
losers on here, is it?
>> Yeah, there some sad folk on here, fella.
>> Who do you think is the saddest? That
Clint, is it?
Uh, I think they all tied with the same
brush. Really, Pete? [laughter] >> Really?
>> Right. You don't know what that means, do you?
>> Yeah. Obviously, like they all like
they're all the same basically. Same
level. Yeah. Obviously, I know what that means.
>> Where's Steven Wood?
>> You're not talking to Monty? Uh, not sure. >> Ah,
>> what did you eat today?
Uh, [clears throat] what have you had
today? I had [ __ ] a mint and dumpster
today. I lad
>> some what?
>> I had mint and dumpster.
>> Oh, lovely.
>> And look.
>> Yeah, I have three boiled eggs, bro. I'm
on a diet like Grezy.
>> Oh, yeah. Grey's dieting lad. >> Yeah.
Oh, you commented before as well. You
said I met my mama in it. You commented
it in it.
>> No, I've not been under no troll
accounts like me. No, but you know you
commented before saying that I met my
mama on your wheel account, didn't it?
That was funny, isn't it?
>> [ __ ] knows, man.
>> They say that on here, is it? I don't know why. >> I
They're not a big laz.
>> Yeah, [snorts] free. Yeah, free boiled
eggs for dinner.
>> Big L, you know.
>> Yeah, they're sad bastards on here.
>> Huh? Sorry,
>> I said they need to get a job and and
get some money in it. These people,
>> they need they do they need to sort
theelves out like they're trying to run
run that Eldidge off and they but they
won't go without a fight.
>> Yeah, they are. They are. Yeah.
>> Do you remember when they done like an
account of your like sheets and that lad? Yeah.
>> Do you remember it?
>> Yeah. I think it was a Harry
>> [clears throat]
>> There was a few of them I reckon. Isn't it?
>> Yeah, there's a few sad people on here, lad. [laughter]
>> Mike, is it?
>> I don't mind Mike me. I think he's all
right. B, you know. [snorts]
>> Yeah, Bobby used to talk about your
states in it.
>> I used to like that bomb, you know.
This is a 40y old man.
>> Ah, he was funny though. I thought he he
I thought he used to make the YouTube me
and I used to think he was funny. I know
he was a troll, but he was funny half lad.
>> No, he used to wind me up, bro.
>> And you remember when he winded LT up
and LT on a video, was it? Yeah.
>> Yeah, I can remember that.
>> You remember it? He said it's all punt
from Lancaster. Yeah.
>> All right. And then he he docked himself
with his added ass flux, didn't he? >> Yeah.
>> And just live above a um [ __ ] pizza
shop or something. Road man thing. Get
in there, lad. [laughter]
>> Yeah. You skin in it.
>> Hi. Yeah.
>> Why do you know when I used I used to
ask Monty Trip H. I used to say, "Why do
these people say that we're skinn?" And
he says, "Cuz they're skin." Remember? [laughter] >> Yeah.
>> It's true though, is it?
>> They've done a lot of that Monty man as
well, haven't they?
>> Yeah. He could be going prison soon, is it?
>> Crazy lad. I don't want to go to prison.
>> He won't go prison for what he done. I don't think
>> he could do. He could do it.
>> Probably do [ __ ] community service.
there. PG my lead.
>> You're right there. You little [ __ ]
Wait, when you get docked, bro. I'm
coming on your door, by the way. You [ __ ]
>> already give you my address, you [ __ ]
>> bro. I will come on your door, bro. I
will come to Belfast,
>> bro. Cuz you don't live in Belfast.
>> Yeah, you don't live in Belfast.
>> You don't live in Belfast
from a woman.
>> You don't live in Belfast.
>> You don't live in Belfast. You don't
live in Put your real voice on, bro. Come on.
better than this.
>> You don't live in Belfast. You say that
you live in
>> Shut the [ __ ] up.
>> Shut the [ __ ] up, you sabastard.
>> About women not wanting you. Do you want to
>> Women don't want you. Hey, bro. We've
all seen you with Autumn. You little
virgin. You little virgin. We all saw
you talking to Autumn. You little virgin
trying to say what did you say? I can
confirm it's a woman. Bro, you're a fat
ugly little virgin. At least I've had women.
>> At least I've had women unlike you. You fat virgin.
>> Still a virgin boy. [ __ ] >> bro.
>> I'm a Okay, bro. How can I be a virgin
sex when your mother paid for it?
>> When the uh I mean I proved I' had sex.
I proved I've had sex. Get in there, Grezy.
>> I proved I've had sex many times. Bro,
we all know that you're the virgin. We
know that you're the virgin. We know
that you're the virgin. And defending
women is not going to make you lose your
beard. We've seen you, bro. We've seen
you with trip. We've seen you with um
>> pissed yourself on the train.
>> I pissed myself. That's not what
happened. Why are you still a virgin?
Why are you still [laughter] a virgin?
>> Well, I still a virgin.
>> Why did I piss myself? Why are you still
on this case?
>> Prove you pissed yourself. You
>> whenever I find out where you live, I'm
coming on your door, mate. And it's And
it's going to be And trust me, I'm
coming on your door.
>> You don't live in Belfast until you live
in Belfast. You don't live in Belfast to
do you until January. 30. Okay. You
don't live in Belfast, you little bug.
>> I do. I do.
>> You fat ugly bongo. Look at you around
all the women. Nobody wants ugly like
you. You are a bun.
Okay then. Okay. Okay. Okay. Why is a women
>> Why is a M had women and you're still a virgin?
>> You haven't had women on YouTube.
Why is a women
>> Why has a M been with more women than you?
>> Okay. So why is a montage never had to
beg women on YouTube like you
>> have you ever had to beg women because
you are the bug.
>> You are the Put your camera on. Put your
camera on. Show everyone your ugly face.
Show everyone the butler face. Show
everyone the ugly face. So disgusting
face. Show everyone why you're still a
virgin. Come on.
>> Why did you watch your sister in the shower?
>> Come on. Making up [laughter] again.
Making up stuff again.
>> You said that.
>> So why are you begging?
>> Yeah. We're greasy lad. You You said you
watch just this.
>> Why are you begging autumn?
>> What am I begging autumn? You just make stuff.
>> Bro, don't watch some little fat virgin
like you, man.
The reason was going to cash is better.
This is the guy.
>> That's why you're single, mate. You're
single. You're virgin. Single virgin
for seven months.
>> I'm single and you're a single virgin.
>> I'm [clears throat] single.
that's never had sex. I've got the single sex.
>> Where's your girlfriend? Where's your
girlfriend? Voice of reason. Where's your woman?
>> Where's your girlfriend, loser? Fat
losser. Where's your girlfriend?
>> Where's your [ __ ] girlfriend? You fat
loser. Show everyone, bro. Come on. Come
>> Staying in your mom's house.
>> Come on. Show your girlfriend. You fat
loser. Wait. You're calling me single
when you're single yourself. That don't make sense.
>> You're a single virgin. You're an actual
You are an
>> You're an absolute virgin.
>> You're an absolute virgin, mate.
>> You're a virgin.
>> Okay. I'm a virgin.
>> You called me single. Show us your
girlfriend. Okay. Show us your
>> I didn't call you single. Everybody
>> see your girlfriend. Let's see your
girlfriend. Your girlfriend. Let's see
your girlfriend. Let's see your
girlfriend. Let's see your girlfriend.
I'll answer any question you want.
You're years of age and you live with
>> You're in your 30s and you're still a virgin.
>> I'm the same lady.
>> Show us your girlfriend. Show us your
girlfriend. He said I'm single. Let's
see your girlfriend. Come on.
>> Are you not single?
>> Come on. Let's see your girlfriend.
>> Let's see your girlfriend. Let's see
your girlfriend. Come on. You called me
single. Let's see your girlfriend. Let's
see your woman.
>> Let's see your woman. Let's see your
woman. Come on.
>> You started it. Let's do this [ __ ] You
said your girlfriend's upstairs. Can we
hear her? Can we hear her? Can we hear your girlfriend?
>> I'm sure you can.
>> Can we hear your girlfriend? Come on.
Let's hear your girlfriend. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
>> Seen a picture of you and you are [ __ ]
>> absolute. You're an absolute virgin.
>> Virgin ugly virgin call you a mistute
virgin. You're an absolute virgin. You
know what? The way you was Did you know
the way you were sniffing around autumn?
You could you could tell you've never
had a girlfriend. Never had sex. You're
a little little loner. You're a sad
little loner that gets bullied on
YouTube by me and you won't do nothing.
You're a fat ugly single virgin and
you're gonna do nothing.
>> Virgin boy. I've had sex unlike you.
I've had Stop call yourself a ma. Stop
calling yourself a bun.
>> Have you ever had a girlfriend?
>> You need to stop.
>> You need to stop calling yourself a bun.
We know you're fat and ugly. Stop
putting yourself down, ugly boy. And
yes, I've had sex unlike you. And I've
been with women unlike you. had sex.
>> I've had women unlike you. I've had sex
unlike you. You've never had sex and
you've never had a girlfriend.
>> And you you've never had sex and you've
never had a girlfriend cuz you're ugly.
You're ugly and fat.
>> You are ugly and fat and YOU'VE NEVER
HAD A girlfriend and you've never had
sex. Stop self-reflecting.
>> It's not It's not as easy to
self-reflect when you're someone, is it?
>> Have you ever had a girlfriend?
>> Yes. Yes, I have. You've never had a
girlfriend? And you've never had sex?
You've never had a girlfriend.
>> You've never had a girlfriend. And
you've never had sex. Projector, bro.
Okay. Why can't we hear your girlfriend?
Why can't we hear your girlfriend? Come
on. Come on.
>> Come on, bro.
>> Why can't we hear your girlfriend?
>> Um, she doesn't like speaking to mons.
>> Because she don't exist cuz you're a fat
ugly virgin that can't attract nothing
cuz you're ugly.
>> She doesn't. She doesn't exist.
>> I've never had a girlfriend, Ma. Let's go.
>> I have had a girlfriend and I've had
sex. I'd like you, ugly bastard.
>> Yeah, I'd like you. You fat ugly
bastard. You fat ugly bully.
>> Okay, so why have we seen me with women?
But we've never seen you with women.
>> I've never seen you with a woman.
>> Yes, you [ __ ] have. You [ __ ]
virgin. You fat ugly virgin. Yes, you have. You
>> call you a m.
>> Yes, you have. You bully yourself.
There's been plenty of videos of me kissing women.
>> Seen you with Oh, are you talking about
listen? I should be single [laughter]
all I want. I'm not single.
>> Women hate you. Women hate your guts.
You know what I mean? They hate you more
than me, bro.
>> They hate you more than me. You're a
virgin, bro. You're older than me.
You're older than me and you're a
virgin. Look at yourself. Look at
yourself. Virgin younger than your mother.
>> You're older than me and you're a
virgin. Take a look at your life. Take a
look at your life with your mom.
>> Stop calling yourself a ma. It's not
going to change the fact that you're ugly,
>> bro. You keep calling yourself a bummer.
It's not going to change that you're
ugly. It's not going to change the fact
that you're ugly. So, stop putting
yourself down until calling yourself
ugly. You can't even put yourself this weekend.
>> Are you okay? [laughter] Are you say Are
you saying that you're not ugly then? >> Yeah.
>> You're not ugly? >> No.
>> Put your camera on.
>> Put your camera on. Cut that camera on.
Come on. Show that fat ugly face.
Put your camera on.
>> Show that that ugly face. That virgin
face. Put your camera on. Put yours on.
>> Put your camera on. Put your camera on.
Let's do at the same time. Put your camera on. >> Okay.
>> You Irish virgin mother.
>> You single little sexist.
>> Put your camera on. >> Go.
>> Put your camera on, Virgin boy. >> You
[ __ ] detention seeker
said it looks like you read I sent a
video of you being owned. No one owned
me. I said this. She's a [ __ ]
crackhead ugly [ __ ] that needs to look
in the mirror. You s bastard.
All right, bro. This V is a self
projector, bro. A proper self projector.
I knew he couldn't stay off YouTube.
And I' and I've had a girlfriend and
they've never been disabled.
They've never ever been disabled like
yours. I've had a girlfriend, but
they've never been disabled like yours.
Funny enough, all of the women that I've
been with, they've never been disabled.
That's where the jealousy comes into it.
That's why you were stalking USA, you
[ __ ] virgin. Trying to get sexual
information, you [ __ ] virgin. What
could have you even done with that
anyways, though, mate? You have sex.
What? You're going to lose your
Valentine's card. You're going to lose
your V card. I don't think so, mate.
You're not having sex. You're still a
virgin. Just like all of them [ __ ]
stories that you was making up with Aisha.
No one's ever had sex with you. You
silly little virgin. Who you trying to
convince? You're [ __ ] You're just the
same as bloody what's his face. B
[ __ ] B. What a sad bastard, bro.
[ __ ] absolute virgins on here, bro.
Absolute life's losers. I'm coming off
here in the new year, bro. 100%. I'm
coming off here in the new year, laddy. [ __ ] 100%. See,
I already told you why I'm on here, bro.
Recently, no one's told me why they're
on here. No one's told me why they're on
I actually have I have a reason. It's
not even an excuse. I mean, I have a
reason why I'm on here. Can't be
bothered to go out. Don't want to go out
drinking. No horror films. There's not
really anything for me to do other than
to sit in the winter and save [ __ ]
money cuz there's nothing else to do.
Why are these people on YouTube?
Why are these people on YouTube? That's
what I'd love to know. Why these people
on bloody YouTube?
Cuz they ain't got a life. They ain't
got no life.
They haven't got no life, bro. That's
why they ain't got no [ __ ] life.
Even on a hot summer's day, Grezy. Even
on a hot summer's day.
Even on a hot summer's day.
Hot summer's day.
Listen, bro. Bro, listen, bro. People
like you, I'm going to wait until you get doxed.
And then you can say all of these things
when someone's in your door, can't you? Sad bastard.
Who the [ __ ] is Joseph Farah? Yeah,
Bill was a projector
calling people single when he's a single virgin himself.
These fat, ugly people need to get off
YouTube and get a life, bro. Serious.
You know, I'm on and off here. Me,
skinned, ugly people, they ain't got a
life. All this money, all this, all
these looks that sat on YouTube every
single day ain't got a life. [ __ ] off,
mate. Absolutely [ __ ] off.
But Greavves, you don't delete the
video, lad. Don't privatize it. Don't
delete it. Put it up there, bro.
You know, you people can't even take a
day off of YouTube because you ain't got
a life. Don't Don't delete it, bro.
Don't delete it. Like, don't delete it.
Cuz these people always make up [ __ ]
These sad little versions, these low lives.
Yeah, just leave it up there, bro. They
always make it even when they're wrong,
they will still think that they're
right. They will still think that
they're right. So, just leave it up there, bro. Sad bastards go bastards [snorts]
on YouTube every [ __ ] day cuz they
ain't got a life,
you know. This is good content.
Sat on it. sat on sat on YouTube every
day calling people skint when they
[ __ ] skit themselves and the only
money that they show is their [ __ ]
shitty little benefit money.
Sad little nerds. They know they would
love to be me, bro. Younger, better
looking than them. They would love to be
younger and hopeful. Younger, better
looking, and hopeful, but they're just
ugly low lives. They got [ __ ] all skin sad people.
That's what they are. Yeah.
Yeah. And then these [ __ ] comments
round me up, bro.
But it's all right. I already said what
I'm doing anyways. They're dying in Dash
now. So they had their chance. They had
Yeah, I weeded myself. Yeah, they would
say that, bro. They would say that. They
would say that, bro.
They always make up stuff and lie.
They're jealous, fat, ugly little lives.
They would say that.
They would say that, bro. You saw the
stuff from the bouncer. They would
always make excuses. These jealous
little low lives. Let them say what they want.
They're sad, fat, ugly, jealous people.
They ain't got nothing. Let them say
what they want. I'm not asked about it.
Greavves is not asked about these sad people. So,
they're definitely jealous of something,
bro. They're definitely jealous of something.
And they'll sit there and and say that
they're not jealous, but yet these
people are older than you and they're
uglier than you.
They're older and they're uglier. So,
what the [ __ ] bro? Like, I'm probably
the youngest on it, I think, now. Uh
yeah, I'm younger than Kaye. So these
little nerds, these all fat skinned
right? Yeah, that's that
fat ugly skin nerd. Love.
Um I'm younger than you. I'm better
looking than you. I have hope unlike
you. I mean, like I've said a million
times, put your camera on.
I've said a million times, put your
camera on and it will explain a lot.
Then you ignore it and then you
continuously tell me to prove that I've
got money and prove that I've got
receipts. So, I mean, you people are
old, ugly people. There's a lot to be
jealous of. Um, you're old. I mean, if
you weren't jealous, you wouldn't do
this every If you was not jealous of
anyone, you wouldn't be on here doing
this every day. You wouldn't be on
YouTube every day with all the money
you've got, better looking, fam. You
wouldn't be on here doing what you do every day.
You'd be on here occasionally chatting.
So, you are obviously jealous of
something. Even if you don't know it
yourself, you are jealous. You're older
than me. You're uglier than me.
So, again, you're asking questions
again. You're deflecting again.
Nah, not every day. N people that's got
money and people that's got a life
bored. No, no, no.
No way. People that's got money and a
life would not do this. No way. I'm
bored. I'm [ __ ] bored a lot of the
time. I just watch WWE. No, they they're
they're clearly jealous for them to sit
on the internet every day hating the way
they do. They're clearly jealous of
something because people wouldn't
bother. If they wouldn't, they wouldn't
bother. So, no, they're clearly fat,
ugly people that ain't got nothing in
their life. Smokey B, Clint, all these
accounts. So, yeah, I've already
explained to you. Again, you're asking
me the same things as I've already
explained. This is what I mean. They're
disabled on this community and then no
wonder why people leave. Oh, why is the
community dead? Because it's the same
[ __ ] spasticated atmosphere with you
people every day. You know, you live
with your mom, bro. I told you I'm
younger and better looking than you.
You're old and ugly. It doesn't matter
who I live with, bro. Listen, listen,
listen, listen, listen. You people are
old and ugly. Don't worry about who I
live with. You're old, ugly,
anxietyridden [ __ ] For [ __ ] sake, it
doesn't matter who anyone lives with.
Look at your own lives. Old, wrinkly,
and ugly. And that's where the jealousy
comes from. Old, ugly, and depressed. As
much as you sit there and say that
you're not, you're fat, old, ugly,
hateful, jealous people. And it's the
truth. And I'll bet all my life on it.
I'm right about you people on it. You
hate the fact that someone's younger and
better looking than you. So, you want to
bring people down to your level. People
that have a life don't come and they're
doing what they do.
You know, you're fat, old, ugly people.
And you're claiming that you're not
jealous. Bro, you'd be jealous of
anybody. What do you mean that you're not jealous?
You're fat, old, ugly, depressed, low-life people.
You know what I'm saying?
ugly, hateful, nasty, depressed little
loners. Depressed little loners. And I'm
going to And I'm going to And I'm going
to talk about this in my video later
when I screen record this [ __ ] putting
this [ __ ] in his place.
You hate that fact that you're old,
ugly, old and ugly. And that's where
this whole atmosphere comes from with
you people every day. It's the truth,
bro. No, no one everyone knows what it
is with you people now.
You know, you hate the fact that you're
old and ugly.
Ugly disabled virgins. Most of you,
you ain't got a life.
Just like you, Walter, you ain't got a
life. You fat ugly [ __ ]
Fat ugly [ __ ]
Fat ugly [ __ ] Yeah. And there's clips
of you keep talking about people being
skinned every day when you skint
yourselves, which is another thing I'm
going to talk about later. How you
people talk about people being skinn
yourselves. So you must be looking at
yourselves every day cuz there's no way
people with all this money would be on
here every day
from the time they wake up to the time
they go to bed. There's no way they're
living their best life. Don't let them
try and tell you anything. They're sad,
ugly, lonely people.
Uh, you ain't got a life, mate. You
ain't got a life. People that are on
here don't have a life. People that come
on here don't have a life, mate.
So, yeah. Old ugly people. I mean, if
you put your camera on, I would show you
what you're jealous of, but you won't
put your camera on. So, until you put
your camera on,
you'll hate the fact that people are
younger than you and better looking than
you. And that's where the jealousy comes
into it. I'm convinced now. I am
actually convinced. I'm actually
I'm not your [ __ ] mate, man. And if I
ever see you, I'll smash you in your
[ __ ] face, love. Yeah.
By the way, I'm going to be making this
woman pay for my food soon, um, Autumn,
and I'm going to make you watch. And you
know what? You might think it's me being
a [ __ ] but you know what? These people got chances, you know.
Yeah. Yeah. again making up stuff again.
LJ's bum boy and I'm going to make you
watch him. I'm going to make you watch.
He wonders why he doesn't get women. Uh
again, dismissing people struggles.
Everyone's seen the approaches.
Everyone's seen the stuff. Your
dismissing struggles is not going to
bait me. Nice try. Nice try. We've all
seen the messages. We've all seen what
they've done. I'm going to make her I'm
going to run up a£500 bill and [ __ ] him
over properly and I'm going to show the
whole of YouTube. And you know why,
Autumn? Because there's nothing you can
do. You can't call the police. You're
going to have to watch it. So, I'm going
to make sure I [ __ ] him over in the
intro. All of these little [ __ ] that
are not going to do anything to me. I'm
going to [ __ ] one over and I'm going to
make you watch. I'm going to make you watch, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to make you watch.
And you know what? You can uh Nice try.
We've all seen me stand up to a man. Get
your [ __ ] autism ass out of here. Get
your [ __ ] all to the bath out of
here. No, it's not going to be an
Indian. It's going to be a steakhouse.
I'm going to run up the bill. And you
know what, Autumn? You can blame all of
these people today for not meeting me.
And you know what, Autumn? You can blame
all of these people today that not that
didn't meet me. I I've been calling
these people out all day, all day and
all night to meet me today and they
won't have it. So, okay, fine.
I'll [ __ ] someone over financially then.
So, that's fine. So, you can blame these
people today. why this woman's going to
be getting [ __ ] over. Yeah. I told
them if you don't meet me Yeah. I'm
going to do a lovely video and make them
all mad cuz you know how obsessed they
are. They're all mad. They're going to
get all mad, but they can't get the
police involved and they can't meet you. So, yeah.
Yeah. So, it's up to you like Yeah. Basically.
You women need to stop being entitled. Autumn.
Yeah, you need to stop being entitled,
bro, cuz you're [ __ ] with the wrong
person. You could ask USA is you could
ask a load of these women, bro.
Wonder why you can't get a woman. What
about all of the approaching videos?
What about all of the messages? Completely dismissed.
Nah, none of these women are good. I'm
not I'm I'm going to I'm going to leave
them with a big bill. Yeah.
Nah, no, no, no, no. I don't give a [ __ ]
if she's nice or she's whole, but I'm
going to [ __ ] her over. I'm going to
[ __ ] them over, bro. Watch.
Oh, you're not going to get a takeaway,
are you, Grezy? It's because I I stink a
piss, do I? Really? Okay, whatever.
Anyways, I'm going to be [ __ ] this
woman over and I want you to watch I
want you to watch it.
Yeah, I'm going I'm going to make you
watch you little [ __ ] little [ __ ]
Yeah, you need telling about yourself.
You need to be owned again, bro. Yeah.
See, the thing is all you're all big
until you meet your match. I've noticed
that with you women. You're all big. Yeah.
Yeah. Well, nicked for what? Not not
paying for a bill. Really?
What? By not paying for a bill, I'm
going to get nicked. Really? I don't
think so. Do you seem to think that you
can get nicked for everything and anything?
I'll be affecting them, bro. [ __ ]
dirty [ __ ] Any woman that I can [ __ ]
over, I'll [ __ ] over
[ __ ] scumbags. Give them a bit back
of what they've gave you over the years.
They're all the same. So, once you've
met one, you've met them all. So, yeah.
And you can blame yourselves for this. Uh,
sados. They are sados. They are sados.
They are sados. They are sados, lad.
Yeah, I'll just walk off. Yeah, I'll
just walk off in front of them. I'll
just walk off in front of them. I was
supposed to last time, but they they
weren't they were meat, so I had to get
them on a [ __ ] wild goose chase. You
[ __ ] women with the same attitude need
to be taught a lesson, bro. You need to
be taught a lesson. Bye-bye, Terry.
See you later.
Oh, I was just arguing with some women.
I don't know if you saw it, but yeah. Of
course I'm of course I'm right about
these people. They're fat, ugly little
low lives. I'm doing a video later on screen recording.
Of course I'm right about them. They're low lives.
Yeah, basically. Yeah, it's on Greavves channel.
Oh, really? Thanks, man. Thanks.
Yeah. Could you imagine that? Eh,
I don't think so.
I don't think so, bro. I don't think so.
Yeah. You need to be careful what you
can do cuz obviously these people get
the police involved cuz they're losers.
They're little informant little fat,
ugly life losers. So obviously you need
to do something where you can't get
nicked but obviously equally [ __ ] them
over the same way. So
So yeah, I'm going to be [ __ ] a woman
over. You can blame these people on here
today. by the way.
Well, well, it is what it is, isn't it?
Yeah. But, bro, it doesn't matter if
it's facts or not. These people always
going to defend women. Like I I I said
today in anger pips that I hope all
women get you know what and they're
saying oh that's disgusting. That's
disgusting. But yet all all of what
women have done to me is completely
fine. What women have done to other
people is completely fine. But they want
to be equal. Remember yeah but they want
But they want to be equal.
Now I'll find someone. I'll find
someone. I will find someone. And then
if I if it doesn't work, I'll find
someone else. So they say that you can't
say you can't wish nasty things on
women, but they're allowed to say and do
what they want. Yeah. Even if you
defended yourself equally, they've still
got a problem with it.
Yeah. They're white knights. They're
white knights. White knights that defend
people for just having a [ __ ] in between their legs,
you know. Yeah. They're Well, they're
white knights. People that try to look
good for women. They're losers.
And I said, I'll talk to them how I
[ __ ] want. No, you know what I'm saying, bro?
I can't wait to [ __ ] this woman over, Autumn.
They all defend. And apparently I lost
on the train, peeps. Apparently I lost.
Even though I literally told her that
she's a crackhead and she's ugly and to
look in the mirror. Apparently I got
told about myself. By the way, I was
half asleep, by the way. Yeah. But
apparently I got owned. Yeah. Okay, mate. Yeah,
they do. They make up excuses. This is
why I don't deal with them anymore,
people. I haven't been out for 3 weeks
now. I haven't been out drinking. I've
just been chilling, bro. Eating
takeaways and stuff.
But, but the thing is, they're always
going to defend these women, lad.
Um, they're losers. I don't know why
they do it, but yeah. So,
I haven't been out for ages, bro. And I
don't have no I don't have no um
I have no plans of I was supposed to go
out this week with my sister peeps, but
I don't think it's a good idea, bro. To
be honest, I'm completely done with them
cuz I'll only be looking for people to
[ __ ] over now.
That's all I'll be doing is looking for
new people to [ __ ] over like bit like
what they've done to me over the years.
Yeah, like this man would say, "Oh, you
talk to her." I said, "No, I will speak
to her how I want if if they're talking
to me like that. I don't give a [ __ ]
what gender they are."
Um, even though they started it and it's
not about being a bigger person. No, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
They're lucky I weren't in a bad mood.
even even a worst mood, bro. To be honest,
they just defend them for having a
vagina. And it's very tiring, bro. Very
very tiring. And I was just like tired
as [ __ ] I stayed up all night, bro. I
collected my winners. I was like, "Bro,
you look like a crackhead."
But again, I'm a [ __ ] apparently.
Yeah, exactly. Exactly. Tell her to shut
her mouth then. Yeah. Tell her to shut
her mouth. That's what I said to him. Yeah. Idiots, bro. So, yeah.
All women are the same peeps. That's why
I gave up with the whole dating thing.
They're clearly all the same. Women are
clearly all bad people. So, I just I
just gave it,
I told her about herself as well. I told
her about her [ __ ] self. I said,
"Have you seen your [ __ ] self?
But apparently I'm the one that got
bullied. I called her a crackhead. An ugly crackhead.
Do you not know what a crackhead is? Do
you not know what crack is?
And I'm trying to [ __ ] talk through
my [ __ ] mouth.
Yeah. Oh, I would hit her. I would hit
her. Oh, I would hit her.
I would do. I would have. I [ __ ]
would have if I if I weren't in a good
mood and I weren't half asleep or
whatever or I'd been I would have I
would have I would have hit her. I would
have smashed her in the face. I would
But no, she knew that. No, no, she knew
that people on the train was going to
defend her. That's why she done it. She
knew that people on the train would have defended her.
Yeah. No, no, no. They knew that the if
if it got to that people would have
defended her. She's a loser, bro. We've
all seen women by themselves. They're
not about that life, bro. They run to
security. They're not bad. They're not
bad people. They're not bad people.
We've all seen them by themselves in
confrontations. They're not bad people.
That and then But the thing is, peeps,
they talk about men's attitude.
They talk about men having a bad
attitude. This is the whole
contradiction is they talk about men
having a bad attitude towards women, but
it's okay for them to have nasty, dirty attitudes,
but that gets dismissed. Basically,
anything a woman does gets dismissed.
It gets dismissed apparently. Any bad
thing a woman does gets dismissed. It's
like Yeah. It's like Yeah, it just gets
dismissed basically. So, you're just
wasting your time.
Yeah, I said I told her I said, "What
the [ __ ] are you looking at?" I said,
"What the [ __ ] are you looking at?"
That's what started it.
You know, you're banned, but right
be like I said, when your address gets
out there, I'll happily come in your
door and we can talk face to face. Until
then, see you later, sad.
Um, and that's basically that, lad. So yeah,
who do you think won in the on the train
peeps? Me or them?
I didn't [ __ ] lose.
I didn't [ __ ] lose. Acting like I
didn't say that she's an ugly crackhead
and there weren't men there. These
people on here make up so much [ __ ]
bro. They make up so much [ __ ] on here.
They make up so much [ __ ] Even when you
stick it on a grown man, they still make
up stuff. They just That's just them
demo here. They just make up stuff on
here. They just make up stuff, bro.
They just make up stories.
They just make up stories and twist things.
Just like with a Newcastle woman,
apparently day one, even though I told
them to go back to Newcastle and [ __ ]
off. Basically what they mean is I
didn't do anything to get me nicked.
That's why they've won.
It's just jealousy on it, is it? It is
just jealousy on this community, isn't it, people?
You know, and they they they still make
up stuff. I think what what it is is
because where you haven't done anything
to get yourself nicked, that's what
they're what that's what they're annoyed about.
That's that's what they're like on
there. These fat, ugly, jealous losers.
Like they would love you, right, to go
out right now and smack a woman in her
face so they can get the police
involved. That's what they would love to
do. These little sad, ugly, jealous
people, they would love to do it. But
because obviously I'm smarter than them,
they will say, "Oh, will they beat you?"
Nah. Which I know when I [ __ ] this woman
over when I dish and ding and dash, bro,
they can't get the police involved. I'm
just going to walk out and make her pay
for it. And obviously, they can't really
get the police involved with that. I
mean, they maybe could, but I mean, I'd risk it.
It's because they can't It's because
basically you haven't done anything to
get um they can't get the police
involved that they're that sad on here.
Fat, ugly, sad, Dennis. Little losers.
Ain't got no life. Got no nothing. I'm
doing a video later to them anyways, but
Oh, by the way, uh peeps, his head got
crushed in the door, by the way.
Yep. His head got crushed in the door.
You know that sim? Did you hear it at
the end? His head actually got crushed
in the door. Yeah. See how the door
shut? His head got crushed in the door.
I was like, "Your head just got crushed
in the door." No, I didn't get on film,
bro. No, you might be able to hear it.
If you listen carefully, you might be
able to hear it. His head got His head
got crushed in the door.
Walk it out. What a loser.
What a [ __ ] loser.
No, I didn't film it. I was just filming me, bro.
But it did happen. I swear to God. On my
dead, dad. My mom's life. It did happen.
I was like, "Your head just got crushed
in the door."
Your head just got crushed in the door.
What do you mean? I stood on business.
What the [ __ ] you on about?
So basically, they're always going to
make up stuff until they can get you
nicked. I mean, I stuck on the bouncer
fair and square. They made up stories.
You can't hit me cuz he's at work. Uh,
you know, I stuck it on them two women
and them two men. Apparently, they beat
me even though I told them to [ __ ] off
back to where they come from. the ugly
[ __ ] but apparently they beat me as
well. They're always going to make
excuses till they can get the police
involved. They done it with Kenji as well.
Well, obviously I weren't going to take their [ __ ]
I I I actually kind of stop Well, I kind
of started it in a way cuz I said like,
"What are you looking at?" I basically
said like, "What the [ __ ] are you looking at?"
First I said, "What are you looking at?"
Then I said again, "What the [ __ ] are
you looking at?" Cuz she tried to give
me some dirty look. So I kind of well I
kind of started it in a way but not
because she gave me a dirty look. So
I don't want to say I started it started
it but I just weren't taking it as [ __ ]
from the get go was I really someone's
giving a dirty look. So
uh what uh she dismisses my struggles
so we don't have the conversation
anymore. We decided it's for the best
because she just dismisses my struggles
so we don't talk about it anymore,
you know? There you go, Triple. What
What did you want me to say,
mate? I was half asleep. I just wanted
to get home. I was [ __ ] tired,
you know? That's [ __ ] why.
Yeah, my my superpower didn't get [ __ ]
after that though to be fair.
But yeah, they make excuses all the time.
You got to understand these people, they
hate you for being for being younger and
better looking than them. So, I mean,
they're not going to agree whether
you're right or you're wrong, lad.
So, yeah, we don't have the conversation
anymore because she dismisses my struggles. Oh [ __ ]
Nope. I don't. But I'm not a copycat.
I don't know cuz I'm not a copycat. Do you?
And he's and and Virgin Boy was lying
earlier. He did used to say you was gay.
He said if you didn't find her
attractive, you was gay. Yes, he did
used to say that. Yes, he [ __ ] did
used to say that when I used to meet
him. Yes, he did. But now he knows he's
been caught out for being a little
copycat. He's guilty now. He's trying to
say, "Oh, no. No, you did. You used to
say that you're homo. Yes, you did."
Yeah, that's what the copycats say.
Peeps, that's what the copycats say.
Yeah, the little copycats.
Yeah, the copycats say that.
Hate copycats. People that have to copy
the crowd. We were speaking about this
the other day, lad.
You're nothing but a little copycat.
Everyone laughing at the skin m you need
to stop. These people on here really
need to stop talking about themselves
and then they wonder why the community
dies because people don't want to see
you people keep talking about
yourselves, bro. You bore everyone.
Why do they keep talking about themselves?
Yeah. I what I think it is with these
people on here, I think they're
they're very hateful people. I think
these people have been bullied in their
life, bro. I definitely think these
people have been bullied.
I definitely think that they're they're
bully victims. I'm not even saying this
to be nasty, bro. I'm being real. I
think they're just ugly, jealous, fat
little losers that ain't got no hope in life. Yeah.
Sad. These people are sad, lad.
They're jealous of me, bro. I know that
for a fact. They're jealous of me
because the way it is obviously jealousy.
They can sit there and say they're not,
but bro, put put your camera on, lad.
What do you think, peeps? I think it's
jealousy on this community. What do you think?
You're younger. You're better looking.
You got more of a life than them. I
mean, you can go out and, you know, you
can you're very mobile. These people sit
in with nothing every day. Just ugly as
[ __ ] Ugly as [ __ ] people that sit in every day.
I think they're jealous of this
community, bro. Cuz they sit there and
say that you're this and you're that,
yet they spend all their life
at you every day. It's definitely
jealousy. And they won't even admit it
to themselves. They won't admit it to
themselves that they're jealous that
you're younger and better looking than them.
It is jealousy. It is 1 million% jealousy, lad.
Definitely jealousy. And they will never
admit it to themselves. They, "Oh, what
do we need to be jealous of?" But
they're old, ugly, fat people. What do
you mean? What? What do you mean when
you got to be jealous of, bro? Bad
ugly fingers. So if you can show your if
you can show your hands. So if you can
show your hands, bro, why don't you show
your face? If you can show your hands,
why don't you show your face and it will
prove that you are the ma. You are ugly.
You are bored. You little low life.
You're all of these things. You're all
of these things, bro. All of these
things. Why don't you show us your face,
ugly man. Ugly little bully victim man.
Showing £800 maximum. I'm doing a video
on this [ __ ] later, bro. Showing your
little benefits. £800.
Sad, sad, sad bastard. Weren't you
trying to say that you showed three
grand the other day? Or was it the other month?
If you Why don't you show us your face?
Cuz you're ugly.
And that's what you'll always have.
Because you're better looking than these
fat, ugly nerds. That's why they're on
here every day. Fat ugly nerd. Showing
these little benefits off. Show some
actual real money, you skin bastard. Yeah.
bastards ain't going to lie.
Calling themselves muners continuously,
yet they will not put their cameras on
because they know that they are the
munters. They know that they're the real
life munters and they can't handle it.
They can't handle that you're better
looking than them. That's where all of
this whole YouTube [ __ ] comes from.
They can't handle the fact that you're
better looking than them because if they
could, they would put their cameras on.
How many times now have we begged these
people to put their cameras on and they
will not do it? They will not show that
fat ugly face and then they come on here
trying to talk about other people that
are better looking than them again
that's got more money than them again
over and over again. You know what I'm
saying with these people?
They're clearly jealous of something. Do
not let them sit there and try and tell
you that even like this Smokey Bros. if
he had a good life, he wouldn't be on it
bullying himself, tormenting himself. You know,
it is because you're better looking than
them. I know the truth hurts. It is the
truth. I know. And it is the truth.
They're little low lives, fat, ugly
little bully victims. They're like
Reddit moderators in a way. They hate
the fact that you're not fat and ugly
like them. So you don't fit in with
these nerds. So what they do is they try
to bring other people down to their
level to to their level.
See if you see here,
they haven't got a life. They're just
fat, ugly little bully victims. Bully
victims of the world.
They ain't got no life, lad. And I'm
going to do a video um about this as well.
They hate anyone that's not a fat ugly
nerd like them. Depressed sat on YouTube
every day. What are you doing, bro? Are
you saving money for a car? Are you
saving money like me? Tell us what what
you're on YouTube every day for Mr.
Better looking. That's not a M and
that's not skimp.
Tell us all about why you're on YouTube
every day. Mr. all of this money
balance. Let us know, bro. Let we really
really really really want to know why
you goodlooking people with all this
money can't go and get yourself a life.
And you know what? I'm going to I'm
going to and I'm going to put and I'm
literally going to um and I'm going to
leave the comments open as well.
You know, you can tell by his fingers
that he's [ __ ] an ugly bastard as
well. Them [ __ ] fingernails don't
even look look normal. They won't show
their face cuz they're big, fat, and
ugly. And that's something that you'd
always have over these people cuz they
know you're younger. They know you're
better looking. So, if they can bring
someone down to their fat, ugly, nerdy
level, you can be ugly and fat like
them. And bro, like I said, if if if
what I'm saying is is is is uh is the
truth. Like I said, you know, feel free
to um show your face if you really want
to see these receipts like like at the
end of the day like that. Yeah. Just
show everyone your face. Prove you're
not a ma. Prove you're not ugly. Prove
us all wrong. Like you keep telling us,
but you can't do it because you're ugly yourselves.
Because you're skinn. You're ugly.
You're depressed. You're on £300 a month
jealous. Recon jealousy every day. You
wake up every single day jealous of
someone that you don't even know cuz
you're fat and ugly.
And it's the truth. And it is the truth.
I know these people better than they
know their [ __ ] selves.
You show them money, they talk [ __ ]
They come out with £800. It's [ __ ]
pathetic now, bro.
They're fat, ugly, depressed people that
hate themselves. They can't even get off
of YouTube and get a life. You know,
that's what it is. You've seen that Jamie Thompson
how many times he stalks me. He hates
that you're not fat and ugly like him.
So, he wants to bring you down because
it's it's to do with looks. They're
jealous of your looks. I've I've got it
now. I've sused these people out because
if they wasn't, bro, if they was not,
they wouldn't be doing this. You're not
let them Don't let these little fat ugly
bongles tell you otherwise, bro.
I've got a screen recording up. I'll do
this later, bro. And I'm going to and
I'm going to sit there and say to these
people one more time. Yeah. that we do
not need to prove ourselves to you fat
ugly low-life people. The sooner you get
that in your [ __ ] brains that we are
not here to prove fat ugly losers like
you wrong because our life is not
proving fat ugly people wrong every day
the suit then you'll actually understand
show your fingers show your [ __ ] face
what's the [ __ ] difference I can show
my face and I haven't even shaved look
at me I need to go to the barbers bro
I can't I show my face.
Uh, these people can't show their face.
Look at me, bro. I need a trim, man. [ __ ]
Why can't they show their face?
You know, I mean, it'd be it would be a
pretty good way to prove people wrong, wouldn't it?
So, that's that. [ __ ] Mongos.
I need to pee, bro. One sec.
some new sayings, lad.
Sad bastards. You can only imagine, bro.
Of course they hide behind their
keyboards, but they're bully victims in
real life, peeps.
The thing is, they're actual bully
victims in real life. Like, every time
they try to go out, they probably get
slapped up for being so ugly, but then
they think they bully other people, bro.
They bully themselves.
Like, how much energy and time do they
put into this every [ __ ] day
trying to tell people that they live off
Kana? Make up your mind. Personally, you
said that I'm I've got bad credit and
now you're saying I'm taking out Kana,
bro. Just because we're not all skint
ugly like you people. Just because
people can afford things, bro, we're not
skint like you. You must be really skint
out 500 pound and stuff. They're getting
themselves confused with me again.
Again, it's part of their It's part of their disabilities.
It's part of these little fat ugly nerds
disabilities. It's part of their disabilities, bro.
They hate the fat fact that they're fat
and ugly and it kills them every day.
Look at the [ __ ] [clears throat] that
they write, lad. It's [ __ ] hilarious, bro. Oh,
and he didn't destroy me at the money
game. Neither did any of you destroy me
at the money game. So, try again.
Colano is basically where you pay off for things.
Yeah, apparently I paid off for my jeans
and trainers. [laughter]
It is funny what these skid low lives
come out with to be honest. It's funny
in a way. It is. It's sad, but it is
funny. Apparently, I pay off for my body
jeans. So, anyone that's got more money
than these little skit people that can't
get off of YouTube, right? It uses colada.
Oh, Jesus Christ. It is funny, isn't it,
bro? You got to laugh. You do have to
I do feel sorry for these people, bro.
[ __ ] it out, bro.
It's definitely jealousy with these
people, bro. 100%.
Is it about money? Yeah, cuz I've got
money. I can go and do what I want and
stuff. They they they don't realize that
it's I can't explain it to you, bro.
It's like people you're able like them.
They're they're um like, okay, let me
let me put it this way, right?
If I wanted to go to Manchester on
Saturday, I could go to Manchester and
do what I want. I've got the body to do
what I want. I've got the freedom. I'm
younger. I'm better looking than them.
They don't like that you are in a better
position in life than them. Like, it's
hard. It's it's hard to explain what
what I mean. But if you know, you know,
bro, like they're they're fat, ugly,
skinned people that've got nothing to
their lives. You can go and do whatever
the [ __ ] you want to go out and do
whenever the [ __ ] you want to do it. You
know what I'm saying? You're not tied
down to anything. And they hate anyone
that's Yeah. younger, better looking,
and got freedom. That's It's hard to
explain it, bro. But it is definitely
this. It is definitely this with these people. Yeah.
They've been doing this for [ __ ] for
years now. Years and years and years.
They don't get paid for it, and they're
still doing it. They haven't killed
anyone. They haven't ruined anyone any
They haven't ruined anyone's life, but
they're still doing it, you know. So
now I can go and do what the [ __ ] I want
basically. If I wanted to get 10 women
women's numbers tomorrow, I could. If I
wanted to leave London tomorrow, I
could. If I wanted to leave the country
tomorrow, I could. Do you get what I'm
saying? These people are old, miserable,
ugly people. And the sooner you get to
know the the the better.
You know what I mean?
Cuz we all know that if you jumped on a community lad
and you're calling these people ugly and
you knew you were better looking than
them, you'd show your face. These people
have got 101 Dalmatian excuses why they
won't show their face. Why they will not
show their face because they are ugly.
That's why ugly bastards. They ain't got nothing. Yeah.
Yeah. They must know about it. Yeah.
Exactly. It's what they use. And you got
to decide with these nerds, bro. It is
self-p projection. I've never lo used
colana in my life. I've never paid off
for anything in my life.
Don't think so. Have I never
I was considering paying off a two grand
phone one time cuz it was two fucking,000.
Um but that was like two years ago.
Never ever paid off a clothes in my
life. Ever. Never.
So yeah, it's like you said, they must
they must know about it very well. They
must know about these things very well
to be commenting on them. That's a good
point you made.
They think that I need sublet money,
bro. I've got more money than you would
ever have. I don't need sublet money. I
can do what I want when I want.
This is what these people don't understand. But yeah.
Nah, I don't think so. I will.
They think that because people can buy
trainers and jeans, they think that
everyone's skint like them. They think
everyone is skint like them, just like
they think everyone's ugly like them.
And then they keep calling people a m.
But these people don't show their face
ever. So just ridiculous, isn't it?
They're definitely talking about their
poverty within their own life, bro.
Definitely definitely talking about
themselves. They love talking about
themselves. They really, really love
talking about themselves, are they?
But then they ask why the community
dies, but they're sat there repeating
themselves every day. But they're smart people,
Stephen. They don't show their face
because they're smart people. They don't
show their face because they're smart people.
But they repeat themselves every day and
they've got no other comebacks. But
they're smart people. Remember? They're
intelligent people. Remember these
little nerds. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. Okay, mate.
But they're smart people apparently.
Smart people that repeat themselves
every day. Yeah. Little low lives.
[ __ ] little nerds.
They repeat themselves every [ __ ]
day, Steven Albert. But they're so
smart. That's why they don't want to. If
they're so smart, why didn't they start
acting smart and stop repeating
themselves every day?
[ __ ] virgins. So, you showed your
face. You showed something. You showed
your money your 800 pound that you just
got paid by the benefit system. You
showed your hands. What's stopping you
showing your face? Don't say you're
smart, bro. You're really not smart.
You're really not smart, bro.
You're really, really not smart.
So what? You know, if you were smart,
you wouldn't be repeating yourself every
day on YouTube if you were smart.
I just think yeah, they're just fat ugly
people that's just jealous of anyone
that's got a better life than them
that's young younger and better looking and mobile.
See, the thing is Greg, I'm quite mobile.
It's hard to explain what I'm what I'm
saying, bro. But yeah, I know what I mean.
I would just love to know how these
people have have got all of this money,
but they'll sit on here all day hate him.
Maybe someone in the comments will be
able to um explain that to me. How they
seem to have all of this money and such
a better life than everyone. Yeah, [ __ ] projectors.
Sad lowife little projectors.
But yeah, I'm going to do this dying and dash anyways.
S little bastards, virgins.
What they are, bro. And I won't be
responding anymore to these people after this.
Sad little bastard little virgins.
Where is this?
Wow. Suming in my piss bank. You're a [ __ ] weirdo.
What am I eating? I had boiled eggs, but
I'm not eating anything today.
I'm doing a video on these clowns, lad.
These are all nerds.
I mean, even Ricky is saying that I'm
not balding. All of this [ __ ] right here
is just a load of projection. That's all
it is with these nerds, bro.
Yeah, I'm going to do a video anyways on these [ __ ]
Why is there piss on my bottoms? I think
I must have went toilet and pissed.
I mean, normally people [ __ ] themselves
when they're scared of someone. They
actually [ __ ] themselves. They don't
piss themselves. I mean, I I've only
ever pissed myself before laughing.
I mean, you got your boy. I mean, you know,
they're sad little bastards.
Yeah, I'm done anyways.
do a video later, bro. That's that.
Anyways, I'm gone.