Bro,
I know I said yeah I wasn't going to
come back until [ __ ] January, but
bro, these little nerds, all they do is
twist things. All these fat ugly nerds
do is twist things. This is exactly what
I was telling [ __ ] Grezy yesterday. Bro,
you got some stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] in
Birmingham team. The team trying to tell
people that they shut themselves. Bro,
you were showing£300, bro, a couple of
months ago trying to flex£300.
Yeah. Do you know what? I'm calling
everyone out today, bro. I want to meet
one of these people today, bro. I
actually want to meet one of these
people today, bro. And I don't want to
hear no [ __ ] excuses. I don't want to
hear no excuses,
you know? I'm really, really wanting to
meet one of these people today, bro. I
swear to God.
One of these fat, ugly nerds. If I can
get my hands on one of these ugly
people, bro, I'll be [ __ ] happy, bro.
I swear to God, I'll be happy if I can
get my hands on one of these fat, ugly,
spasticated little [ __ ]
keyboard warriors, bro. I'll be happy,
bro. Just just one of them, bro. Please,
someone meet me today so I can smash
your face in. Please, somebody meet me
today so I can smash your [ __ ] face.
And yeah, I'll put the link out in a bit
and then anyone can join. Just let me
smack up your face and smack your teeth
down your throat. Please, anyone, bro.
Anyone who's watching this today,
anyone. I'm calling you all out, bro.
Yeah, I'm calling you all out. And I'm
going to put the link out in a minute as well.
Yeah, I'm sick of them, bro. I'm [ __ ]
sick of these little fat, ugly little
mongos on here. These little spasticated
little autistic [ __ ] Mongs. Yeah, and
I'm calling you all out, bro. You're not
going to do nothing. I'm putting a link
out in a bit anyways when more people
join. Yeah, I want one of these people
to meet me today so I can smack their
teeth down their [ __ ] throat about I
shhat it from a woman. Are you [ __ ]
mad, bro? I told her she was a crackhead
and she was boring. Yeah, let me see if
I [ __ ] it from one of you. Let Me meet
me today so I can smack your teeth down
your throat in into PD. Come on. Come
on, you little [ __ ] mongos. Yeah, let
more people join and I'm going to put
the link out and I'm going to meet
someone on here today and I'm going to
kick your teeth down your throat, spit
[snorts] in your mouth. Yeah, trust me.
No, I haven't gambled. I've told you a
million times I don't gamble. I'm just
sick of these little clowns on here,
bro. I'm sick of these little mongos.
Why would I gamble? I've told you
specifically I do not gamble. only on
the football occasionally. These [ __ ]
are pissing me off, bro.
These little fat, ugly, autistic little
[ __ ] little wankers. Yeah,
simple, bro. Well, why are you asking
the stupid bro? It's Monday, bro. Why
would I gamble? Why would Why would I
gamble when it's a Monday, bro?
Why would I gamble when it's a Monday?
It's It's a Monday, bro. So, why would I
gamble on a Monday? I haven't even left
the house. Why would the [ __ ] would I
gamble on a Monday? For what reason, bro?
Anyways, [ __ ] all that. I'm going to put
a link out in a bit. And I I want one of
these people to meet me today, bro. I
want one of these people to meet me
today. I really want to hurt one of
these little nerds. These fat ugly
nerds. I want to smash their ugly face
in, bro. Let's see what they're really,
really about, bro. Let's see what
they're really, really, really about.
Because, you know, years and years and
years of this [ __ ] [ __ ] Let's
see what they're really, really, really,
really, really, really about. You got
this [ __ ] profit loans, bro. No, it's
not a gambling loss, bro. So, every time
someone tells these people about
themselves, they've lost money gambling.
No, it's not a gambling loss, you know.
It's just I hate these people in here,
bro. Do you not listen listen? Did you
not Did you not understand the other day
when I stayed up all night to show you
how much I hate these people? Yeah. Same
with you, Provident Loans, if you're
watching this. Oh, you always Tim. You
[ __ ] spasticated fat old man. Yeah,
you're another one. you fat, spasticated
Birmingham little rejected old man, bro.
Oh, long story. Basically, um I won £110
uh last week and I put a barcode up by
accident, bro. Yeah, I put a barcode up
by accident and obviously I wanted to
beat them to the bookies um before they
could beat me to the bookies. I didn't
need £110, but yeah.
Yeah, I didn't need the £110, but I
didn't want them to have the last laugh.
So, I stayed up all night, bro. All
night I stayed up. Yeah, I stayed up all
night just so they didn't get that money
because I hate them, bro. You don't
understand how much I hate these people
in this community, bro. Yeah, that was
dedication, bro. I just kept drinking
tea. Yeah, I went to the bookies when it
first opened just so they didn't get the
last laugh. Didn't need £110. I could
easily give it to my mom. A homeless
person didn't need it. You know what I'm
saying, bro? That's how much I hate
these people on here, bro. You don't
understand. When I get my hands on one
of these people, I will smack their
teeth down their [ __ ] throat, bro.
Let's see if any of these people come on
the links. I'm going to put the link up
in a bit.
Uh cuz I I post my winning tips on here,
bro. If in case people want to copy it,
like tips. Yeah, I I've been doing it a
couple of times, bro.
Yeah, I've been doing it a couple of
times, bro. But yeah, I stayed up all
night basically for that and that's how
that train thing happened. [ __ ]
bullied, bro. Meet me today, one of you
people. I'll bully you, bro. If I bully
any of you, PC, any of you, any of you
little haters, you know who you are.
Meet me anywhere today, bro. Meet me anywhere today. Yeah.
Yeah. And you know what? It wasn't even
about the money, bro. It wasn't even
about the money cuz I I'd get the 110
and give it to a homeless person. I
don't give a [ __ ] about £110. It's the
fact I didn't want them getting it.
Ghosting. It's the fact I didn't want
them getting it. Anyways, I'm putting
this link out in a bit and if any of
these people want to meet me today, bro,
I'm going to go with gun strap. Anyways,
so let's see if any of these mongos are
really really about it.
Same with that Provident Loans. You're a
laughing stock, bro. No one shattered
from anyone, mate. Yeah. How long have
you been doing this in Birmingham now,
bro? You're you're you're a clown, bro.
Don't No, I don't watch him. I don't
watch him, Ghost. It's the same atmosphere
about a woman destroy me. That [ __ ]
little scar didn't destroy me. I told
her about herself and I was [ __ ] half
asleep. You like to make things up. This
is what they do with this community.
They like to make stuff up,
you know. Let's see if any of these
people want to meet me today, bro. Come
on. I'll give them a good oldfashioned
ass whooping, bro. A good old ass
whooping. I don't want to hear about how
none of these people people don't live
in London or near No, no. I don't want
to hear any of that [ __ ] mate. I don't
want to hear any of that [ __ ] Yeah,
cuz you do, bro. You know these people
do. They're [ __ ] little nerds. Fat,
ugly, little disabled, little single
little virgin nerds. Just cuz I'm
telling you about them, bro, it doesn't
mean people's lost money. Why would the
[ __ ] would I lose money, bro? Because
I'm speaking the truth. Does every time
Peter Belly speak the truth, it means he
loses money? Please, bro. It's
embarrassing. I haven't even left the
house today. So, that would be a bit
hard to lose money, isn't it?
Lord is another one. If he ever comes
here, no, bro. I hate these people. I
hate most of these people in it. You
don't understand, bro. I hate most of
these people. I just want 10 seconds
with them so I can [ __ ] smack their
face in coming on here every day
creating the same disabled atmosphere.
I want one of these people, bro. I want
one of these people.
Yeah, people can, but I don't. So, no
greasy. I was reading some of the
comments, bro, and these people are
[ __ ] annoying me, bro. I really want
to meet someone today for a fight. Yeah,
I really, really, really want to meet
someone for a fight, bro. I really want
to smash their teeth down their throat.
Have you Have you ever seen Have you
ever seen on this community someone's
teeth get smashed out yet? No. But you
will today if one of these people want
to meet me. If one of these people want
to meet me today, I'll gladly smash
their teeth down their [ __ ] throat
making up [ __ ] fake [ __ ] Let's see
what happens to you today if you meet
me. Come on. Come on.
[ __ ] little bogos. These little
[ __ ] virgin accounts like the Flash
and that. Bro, you're sat there a fat
ugly virgin. Can't get a woman. Never
been with a woman. Skint as [ __ ] Yeah.
Skint [ __ ] ugly people. Skint ugly
people. Just like you, Provident Loans.
And guess what? You're the one that
comes on [ __ ] Hangouts, don't you,
bro? Oh, the always the oy Tim. You
[ __ ] Brummy [ __ ] Yeah, you
[ __ ] bra [ __ ] with 300 quid to his [ __ ] name.
The o the oy him. You [ __ ] UB little
reject. You're a little UB40 little
[ __ ] reject. That's what you are,
bro. You're a UB40 [ __ ] reject. And
here's another thing. Yeah, since we
know this Kevin Murphy watches this. Why
don't you get your ass down to London?
Yeah. Why don't you get your ass down to
London right today, right now, bro? Come
on. Why don't you do it? Why don't you
do it? Why don't you do it? Why don't
you do it? Why don't you do it, bro? You
keep asking people to come back to
Liverpool. Every time people come to
Liverpool, you make excuses why you're
not there. You know, we all we've all
heard it. So, why don't you come to
London, Kevin Murphy?
You [ __ ] scouse a little mong
[ __ ] bro. When I get my hands on one
of these people, please, bro. Please, please.
You know, even Prime, if you want to
meet me today, Prime, I'll meet you. I
have no problem meeting you if you want to meet
any of these people. [snorts]
I don't care about money. I just think
it's bad flashing £300. Well, he was
flashing £300. That's That's why he was
flashing it. He was flashing £300. And
yeah, bro, they care about money cuz
they ain't got no money. They're skint.
They ain't got no money because they're
[ __ ] skint. That's why they weren't
here every day cuz they're [ __ ] skint
lad. I don't care who's got He was
flashing it. I think who the [ __ ]
flashes 300 [ __ ] pound
[ __ ] wrong, bro. It's same atmosphere
on here, is it? Same atmosphere on here.
Scrap that, bro. I'd love that fantasy
stories. Oh, I would love that fantasy
stories out of anyone, bro. If I could,
it would be that fantasy stories out of
anybody, bro. Yeah, I know. It sounds
mad, isn't it? Yeah, bro.
Bro, I would I would love this f I would
love this fantasy stories out of anyone.
Oh, bro, out of anyone for for two
reasons. For two reasons.
I would I think I'd pick him and then
the second would be V. If I could pick
any of these [ __ ] and they've come in
hangouts. Yeah, bro. I would love I
would [ __ ] love.
How many fights have I turned up? Every
single one of them. But you wouldn't you
wouldn't know that because you're all
biased on here. Yeah. Yeah, I mean
you're all biased on it, but yeah, it
would be fantasy stories. Yeah, it would
definitely definitely be fantasy stories. Yeah,
they're jealous of anyone that's better
looking and younger than them that's got
and that's got a life, bro. For [ __ ]
sake, they're jealous of every everyone.
Anyone that's normal that comes on this
community, they'd be jealous of them
because they're fat, ugly little low
lives sat on sat on YouTube every day,
right? Yet they claim they got all this
money. They claim they've got this life, right?
But they've got all of this money, bro.
It doesn't add up. Ghost. Uh,
who flashes? Uh, well, I flashed the
money for a reason because No, no, no.
But I I flashed the money for a reason.
It It was a bit different. Yeah. I mean,
it was It was a bit different. Nice try,
though. Uh, that was a bit different. I
was showing it to annoy you that you
didn't get the money before me, bro. If
I wanted to really play the money game,
I'd beat all of you. I would literally
beat all of you. I if I wanted to, I
would literally beat all of you if I
wanted to play the money game. So, don't
start with that again, mate. I I showed
£110. Yeah. Yeah. To show that you
didn't get it. [laughter] To show that
you didn't get it. And guess what? No
one showed me £220.
So that's all that's all that's all that
that that that tells you something,
doesn't it, lad?
No, he's not coming on here. He's not
allowed on this channel. No repeating
self-reflectors on this channel, bro. So
yeah, 110 and and no one showed me 220.
So I mean, if if no one's showing you
220, I don't think anyone's showing you
thousands, mate. You know,
because I don't like the fat, ugly
[ __ ] bongo, and I don't like his
followers either. It's the same
atmosphere. Oh, Grezy, I'm having some
chicken and chips today.
Sorry, bro. I can't help myself. [snorts]
I shouldn't really, but uh I'm not
cooking today. I can't be bothered. I'm
just going to go to a chicken shop. I
need to change my diet cuz of my my gums
and [ __ ] but
uh I don't know, bro.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, just like some fried chicken, bro.
you must be talking about yourself. That
self projecting though, isn't it,
Smokeoky Be, you're getting a word.
Well, you know all about yourself, lad.
You know all about skin your skin
yourself. So takes one to no one. As I say,
talking about yourself, you only know
about your own financial circumstances.
So you're talking about yourself, not
talking about me. You're not talking
about someone that you don't know, bro.
You're talking about yourself. It's
boring now. Come up with something
original. Come up with something new.
And that's not self projecting.
Do you know what I'm saying, bro? So yeah.
Yeah. You need to stop. All right. I was
watching Savvy Guy uh yesterday,
Douglas. Um I was watching him, bro.
Yeah. You you were showing £1,700.
Get a grip, bro. Yeah. 1700. Get a grip,
bro. You're [ __ ] skint. Another thing
is uh another thing is uh um this sinks
that sing works. He was talking about
sing. He was like, "Oh yeah, sing works
and that sing works."
Yeah, Smokey, if you had all of this
money, you wouldn't be on here. If you
had all of this money, you wouldn't be
doing what you do on here. Your YouTube
activity gives um gives you gives you away.
Your YouTube activity just gives you away, lad.
Come to bully me, bro. You don't bully
me because you'll never meet me. If you
really bully me, why don't you come to
London and meet me, bro? I'll tell you
exactly where I am. I'll smash your face
in, bro. Some fat old ugly man, some fat
old ugly man like you would never bully
a guy like me, bro. Come and meet me
today then. No, she didn't stick her
right on me. I told her that she was a
crackhead. I told her that she was a
crackhead if you actually watch the
video properly and that she's boring me.
No, she didn't stick it on me. But
anyways, I will happily meet you today
and I'm willing to I'm willing to uh I'm
willing to test your theory, bro. Meet
me today then and do not make excuses.
Meet me today. Yeah. You're only half an
hour away from London. Yeah. And I'll
see this bully man. Yeah. Bro, I'll
smack your teeth down your throat. I'm
more than happy to do it. I will happily
meet you today. Yeah. Yeah. Come to your
What are you half an hour away from
London, bro? You're not about that life,
Smokey. You don't bully no one. You're a
fat, ugly virgin old man and you're
ugly. And I'll prove it today. You're an
ugly [ __ ] Come to London today, ugly
man, and let me bully you to your face.
Not behind a keyboard. Bro, I'm not
coming. No, no, no, no, no. You can come
to London today. Yeah, I've got plans
today. I'm doing stuff today. You can
come to London. Yeah, you're only half
an hour away. Come on, man. I've been
[ __ ] up and down the country. Come
on. Come on, big man. Come on, big man.
Bro, I'll slap you so hard in your
[ __ ] mouth, bro, that that you won't
even want anymore. Yeah, that's it, bro.
I'm too skinned to leave the house, bro.
Stop self projecting. Come and meet me
in London today and I'll [ __ ] you up. I
will [ __ ] you up, bro. It won't even be
like like no prime thing. I'll start
getting ready soon. Stop bottling it
now. Stop bottling it. Stop bottling it.
What are you bottling it for?
And look at Joe making excuses for
women. But I I I don't mind Grezy
putting it up, bro. Because I mean,
they're always going to make excuses
anyway. So they make excuses when you
stick it on a man. So these people
always make excuses.
Yeah. I love the excuses though, man. I
love the excuses.
Listen, come to London today so I can
smack you in your mouth. Stop making
excuses. Are you Are you meeting me or
not? Are you meeting me today or not?
You [ __ ] skimp [ __ ]
Well, the thing is, Joe, if someone's
eating then you move carriages or you
ask them politely, can you not do that?
So, no. No, it isn't me. And do you know
how I know that, mate? Cuz I've had
people I've had people eat on the train
and I've moved carriages or just don't
say anything. So yeah. Yeah. In this
case, maybe it's not me, [ __ ]
considering I've used the train a
million times. But again, always
defending women to make yourself look
good. Just like that guy on the train. E
listen bro. Bro, I've already been to
Milton Kees and you shattered it then.
So you're not coming to London then? So
you're not coming to London? You're an
idiot man. You don't, bro. Someone like
you trying to say that you're bullying
me, bro. I would smack your teeth down
your throat. You ugly Milton Kees out of
London little virgin little skin wanker.
Uh, there is wrong with defending women
when they're not in the right. Uh,
ghosting. There is a problem with
defending women when the women are not
in the right. It's called sing. Anyway,
Smokey little skint 1,700 a month boy.
Skint boy, come and meet me today. Come
and meet me today. Milton Kees boy with
a shitty little roundabouts and come to
London, bro. You're only 25 minutes away
from London. You're getting boring as
well, bro. You're getting boring. You're
You're getting boring. Some little nerd
skint nerd on YouTube trying to give it
large when he lives in Milton Kes. Bro,
we can't even take you serious. I told
you where I'm going to be today. Come
and meet me. Come and meet me. Come on.
For [ __ ] sake. How many times have I
been to Manchester? How many times have
I been [ __ ] everywhere, bro? Just
come and meet me today. I'll bully you
in person. I'll bully you in real life.
I will show the ugly bully victim in
real life. I'm sure everyone would love
to see it, but you're not going to do
it. So, there's no point. You're a
little loser, bro.
Nope. I haven't lost money. Again, I
repeat myself to you autistic people. I
only gamble occasionally on a football.
It is Monday.
No, I just don't like these people on
here. I just want to get my hands on one
of these people on here. I hate their
biasness. I hate the way they twist
things. Um, you know, I don't like these
people on here. Me staying up the whole
night the other day proves how much I
hate these people. I just want to get my
hands on one of these people and beat
them badly. Beat them. Spit in their
face. Everything, bro. I want to [ __ ]
them up. Put them on YouTube. Smack
their teeth down their throat so they
don't ever come on here again. No. I
haven't even lost money. I've got plenty
of money. Plenty of money. I've got
plenty of money.
You know, no, it's when I went on
Greavves video and they twist things.
So, do you know what? Yeah. Let them
have their little W. I'm willing to meet
people today. I'm willing to meet people
today. I am willing to meet people
I'm willing to meet people. I just don't
like these people on here. I just don't
like these haters on here, you know? So,
I would love to get my hands on them,
bang them in the mouth, smack their
teeth down the throat, and I'll [ __ ]
never come back on here again, bro.
Yeah, bro. No woman has Smokey B. I'm
trying to meet you today, and you keep
making excuses, so you're the one that's
being the bully victim. I'm asking you
to meet me so I can smack your teeth
down your throat and you keep avoiding
me. So, bro, I'm willing to go today if
you want. I'm more than happy to I'm not
going to lose to some [ __ ] Milton Kees wanker.
Some Milton Kees boy? Are you mad, bro?
Do you think I'm going to lose to
someone from Milton Kees? Some skint
little [ __ ] like you? Really, bro? You
really think I'm going to lose to some
Milton Keane skinned little wanker like
you, bro? Come on. Come on now, bro.
Yeah, I want to meet these people, bro.
I want to meet these people. No woman's
ever bullied me. Smoking me. Was that
Did that woman on the pot bully me when
I made her scared of me? What about the
women in the Weather Spoons when they
had to get the security guard? No
[ __ ] rape victims ever bully me. No
[ __ ] rape victims ever bullied me,
bro. They get [ __ ] raped by people.
Do you think people that get raped to
bully me, bro? Are you [ __ ] mad?
Anyways, come and meet me today, big
man. Listen, come and meet me today so I
can smack your teeth down your throat,
right? I've had enough of you [ __ ]
people on here to to last me a [ __ ]
lifetime. Do you want to meet or not?
Let me smack your teeth down your
[ __ ] throat so everyone can laugh at
you. Stop making excuses. Milton Kees
boy. Milton Kees boy, you go on that
you've got all of this money. Just
travel 25 minutes, bro. It's the
outskirt. It's the outskirt to London.
Come on. Come on. Bring your misses with
you. I'll slap her in front of you as
well. Listen. Do you know what, bro?
Bring your misses with you and I'll
bully you and I'll bully your misses in
front of you. Come on, bro. Please come
and meet me. Please meet me, bro. I want
to meet you. Please. I want to smack
you. I want to show everyone what you
people are like in real life, bro. I
want to show everyone what you keyboard
warriors. I will threaten women as much
as I want. I will slap his woman in
front of him and I'll tell her to get
raped. I'll tell her to get [ __ ]
raped. I will tell her to [ __ ] get
raped and I will threaten her as much as
I want. Are we going or not? Are we
Because I don't want to go to Milton
Kings. I He is telling me that I'm
skinned. He is telling me that I'm
skinned. Right. He is telling me that I
am [ __ ] skinned. So come to London
then. You're telling me that I'm skin.
That's what you said. Okay. Come to
London then if I'm skin. If I'm if I'm
skin, come to London. Come on. I've got
no money. Okay. I've got no money. Okay.
I've got no money. I've got no money.
Okay. Okay. I've got no money. So then
come to London then. Right. So come to
London then. If I've got no money, come
to London. If I've got no money, come to
London then. You've just said that I've
got no money. Right. That's what you're
saying. Okay. I've got no money. So come
to London then. So now you've got no excuses.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Don't
tell me about I can't threaten a woman.
I'll do I'll do what I [ __ ] want in
front of any any [ __ ] man. I'll do
what I want in [ __ ] front of any man.
You don't [ __ ] tell me what to do,
bro. Don't [ __ ] try and tell me who I
can't can and can't threaten. I will
threaten a woman any and I'll tell them
to get raped in front of them. Don't
[ __ ] try and tell me who I can and can't threaten.
I'll tell them to get [ __ ]
disgustingly raped. Don't [ __ ] try
and tell me what I can and can't do. No.
No. No. No. No. No. No, you have just
said that I'm skinn. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no. One second. Right. You have just
said that I'm skinned, right? £30 for
the month, bro. Where the [ __ ] do you
get these things from? I've got £30 to
last me a month, bro. Are you talking
about yourself or something?
£30 to last me a month? What the [ __ ]
are you talking about? Uh, what about
what these women do, ghosting? What they
do is disgusting. What these women do is
disgusting. Don't be a white knight.
It's never going to get you laid. Don't
Don't be a white knight, bro. They're
not going to let you hit. £30 to last me
a month. What the [ __ ] are you talking
about, bro? Yeah. And I own you. You
can't even come to London with your rape victim, Mrs.
Bro. Why are you Why are you being a
white night ghost? Listen. And I bully
your I've just told your MS to get raped
and you're not going to do nothing about it.
Your woman is to get raped. [ __ ] you.
And I hope your woman gets raped and
you're not going to do nothing. They
hate you too, bro. You little rape
victim. Show everyone your ugly misses.
Show everything your ugly misses. You
little your Mrs. is a rape victim. Yeah,
you're sat there trying to tell me
you're sat there. Well, why are you
defending women for the sake of
defending women then ghost? Bit bit
immature. I think what women do is
disgusting, but we won't get into that
anyways. Bro, they hate you as well.
Women hate you people as well. You're on
YouTube little virgins and you can't
even get laid,
bro. They don't bully me. Well, I do. I
hope all women get raped. Well, I did. I
just done it. I hope they all get raped.
Well, I've just done it. So, I hope all
women get raped. I've done it. I've said
it now. And if anyone's got a problem
with me, And if anyone's got a problem
with me, I'm more than happy to meet
anyone today. I am more than happy to meet anyone.
Yeah, I am more than happy to meet
anyone. [ __ ] hope they all get raped.
And I'm more than happy to meet any of
you people today. Right. And I'll put
the link up. Simple.
[ __ ] idiots, bro. [ __ ] Mongos.
Anyways, if you're not going to meet me,
[ __ ] off. Simple.
Stupid little idiots, bro.