Uh, all right. Oh,
I'd love to see what the response is to
that. It's the truth.
Would I reply to myself?
Yeah, this is what I mean with these
people. I'm coming off of it after
today. Anyways, after I do this last
video, bro, 100%. Yeah,
100%. I was talking to someone about
this. I'm I am coming off here after today, bro.
Away from these jealous little life loser virgins,
life loser, virgins, fat slobs, jealous
people. What's the point of wasting your
life on some bunch of fat, ugly, jealous
people that ain't got no life? Yeah, bro.
I'm off here after um
I might even do this. I don't know why.
Don't know. Yeah,
they're just jealous fat ugly low lives.
I was speaking to my mom about this as well.
We were speaking about this, bro. It's
really, really not worth it with these
fat, ugly, jealous losers.
They'll never stop. It's like what
Ronald Pump said, they're jealous of
you. I should have listened a long long
time ago with these fat ugly freaks.
I should have listened, bro.
I got a bit too deep in it.
[snorts] Yeah. With these ugly fat virgins. Yeah.
They hate you cuz you're better looking
than them. So no matter what you do or
what you say, they're always going to
come and chat [ __ ] And that's the
conclusion that, you know, I I come to
with it, bro. to be fair with these
people like 100%. 100 million%.
I mean, even Joseph Farrell, look at
Joseph Ferrar's comment. Look how he
contradicted himself. Two thumbs up.
Two thumbs up, lad. So,
you can see what I mean. They're just
all biased little low lives on there.
Jealous fat ugly people. They're not
even worth talking about or talking to these losers.
That's that, bro. So, yeah.
That's what they are, bro. That's their life.
biased little life losers.
I would warn anyone, bro. Anyone that's
young and decent looking, I would tell
them to stay away from this community
cuz you'll get pounced on by the fat slobs.
By the fat slobs, fat slobs.
Yeah, you need to stop trolling. It's
bad. And I'm coming off it from tomorrow
anyways because of you people.
you fat, ugly little low-life people
that create the same atmosphere every
day. I want out of this shitty
community. I'm off here from tomorrow
100%. I don't want to argue with people
that are jealous of me. I'm never going
to be getting that time back. And anyone
that wants to say otherwise, I'm more
than happily put the link up and you can
put your cameras on
just in case you think you're going to
lie to yourself. Just in case you think
you're going to lie to yourself, mate.
Bunch of fat, ugly people that are
jealous of you. You're never You're
never going to get this time back
arguing with these numpties, these
virgins, these sack of shits, these
bully victims that have been bullied
their whole life. You're never ever
going to get that time back, Peter
Belly. The amount of times you keep
arguing with these bully victims, these
low lives, these skint people that do
[ __ ] all but talk [ __ ] behind a
keyboard. You're going to be on that deathbed, bro.
But and you're wasting argue with a
bunch of jealous fat virgins that can't
get off a website. Imagine it, bro. The
[ __ ] That's what you call the
absolute You know what, bro?
Reddit. I haven't been on Reddit.
Yeah, bro. Because they're stalkers.
Because you're younger and better
looking than them. It kills them. It's
like what Ronald Pump said. This is
where all of this stuff comes from.
It's because they hate that you're
better looking than them. You've got
what they don't have. better looks,
better money. They're fat. They're ugly. They're loners.
They're ugly people that can't get for
YouTube. They're not even [ __ ] people
to be to be took serious, bro. You know,
no one cares, bro.
Even that Joseph Ferrar comment,
they hate that you're better looking at
them. The pennies dropped. It's dropped.
Yeah. Out of the hole today. I know this
lad. Of course they're obsessed with me.
I'm younger and better looking than
them. They're fat slobs.
They're fat skin slobs. Of course
they're obsessed with me, bro. It's
nothing new. We just found out the
reason. They're fat, ugly life losers.
Skint little nerds. Skint bully victims.
We know what they are, bro. Just leave them.
Yeah, they're ugly people. Virgins. I
told you, bro. That's what they are when
they are sad, idiotic little virgins
that's never been anywhere near a woman
sexually. Their family hate them. Think
about it, bro. It's December. Do you
think near Christmas these people are
going to be off of YouTube? Do you think
these people are going to be off of
YouTube? No. They're never going to get
off YouTube, bro. They're going to be on
on YouTube on Christmas. You know,
they're going to be on YouTube
Christmas. They're fat, ugly life's losers [snorts]
because they're fat, ugly people. No one
wants them. They're losers.
Obviously, bro, you know, you know the
answers to this. They're fat, ugly,
disabled people. They're bully victims.
Skint. Well, how can they get a life?
They got no money, bro. What What life
are these people supposed to be having?
You're telling them to get a life doing
what? They've got no money. They're skint.
What? What? What do you want them to do,
bro? You know, they're skint. They're
ugly. They're single. They got no
family. They got no one. What What What
do you want them to do, bro?
What do you want these little sad, ugly
people to do that ain't got no money?
Where are they going? What are they
doing? Come on, bro.
They're sad little skin burdens. And
this is why I'm coming off this, bro.
from tomorrow. 100.
You sir little. Yeah, whatever, bro. Go
away. Keyboard lawyer. Do you want to
come in the hangouts? Uh,
they don't have families. This is what
I'm saying. They don't have families.
They got nobody. But I was I was talking
to my mom about this earlier, bro. They
ain't got any families.
They got nothing. They got nothing.
These people, this is why they do this.
Yeah, they're little sad acts little
virgins. They got nobody in life. That's
why they do this. Sad disabled people.
Sad disabled fat ugly people that have
been on the internet for years. All
washed up [ __ ]
The link's up there if you want to join.
You can put your camera on and show us your face.
But yeah, I'm definitely definitely
coming off of this um tomorrow anyways,
lad. So hopefully Joseph Ferrar hasn't
gone to bed and he can come in and uh
explain why he's so biased cuz I'd love to know.
It's all biased. They're all jealous.
They're undercover haters, bro. Even
Joseph Ferrar, you'll notice that
they're they're undercover haters.
They get on Why, bro? Why do these
people get on with each other? Cuz
they're fat and ugly. They're all nerds.
They're all bums. They're all fat.
They're all stinking.
That's why they go for the younger,
better looking, cuz they know that
you're better than them in every way.
But they don't admit to themselves. Oh,
no. No. Won't admit to themselves.
They're smart, apparently, bro. They're
apparently smart. They're apparently
smart people, but they repeat themselves
every day. Kill the community. They kill
Yeah, they of course they all hate me,
bro. I'm better looking than them. Of
course they do. I'm better looking than
them. I'm younger than them. I've got a
life on like them. Of course they hate me, bro.
Because I'm younger and better looking
and it's what kills them. What? It's
exactly what Ronald Pump said. You're
younger, you're better looking, and it
kills them. And he was so right. He was
so right about that cuz it's so obvious
now. It's they're making it so obvious
to the point where people can't even say anything anymore.
But she just says same as me. They're
just jealous. They're just jealous
people that ain't got a life, that
haven't got anyone. It's just It says
the same thing as what I said.
They're jealous, ugly people.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. What life have you got?
Sat on the internet every day from the
time you wake up to the time you go to bed projecting.
What life have you got? What life have
you people got sat on the internet all day skinned?
Right. What life have you people got?
sat on YouTube, no job, no money, no
looks, no nothing. What life have you people got?
What life have you people got? Come on,
tell us. Tell us. Tell us. Okay, fair
enough. You said that. What life have
you got? Nothing. That's why you're not
even worth reacting to. You're little
clowns, mate. You're ancient. You've
been on here for 10 years, bro. 10
[ __ ] years. You're a You're ancient.
You're just fat, ugly, jealous people
that ain't got nothing in life. It's a
hard pill to swallow, maybe, bro. But
it's the truth. I know you don't like
it, but it is the truth.
Yeah. Okay. Well, why don't you come in
right now and show us what you got, bro?
We'd love to see it. Why don't you come
in the Hangouts right now and show us
what you got? If you had a good life,
you wouldn't be on here doing what you
do every day. Said it once, say it
again. So, that's that.
You people sit on here, bro, till early
hours in the morning typing [ __ ] I've
seen you [ __ ] over and over and over
again cuz you're little self-p
projectors. That's what you are. Little
self projected people. When are you
going to get a life?
You sad, ugly people. And yeah, I never
said they don't all hate me. Of course
they hate me. I'm better looking than
them. I'm younger than them. I've got
more of a life than them. I got more
bollocks than them. Of course they're
going to hate me.
Put your cameras on, bro. Put your
cameras on. No, you can't do that, can you?
Put your cameras on, lad. Show everyone
what you look like. Show everyone your
weight. Come on.
Madness, bro. Mad.
I'm coming off YouTube for a while.
Yeah, bro. It's the same atmosphere with
these people. I only went back on it
today because, yeah, these comments were
winding me up, bro. And guess what? No
one wanted to meet me. So, yeah.
Come in now then and show everyone what you got.
Yeah, it's bor It's boring as [ __ ]
Triple H, bro. It's boring as [ __ ] It's
just a bunch of fat, ugly life losers
that just hate every day and repeat.
They kill the community, bro. It's boring.
And then even Joseph Ferrara's um even Joseph Ferrar's
is uh is biased as well.
If I was fat and ugly like these people,
they'd have no problem, bro. They all
get on with each other because they're
all the same. Fat, ugly, stinking.
That's why they all get on with each
other. They're they're life's losers.
That's what they are. Life's losers, lad.
So, where's Joseph Ra?
Where is he?
They definitely don't work. They wake up
every morning, right, and then they
think, "Who we going to [ __ ] with today
on YouTube?" They wake up, they
literally wake up at like 7:00 in the
morning, bro. And they just like, they
don't even wash. Then they just [ __ ]
with people and [ __ ] with people and
[ __ ] with people and then they think,
"Oh, who's the next person we're going
to [ __ ] with?"
Yeah. They don't work. These people
don't work, lad. They got no life. They
got nothing. That's why they do what they do.
They'll never admit it, but it is true,
lad. They don't work.
Even Joseph Ferrar's biased. Triple.
Even he's biased.
And I told you exactly how he's biased
in the video. He's [ __ ] biased, bro.
They don't like anyone that's not fat
and ugly like them. That's basically
what it is. Anyone that's better than
them, they're they're jealous of.
Yep. That's what they do. But they've
got all this money. Their life is better
than everyone else's, but they sit on
YouTube all day hating. What do you
know? Eh, all this money, all this life,
running everyone else down, everyone
else's skin, but here they are on
YouTube every single day. So I ask
again, are you saving for a holiday? Are
you saving for a car? No. Okay. So why
are you on YouTube every day?
I'm not going to be on YouTube tomorrow.
And we'll prove it and I'll prove it.
Yeah, they'll be on here Christmas.
They're on here every day, lad. They'll
be on here Christmas. They'll be on here
New Year's Eve because they ain't got a
life. It's simple. They will be on here
Christmas, New Year's Eve.
Been saving for years. Um, I took weeks
off of YouTube. You can't take a day off
of YouTube. Come back to me when you can
take a day off of YouTube.
I've took weeks off of YouTube. Weeks.
Weeks. Multiple times. You can't take a
day off of YouTube. So,
I mean, yeah. Come on. Yeah.
>> So yeah, these people will be on
Christmas. L will be on their Christmas.
Even though they pretend that they don't
go on here, they will be on their Christmas
calling people skin when they're skin
themselves. You know how the cookie
comes, bro? It's their life, isn't it?
These little mongos are not worth it on
here, bro. These little These Mongs are
not worth it on here, lad.
If you really want to get at these
people, just wait until one of them get
doxed. And at the end of the day, just
wait until one of them gets doxed.
If that if you really want to do
something to someone, just wait until
they get docked. That's simple as that.
Don't give them any air time until then, you know. >> Yo.
>> Yo, bro.
So, these people are here on Christmas
day. at Christmas. >> Yeah.
>> No, I don't. No. No way. They'll be on
here on Christmas Day. Christmas about
Christmas about family time and that.
Like you believe they won't be on I
don't think they'll be on Christmas Day. No way.
>> No, they were last year on Christmas Day. >> Really? >> Yeah.
>> I don't know. I wasn't on Christmas. I
was on Christmas Day.
>> Why wouldn't they be on here Christmas?
They've got no life. So what?
>> Christmas is about spend time with your
family and that in it. Like
>> But they don't have family, bro. These
people do not do understand.
>> So what you're trying to tell me is they
don't have one day off a year on this
YouTube. Not one day. The the only time
they're off is when they're sleeping. [laughter]
>> Now you're trolling.
>> Nah, seriously. Yeah. They like you get
Listen, bro. Listen. L and Demlock,
they're going to pretend they're not on
here Christmas. They will act like
they're not, but if someone goes live,
they'll be there, bro. They They are on
Christmas. They were on it last year.
>> [ __ ] me. That's insane, lad.
>> [ __ ] hell. How the [ __ ] did we So
basically they don't have a day off then. >> No,
>> they don't they get bored of it.
>> No, it's their life.
>> Timmy's empty bank account which someone
said you were on last year.
>> No, I wasn't.
>> I know. I've never been on on Christmas
day. I don't think they got all this
money, all this life, but they're sat on
here every day. Mad it.
>> Yeah, I thought you were trolling them
when you said they don't take a day off.
I thought they might have been off for
Christmas dear. Man,
>> I'll go live on Christmas. I I I'll go
live, right? And I'll walk away from the
phone and I'll go to a shop and and when
I come back, I'll end it and I'll show
you who's on.
>> Yeah, man. Yeah, lad.
>> I'll do that this Christmas. Yeah. To
see it and then you'll see who's on in
it and I'll squeeze on it. [laughter] >> Yeah.
>> Have you seen that account, the UK biggest nonser?
Look. Yeah. Yeah,
>> there's some there's some accounts with
Monty's face, isn't it?
>> Of whose face, bro?
>> Monty and Monty's mom. Do you remember
they made an account of Monty's mom?
>> Ah, yeah. They said in your chat a lot a
lot of times, Leslie, that they
>> I thought it was funny like Yeah. But
it's sad when you think about it, is it? >> Yeah.
>> So, you go on Christmas Day, but moan
about the others why go on on Christmas Day?
>> No, I said I'm going to go. He didn't
listen to what I said, did he? The
idiot. I said, "I'm going to go live,
walk to the shop, and walk back. I'm
going to leave my phone here. Then I'm
going to come back. And when I come
back, I want to see who's on there. I'm
going to end it
>> just to see. It'll be on Christmas." Dear, bro,
>> they will. They will.
>> They [ __ ] will. We We'll see, won't
we? We'll We'll stay in it. I I'll put I
don't mind putting a bet on it if you if
you want. I I'll put a bet on it.
>> That's mad.
Now, that is crazy. If they
>> Okay. If I was on YouTube last year, how
do you know I was on it last year? I'll
send that. Okay. Okay. One second. If I
was on If I was on there last Christmas,
how do you know that?
>> That's what I'm saying.
>> Someone said he was on last year cuz it
is warning about
>> How How do they know that though? How
would they know that? Ask them that it
because they're obviously on it
themselves. Is it
bastards in it? Mad last.
>> Oh, that Joseph Ferrar is a bit biased, bro.
>> Ferrar. Yeah, he's used to be all right with you.
>> No, but he's No, but he's biased though,
is it? Yeah,
>> he is biased. He is biased, lad.
>> Mad lad.
>> I will 100% be on it extra stay because
I'm working extra stay and boxing day
earning mega money. Sounds like a
fantasy to me.
That sounds like a fantasy, isn't it?
>> Crazy, man. [clears throat]
>> Working work Christmas day.
>> Nah, but some people do actually wear
Christmas day. Like it's [ __ ] m I
don't wear Christmas day. Like
>> you think these people work? Nah,
>> I think some of them do. Yeah. Yeah.
>> You like 10%.
>> I don't know to be honest with you, but
[ __ ] it's mad.
Yeah, but do you not believe Joseph
Ferrar is a little bit biased though? He
says that he doesn't like liars but he's
constantly on Lord Jan and he's the
biggest liar. So he is biased. Definitely biased.
>> Yeah, that Yeah, he'll probably be all
right with your women, didn't he?
>> Yeah, he's all right, but he's biased.
But he is biased though.
>> You think that'll be on Christmas Day, lad?
>> Yeah, that virgin. He's always on
>> You said you'll get laid if he goes to
Newcastle. That's the one bad fat life
you are. Peter,
>> you said you you'll get him laid if he
goes to New if he goes to Newcastle.
>> Yeah. Or what?
>> You said you'll get him laid.
>> Who? Sean.
>> Yeah. You said if he come, you can get
him laid. Really?
>> I think you should just put all this
behind you, man.
>> No, I don't like that freak. He's Bro,
do you not understand that when you cut
contact with people, you don't want
nothing to do with them?
>> Yeah, but you always talk about each
other, lad. cuz he's because the [ __ ] he
does is mad like the copycat things like
just to be a copycat. I just can't I
don't know. It's weird, isn't it?
>> Mad lad.
>> He was a copycat in it for
>> you. Remember that Kan lad? He used to
be coming. I think he got sick in the
end, didn't he?
>> No, he'll come back. He comes on every
month or so. Yeah.
Yeah, you do get sick of it because it's
boring, isn't it? All right.
>> You know, you like that Grezy.
>> Yeah, Grey's all right. Actually, he's funny.
>> Seems all right. Greasy.
>> What did I say? It's a fedo community in it.
>> There's some people who aren't well in this community.
>> What? They a sick puppy.
Sick sick puppies, aren't they? >> Really? Hi.
>> Bless you. Then
>> Monty, man.
>> You out Saturday? >> I'm out of Yeah,
>> I'm keeping off at
>> Why don't you Don't go out boxing day.
Why don't you just go out New Year's
Eve, bro? It'd be better.
>> I know. I know. When I was in the garage
from you, I was going all year. Like,
>> cuz if you like, think about it, bro. If
you if you don't drink now, you go on a
detox and you just save like you it
you'd be better New Year's Eve, I think.
Me, but up to you anyway. You do what
you want. Yeah.
>> Might feel.
>> Have you ever been to Newcastle on New Year's Eve?
>> Uh, no. No, I haven't actually.
>> I wonder what it's like.
>> It'll be even, won't it?
>> Be what? Oh, yeah. Be even. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Be packed chocolate ch it. [laughter]
Yeah. Be funny, man. Huh? full of funny. [laughter]
>> Yeah, I've been out a few times. New
Year's. You ever have you ever spent in
another place? Nah.
>> Um D [ __ ] I been a borrow as well. Middlesbrough.
>> What? New Year's
>> N as well.
>> Were they Were they Were they playing the fireworks? >> Sorry.
>> Were they Were they putting Were they
doing the fireworks? >> Yeah.
>> Really? Was it Was it busy? Yeah, bro. >> Yeah.
>> Well, bless you then. >> Yeah.
>> What you Why did you go Middlesbr
though? [clears throat]
>> Not far me and all that.
>> It's a [ __ ] old bro. [ __ ] off scary place, bro.
>> Where is the train station?
>> I had to take two trains to go
Middlesbrough. When I went
Middlesbrough, I took two trains.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'm mad going by myself and
that. I was mad for it. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I seen the video. Yeah. Yeah. I
watched the video. You're in Middlesbor like I
>> don't even know why I went. I don't know
what possessed me to go there, bro. I
just booked like an Airbnb in it.
>> How much you pay for that? I
>> think it was only £22. What a night.
>> Did you call that Trevor Dawson out?
>> You didn't come out in it.
>> [ __ ] I heard he's a foul, man. Is it
>> toy said that, didn't he? I don't know.
Yeah, you remembering it. >> Yeah,
>> I'm not doing anything Friday.
>> He's got a list.
>> Ion is stalking me on Reddit. You know
these people are stalking me on Reddit. Triple
>> I've seen that Red Star. Um,
>> no, but it's Gun as well. It's Guno as
>> Oh, is he is he on there as well?
>> Yeah, they're sad people in it.
>> Why do they do this? [laughter]
>> They told you on F YouTube. Sorry,
that's that's it. But like why do they
call you on the Reddit and [ __ ] other
forms of social media? Like you know
what that is? Like it's um what's the
word called? It's uh stalking like harassment. [laughter]
>> Yeah, they're sados, isn't it?
>> Yeah, but you like it.
>> That Jamie Thompson is a sad sad B. I
that that Jamie Thompson's jealous of me, bro.
>> I don't know.
>> The fat ugly one.
>> You've seen him in it?
>> No. No, I don't. But no,
I'm not going.
>> Wait, I already told you I wasn't going [laughter] >> Thailand.
You You will go to Thailand, isn't it?
>> Yeah, I probably would go to Thailand,
me, lad. Yeah,
>> you know people that's been in it. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Been Yeah. Yeah.
>> Well, they are they still there?
BL I used to I used to work with a bloke
and he used to go like three times a year and >> really
>> you'd get laid over there lad easy.
>> Yeah obvious yeah of course you would
>> but people go over and lipstad
is it that is bad has he? >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] hell mad lad.
>> He teaches English.
>> He does what?
>> Oh he got a job over there. Has he?
Yeah, obviously that's how he like Yeah.
He's on a £700 a month, but obviously
£700 a month over there is a lot more, you know,
>> a lot of money over there.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So he Yeah. He has a
girlfriend. He said it's easy to get girlfriend there.
>> Yeah, it will be. There's loads of
[ __ ] brasses and that, isn't there? [laughter]
>> You know that.
>> Yeah. The 71 over there is meant to be
mint as well, lad.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. There was the
80s. Tell me about that. But would you
go by yourself? Yeah.
>> No, I wouldn't go by myself. Probably not. But
>> that's what you done. That's mad. It
>> watches to get away from the UK. [snorts]
>> Did he ever get any stick on here? That ant man. >> Yeah.
>> I wasn't about when he was about me. It
was before my time. That
>> Yeah, they used to call him a nons.
>> Who man?
>> Yeah. I seen a couple of old videos
before them and he he used to be a
gambler, didn't he? I think he used to.
>> Yeah. He lost he lost money in the
bookies. Yeah. And he said, "You take my
money, I [ __ ] take yours." I was dead. [laughter]
>> Yeah. He used to drink a lot as well, didn't he?
>> Well, that Joseph Pra is so bad on the
gambling, isn't it?
>> He always wins, doesn't he?
>> He needs to chit out though, isn't it?
Yeah, but you know, one day it's going
to go bad, is it?
>> He'll do his bars one day. Definitely.
>> It will happen, bro. It will happen. It
happens to That's why I don't touch them
machines anymore. That's why I don't
play roulette or slot mugs game is it?
>> Yeah, there's a lot of [ __ ]
>> You I reckon you'll be on Frankie soon.
>> I don't gamble, mate. Really? And
>> just man, that's all I do. I don't even
play the blueprints in the pubs and
[ __ ] You don't win out too hard. Too
hard to win out on them blueprints, man.
>> Is it okay to put 20 pound in a slot machine?
>> 20 bar in the in a blueprint the pub.
Yeah, but I wouldn't put 20 bar in the
book. Where's the money?
Yeah, I might I might if I go out on
Saturday, I might put 20 pound in
Frankie and just do
>> put 20 quid in Frankie and get 50 B. Few
drinks in it.
>> Yeah, a few drinks. Yeah, I'll just do
50 piece spins in it.
>> Yeah, that's fair bonus. Come get 50
quid. Print the collect the winnings and
then put your 20 bar back in. 30 quid.
There's like a five a pint put up here.
So there's like six pound in it.
>> Yeah, it's a five a pint here. If it's
not central London but local it's like5
so it's cheap isn't it? The place I went
the other day was5 a Guinness cheap bro is it?
>> Yeah it's decent like yeah five up here
but you can get
>> How many do you have again?
>> I can have a good I can have 10. Easy
>> So what £50?
>> Well you could easy have to but you you
So what do you do after what do you what
do you do after the 10? That's it. Um,
no. I go and [ __ ] a Red Bull me
sometimes. But sometimes that's what
Yeah, but that's what get [ __ ]
hangovers and that is it.
>> I'm just going to try and stick to the Guinness me.
>> Yeah, but you you can only drink so
much. Some people know some people who I
drink if they can only have like five or
six and then they blow up. But
they struggle to get them down afterwards.
>> I reckon you should I re I reckon you
should go on the sniff again. Yeah, man.
>> You used to love a bit of sniff.
>> I know.
>> What did you did you when you used to do
you used to do it in home at home alone, isn't it?
>> I sometimes mate I well after I've been
on I used to had some [laughter]
Did you used to approach after it? Nah,
I never I never
I never approach like
been in relationship for I' been five year relationship.
>> No, but when I was talking to you on the
PlayStation, you used to try in it.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I did. Yeah. Yeah.
Mr. What are they saying again?
>> Say that again.
>> So, what happened when you used to try
like before you was in a relationship?
What do they say to [ __ ] just to buy
them a drink and think that I just have
a crack on and there like it's not you
make it out you make it hard. I don't know how
>> because it is struggling and that I
don't understand why I struggle ming.
>> Yeah, but we're in different locations.
>> Yeah, true. That's true. But
>> I had it easier in Newcastle and every
time I went up there, which was only three times.
>> Yeah. You had a bit of luck in
Newcastle, didn't you?
>> Yeah. So, could you imagine I live there?
>> Exactly, lad. You'll be getting put your
left, right, and center.
>> You weren't here, though.
>> Full of stuck up content. London, lad.
>> The only hope is that if you come across
a tourist that's looking for It's just
rare, bro. Is it? It's just rarer. It's just uh
>> that's it there. Asylum videos and road
man things get people up the town. Yeah.
>> Do you remember that? Do you remember
that uh Woody account?
[clears throat] Who? Who? Woody.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. Well, they post Harry.
>> What about security Steve?
>> I think they're all Harry Fraud.
>> Yeah, I think so. Yeah, they weren't it.
>> They They've run that Mark Edwards off.
They've run Eldridge off. Well, Eldidge.
>> No, they're trying to run me off in it.
>> Yeah. They just won't get you and that
money man off, will they? [laughter]
Money man weren't live today, was he?
>> He hasn't been on, I don't think. >> No,
>> he goes on late, doesn't he? Go on like
about 12. He was on last night. I nipped
in last night about 12.
>> So, when you used to go out of
Newcastle, did you used to get stay in a
hotel or did you used to get the last train back?
>> All right.
Good old triple
by UK asylum. Did you see my video on Joseph Ferrar? He's biased.
He's a biased nons lover.
I went to get an Indian but uh yeah the
shop was closed so yeah
they're stalking me on Reddit again. UK asylum.
They're stalking me on Reddit again. Road manings.
Yeah, they're stalking me on Reddit. These people,
they won't leave me alone.
They won't leave me alone.
These people on YouTube are stalking me on Reddit.
This account is called Morgan USA 2023.
They're just stalking me, stalking my
posts and stuff. Yeah,
Morgan USA 2023.
That is sad, bro. These people are so
sad on here. Yep.
Yeah. I'm going to make it. They keep
stalking me. Road man things. I don't
know why they keep stalking me. They
won't leave me alone.
These sad, jealous people won't leave me alone.
They won't leave me alone.
Why do they go for me on this community
road man things? They never leave me alone.
Why do they go for me?
Yeah, [ __ ] bombs on here.
Yeah. an Indian but it was closed so I
don't know what I'm going to eat probably nothing
I think these people are jealous that
I'm younger and better looking than them
road man what do you think
I'm younger and better looking than them. Um, I don't