Okay,
I was going to go live by the way, but I thought I
on a live stream. I was even planning to
go live to be
your comment, bro. No one needs to show you anything.
You people have been showing money
multiple multiple multiple multiple
times and you have already proven how
biased you are which is why no one waste
their time if you don't [ __ ]
little self-reflectors. You've been
embarrassed multiple multiple multiple
multiple multiple times.
I didn't come out of my mom's womb to
prove myself to fat ugly projectors that
I've got nothing in life. Everyone's got
everyone's got a goal in life and that's
definitely definitely definitely not
[ __ ] mine. So, I mean, bro, you you
you've embarrassed us for a change. Show
us money. Show us that you're not fat
angry mother. You show us something for
a change. I bet this would like that
one. You know what I'm saying? Like you want here
talking about a [ __ ] pension that you
can't even touch. Like you're you're
trying to compare financial Oh [ __ ]
Financial circumstances with a pension
that you can't even touch.
So that's not no disposable money.
That's not liquid money. And then you're
trying to think that you're burning
everyone out. And then you're telling
people that they need to embarrass
people. Bro, I am not showing you
disabled people no money. You show that
you're not ugly. You show off somebody
and then come back to me. You start
embarrassing me for a change. Every
single time I've been asking you to come
on here and show your face and you won't
do it. All of these stupid little
accounts. You start showing your face.
You start showing your money and then
come back to me. You biased little [ __ ] mong.
You [ __ ] biased little dick sucker.
We saw that we [ __ ] nonss and l you
[ __ ] little [ __ ]
[ __ ] off you [ __ ] little knobs lover.
So guys, I just had to [ __ ] I just
had to get that out there with this pathetic clown.
That's uh that's his favorite word.
>> [ __ ] little nerd.
>> You You show us money. You show us what
you look like. You show us your cars.
You show us something for a change. You
know, stop asking us to show stuff. We
don't need to prove you people wrong
again and again and again and again and again.
[ __ ] off you [ __ ] little bias nons lover. Oh [ __ ]
That's all I got. Woke up.
Little [ __ ] bias nons.
My mom's got these people are [ __ ]
disabled on here. >> [gasps] [snorts]
>> Guy's a [ __ ] idiot, bro. The guy's a
[ __ ] idiot. Why do you want us Why do
you want us to show you stuff whenever
you show stuff, you never bring it up?
Cuz you're a biased dick sucker. It's
like what Kieran says. Anyone that's not
blocked by nons legs,
they can't be trusted. Why? Why do you
want to be Why do you want to be
embarrassed again? You clearly have no
shame every time you are embarrassed.
money, women, better looks, better life.
Every single time that you're embarrassed,
uh you come back for more because you
have no shame. So when how many times
can you embarrass a person? You know,
you start showing your face, you start
showing what you look like, show that
you're not a fat, ugly mutter, and I'm
talking about people in general, and
then come back to me. I did say I'd
happily show money if you show your
faces. I think I did happily say that
I'll show you money and I'll show you
receipts. And I think that was a good
deal, you know.
Then come back, then come back to me,
you know, a [ __ ] biased audience.
Really? Who's entertaining a biased
audience? Come on, bro. It's [ __ ] stupid.
Guy's a [ __ ] idiot.
So yeah, bro. I was thinking of see the
thing is this is what I'm saying. Yeah,
this is what I would have done 5 years
ago. I would have just put five on the
pound of brunette and gambled. But the
thing is the thing is I don't need to
prove myself to these people. And the
sooner you realize that, the better. You
don't need to prove yourself to these [ __ ] morons.
These [ __ ] morons that ain't got a
life. You don't need to prove yourself
to these people, you know. And this goes
for anyone on here when they're trying
to, you know, self-reflect their life
onto you. You don't need to prove
yourself to these fat ugly people. Yeah.
The [ __ ] the doctor didn't snip the
binnical cord from your mother to prove
yourself to these [ __ ] biased people.
The sooner you realize that, the [ __ ]
better, bro. Anyone who's watching this,
you don't need to show money. You don't
need to show anything to these people.
You know what I mean, bro?
Just self projection every time with
these people. You don't need to show
anything to with these people. [ __ ] idiots.
These people are [ __ ] idiots on here,
bro. [ __ ] absolute clowns on this
community. Look at this person that
commented. said, "Why you run away and
hide all your videos?"
I said, "What do you want about you, moron?"
>> Here we go. 3 months. I posted in
poverty and there
>> you're not in poverty. If you if you get
tw if you have 1,200 pound a month and
you don't have no bills, you are not in
poverty. You are definitely definitely
definitely definitely not in poverty. I
can tell you exactly what I've done in
the past [ __ ] 3 months. You're
definitely definitely definitely
definitely not in poverty. Um I would go
as far as saying that if you had £500 to
last you a month, that's not even poverty.
You wouldn't you wouldn't be able to go
out or do much. But bro, this guy really
has no clue about life. and and the six
people that liked his thumbs up, they're
just they're just idiots on here, you know.
So, it does it does mean that it does
mean that this guy's and he said
anywhere in England. So, if you had your
own place in Sheffield, right, or yeah,
anywhere and and so £1,200 are going to
lost a single person for a month.
They're absolute idiots on here. You
know, these people on here should know
more than me. They're older than me.
They're [ __ ] older than me. They
should know more than me, but they don't, you know. Yeah,
they're [ __ ] absolute idiots. [snorts] Embarrassed, bro.
You people get embarrassed every day.
You've been embarrassed for years and
you still come on here talking [ __ ] So
what's the what's the point? I don't get it. Uhoh. Yeah,
these people are idiots. uh of this community.
This guy is an absolute idiot.
Doesn't know anything about life.
I didn't run away. I deleted my videos
because I'm done with this [ __ ]
stupid [ __ ] weirdo community. But I
thought I'd reply to this clown again.
Why don't you embarrass us for a change?
Why don't you show your face and prove
that you're not projecting the M line
every day? Nope, you won't do that. You
completely ignore all of that and then
ask people to prove themselves to you.
No one needs to prove themselves to you.
Fat, ugly, biased people.
People are clearly virgins still.
They're clearly all virgins even though
people prove they've had sex. They're
clearly everyone's clearly skinn even
though you've been shown money multiple times. So
just just worry about that, bro. You
know what I'm saying?
Just focus on [ __ ] sucking your
boyfriend Nons's dick every time I go at him.
No one cares about that. That's repeating.
You need some new content, bro. That's repeating.
That's so old that I don't even look
like that anymore. You boring people
need to come up with some new material.
This is boring, bro. Come on, man. I
know you can think of some new I've I've
even given you some I've even given you
some tips before to be honest.
Boring repeating same people, same comments. [gasps]
Come on, man. You're better than that.
It's so old. That's That might as well
not even be me anymore. It's boring.
Very very very very boring.
Very very very very boring, man. And
what we submit new it's boring.
So what we submit do? No one no man
could ever treat you like that. I could
do it. Meet me. Well, not today. Meet me
today. I'm busy tomorrow. I'll treat you
like it if you want. Meet me today. I'll
give you my WhatsApp number.
I'll give you my WhatsApp number if you
want. Everyone's got it. But I'll give
you it. I'll treat you like that. Where
do you live?
This is what I mean with you little clowns. No,
don't start something you can't finish.
Right. You've just said that no man will
treat you like that. You're not about
it. I'll meet you today. I'll happily
meet you today and treat you like that.
I'll do worse to you if you want.
So don't don't start making excuses now.
You started it, so let's finish it.
Uh no, no, no. One second. One second,
bro. It doesn't matter. You just said no
man will treat you like that. I'll I'll
meet you today. I will meet you today.
I will meet you today if you want. Okay,
bro. So So you're not going to meet me
today then? So you're talking [ __ ]
Okay, thank you. [snorts] So you're
talking [ __ ] Uh we're just talking
about you. You biased little uh [ __ ] Joseph.
Why do people need to keep embarrassing
you fat bias people?
And I showed a porno and you still call
me a virgin. And you and you're fast
enough to suck up Knots's Not Legs's
[ __ ] dick. It got a girlfriend. He's
got a girlfriend. Ever. Ever since then,
I got put off you and I will never show
you anything again. And even when I
choose to gamble, I will never ever ever
ever show you anything again.
You have every time I was going out, he
was sucking up his dick. Oh, they got a
girlfriend. They got a girlfriend. And
you know I'm right because I heard it.
You never once went on this channel and
defended me. You [ __ ] nons lover. You
na lover. And that's why And that's why
you're not blocked by him cuz you're a [ __ ] nonslover.
You na loving [ __ ] And you was never
And you was never blocked by him ever.
Suck it up his dick. You fat ugly [ __ ]
Yeah. Joseph with your [ __ ] pension
that you can't even touch. You skint
[ __ ] mog. Do not [ __ ] come on here
and try and tell me that I need to prove
you people wrong. Yeah, prove me wrong
for a change. I want to see money. I
want to see looks. I want to see your
misses. Embarrass me. I want to be
embarrassed. I want to be embarrassed
for a change. And I will put the link up
and I and I'll give you I'll give you a
chance to embarrass me. Come on, you na
lover. Come on, you [ __ ] nons lover.
Come on, you nonslegs lover. Come on. I
want to see your misses. I want to see
your face. I want to see everything. I
want to see everything. Embarrass me for a change.
No, but on a serious note. Yeah. You You
have been shown money. You have been
shown women. You have been You've been
shown [ __ ] million and one things.
And you still come on here and talk
[ __ ] And we did not get sniped from
Laney's umbilical cord to come on here
to prove you people wrong. You need to
get that out of your head. You need to
get that out of your [ __ ] head, lad.
Well, you never Well, I didn't see you
on his channel. Um, you know, backing me up.
Well, why didn't you back me up then,
you nodd lover? You're not blocked by him.
Yeah. And you didn't mention the porno
that I put up, did you, on his channel?
You didn't You didn't mention how I was
in bed with someone, did you? You [ __ ] nonsubber.
And I think it's more possible somebody
in a three year relationship
to be a virgin than someone that's
actually proved they've had sex. Believe
it or not, I I think if someone's
actually proved they've had sex like I
have, that's that's even less possible
than someone proving that they've had,
you know, having a girlfriend and he is
absolutely a virgin. Right. Anyways,
Right. Yeah. Well, why were you backing
him up then? Why are you backing him up?
Why are you sucking his dick? Same
question to you then. Okay, same
question to you. Why are you sucking his
dick? Why are you sucking up his dick?
And I can tell you right now that it's
more possible somebody to be in a free
threeear relationship to be a virgin
than someone that's actually proved
they've had sex. If it he don't need
backup either, but you were sucking his
dick. You were sucking up his dick. You
n lover about seven times. About seven
About seven [ __ ] times you done it.
Yes, you did. Sucking up his dick. S.
Oh, we got a girlfriend. You done it
seven times, you little nons lover.
You've done it seven times, you little
nonsubber. Yeah, he doesn't need backup
either. So why are you sucking his dick?
No one need No one needs backup on here.
Nobody needs backup on here. So why are
you going and sucking up his dick? And
ever since then, I knew to never waste
my time on you people again. No, he is.
No, no, no, no, no. I don't care who's a
virgin or not who's a virgin. Why are
you sucking his dick when I'm going at
him and you're not saying anything when
he's going at me?
Why are you sucking his dick when he's
going at me? And he absolutely is a
virgin. I know him better than he knows
himself. He is a virgin. So he is a
virgin and I'm not a virgin.
So So why are you so fast to suck up his
dick seven times? I'm asking you. Why
are you sucking his dick seven times?
But then when he's going at me, you
didn't say anything. So does he need
backup? So what are you are you his are
you his slave or something, bro? You're
a biased little nonslover. That's why I
don't show you people anything anymore.
Money because you're all biased fat
[ __ ] nonslubbers. That's why I don't
waste my time on you. Simple.
No one needs backup. So why are you
backing him up? Why Why are you backing
Why are you backing him up? He's You're
not blocked. You're not blocked on his
channel. You [ __ ] little nonsloving
You [ __ ] nonsel loving [ __ ] You know
you're biased and you know it for a fact
cuz even when you even when I bring up
the L J thing, you say, "Well, other
people have called him out for it."
Other people other people are not you.
Nah, bro. I' I'd bro listen listen.
I'd rather not get my sausage sucked
than be with your fat ugly misses.
You're fat, ugly, misses, mate. I would
never let them hands around my [ __ ]
dick. Yeah, simple.
Yeah, he hasn't blocked you. So why are
you not defending me on this channel
when you're fast enough to defend him? I
don't I don't want you to defend me. I
just think it's a bit weird how you're
fast enough to prove to defend someone
that's not actually proved they've had
sex, but when when he's going at me,
you're you're not saying anything. Why
don't you just not say anything? How is
it not possible for someone to be in a
relationship for 3 years and be a
virgin, but it's possible for someone
like me to to to to You're an idiot.
You're a biased nonslover. And you do it
with Laura J as well. [ __ ] off, you
little nods lover. You [ __ ] little
nods lover. [ __ ] off, you little biased
nods lover. I am not showing you
nothing. You show your face and come
back to me and I'll show you money. I I
I will go to the bank and pull out some
money when you show me your face. How
about that one? You show us your face
for a change.
I'm paying for sex. Really? So I paid
Sig for sex. So I paid the one in
Nottingham for sex. So I paid one on my
birthday one for one night sex. Really?
Really? Really? I paid I paid a
19year-old for sex the first time I met
her. Really? Really, mate? I don't think
so. I don't think so, mate. I don't
think so. But I'd rather [ __ ] pay for
sex than be with what the [ __ ] you're with.
No. No. You just said I pay for sex. I'm
just listing people that I've been with,
mate. So, you need to go to your you
need to go back to your boyfriend's
channel, nonslegs, and talk about, oh,
he's got a disabled girlfriend who he's
never proved he's had sex with, but that
means he can't be a virgin. He can't be
a virgin because he's he's been with a
disabled girl. He's been with a disabled
girl. Uh yes, I can technically if I
wanted to keep trying. Yes, I can. And
I'd rather not have sex than be with a
fat ugly whale that you're with and a
[ __ ] disabled [ __ ] that he's with. I
I've got standards unlike you two, you
know? I've got standards unlike you two.
Why don't you show everybody your
[ __ ] pension again? We'd love to all see it,
bro. I could get sex if I wanted to.
Maybe in a month. What? What's the
matter to you? I don't want a fat ugly
[ __ ] that you've got. Shouldn't you be
sucking legs boyfriend talking about how
he can't be a virgin cuz he's got a disabled girlfriend?
Shouldn't you be on his channel sucking
his dick, you fat bastard or sucking L's
dick? But furthermore, I thought you
said you weren't coming on here anymore.
So, anyways, you people need to start
embarrassing me. I want to see money. I
want to see your face. How many times
have I asked you people to show your
face and prove that you're not the Mer,
but you can't do it. But then you come
back and ask and then you ask people to
show receipts. We people don't need to
show you people anything. That day,
right, since you were sucking N legs's
dick, I was like, "Nah, that's it. I'm
never ever ever prove myself to you
people again." Oh, he got a girlfriend.
They got a girlfriend. He got a
girlfriend. You remember Joseph Ferrar?
You [ __ ] biased little nonsloving
Yeah, you [ __ ] fat nonslover. You know,
[ __ ] nonsloving bastard,
you know. Yeah. £1,200 a month is poverty. [laughter]
You're an idiot, bro. You're an absolute idiot.
You're an absolute [ __ ] idiot. You
ain't got nothing in your Do you know
why I I I I think that you people are
jealous? Do you want to know why?
Because of what you do on here every
day. You wanted to know why I think
people are jealous.
It's because of what you do on here. I
don't think I'm good-looking. I don't
think, oh, I'm younger than you. It's
because what you do on here. That's why
people think that you're jealous. It's
because of what you what you actually do
on here. The obsession, the weirdness.
It's because of what you do on here.
It's acts of a jealous person.
I'm not in poverty, mate. I am
definitely definitely not in poverty. If
I was in poverty, I wouldn't be able to
eat. I wouldn't be able to go out
drinking. I wouldn't be going out
tomorrow. Uh definitely definitely not.
But again, just worry about this pension
that you can't touch.
I don't know. I don't know why he's up
his ass cuz he's a he's a little nons.
He's a little nons.
Oh, he's got a disabled girlfriend, so
he can't be a virgin. But yet somebody
that's put a porno up can be a virgin.
That's what I'm saying. They're disabled
on here. This is what I mean with these
people. They're [ __ ] disabled, bro.
That's why I don't really combo him
anymore cuz they're just disabled. This
is what I mean with them. They're
disabled little nons lovers.
That's what I mean, bro. They're not
even worth They're not even worth
talking to, bro. These people, they
really really are just not even worth talking to.
But I understand it, bro. You know, like
I was saying the other day, it's it's
coming Christmas now. These people ain't
got no family. Their family have
disowned them. I get it, bro. So, it's a
lonely time for them.
So, yeah, I I got a lot of um calls
today whilst I was sleeping
all because of these people on YouTube.
So, yeah, that this is why we think
you're jealous. We think you're uh we
think you're jealous because of what you
do on here. Uh not cuz what I think I
am. So, no, definitely definitely not.
I'm saying that you're you're up nons
legs his ass cuz you are up his ass. Cuz
when I've got at him, you have you have
defended him seven times. You have done
it seven times sucking his dick. So,
this is what makes me think you people
here like nonses.
Cuz you talk about Monty. I don't even
like Monty being a nons, right? Oh, he's
a nons. He's a nons. He's a nons. He's a
They haven't. They've got [ __ ] all. Of
course they've got [ __ ] all, bro. Of
course they've got [ __ ] all.
I've got people that make their life
stalking me. Of course they've got
nothing. They're fat, ugly people.
They're not even They're not even worth
talking to, lad.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Because I've I'm I'm with my mom and my sister Christmas.
Uh that's how I can talk about you people.
So yeah, that's how I can talk about you
people cuz I'm at my sister's Christmas
with my mother. So that's how I can talk
about you people. But it does seem that
the the projection gets strong.
[ __ ] off, weirdo.
And this is what I mean with these
people, bro. This is what I mean. So
yeah. And and we think that you're
jealous. We think that you're jealous
because of what you do on here. I don't
think anything of myself. I I really
really don't. I mean, look, I got my
haircut the other day, uh, yesterday,
and I think I just look normal. No one
thinks anything of themselves. We go by
what you do. We do, we go by your
actions on here. The actions of
40year-old jealous people.
We go by you. We go by you people.
We go by what you do on here. Um, Jamie
Thompson calling me
stalking me everywhere. That's only acts
of a jealous person.
Yeah. Freeze on benefits again, bro. Like, can you
Yeah. Freeze on benefits. Again, you
don't know how much money I have. This
is exactly what I mean with you self-projecting people.
Yeah. Cory, you realize that uh the the
self projection gets really bad um
around December time.
It gets really bad around December with
these um self projectors
cuz they realize they got no family.
They failed at everything in life. It
gets really bad around December time, dad.
So, just be prepared for that.
Yeah, I don't understand why you're so
asked about my life and what I get. Just
worry about your pension and your fat
misses, you little nonslover. That's all
you need to worry about. That's
literally all you need to worry about.
Like you're in your 40s and and you're
still gambling every day like a [ __ ]
loser. And then you're trying to tell me
I can't afford to gamble. You're a
[ __ ] idiot, mate. Like I said, if
this was years ago, I would have just
put £500 on roulette now. But I don't
need to prove myself to you fat ugly
people. And that's something that you
need to understand. People don't need to
show you receipts. People don't need to
show you money. People don't need to
show you fat, ugly people anything. And
the sooner you realize that, the better.
You know, the the sooner you realize
that people don't need to show you fat,
ugly moms anything, the better. Like, it
is actually the better. Yep. [snorts]
So, that's that is it.
Yeah. Well, show yourself then. Okay.
Show yourself. Show yourself.
Yeah. Okay. Show yourself then. I don't
understand how you can criticize other
people when you have a pension that you
can't even touch. You people are [ __ ]
idiots on here.
[ __ ] absolute. These people on here
are idiots. I see why you come off of
here um Cory for a little bit. You need
to reset sometimes, bro. Is it otherwise
you you actually develop brain damage?
What? Same question to you then. What
benefit would me keep proving myself to
bias people bring me?
Same question to you then. Same question
to you. You people keep coming on here
asking me to show receipts for my
things, right? and showing you money
which has been done in the past and
you're all biased. Same question to you
then. Same question to you. You know, [ __ ] [ __ ]
I had someone on here, Cory, trying to
say that I pay off for my jeans and trainers. [laughter]
The jealousy is strong.
The jealousy is [ __ ] strong, bro. Did I mad?
Yeah, apparently I use colon. That's
news to me.
That is madness, lad.
Imagine that. [ __ ] hell. That is a madness.
They said they they said I use Kana. Oh [ __ ]
They said Kana, bro. [ __ ] hell.
[ __ ] Colana, bro. That's hilarious.
That's [ __ ] hilarious, bro. So that's
what I mean. Even when you prove that
you've got more money than these people
or like you can afford things that they can't afford,
uh they just make up stuff.
But don't forget though, um Corby, these
people are not jealous.
No, there's not a fight tomorrow.
I'm not meeting any of you clowns in this community
unless you come on my door
because you're all biased. Simple as
that. Because you're all biased.
Because you are literally all biased.
And I think the only three people that
are not biased are not even on him anymore.
You know, because you're all biased.
You're biased around everything. This is
what makes me think that you're jealous
because of what you do on it. It's not
like I'm just saying stuff for the sake
of saying it, Cory. I'm saying what I'm
seeing. That's why I say that I think it's jealousy.
But yeah, that's the only time I would
to be honest because you're all biased.
You're all biased on here. Well, most of
these people and well, 98% are biased.
You know, I I I I stuck on a bouncer,
Cory. Oh, you know, he can't hit you.
He's at work. Okay. And you show money.
Oh, they ignore it. And then you show
receipts and apparel
and then they try to save Clara. So you
just never win with these fat jealous
people, do you? So yeah,
but I'm not asking anyone to come on the
door. I'm just saying that's the only
way I would fight
because there was literally no I I've
spent a lot of money over the years and
time over the years on these people and
they're just all biased.
They're just all biased. Joseph Ferrar
is a [ __ ] who likes to uh lick
[ __ ] nons's ass multiple times. I
don't know why these people here like nonsers.
Probably cuz they're nons themselves.
But you know Yeah.
He doesn't think, Cory, that it's
possible for somebody to be in a
relationship with to be a virgin to He
doesn't think it's possible to be in a
relationship and be a virgin with a
disabled girl, but he thinks it's
possible to be a virgin even though
you've proved you've had sex. That's
Joseph Far's logic.
Even though I've been in bed with women,
multiple different women, I'm I'm I'm
apparently that's questionable that I'm
a virgin. But if someone's in a
relationship with a disabled person for
3 years, that means they're definitely
not a virgin.
I know it doesn't make any sense, does
it? But that's just these people, isn't
it? That is just these people.
They're idiots, bro. They're really
They're just idiots on this community, bro.
Real idiots. Real [ __ ] idiots.
Yeah, I had a lot of calls like I was um
saying um when I woke up, call after
call after call after call after call.
But don't forget these people are not
jealous. Cory Jamie Thompson's not
jealous. Nah, he's not jealous. Yeah, he
sits on YouTube stalking every day and
we know what he looks like. But nah,
he's not jealous. Of course he's not.
Some people just waste all their life on
other people that that they're better
than. Yeah, that makes a lot of sense,
doesn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. But they're not jealous, don't
forget. Cuz uh well, you're 28 and your
looks are fading by the day, apparently.
So, they're definitely they're not jealous.
See, what I was saying, Cor, is if if
these people was on here, yeah, just
doing their own thing, then I would just
think that they were normal people
like that are just not jealous of
anyone, but it's it's actually what they
do on here that makes me think that
they're jealous because of how much time
it takes and how long they've been doing
it for. And they will never stop. So, it
just proves that it it is jealousy with these people.
You know, Cory, it definitely definitely
is jealousy with these people. Definitely
Joseph Far is a [ __ ] nons. Yeah.
But like I said, if you're not fat and
ugly like these people, they're always
going to pick problems with you. So if I
was fat and ugly, right, and I went on L
JS, they they'd have no problem.
they'd have no problem. They they'd
invite you with welcome armors, but
anyone that's better looking than them,
that's got more family than them, they
get jealous and they do all of this
madness. Hey, Dusty, we was just talking
to uh Joseph Farra about he comment on I
was just telling them how he's biased.
I said, "Oh, so how so why are you fast
enough to his rescue when I'm calling
him a virgin, but then when he's calling
me a virgin, you don't say anything?" He
says, "You don't need backup." Neither
does he need backup, but you backed him
up seven times. You [ __ ] biased nonslubber.
Yeah, he doesn't need backup either. And
he hasn't blocked you from his channel.
And I don't see you defending me once.
So stop telling people that they need to
prove this and prove that to you [ __ ]
losers. You know, you prove that you're
not fat and ugly and then come back to
me, bro. You start showing stuff and
then come back to me and ask me what I
need to prove to you [ __ ] Mongs. Yeah.
1,200 pound is is poverty, by the way.
1,200 pound is poverty.
1,200 pound is poverty, bro. [ __ ]
hell, man. That is madness. I've never
heard such ridiculous [ __ ] in my life.
Really, really, really. They're just
idiots on here, bro. Really just idiots.
Why don't they just do their own content
without trying to compare themselves to
[ __ ] other people?
I just don't understand this
this [ __ ] bro. I really don't. I don't
understand this [ __ ]
That's what I was trying to explain.
It's not even It's probably better than
average, to be honest. It's probably
like 70% good. 75% good.
Yeah, that's what I was trying to
explain to them, Mong. But he doesn't
understand it, bro. He doesn't understand it.
I had 1,700 pound yesterday. Uh, sorry.
Um, last month I've got a bit less this
month, but I still have over,000 pounds.
I can do whatever I want to do.
So, I don't understand why you adjust to
any money you get to a limit. I mean, to
a limit, right? I mean, to a limit you
do. I mean, you're not gonna get used to
300 pound a [ __ ] month, but I mean,
like, you know, if you got five grand,
say you got five grand and then you got
and then you was down to like £1,700 a
month, you would adjust in about 3 months.
You would adjust in about Yeah. 3 months.
Yeah. In about 3 months, you would adjust. Yeah.
It would take you about 3 months, bro.
Yeah. Yeah, no one cares about you. You
little biased nonslover. Yeah, he
doesn't owe me in any way, bro. And no
one's explaining themselves to you [ __ ] nonslubbers.
Well, yeah, cuz you can't you can't pay
rent with £1,200, can you?
You can't pay [ __ ] rent with a pound. Yeah.
So, most people that work are not even
left with that by the time they've paid
everything. Well, maybe
I don't know. 75% people aren't. So, I
don't I don't understand what's the
comparing about. I don't really
understand. If I wanted to go and play
Frankie right now, I could do it right
now in every single bookie in town. You
do not know what people have. It's
[ __ ] ridiculous, bro. Worry about
what you have and then you won't get
embarrassed in the [ __ ] future.
Yeah. But they say that and and it's not
because the and it's not because they go
at me dusty because even if I was to
quit YouTube that only three people
would go at him, maybe three people.
There's like three or maybe three people
will go at him, not everyone. So Monty's
wrong. He says, "Oh, it's because he
goes at you." And it's not because he
goes at me. Cuz even if Monty goes at
me, right? Say if Monty goes at me right
now. Yeah. Say Monty starts calling me
out and everyone's big him up on his
channel. If I start saying that he's a
nons and I start talking about Natalie,
everyone will be on my side as well. So,
they just love nonsers on this
community. That's what they do. They
just love nonsers. And they don't think
that Monty's a nons. They really,
really, really don't. They think he's a
nons. That's why they keep defending
him. Cuz if, like I said, if Monty was
going at me every day and I went at him,
people people mo same people would be on
my side. So, how does that make any
sense? It's because you It's cuz you're the [ __ ]
I think jealous people get along with
other jealous greeneyed monsters. I
think they get along with each other.
Yeah, but okay then. What? Okay then. So
why have people hate him? Do why have
people hate him? Why is Joseph Ferrar
when I call him a virgin straight to his
rescue? Say no, he's not a virgin. He's
got a girlfriend seven times. But then
when he's going at me, he doesn't say
anything and he's not blocked on his channel.
So that's a bit fishy, isn't it, mate?
That's a bit fishy vagina, isn't it? Do
you do you not agree? Cuz they're all
biased on here. This is what I'm saying,
bro. They're all biased on here.
And you might not see it as a problem,
but I see it as a problem because it's biased,
you know, because that's uh
because that's biased.
That is biased, Dusty. It is That is biased.
It is biased.
Yes. But what I'm saying is when I was
calling him a virgin, how many people
have you had come to his rescue saying,
"Oh, he's not a virgin. He's got a
girlfriend." But no one talks about me
putting a porno up and there's no way I
can be a virgin. This is what makes me
That's why I said it was jealousy on
here because of what they do on here,
bro. you know, not because I think I'm
good-look, not because I I don't think
anything of myself, bro. I'm thinking
about what you're doing and that's why
I'm thinking that you're jealous. It's
like I was just explaining before you joined
like what that Jamie Thompson does. I
don't think you understand, Dusty, how
much these people actually stalk me.
They stalk me on Reddit. It's clear as
day that if they're not jealous of you,
they want to [ __ ] you. So, it's either
jealousy or they want your ass. So, it's
one of the two. So,
they're just idiots, bro. They're
absolute idiots. I won't going to go
live today if it wasn't for that [ __ ]
Joseph Ferrar. I need to stop going on
that channel because we just keep having
the same [ __ ] argument.
But like I said, yeah, Dusty, maybe
three people will go at him, LJ
included, but no one else will. L. The
only people that go at him is LJ Harry and
Oh, there was another account. I forget
their name, bro. Uh,
there was another account. There was
another Oh, Trevor Dawson. They're the
only three that go at him, bro. When I'm
not on here. Is there fourth one? I
don't think so. Nah. Nah. So,
yeah. There's three people. Like I said,
bro, you'll get about three people on
here. I'm biased.
Just the same as you'll get three people
that go for him when I'm not on here.
Do you do you understand?
Do you understand what I'm saying? So,
I had a nice news. I had a nice news in
this bed, bro. I was watching some WWE
videos. Oh, and I conked out. I
completely conked her out, bro.
Lush. Absolutely lash, you know. Yeah. Yep.
No, but what I'm saying is when I if
Monty went at me, right, and I went at
Monty, there'd be people on my side. But
if Virgin Boy goes at me and I go at
him, there won't be anyone on my side.
You see the difference?
Do you not see the big difference? But
like I said, greeneyed monsters get
along with other greeneyed monsters.
I love how he tried to retract his
statement when he got caught being a
copycat. That's the funniest thing ever,
bro. He literally got caught being a
copycat and then he tried to retract
what he said,
idiot. You know, you're a little copycat.
I like my haircut, you know. I got I got
it shorter this time cuz when it's too
long, it grows so fast, bro.
It's not about the things I've said.
It's not about the things I've said as
well, mate. These people have been
starting. Listen, listen, listen. Like I
said, right? It's not about the things
you've said. That's an excuse. No, no,
no, no. That's an excuse. Right. When
you when I come on here, when I was 21,
I had people trolling me. Bro, anyone
that's younger and better looking than
them, they're going to go for they're
going to have a problem with. They're
going to pick problems with. It's not
about what you've said. It's not about
what you've said, bro. You know, it is
not about what you have said. own. That
is an excuse, right? Look at the stuff
that Monty said and the stuff I've said.
We still met up with each other. We
forgot everything. It's it's a it's jealousy,
right? What it is with these people,
right, is that they will go at people
they will go at people, right, until
they give a reaction. So, they want a
reaction. Then, when you give them a
reaction, they're trying to say, "Oh,
well, you've said this, bro. Even if you
said nothing, they would still find
problems with you because you're better
looking and you're younger than them and
you've got family unlike them. It's not
about things you [ __ ] said. It's not
about things you've said at all.
You know, that is an excuse. That is a
[ __ ] excuse. Because I, you know,
when I when I first come on here, the
only thing I said was about women.
And people didn't have problems with
what I I said about women. They have
problems with what I said about kids and
they still done their [ __ ] even years
ago. Even when I met Fraser
even before I started saying stuff about
kids when L J started going for Timmy
and I proved that he'd never be fast
enough to come for me. That's I think
that's when I started talking about
kids. Even before that these people was
doing this [ __ ] It's not about [ __ ] you
said about kids.
It's nothing about that at all. They
know that you're not a n. They know that
you're not a pedophile. Look around my
mom's area. They know that I'm not
launched. They know that I'm not a
pedophile. They don't even I even have
kids talk to me. So, it's not about
things you've said. It's that these
people are just jealous that, you know,
you're younger, you've got a life,
you're better looking than them, and
they can't stand it. It's a bit like
what what Ronald Pump said.
The money thing is true, but I don't
think I mean, yeah, I guess that is true
as well if you got more money than than
them as well, but you don't even need to
have loads and loads of money either.
You could just simply have a life.
I can't explain it, bro. And I don't
think if none of these people done what
they done, I wouldn't think that they
were jealous. I I would not think anyone
would be jealous of me. I don't. But
it's what they're doing, bro. Do you not
understand? It's only acts of a jealous
person. This is what I'm trying to
explain to you. But yeah, it's not about
things you've said. It's definitely not
about things that you've said.
It's not about things that you've said,
bro. Just like the women [ __ ] is not
about things you said. Look how many
women [ __ ] you over before you started
saying that [ __ ]
You know, like that USA is I started
[ __ ] with her after she done what she
done. So it's it's not that. It's not
that at all.
what probably happened. I can't remember
exactly what happened, but I probably
come on here complaining about women and
then you had white knight simps
attacking me and then I just said, "Oh,
[ __ ] you. [ __ ] women." And all of that
and then this escalated from there. So,
there was definitely people bothering me
before I said anything. I know that for
a fact because on PlayStation, there was
none of this kid [ __ ] You can ask
Monty, you can even ask the skin virgin
in the bed [ __ ] with no bed in it that
there was no
There was no kid talk. Me, Monty, we, no
one spoke about kids.
No one said they're going to do this to
women or kids. No one said there was
none of this what's on it now on that community. So,
I don't know exactly what people have
said, but yeah.
You always get jealous people, jealous trolls.
So, it doesn't it doesn't really matter, bro. Cuz
if you're still if you're still clinging
on to what people have said, that's
clear signs of autism, bro. And how I
know this is cuz I've got a sister and
she was mad when she but now she's she's
just like whatever. So
yeah, it is that that's just an excuse,
bro. Kids and [ __ ] is just an excuse in
almost 2026. It's it's it's an excuse
now, you know.
Hey, Triple. I went to the barbers. I
got my haircut yesterday. Ready to go out tomorrow.
Yep. I had a lovely snooze, so I can't wait.
Yeah. I had to get a trim, bro. My hair
was getting really long.
Yep. I don't know what I fancy to eat today. Dusty,
I'm going to meet someone on Saturday.
I'm confident I'm going to meet someone
on Saturday, Dusty,
because Reddit told me I would.
Yeah, Reddit told me I would.
I had this pro I had a problem with a
with a woman on uh Reddit again
yesterday, Dusty. We was talking and
she's like, "Oh, I don't know what
they're doing. I don't know." It's like,
I just don't understand.
I just don't understand the sugar
coating for it. I really really don't
understand the the the sugar coating.
Just I'm not I don't want to keep doing
this again. I just if someone's done
wrong, can can you just say that they've
done wrong like that? That you don't
need to sugarcoat stuff saying, "Oh,
they you know, they did they I don't
know why they do it." You know,
why they think that women can't do no
wrong? I I just don't know, bro. What's
wrong with them? I don't know what's
wrong with these people, Dusty. Why they
really think women can't do no wrong?
It's like I keep saying, it's not the
worst thing leading someone on. It's
[ __ ] But just admit you've done it. I
don't know why they make excuses.
They're scared of taking any bit of accountability.
Nah, not tonight, bro. Tomorrow.
Yeah, I got my haircut yesterday cuz I
thought, yeah, [ __ ] it, why not? No, tomorrow, lad.
And then next week,
still thinking what to do New Year's
Eve, bro. I was thinking of maybe going
Nottingham or I don't know what I'm
doing, bro. I really don't know what I'm
doing. I was going to go France, but
then I might as well just go to [ __ ]
France in in March.
Like, I feel like it's just better if
you went in March.
It just seems more it makes more sense
to to go and watch March cuz if you go
New Year's Eve Yeah.
It's like £300 for a day with a hotel.
So by the time I'm spending money that's
like 500. Yeah. Or and obviously things
are going to be a lot more expensive
because New Year's Eve or you can just
go in March and stay two nights for like
250. That's two nights and then probably
spend the same and the weather's better.
I don't know. I think just March would
be better to be honest.
Then I was thinking of Manchester, but
then you can't get any trains to Manchester.
Yeah, Nottingham. There's a good deal in
Nottingham, but I don't know what I
don't know what I'm doing, bro. I don't
really feel like leaving London again.
Like in here in this country, I don't
know, bro, what I'm doing. Edinburgh. I
was looking up Edinburgh, Dusty. Yeah,
the [ __ ] hotels were like 500 quid.
[ __ ] that, bro. If that was if that was
like cheap enough, if it was like 1601
170, I would probably went there to be
honest. They're like450 pound, bro. The hotels
I would not pay. Well, in this Well, in
this country, I think the most I've ever
paid was about 174 and that was leads. I
don't think I'd ever I don't think I'd
ever pay more than 170 for in this
country. If another country, I would.
Bro, they were like [ __ ] pound like normal hotels.
That's ridiculous, bro. That is
ridiculous. Why would anyone do that, bro?
So, New Year's Eve is like,
it's just too expensive, bro. Like, it's
not worth it.
It's not worth it, is it? No.
Well, it's definitely definitely not
worth it, bro.
But with Nottingham, you can get a nice
hotel. The trains for 150, which I don't
think is bad. And it's a really good
hotel. I don't think that's bad. 150.
But I don't know. I'll probably just
stay in London. [ __ ] it.
Yeah. So you go in March, it's like 270
for 2 nights. So that just makes more
sense. And the weather's better.
Yeah, it makes more sense. Just wait
until March. Definitely do these guys
somewhere in March.
I'm not out tonight, Captain.
I'm out tomorrow.
Don't know how many numbers I'm going to
get because I'm only staying local. But
like I said, I'll be up next week anyways. Well, yeah.
How are you going to lose it? How are
you going to pop it?
>> Yeah. I want to play some pool.
I could go out today, but then I'd
rather just save myself for tomorrow, you know. [clears throat]
>> [clears throat]
>> Put one more for that. Oh, [ __ ]
I just thought it made more sense to get my haircut yesterday,
but that's why I did. Oh,
buy some fried chicken today, Dusty.
I'm going to go to my favorite chicken shop.
Okay with you, boss.
Where's Greavves? I hope he's all right.
I hope he hasn't had a heart attack.
Let's see little heart.
I'm probably going to clean my um pillow
slipped, you know. I like fresh pillow slips.
I got a haircut on that, you know.
I slept like a bubba. Oh gosh. >> Yeah.
My little friend in Scotland said the
same thing as well. So they must be
right on Reddit. I'll take their advice. Dusty.
Yeah. Oi Ricky Millington. Triple H. I
saw that account comment on my thing two days ago.
I triple Ricky Millington. [laughter]
Ricky Millington triple.
It goes on timies as well, would it?
Rickster, I call him. Yeah.
[ __ ] Do Fra.
Joseph Far is a little nods. Triple H.
I wouldn't trust him around your kid.
He's probably the new Jimmy Savo.
He's probably the new Jim Jimbo Savile.
Yeah. I don't know who it is though,
bro. I never let Joseph Ferrar around
anyone's kids, bro. He's He's a proper non lover. Rickar Millington.
I like Rick Star Millington.
Are you out today, Captain
Triple H? Are you out today, Captain?
Yeah, like I said, I'll be out um
tomorrow, even though I got my haircut yesterday.
Looks better, but it it looks better
after a couple days, you know.
Oh, Thursday. Yeah, you like Thursdays
like me, don't you, Captain? I would
have went out, but obviously I'm
planning to go out with my sister in it.
So, I would have No, I don't think I
would have went out yesterday. It was
raining yesterday. It would have It
would have even been yesterday or today, but
Yeah, you can. Uh,
how much did you spend, Captain?
How much did you spend, Captain? like 2030.
How much did you spend yesterday,
Captain? I'm not sure. Oh gosh. Go away.
What did you do?
>> You silly geese. 80.
That's not bad then, is it? Captain,
did you meet any birds? Did you meet any pals?
That's how much I'll probably be
spending tomorrow. 80.
Yeah, I'll probably be spending 80 tomorrow. Yeah.
Bless you. Long as you had fun though,
Triple. As long as you had fun, lad.
Bless you in life. Bless you.
Long as you had fun. Bless.
Bless you then.
Bless you then, Captain.
I need to get some food in a bit, bro.
I'm [ __ ] hungry. I don't know what to
get. Triple. I don't know if it's going
to Nando. I haven't been Nando for ages.
I ain't been to Nando for a minute, bro.
Like a minute.
My god. Nando, bro. I can't lie. I ain't
been Nando since I was with my sister
months ago. I used to hammer it all the
time. Yeah. I think I'm going to Nando.
I'm going to go Nando.
I'm going to get two sides. I think I'm
going to get half a chicken and two sides. Okay, boss.
Triple H. Okay with you, Captain.
I'll walk there and then [ __ ] get a bus back.
Okay with you, Captain.
Okay with you, boss.
Make it so.
Why do video to the virgin?
Should I go Nandos? I can go five guys, but then
I really want to eat in somewhere today.
I don't know, bro. I don't know.
Thing is with fried chicken, it's really
bad for your skin, isn't it?
Yeah, fried chicken is really bad for
your skin. Triple
I don't know. I don't know what to eat,
bro. That's annoying when you don't know
what to eat.
They'll be back later. Yeah. Peace out.