Yo.
Yeah. I was just sat here thinking, right?
I was thinking about what's the point of
being born with a dick if you can't use
it. I'm actually lying in bed. I sent
Antman a voice note about this and I
generally don't know what's the point of
having a dick if you can't use it and
you have to put yourself through so much
[ __ ] and heartache just to be able to
get laid. I'm just I'm just wondering
what what's the point
really because if you if you was born
with no dick and you had to pee in a
bag. I mean it would be better if if if
you knew that you'd have to approach a
million people in order to even get sex
once and then get [ __ ] over in the end.
Sorry. This is what happens when you're
in the minority. You see, this is what
happens when you're when you're in the um
10% minority, you know, that's trying
more than, you know, most people in the
world. These these these things pop up.
I'm sorry, Dusty. You got understand
it's a bit it's a bit biased, son. I
know it's a bit boring and whatever, but
the thing is, bro, like you have to
understand that I've um I've been
through a lot of [ __ ] with these women.
So, occasionally this is going to
happen. You know, this is going to pop
up and stuff like a bit like how people
have like people that have been bullied
or stuff like sorry, this is this will
happen sometimes, bro. I can't help it,
you know, cuz I'm not like a normal
person that's, you know, just tried like
a a few times and stuff.
So, it's going to it is going to happen
sometimes, bro. So, it's just the way it
is. When you've when you've had bad
experiences that I've had and the amount
of tried, it's inevitable that it's
going to pop up. You're not a normal
person that's only tried a couple
[clears throat] of times. Sorry, man. I
was just I was just wondering to be honest.
I I have to go out tomorrow, bro. I
really don't want to go out tomorrow,
Dusty, but I'm going to have to. I can't
let people down. So, if it weren't for
my sister, I wouldn't be going out
tomorrow. See, bro, this is what
happens. I think about it, and the more
I think about it, the more you think,
nah, there's no point.
And I was talking to Ant-Man about this.
And I'm thinking like, what what is the
solution to this?
And then I was think and then I said to
him, and I and I generally think that
the only way out of this is is is
joining the porn industry or going to Thailand
where you're treated better, better
weather. I I don't generally don't see
any other way out.
I generally unless you want to go on the
street for 2 months and disrespect
yourself. So I mean it's
I generally wish there was a way out of
this bro. Honestly I wish there was.
Yeah. a month, two months, you can well,
you can live there cuz this ain't a
life, bro. This really really like if I
hadn't tried the way I tried, then I'd
be blaming myself. I'd be like, "Okay,
yeah, you haven't tried." But
it's really, really, really, really
depressing. I mean, you can live there.
Well, no, you go on holiday there and
then if you if you like it, you can live
there. You can teach English. You can
earn £700 a month. Do what Ant-Man does.
cuz at this point something has got to
give. You know, I don't mind going out
tomorrow with my sister and you know
whatever, but after that, bro,
I really really don't want to do it anymore, bro.
You know, I've done what I've had to do.
I shouldn't even have to be trying again.
And I was saying the same I was saying
to Antman, like, you don't understand,
bro, that I've tried. You've only tried
10% of what I've tried. Not that it's a
not even that it's not that it's like
for you know it's a competition thing
but it really is never ever ever going
to change in this country bro.
It really really really isn't.
So that's that.
So you either join the pool industry or
you or you live in Thailand. That seems
to be the only way.
Cuz it will never change here bro. Never.
You'll just keep getting bad
experiences. Bad experiences. Bad
Sucks to it, bro.
So the these things are This is going to
occasionally happen, lad.
This is going to occasionally happen. Oh yeah.
This is why I stayed in so long before
because you think about, oh yeah, let me
go out. Let me go out. And then the more
you think about it, the more you think
about your experiences,
the more you go against it. So
that's why I stayed in for so long, for
as long as I did.
I think we're 5 weeks now, though. It's
getting longer and longer and longer.
It's getting longer and longer and longer, bro.
It's really, really bad.
I wish I could be like these people. It
doesn't bother, but it does bother me
cuz of my history.
And that's what's always going to be
different about you and these other
people is you've got this history. So,
no matter what anyone tells you, you
know your bad experiences.
Hey, UK asylum. I was just wondering,
yeah, what's the point of being born
with a dick if you can't use it
or you have to go through disrespecting
yourself, a lot of effort, and a lot of
money to use it. Like, you might think
I'm taking a piss. You might think I'm
trolling, but I'm not. I actually
messaged a couple of a couple of my
friends, right? I said to them, like,
not to sound weird or anything, yeah,
but what's the point of being born with
a dick if you can't even use it?
like to its full potential.
Obviously, they know my history and
stuff. I just want to know like what's
the what's the point? You can't meet
anyone. You can't meet a normal person.
Nah, you'll never be happy in this country.
So, I either have to join the porn
industry or go or live in Thailand.
That seems to be my only way out. That
seems to be the only way to win at this.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. But you
you're never going to meet anyone. Well,
that's what I'm saying. But you're never
going to meet anyone. So, what was the
point of you having a dick if you're not
going to use anyone? You're not going to
meet anyone. Sorry. Use anyone. You're
not going to meet anyone.
What's the point of being frustrated and
being depressed every time you do try?
Like, I'm not even joking. I'm being
deadly serious. I was lying down
thinking about this. I was messaging
some people that you're never going to
meet anyone. If it wasn't for my sister,
I wouldn't be going out tomorrow.
I would not be going out tomorrow, bro.
If it wasn't for my sister.
So, and obviously I can't let people
down. So, I don't mind putting up with
it and stomaching in it one more time. But yeah,
you can't meet anyone though, Grezy.
That's the thing. You can't meet no one.
And look at I was talking to this woman
on Reddit. She said that she didn't kiss
anyone for 5 years, but now she's in a relationship. So,
you didn't kiss anyone for 5 years.
But it doesn't bother people like that
because people like that, it's their choice.
they they have a choice in the matter
whereas you well
you you do have a choice and you don't
have a choice. It's it's it's a funny
one because yeah you might find someone
if you approached every day for like a
month but good luck with that finding
the energy to do that. So it is it's
more what you would have to go through
to even have an option. I think I think
that's what what what what it is to be honest.
It's weird. It's it's like an in between
one. So with them people it doesn't
bother because if they don't want it
then they don't want it. So it doesn't bother people.
They can just live off the attention. Do
you know what I mean Grezy? They could
just live off the attention.
It's like if you're in Thailand and
you're having sex all the time, you
won't you won't care about sex. You
don't want it today. I don't want it
today. And you could probably go for it
without a long time because you know if
you wanted it, you could have it. So the
attention and you could just live off the attention.
See, I know what I'm talking about. I
know these I know these things.
So yeah, be getting more bad experiences
tomorrow. Wish me luck, Grezy.
More bad experiences tomorrow.
If I get one number, I'm just going to give up.
Nope. If I get one number tomorrow,
Greavves, I'm not going to get any more.
As long as I've got one, I can say, you
know, I've tried and that's it. And then
the rest I just want to have fun. If I
can just get one solid number, then I'm
not going to get anymore.
Is that better for you?
No, I do have memories. I do have
I do think the dating game is unfair.
And don't forget, I'm in the minority as
well. So, it's worse for me.
So, yeah. See, if I didn't approach or I
didn't try, then I could blame myself
all day long. But I can't even blame
myself. That's the thing. At this at
this point, you can't even blame yourself.
I I literally can't even blame myself.
That's the worst thing about it.
You can't even blame yourself. That's
the worst thing about it, you know.
Yeah. I can't go out drinking tomorrow
and not approach, bro. That's
I couldn't do that. I could not I could
not do that.
I could approach and get one number and
then give up after that. But I I
couldn't not cuz that to me is just
I don't know. I've I just wouldn't do it
without approaching, you know.
I don't know. I don't No, I wouldn't do that. So yeah.
Yeah. This woman says she's dating someone.
Yeah. You either need to go to Thailand
or you need to join the porn industry.
I don't see there being any other way
out of this to be honest.
It's mad how it has to come down to
that. You can't just meet someone. You
can't just meet someone naturally.
Bad, isn't it?
Bad, bad, bad, bad, bad.
No, it's not the same as escorts because
you don't have to use a condom.
It doesn't matter, bro. It's better than
nothing. It's better than nothing.
Escorts are better than nothing.
Yeah, of course there's no Yeah, but
it's better than nothing, isn't it?
Think about it, lad. It's better than nothing.
Anything's better than nothing. That's
better than nothing, isn't it? So,
it's better than nothing.
Could you imagine? I had to worry about
money as well. Oh, Jesus Christ. [ __ ]
that. Could you imagine?
Could you imagine have to worry about
money on top of this? [ __ ] that [ __ ] bro. Really
care to elaborate.
I think it's bad to be honest with you.
I think it's bad. Really bad.
Really, really bad.
I wouldn't mind if I hadn't tried. Then
I could be like, "Yep, I'm the blame.
I'm I'm You know what I mean? But that's that.
So, if I get one number to mine, and
after I get one number, I'm I'm not
trying anyone else. I just want to go
and chill, you know?"
Yeah. But Alicia needs to get satisfied.
I don't know how you would beat someone
nowadays. I think you'd have to be like
a footballer or something. I generally
think you'd have to be some sort of
footballer, bro, like Ronaldo or someone
like that. I generally think like that's the only
way you could find someone
is if he was like some billionaire now,
bro. I generally think if he was someone
No, they don't. Not all of them, bro.
Not all of them.
So, why do people on Reddit keep saying
I'm I'm going to meet someone then?
Well, maybe they do, but I haven't seen
it, bro. What the [ __ ]
Yeah. I don't think I'd go out
for a long time, bro.
If it wasn't for Yeah.
You reckon I'll meet someone even though
I've been trying for six years and
haven't met anyone?
Even though I've been trying for years
and years and years and met thousands of
women. Very, very, very unlikely, bro.
You must not know about my history.
Only people that say that are people
that dismiss my struggles. So, you
generally think, okay, okay, let's let's
go by this logically, right? So, been
all over the country, been trying years,
met thousands and thousands and
thousands of women, haven't met anyone.
And you think the next time you go out,
you're going to meet someone? Really?
Considering I've tried more than 90%
of people in the world, 90 95%.
What's really the chances
in almost 2026? I don't think you're
going to find someone cuz if you would
have, you would have found someone by
now. And it always goes because when
someone's got a history like me, it
always goes back to well, you would have
found someone by now with all of that
traveling, with all of the approaching.
Okay. And if you keep trying, you still
won't meet anyone.
Yeah. And if you keep trying, you're
still not going to meet anyone. So, it
doesn't matter whether you give up or
you don't give up. Cuz even if you try,
you're still not going to meet anyone.
I've not had a date since April. So, right.
I'm not so sure. I reckon if you was
going to meet someone, you would have
definitely met someone by now.
Again, you're dismissing the fact that
I've been up and down the country and
have approached thousands of women. You
are dismissing my struggles cuz anyone
that wasn't dismissing it would not tell
you that you're going to meet someone.
Right. Any thoughts on the me going up
and down the country approaching
thousands of women? No. Just just
dismiss it. Right. That never happened,
did it? I'm pretty sure if you was going
to meet someone, you would have met
someone by now. I'm fairly fairly confident
with the amount of ev with the amount of
approach and I've done I'm I am
confident you would have met someone by
now. I'm fairly confident.
But you you clearly are dismissing it
because you wouldn't be telling people
that they're going to meet someone. You
wouldn't be telling someone you're going
to meet someone. I have not had a date since April
and I'm like 26 numbers in. I don't
think you're going to meet someone.
I I generally don't think you're going
to meet someone, bro. I think if you said
I don't know uh meet someone really,
bro, come on now. I mean, well, you will
meet someone technically every time you
approach, but will you get in a
relationship? Will you have a sex life?
Absolutely no way.
Just like that guy in Little Britain
says. Absolutely no way.
Greavesy. Absolutely no way. No chance.
If you're very very very very lucky, you
might get a date that friend-zoned you.
I think you might get a date that friend-zoned you.
I wonder how much money we have spent
and how many approaches we've done
since the last date.
Sums it up quite well to be fair.
No, you're not going to meet someone,
bro. No way.
And it's better off not trying, Dusty,
because you already know the result. So
why are you trying when you already know the result?
You're just creating more bad experiences.
And the more bad experiences that you're
create, well, not creating, but
experiencing, the more bad experiences
you're you're experiencing, you're going
to lose hope more and more and more more and more.
You understand? So,
sounds like I'm being awkward and that,
but I'm not, bro. Like, I'm I'm being
difficult, but I'm not.
It is false hope. You're never going to
meet a woman. You're never going to meet
anyone. It doesn't matter what anyone
said. You know, anyone says, "Bro,
that's why I'm so like lazy. I can't
even be bothered to try anymore."
But like I said, I'll be out tomorrow
and it'll be a oneoff. So,
it's lucky I got my haircut yesterday,
otherwise I wouldn't be I mean, I got my
haircut in it. It was a day out. So, I
can just go out. But then that's me done
for a long time.
And it's not money dusty. I can afford
to go out whenever I want. I can do
whatever I want. Nothing to do with money.
Yeah, I'm going out because my sister
wants me to go out and I don't want to
let people down. So, I kind of have to
go out. I wouldn't be going out if it
weren't for my sister.
So, if it wasn't for my sister, I
wouldn't be going out.
And this place is like, I've got nothing
to lose by just going into town and drinking.
I've got nothing to lose. I'm not going
central London. I'm staying local. This
is the first time I've stayed local in years
and I don't want to let people down.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be going out.
Yeah, good one, Triple H. We're not
going over that again.
No, I am approaching tomorrow. I have to
approach tomorrow. I'm drinking. Why
would I go out and not approach?
But if I get one number, I'm quitting.
If I As soon as I get one number, I'm done.
I'll get one number and that's it.
Yeah, I'll get one number and then
that's me done.
Or even a Snapchat and then that's me done.
There's not going to be keep doing it,
doing it, doing it, doing it, doing it.
So yeah, and he's play and yeah, I'm
going out tomorrow. Nope. So, yeah.
What do you want me to do, Dusty? Go on
the street and approach every day.
No, not even a seven out of 10, Dusty. I
don't know what it is with you bloody
bastards and you seven out of 10, bro.
Even the fours and the fives have attitude.
Even 40y old women have got attitude,
bro. I don't know what is it with you
and these seven out of 10. They've all
got attitude. whether they're a one out
of 10 or a 10 out of 10.
You know, do you know what I'm saying, Dusty?
It's not They're not only sevens and
tens that have attitude, you know, bro.
They've all got attitude.
They've all got attitude. 20 year olds,
18y olds, 30y olds, 40y olds,
50 year olds. Maybe maybe when they're
50 they don't have attitude. But yeah,
they've all got the same attitude, bro.
No, even they'll reject you.
When will you learn that you're talking
about yourself and you need to get off
of YouTube and stop self projecting
cuz you are single.
Single people telling other people that
they're going to be single forever. Self projection.
Self projection by fat ugly people.
Well, that's never going to change. I
don't understand how they can call you
when they're single themselves.
And then when you're calling them, they
they they pretend they can't hear it.
Bro, you're stinking and you're single,
you fat ugly [ __ ] Go self-reflect on
another channel, [ __ ] So, yeah.
There's literally nowhere to turn, bro.
It's It's a sad I just wish I was born
in another country.
I wish I was born in Thailand
or I lived in China or somewhere, you
know? This is no life for anyone, bro.
There's This is no life for anyone.
There ain't no life for anyone here,
bro. Telling you. Yeah.
And it's the experiences that are
depressing as well. It's not even one
anyone. It's the bad experiences.
They're so depressing.
I need to leave this country, bro. Oh yeah,
I'll be having some more bad experiences
tomorrow. Can't wait.
Wish me luck. More bad experiences tomorrow. So sed one sec.
It's bad, ain't it, lad? Imagine
people that have to work as well, Dusty.
People that actually have got a but uh
and they have to go to work. [ __ ]
Bad, isn't it?
It's really bad, bro.
More bad experiences tomorrow. Yay. Can't wait.
I can't wait. Dusta, more bad
experiences tomorrow with women. Yay. [ __ ] off.
Laney says they're not all the same. Dusty
Yeah, Laney says they're not all the same.
Yes, they [ __ ] are.
Yes, they [ __ ] are the same.
They all Um,
oh, there we go. Got banned on Reddit.
It will never change in this country.
It's not about luck. It's never going to
change. Luck is putting money on
roulette and hoping you win. Luck is
putting money on the football and hoping it wins.
It's not about luck. It's impossible.
And I've been banned on Reddit now, by
the way. Sir,
why do these Reddit mods ban people,
Dusty, even when you don't post stuff?
Is it a power thing?
Why do they need to feel in control,
bro? It's [ __ ] sad. These Reddit
moderators are [ __ ] sad, bro. Sucks it.
It will never be different.
No, I just message people. I just
private message people and a couple of
hours later they ban me.
No, I just message people. I don't post
stuff anymore. There's a few reasons
why. Because these people on here stalk
me and the gay Reddit mods.
It seems like it is a power thing.
They they they banned my IP. They they
flagged up my device. So when they ban
you, they ban your IP.
But they still have to manually ban you
when it when it pops up.
I don't know, Dusty. It seems like a
power thing to me.
Depressing, bro. Is it?
This is enough to put anyone in depression, bro.
I don't know.
It's so sad, isn't it? Grezy. Yeah.
They say you meet people on Reddit.
They told me I'd meet someone grievy.
That's what people on Reddit told me.
I blame you, Grezy.
Yeah, I I blame you, Greasy.
>> [clears throat]
>> sucks it, bro.
So depressing, bro.
Because people on Reddit told me that
I'd meet someone years ago. Greasy.
That's that, bro.
Yeah. You got You got more chance of
winning the lottery, mate.
It doesn't matter what I want. Does it
matter what I want? It What you want doesn't matter.
If you want a relationship, you're not
getting a relationship. If you want sex,
you're not going to get sex. If you want
love, you're not going to get love. If
you want a child, you're not going to
get a child. So, does it really matter
what someone wants?
It really doesn't matter what anyone
wants cuz you're never going to get it
in this country.
>> Nah, it's never going to change
you. It's always going to be the same in
this country. It's not gambling, bro.
It doesn't matter because it's never
going to change. And if you didn't
dismiss my struggles,
I mean, I put an approaching video up last month.
Did you watch it? The one in Liverpool
Street where they all was pretending
they had boyfriends. Did you see it, Dusty?
Luck and fate. I'm pretty again, this
has been going on for years. Okay, Dusty.
And trying does.
Yeah, I agree with you. So, you think
I'm always right? Okay, so moaning about
it don't change it. Okay, so does try
and change it.
Trying just makes it worse because you
just get more bad experiences and more
and you come across more toxic women.
So, what what is the solution? Leave. >> [snorts]
>> What the [ __ ]
Whoa. Am I lying?
One second, man.
I haven't tried for five weeks.
Yeah, but the thing is Dusty, I haven't
tried for 5 weeks and it's not because
of money. So, I'm getting there, aren't
I? I'm really getting there. Yeah, Greasy.
Greasy. Somebody asked this person on
Reddit, "Why did you give up with
dating?" And they replied saying, "If
you if I hear I'm not looking for a
relationship one more time, I'm going to
go on the [ __ ] watch list.
I know how they feel, bro.
Listen, if I hear that one more time,
I'm going to go on the watch list.
Yeah, because people are sick of
repeating in it. Kind of like that comment. [laughter]
Yeah, it's true. Yeah, they're repeaters, bro.
So, what's the new copycat statement?
Well, a new one's been made, has it? Wow. [laughter]
What? A new copy statement has been
made. [ __ ] don't let [ __ ] Don legs
[ __ ] know. Don't let that [ __ ]
copycat know. You know he likes to
follow the crowd. [laughter] Yeah.
Because I've been with because I've been
with in because I've been with escorts.
Huh? I'm not an incel
because I've been with escorts.
Am I reading right, bro? I've been with
more than escorts. I've been with many
normal women. I'm an unbiased person. I
know I'm not an incel and I've been with
more than escorts. I've been with normal
women. I'm an unbiased person that can
tell you what it is. I I'm not a copycat.
I'm not one of these people that say
women don't owe you nothing. women
change their minds as you know that as
you know Grezy I'm not a copycat
and I've been with modern escorts I've
been with normal women that weren't escorts
so I don't know why you're saying I've
been with escorts I've been with normal
women as well who I didn't have to pay
but I did forget you are biased on it so
I don't I don't take Yeah
I'm just people that can't defend
Yeah, the hate you have for women is mad.
Same conversation again. The bad
experiences I've had.
Well, you would hate them after the bad
experiences you've had. Again,
dismissing my struggles. See, you're
saying that people don't dismiss your
struggles. Of course, you would hate
them because of your experiences with
them. And this is where it goes round
and round and round in circles. Greasy.
This is exactly what I was trying to say. uh
no matter how many times you tell them
your experiences it don't suit them it's
like you're talking to one second I need
to find this name as well
why are you talking about escorts when
I've been with normal women
or or not escorts.
Huh? What are you talking about? I'm I'm
just not an asslooker.
I can see right through them. I don't
have to defend them to I don't c I don't
follow the crowd.
See, when you're when you're explaining
your experiences, you might as well be
talking to that. Look,
you might as well be talking to that. Look,
you'll get more sense out of this.
than a struggle dismisser.
You get more. You're saying that you
hate women. Yeah, I've spent the past 40
minutes explaining my experiences with him. S white night.
White night. White night. White night.
Yeah, grievy. If you don't think women
are perfect, you're an incel.
If you don't lick their asses, they name
you as an incel. Lad, that's just
calling like calling a woman a [ __ ]
Yeah, it doesn't really mean much, you know.
Why are you saying that you've been with
escorts, though? That's weird. I've been
with normal women that were escorts.
Doesn't mean you can't have an opinion
on what they're like. I mean, I've I've
like I've been giving people the benefit
of the down doubt for years. Week in
week out, week in week out. What do you
want? What else do you want someone to think?
I don't know what else they want you to think.
Nah, no one gets to me. I just don't
know why you're dismissing my struggles.
They should call me Peter Belly dismisses struggles.
No, you said that the hate for women I
have is mad and I'm trying to tell you
my experiences that you keep ignoring.
What else would you like me to think?
I'm and I'm asking you a question. What
else do you want me to think after my experiences?
That's what I'm asking you. That's what
we're trying to get. You're saying that
the hate for them I have is mad. My bad
experiences are mad. I'd say
Oh, no. But no, no, no, no, no. It's not
about people being a problem. You just
said that the hate I have for women is
mad. Why is it mad? It's justified. No.
After all the bad experiences I had. Why
is it mad?
Why is it Why is it mad? And I'm going
by all the bad experiences I've had with
them. Why would it be mad?
Why Why would it be mad? The time I
spent, the money I spent. Why is it mad?
It's like wanted.
It's It's completely warranted.
Oh. So, what what what would you prefer
me to think? That they're not all the
same? I I'd be lying to you. If I told
you they're not all the same, I would
just be lying to you. And I I don't want
to lie to you. I don't want to be a
liar, you know. So, I'm not I can't sit
there and say to you that uh that they're
um that they're not all the same because
they are all the same. I'm not going to
lie and pretend they're not. I mean, you
can watch my approaching videos. It's
literally always the same [ __ ] with
them. They are literally all the same. I
can't lie to you, you know.
No. But what I think is is is mad that I
haven't gone and killed someone by now.
That's what I think is very very mad. I
think what's so mad is that you ain't
killed someone after all the bad
experiences I've had. I'm surprised I
ain't killed someone.
That's another thing.
You know, it's completely justified.
You've been giving people the benefit of
the doubt for years to prove that
they're different. Why is it mad? I
would say the same thing to a woman
who uh who's met men for years. I I'd
say that that's justified.
These women are bad people, bro. Bad
people in general.
When's a new copycat statement going to
be made, Grezy?
Yeah, that was funny to be fair. Copycat statement.
couple days, like two, three days. It's
normally every couple of days, isn't it? Yeah.
Okay, Greavves you. So why did Nlegs
Why did Nons legs go to Amsterdam when
that was my first holiday?
My first holiday was Amsterdam. So why
did why was his first holiday Amsterdam then?
Why did you go to the same place as me?
That's a bit strange, isn't it? Like
what's the odds? Was [snorts]
he being a copycat? Really?
Did he want to fit in? Well, he wanted
to go as well.
What? Did he Did he want to fit in? He
didn't want to feel left out in it.
So what you're saying, he didn't want to
feel left out
cuz there's no way you went to Amsterdam
and then someone else has just gone to
Amsterdam as well the first time. That's
like one in
one in a million. It's no coincidence, you know.
Well, you know why I went. Well, Dusty,
you know why I went, lad.
You know why I went.
Uh, cuz I don't target I I don't target
disabled vulnerable women. That's why I
don't go for disabled women that can't
talk. Well, Dusty, you know why I went?
And I actually did smoke when I was
there. I actually did smoke weed when I
was there several times.
Yeah, I don't know why he went cuz
he didn't use escorts and he didn't smoke weed.
That is weird. That is strange.
That is That is That is strange.
There's definitely a copycat them.
There's so many nice places in the
Netherlands, Dusty, and Amsterdam is not
one of them. It's the capital. Why do
people go there?
I went there, you know, I went there and
I smoked weed when I was there even
though I don't smoke weed.
So why did why did non why did
non-slaves go then?
Yes. So why did nonslaves go? [clears throat]
Yeah. So why didn't Nons go right after me?
That's weird why he went cuz he doesn't
smoke and he doesn't do escorts.
And that was the first place he went.
dusted. There's no way that's a
coincidence, is it?
>> Madness that is, bro.
It's strange though cuz he always used
to be against people that copied. He
always used to say that, "Oh, I don't
like people. I've got a mind of my own
and stuff." And you would have thought
the way he dresses,
he always used to say that he he hates
people like that, Dusty.
He always used to say he hates people
that do that. That's weird.
He always used to say
and he got he got caught out with the
chevel co thing, did he, Grezy? I showed
him up on the forum. Now he's starting
to say he didn't say that. Yeah, cuz he
got caught out, didn't he?
He got caught in the act.
My PC blood caught red-handed.
Caught red-handed being a copycat. Yeah,
caught red and had been a little copycat. Yeah,
I'll be wearing my vapors tomorrow,
Dusty and my Ammani jeans. Yay.
Be drinking loads of Guinnesses tomorrow.
£5 a Guinness bargain.
got my little haircut done. So yeah,
we'll see if there's any changes
tomorrow. It's going to be so weird
approaching with my sister there, but
I'll do it anyways. I don't give a [ __ ]
I never forget the day. Yeah, I
approached somebody and they were next
to my friend. Oh my god, bro. I wanted
the ground to swallow me up, Greasy. Oh
my [ __ ] god.
It was so embarrassing, bro. It was so
so so embarrassing.
Trust me. I was like, "Oh, damn."
Cringe. Even thinking about it now is
cringe. But I'll do it tomorrow. I don't
give a [ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] I
absolutely don't give a [ __ ]
Maybe I'll find someone to whine and dash.
Yeah, I'll be drinking Guinness tomorrow. Yep.
But it's the only way you'll ever find someone. Dusty.
You couldn't do it.
Well, it's the only way I've ever gotten laid.
Yeah, but maybe Yeah, but maybe they
just approach people in pubs and clubs.
It is. It is the only way.
Okay. If I wanted Okay, if I wanted to
find someone now, okay, if I wanted to
that's the only way I could ever meet someone.
I might meet someone in a pub maybe, but
I'm saying generally that would
literally be the only way.
I met USA on the street. I met I met
loads of dates from the street. I met
the 19year-old from the street.
So, I don't know about other people, but
I know me that's the only way I would
ever be able to meet someone
as these dating sites don't work. So,
that is the only way.
It might take a while, but yeah, if I
had an approach, I'd be a virgin if
you're not counting escorts.
I haven't met anyone
on a dating site.
I haven't met someone on a dating site
for years, bro.
I think I've met three people on them.
I think I met three people on dating apps.
Yeah, I've met three people on dating apps. Yeah.
And also, you have to really lower your
standards on dating apps, Dusty. When I
was last out on a Thursday, I met this
guy. Yeah. He looked a bit like me, like
with a man bun. He was taller than me,
had a beard, and his date was some fat,
ugly single mom.
So, I mean that tells you about the game
in itself. Single mom. She was really
big as well. And he was just like a normal
Yeah. decent looking guy. So, I mean
that's the one from Red.
So, I mean that in itself tells you, bro,
how bad it actually is. Ready? Yeah.
I thought you was going to try these uh
these dating apps, Grezy. You said in
April you was going to try the apps.
Yeah. Do you remember that one that I
met in Readen from the dating app?
Jesus Christ, bro.
How I was lucky to get out of that. The
one in Reen, is it? >> Yeah,
I was thinking of using escorts again.
Not even just because I'm horny, just
there's no point in having a dick if you
can't use it, Dusty.
And I'm like, I don't really get horny,
but what's the point of, you know,
having a dick if you can't use it, you know?
Bless him. Then
if I was a virgin, could you imagine how
bad I'd be if I was a virgin?
I couldn't let that happen, bro.
I couldn't let that happen.
Imagine I tried all these years and I
was a virgin. [ __ ] that, bro.
[ __ ] bro. That's mad.
It could happen. It could happen to some people.
You think I'm a virgin?
Thank you, bro. I think you're very handsome.
You think I'm a virgin and I think
you're handsome. Thank you.
No, it doesn't bother me when them
comments. The only reason I say [ __ ] is
because it's just the same repeating
with these self-p projectors.
It's not even that their their comments
are triggering. It's just the it's just
self-projecting people, isn't it?
You're going to have a long You're going
to have a hard shock, Greasy. When you try dating,
you're going to have a You're going to
have a hard shock.
You're going to have a really hard
You're going to have a really hard shot, bro.
Cuz you think that you can find someone,
Greavves, and you can just go out and
find someone. That's what you think.
That's what you're led to believe.
People on Reddit tell you that you'll
find someone and [ __ ] That's what
people on the internet tell you.
Good luck. You're going to need it. Or
maybe you get lucky.
You'll get lucky. Maybe. Yeah.
I got some money.
to go out. Good morning.
Yeah, I'll post the link in a minute. Uh,
I'm not taking it. I'm just bringing my card.
I'm not taking I'm just bringing my
card. Play couple of games of pool,
drink some Guinness, have some food. I'm
I'm not taking anything. I'm just taking my card. Yeah.
Going to make myself a cup of [ __ ] in a minute. Yeah.
I don't take money out with me. I just
take my card with me, bro. Yeah.
No, I'm going up. Someone else is coming
with us as well.
I norally go central London, but you
won't go central London. I'll go central
London next week by myself.
I'll go next week by myself. Yeah.
Yeah, I'll go by myself next week. Not a problem. Good.
How are you going to lose it?
No, I'm wearing my coat, black t-shirt,
jeans, and the vapors, lad.
No, I'm not wearing that. cuz [snorts]
it's not the place to dress up. It's the
casual place. It's not the place to
dress up, you know. Nope.
Not at all.
Grey Monty said the court gave him a warning.
The court gave him a warning.
It's a country designed to annoy you.
Yeah, this is a country designed to
annoy you, Grezy. Someone likes that
saying. It's true, isn't it?
It's designed to annoy you. It is the
women, the weather. Yeah,
it is designed to annoy you, get under your skin.
Of course it is, bro. That's why people leave.
Why? This woman replied on Reddit. Yeah. Yeah,
this person on Reddit, uh, Greavves, he
said, "I do understand it bothering you,
but in my opinion, that's not how things
work. Women are not given their bodies
because their bodies aren't supposed to
be given. They have sex with men they
want to have sex with. It's not a favor
they are doing for the man for being nice.
Well, you need to tell that to these simple
one of these accounts that are blocked I
assume. Self-reflecting again. Bye-bye, self-reflector.
And he's never shown 20 grand in his
life. And that 13 grand was his daddy savings.
But who cares?
No, I'm not gambling tomorrow.
That Timmy's skin in it. Grezy, you were
showing £100 yesterday.
He was showing £100 yesterday. Grezy.
I just want to get tomorrow uh out the way, bro.
Fingers crossed 2026.
No more repeating on this community greasy. Yeah.
Cuz I'm going out tomorrow drinking. So after tomorrow
I can go back to my nestic cause and be depressed. Yay.
Right. So if I don't talk about women,
these people are not going to say skint
and stuff. Yeah.
Okay, Grezy, I promise. Right. So in
2026, none of these people are going to
be on here saying skin
to each other.
So none of these people are going to be
self-relecting to each other. No, I'm up for that.
Yeah, but I just want them to stop
repeating. It's boring. The skin [ __ ] is
boring now, man. It's been going on for
seven years. Reevesy, it's been going on
for seven years, man.
Like, every time I go on Timmy's, it's
the same thing. Skin. Every time I look
on it, it's skin. I just want them to
say different stuff now, man. It's been
going on for seven [ __ ] years. It's
been going on for seven [ __ ] years, bro. >> [laughter]
>> It's getting pretty boring now. Think
about it. And me and Monty basically
grew up on this site and it's just been
the same [ __ ] ever since.
Yeah, good one, Dusty.
Yeah, good one.
Yeah, seven years, bro. Seven years this
has been going on.
Your skin, you're this. You're that.
You're this. You're that. You're this.
You're that. [ __ ] hell. Seven years, bro.
with these self-reflectors.
Monty said that will upset the
self-reflectors today that he didn't go prison.
He said that will that will uh that will
hurt you self-reflectors.
I don't know why they bring up money on
here, bro. All the time they always say
skint skin. I don't know why they do it. This,
you know, I find it weird, Grezy. What?
How did that start anyways?
Cuz I think me and you come here at the same time.
Yeah, the police took my passport.
Yeah. Okay, bro.
Yeah, my passport's right here.
So, that's a bit impossible.
Self projector. Bye-bye. Yeah.
I'll probably watch some WWE in a bit
greasy and go to sleep.
Oh, depressing, isn't it?
Go sleep. I say go to sleep. I'll
probably be up until like 4:00, to be
honest. I go to sleep at about 6:00.
I go to sleep at 6:00 in the morning. one here.
Yeah, they say that you'll meet someone here.
That's what Reddit told me. Yeah,
one second. I need to listen to his voice. Huh?
yo. Um, Grey Antman said the only way is
Asia. He said that if it was going to
work in England, it would have worked by now.
What do you think of that, Greasy?
He said if it was going to work in
England, it would have worked by now.
You think he's lying?
Yeah. They said if it was going to work
in England, it would have worked by now.
Well, I'm going to make myself a copper
[ __ ] One second.
Nah, I didn't call him an
He's a cool guy.
My adman's a cool guy.
agrees with you. Peter Benny doesn't
know where to turn.
Peter Belly doesn't know where to turn.
Do you remember Greasy?
Eat a belly.
They say it happens. Yeah.
She said, "No, not interested in casual
sex. It's a matter of safety or and
hygiene for me."
That's a bit boring, isn't it, Grezy? Yeah.
Think of that greasy. A bit boring.
It's a bit boring, isn't it?
electric electric toothbrush. Grezy,
you think Reddit is a power thing, isn't it?
Greasy thinks Reddit is a power thing, don't you?
Yeah, he thinks Grezy thinks it's a
power thing as well to some degree
a little bit. Don't you Grezy? You said I think
the mods ban people to feel powerful in it.
Yeah, they do it to feel powerful.
Yeah, I am, bro.
And I wouldn't care if I wasn't either.
This woman said, "I don't sleep with
someone until we're dating." And even
so, it might take a while. Do you believe that? Come here. Yeah.
Yeah, this woman says she doesn't sleep
with someone until they're dating.
She says she kissed on first dates,
but she doesn't see until they date him.
How did I, bro?
Oh yeah. Bless you, Greavves. Well,
Greavvesy, you can come around here for Christmas.
Yeah, you can come here G if you want.
She don't want to know.
He don't want to know you. You know,
you went absolutely nowhere near that girl.
doing an absolutely
nowhere near that girl.
Oh, do you like that?
You little copycat.
The biggest copycat on this community, Greavves,
>> who would you say the biggest copycat is?
Look at that [ __ ] virgin.
No, I'm no copycat. Yeah. Heat. Yeah,
I'm going in a minute. Anyways, I'm
going to make a tea and
probably go to bed.
I got a depressing day ahead of me tomorrow. greasy.
Yeah, I got a depressing day ahead of me, lad.
Say go to bed. I probably, like I said,
I'm not probably going to sleep until
about 4:00 or 5.
Yeah, I got a depressing day ahead of me tomorrow, lad.
More bad experiences with women. I don't
think the [ __ ] collection can add
anymore. I think the [ __ ] collection is full. Yeah,
there'll be more stuff to add to the
[ __ ] collection tomorrow.
It agrees. It just another one to add to
the [ __ ] collection.
So they say, dusty.
So they say. Yeah.
So odds it's going to be different
tomorrow. I'm saying one in a million.
I think I've got a pound in the draw. I
can put a pound on it. What do you
think? Everyone have a bet. I think it's
one in a million. Yep.
So, what do you reckon the chances is
going to change tomorrow? Dusty, put
your bets on. I'm putting one I'm saying
one in a million.
One in a million, bro.
I think one in a million. What do you think?
One in a million.
People on Reddit say it will change.
One in 10 million. I'm saying one and
eight. I'm saying one in a million. I'm
being nice by saying one in a million.
No one likes a let down.
Doesn't matter about dropping your
standards. It's still going to be the
same. Bro, you're talking to me, bro.
You're talking to me.
You're talking to someone that's been
[ __ ] all over the country, bro. What
do you mean drop your standards?
But no one likes a let down, do they, Grezy?
No one likes a let down.
You know that. And I know that.
I'll wait until it's been made. Yeah. No. Yep.
Well, I'll be in bed soon and hope I
don't wake up.
Knowing what I'm in for tomorrow is so depressing. depressing, bro. So depressing.
It's really bad, bro. It Yeah.
Yeah. We're definitely not changing
tomorrow. Definitely not. man. Yeah.
gone about [ __ ]
daddy's life saving from [ __ ] what
he goes on about daddy's life savings
this nonslegs has been doing this for years you
It don't matter what they say.
I agree. You know this nonsle has been
doing this for years. You know,
these people have been repeating
themselves, bro. You know that all night
mic back when I was at the old house
with Laney? I remember. You know that
all night mic? I remember having the
same conversation in the summer.
Yeah, they're repeaters, bro. They're
repeaters. I remember even like Yeah, I
remember, bro. [ __ ] That's a long time.
You know, these people have been repeating themselves.
They don't get bored, but they say that
they've got a high IQ. This is what I
don't understand. They they call people
low IQ, but all they do is repeat.
I actually remember in Old House with
Laney. The old house with Laney,
they were doing this. Even then they were repeating [ __ ] mad. Yeah.
How what I mean they dismiss my
struggles, right? Is they like say a
woman does bad, right? And you react to
it saying, "Oh, I'm going to confront
them." They'll be like, "Oh, yeah, you
shouldn't do that." No, no, no. So they
are they they always go back to
dismissing what they do. Would [snorts]
you agree on that Grezy
that they always go back to dismissing
what they do?
Yeah. They've been repeating
back when I used to go on walks back in
the summer in the in the old house.
We're talking years ago. So, but they
say that they've got high IQ.
They show they they say they don't show
their face because they've got high IQ,
but all they do is repeat themselves.
So, who knows? They're [ __ ] idiots, isn't it? Yeah.
Monty said they'll be repeating
themselves even when they're dead.
All right. So are they they dismiss
people's struggles then we
I'm only bringing this topic up because
I'm going out tomorrow. So,
oh, I'm not looking forward to this, bro.
More bad experiences.
I'll be on [ __ ] Reddit tomorrow. I'll
be on Reddit all night, bro.
This [ __ ] is making me suicidal, bro.
Thinking about this,
why is this guy saying on Reddit,
"It's not self-inflicted. I'm going by
my experiences and they definitely weren't self-inflicted.
Now you're this and you haven't groomed
properly. This guy's saying I haven't
groomed properly. Of course I have. And
would it matter if I have or haven't groomed properly?
I mean I have but I mean even if I didn't
I mean what? You're still going to get
the I have a boyfriend. You're still
going to get the same [ __ ] Does it does
it matter if someone has or hasn't?
It's not self-inflicted.
I didn't ask to get all of these bad
experiences with women. So, how can how
can you say it's self-inflicted
as a boyfriend? Probably. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm going to wash my hair
tomorrow. Obviously. Not groomed
properly. Seriously, bro. Seriously.
say that I'm not groomed properly when
I'm always [ __ ] groomed properly.
And even if you're not even if you're
groomed properly, you're still going to
get the same old.
So what what is it?
They always love blaming men, don't
they, Dusty? You're not groomed properly
or your body's not this. They always
love blaming the man.
It will never change. It will never
You've got more chance of this community changing
than this changing.
And why does it matter if someone's
groom properly or not, bro?
Still not going to make a difference.
You're still going to have bad experiences as usual.
Doesn't matter what you you [ __ ] look
like. It was always going to be the same old
Yeah, I'll be gone. I'm making a te a bit. Good. Yeah.
Yeah, he went live.
They just gave him a warning. Yeah.
Why are all of these people telling
people to work on their looks anyways,
bro? What's that going to do? You could
you could look you could spend £70 on a
barbers, bro. You could spray your face.
You could spray your clothes. You could
wear the best clothes and you're still
going to get the same old [ __ ]
I mean, yeah, get a trim, you know, your
beard and your hair. Like, you don't
need to do extra stuff like style and
it's not going to make a difference.
You might as well go out greasy looking
like a [ __ ] terrorist. You probably
have more luck.
It doesn't matter what you look like,
bro. Don't matter what you look like at all. Yeah.
And I can tell you that for a fact as well. So yeah.
[sighs and gasps] Yeah,
you remember Grezy. Let's poke let's
poke fun out of the people that ain't
wanted by no one.
That's what Valentine's Day is for.
Let's make [laughter]
It's a day to It's a day to poke fun out
of the men that ain't chosen by nobody.
Yeah, let's poke fun out of the men that
ain't chosen by no one.
Who is he?
That guy is funny as [ __ ] bro.
I might meet someone by Valentine's. Is
it? Do you reckon I meet someone by Valentine's?
>> Yeah, I'm a virgin, bro. Didn't you know?
Lunch Legs is an absolute virgin.
He's an absolute one.
Talking about grooming and looks and
[ __ ] It doesn't matter how you groom,
you're still going to get the same old
Why does that matter? I don't understand
why that matters. I'm not styling my
hair tomorrow. I'm just leaving it like
this. I'm going to wash it and I'm just
going to go out like this.
I'm just going to go out like this.
Yeah. He's had disabled women that don't
sleep with him. Maybe. Yeah. Well, not actual women.
Yeah, he's had he's had he's had
disabled women. I've had I've had
several normal women.
He has not had more women than me. No
way has he had more women than me. Which
is which that's what I'm trying to say,
Grezy. That that's that's my point is
that's why I don't understand where the
whole sing comes from where the whole
people are thinking that women are
angels. Greavvesy cuz all of these
people, all of these cont all of these
contestants have had less women than you.
That's the bit I don't get, Grezy, is
that they don't women don't like them.
Women will never sleep with them and
they still defend them. And they've had
less women than you as well.
That's the bit I don't
I don't understand. That's the bit I've
never ever understood. Like Virgin Legs,
he has nowhere near as many women as I
have, even normal ones. and he still
defends them and he's with a disabled
girl. They don't even sleep with him.
So, it's weird. It is strange
why they do it.
I'd love to know one day why they do it.
Cuz the women don't like them. The women
will not sleep with them and they still defend them.
No. No. What I'm saying is Grezy, it's
not about competing. And I'm saying, why
are these women, sorry, why are these
people that have had less women than you
that don't get women defending women
like like the guy on the train and
people what's what's the point? Women
don't like you. Women are not going to
sleep with you, you know?
So why do they defend women when women
don't like them?
And all of these people have had less
women than you. Not that it's a
competition, but they haven't had as
many women as I have. The guy on the
train hasn't. Virgin boy hasn't. But
they still sit there and defend them.
And women don't like them.
Never never understood them kind of
guys. Never did.
They must think that one day a woman's
going to jump on their dick for defending them.
I don't know how you can say all of the
[ __ ] that I do is self-inflicted.
How is it self-inflicted?
How is what I do self-inflicted when
it's it's going by experiences?
How is it self-inflicted when I'm going
by my experiences? That doesn't make any sense, bro.
What do you mean? I got it to myself. [snorts]
No, not really. Because I've had chances
to be in relationships.
Yeah, but Dusty, people on Reddit tell
me I have to keep trying. So, which one
is it? You know,
you know what I mean?
I'm only thinking about this cuz I know
what I'm in for tomorrow.
Yeah, but I quit gambling. But I quit
gambling, didn't I, Grezy?
I know. Yeah. Well, the thing is,
Gregie, this is what always makes me
laugh, right, with with these people
that are talking about women and knowing
more women than me. And I tell nons, I
absolutely do know more women than you.
And at the end of the day, you've only
been in a relationship with one or two
women. Yeah. They're individual women.
You don't know more than someone that's
been traveling up and down the country.
been up and down the country
meeting women. Just because you've had
one, two, or three relationships with
individual people, that does not mean
you know more. That that does not mean
you know more about women. I don't know
why people think that if they've been in
a relationship, they know more about
women than you.
But I was literally meeting women every
day. So I don't I don't understand that.
That doesn't even make sense. It really
really does not make any sense. And the
thing is Grezy, he's not happy in that relationship.
But anyways, it doesn't really matter.
He's not even happy in the relationship.
That's all he can get cuz he's too ugly.
Um, so he's not even happy in that
relationship. So, I don't even know why
it why it matters.
Not really because I've had chances to
be in a relationship. So, no, not
really. You know, not really at all.
It's not that hard to maintain a
relationship. Not really.
Not really at all. I've met people more
than once, several times. And he he
doesn't even Also, another thing is he
doesn't even like who he's with
cuz of um that's why he stalks me and
stalks USA is he and stalks and it's cuz
he's not happy in his own relationship.
This is part of why he does what he does. So
he's not even happy in the relationship.
But he's not even happy in the relationship.
It doesn't even matter what she is by
what he does on YouTube. Stalking USA is
he. He's too ugly that he knows he can't
get anything better.
That's why he's jealous of me cuz I've
had better and I'm not the one defending
them. I know. It's weird, isn't it?
He wishes he could get with like USA and
Sig and all of these, but he can't
because he's [ __ ] ugly.
Yeah, Trip Rates. I'm I'm jealous of
someone with a disabled girlfriend.
Yeah, I know, bro. Yeah, I know. I'm
very very jealous. Yeah.
Yeah. I I want a disabled girlfriend,
bro. You got me. Yep. You got me, man.
That's what it was all along, is it?
Yeah. So, what are you going to do then, Grezy?
Yeah, he's not happy in that relationship.
I don't know about her. I don't I don't
really know much about He's definitely
not happy in that relationship. Uh
but he's too ugly to get anything else.
So that's why he self projects.
Tries to call me ugly when I'm better
looking at him
cuz he's insecure, bro. That's Yeah. Yep. >> [gasps] >> Yeah,
they don't have sex. They don't have
sex. Definitely definitely don't have
sex. And again, Dusty, I don't see you
on his channel when he's calling me a
virgin. So, I have no reason. I have I
have no idea why you're bringing that
up. But anyways,
yeah, we're the same age. I'm 28. You're
Yeah, I don't see you on his channel
backing me up. Strange.
[snorts] Well, anyways. Oh, are you?
Well, Joseph Ferrar ain't.
Well, Joseph Ferrar isn't.
They definitely definitely don't have sex.
Definitely definitely don't have sex.
Not at all.
No, they don't. He's a virgin. I know
better than he knows himself.
Yeah, Joe got the ass with me just cuz I
told him that he's a biased nods lover.
He is a biased non-slaver. I didn't say
anything that weren't true. Instagram nitpicking.
Got to lose some face fat and then have
the beard shorter. But you're a handsome
dude. Like I said, so I've showed him
I've showed him a video where I've
groomed and had my haircut from like last month.
They don't have sex. And I'm not getting
into this anyways, bro. I'm not getting
in this conversation. I don't know why
you keep bringing it up. So, yeah. So,
once you have the beard shorter and you
lose face fat, you're all of a sudden
not going to get bad experiences with women. Really?
So, all of a sudden, right, when you
have your beard shorter and you lose
face fat, you're all of a sudden going
to stop having bad experiences with women.
No, I don't think so, bro.
I really don't think so. I used to go
gym all the time when I was 21, 22.
Never made a difference with women.
When I used to travel, I used to go gym.
I used to cook. You still get bad experiences.
Yeah. Well, they're obviously not having
sex because he has more time to spend on
the internet, right?
I don't know where he would have the
time to have sex. If he's constantly on here,
but I know they haven't had sex, so I
know they haven't had sex. He's a virgin,
mate. He's on here more times than he
spends with his misses. They don't have
sex. Furthermore, the question would be,
where are they having the time to [ __ ]
when they're on here stalking me?
[laughter] Nothing's happening in that bedroom, mate.
the amount of times. Anyways, I'm not
talking about this anyways, bro. It's
ridiculous. It's just biasness and I
don't care about it, bro. None of you
are defending me when he's talking [ __ ]
about me, so I don't give a [ __ ] Don't
be biased on another channel. I'm sick
of the biasness
and I'm not going to start [ __ ]
calling this and calling that and
calling this and calling that. I can't
be bothered with the biasness.
Yes, he's a ver he's not a virgin. I'm a
virgin. Even though I proved I've had
sex, I'm a virgin. Are you happy? Yeah,
bro. I'm jealous of what he has in a
bedsit. No money. Ugly. Yes, I'm
jealous, bro. I'm admitting to
everything that you're saying. I want a
disabled girlfriend. I want to be in a
bedsit. I want to be on £1,000 a month.
Okay. Yeah, I'm jealous. Very jealous.
Now, can we move on now? Because it's
not like you're going to ever stop
talking about it unless someone admits it.
Yeah, a relationship with a disabled
girl. I don't want a relationship with a
disabled girl is what I say to you.
You don't listen. Yeah, a relationship
with a disabled girl is not a badge of
honor. A relationship with anybody is
not a badge of honor. Yes. The say a
girl and I've had and I've had chances
to be in relationships. So why are you
talking about relationships?
Right. I've had chances to be in a
relationship multiple times. Multiple
multiple multiple times. So, I don't
know why you're carrying it around like
it's a badge of honor.
Seriously, I've had chances to be in a
relationship. But even if I was in a
relationship, you'd still tell me I'm
not in a relationship. You're all biased
and I don't care. This is why I don't
give a [ __ ] about talking about this
[ __ ] because, bro, you're all biased on here anyways.
Why does it matter? Huh? See,
this guy was like, "Keep," he said,
"You're right. It doesn't keep doing
what you're doing and going nowhere. You
got it, G." Well, well, yeah, it's
common sense. Yeah. Even if you have a
better body and you reduce body fat,
Yeah. You're not going to meet a woman.
It's never going to change. It doesn't
matter what you look like. Homeless,
fat, skinny, you know.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Whatever. I'm not
answering it anyways. Whatever. [snorts]
I'm not I'm going to ignore all of these
questions now cuz I know what you're
trying to do and I'm just going to
ignore it. Okay, bro. Whatever.
So, yeah. Okay. So, I don't know why
this guy's being sarcastic.
So, you think if you lose face fat and
you go to the gym, all of a sudden
you're going to meet someone.
Yeah. Yeah. I ignore facts just like you
ignore people put porn videos up. Bro,
you're all biased. This is why I don't
get into it with you. No, I don't get
into it with you people cuz you're
biased. It's a waste of my time.
We've seen it with the launch legs
thing. You're biased. That's why I
ignore it. Cuz I don't I don't entertain
biased people. Why do you think I don't
show receipts? Cuz you're biased. Why do
you think I don't show money? Cuz you're biased.
I don't show biased people stuff.
Right. Yeah. So, I've proved that I've
done Yeah. Okay. And he's not proved
that he's had sex. Mate, I've been in
bed with several different women. Again,
I'm not doing this. You're biased. Like
I said, I'm not doing this again. You
obviously like nons. That's your
problem. We're not getting into this.
I've been seen in I'm not explaining
myself. I'm not explaining myself again.
You're all biased. That's the end of
that. I'm not I'm not getting into this.
You keep thinking someone that's got a
disabled girlfriend has had sex. I'm not
interested. I know the truth. I know
what I put up. End the story. Think what
you want. I don't care. I'm not banning anyone.
You know, if you want to keep defending
a N or being a N lover, that's up to
you. I don't care. I'm not even banning
anyone because of it. So simple.
Yeah. Okay. Whatever. I'm ignoring your
comments now. Anyways, back on to this
guy on Instagram.
You know, it's already been established
that you love nonses. You're biased nons
lovers. I'm not interested. I'm not even
banning people. So, you can't even say I
banned. I've shown more money, more
women, better looks, and you still talk
[ __ ] That's why I advise anyone, don't
bother with these people. Do not bother
with these people on here. I've showed
better money, better looks, more money,
more girls, and they still talk [ __ ]
Don't bother with these people. Like, I
weren't even going to. No. He showed
£13,000 of his daddy's savings four
years ago. Where's the 13 grand now?
Where's that 13K now? He don't have it
cuz it's not his money. I shown seven
grand and I made you all run away. Yeah.
I showed seven grand and I made you all
run away. You couldn't show me nothing.
That was the evidence that I needed that
you were skink yourselves. And ever
since then, I never bothered ever again.
Uh 1.5 grand, two grand, three grand and
you I made you all run away. That was
the evidence I needed to know that you
people were skin. And then that's like
I'm never showing you anything ever again
cuz I know you're little biased nons
loved jealous people. So I don't waste
my time. It doesn't matter what I
showed. I made you run away.
I made you all run for the hills. That
was my little evidence pack that I
needed that you people were
self-projecting. A wise man learns from his mistakes. Yeah.
And guess what I've had that he's never
had? My own money and a girl that
weren't disabled. Is that too far?
I mean, the guys admitted to liking 15y olds.
So, but like I said, you're non-slers.
You're jealous like him. Jealous people
think alike. So, I don't care. I don't
even need to ban any comments. I'll just
leave them up.
Two jealous people with green eyes think alike. You know,
you people always talk [ __ ] It doesn't
matter. No. Why do you think I don't
show like if I a four year uh excuse me,
four years ago, I would show receipts.
I would show receipts for the the things
that I bought. But then I realized that
all these people are doing is self- projecting.
So whatever you show them, they're still
going to talk [ __ ] You can show them
money. You can show them better women,
which I've showed, and they're still
going to talk [ __ ] And real and and and
then the sooner you realize this with
these jealous people, the better.
They're a waste of time, bro.
Waste of waste of waste of time,
bro. None of you people talk facts. You talk [ __ ]
That's why I ban you, because you talk [ __ ]
You don't talk facts. There's no facts
to hate because you don't talk facts.
You talk [ __ ]
The facts is I've shown more money than
him. I've had better women than him. And
I've never had to resort to disabled
like him. That's what the facts are.
And anyways, can you stop this [ __ ] for
next year as well, please? Do you think
you could stop it from next year? Cuz
this will be eight years now this has
been going on since I've been at the old
house. Do you think you could change up
the content a little bit?
Do you think maybe next year you can
change the content up a little bit and
stop the self projecting?
But we're all getting bored of it now,
bro. We're really really getting bored of it.
I have shown seven grand. That was my
own money. And that 13 grand was was his
daddy savings that he can't show now.
You're bragging about it now, but
where's the 13 grand now?
That wasn't his. Where's it now then? If
the money was his, he can show it now, can't he?
I mean, he's got his own channel, you
know, mate. If you had 13 grand, you
would have shown the 13 grand when I was
showing you the seven grand. That's his
dad's money. That's not his. And he
can't show it now. Uh, which is the main
thing. So, um, you can't show the money
now cuz you don't have it cuz it's not
yours. So, you can keep going on about
it all you want. No one cares. So,
yeah. again. You little nonslubber.
You're on the wrong channel because he's
not going to be on this channel.
Yeah, I Yeah, I know about the jealousy
from you people, man. You people are
jealous of me. Younger, better looking,
more money. I know it's a tricky one.
You're jealous of me. That's why you
won't leave me alone. That's why I've
had to come off of it several times.
Yeah. The jealousy towards me. I can
smell it as well. Funny enough, all of
these channels that are dedicated to me, retaly,
mate. I can smell it like burnt popcorn.
Well, you people do every [ __ ] day.
All cuz someone's younger and better
looking than you. And it's the truth.
And you won't admit it to yourself. You
will not admit it to yourself. Let me
guess. Let me guess. Before you answer,
you're going to say, "If you're so
good-look, why don't you have a
girlfriend?" Right. It's so predictable now.
Yeah, bro. You don't pick, bro. But none
of you people do pick on me.
But you don't pick on me cuz I'd smash
your teeth down your throat if any of
you met me.
Because if you did, I'd smack your teeth
down your throat. So you don't pick on
me. You people pick on your ugly selves.
And again, uh, nonslegs have has
admitted to being a non, right? You
don't like anyone that's younger and
better looking than you.
It's because I'm younger and better
looking. It's got nothing to do with
kids. I've been on this community seven
years and you people have been doing
this for seven years. It's nothing to do
with kids. Leave kids out of it. Stop
talking about kids.
Stop using kids, innocent children, to
justify your jealousy, right? Don't stop
talking about kids.
Stop talking about kids. It's nothing to
do with kids. Why are you talking about
kids? Shut up. You're jealous. That's
what it is. You don't.
You don't live in London. Shut up.
You're boring. You don't live in London.
You're boring, bro. Anyways, can you
stop this from next year? Anyways,
can you stop this um from next year? Do you reckon?
New content or what?
Why do you go on about kids as well? Why
do you keep using kids as an excuse? I
don't understand that. It's got nothing
to do with kids.
It's got nothing to do with kids. Why
are you talking about kids? It's got
nothing to do with kids.
You don't like it because you're going
to be alone on Christmas with no family.
You're fat and you're ugly and you ain't
got no money. Just own it. Just own it,
bro. We're almost in 2026. It's got
nothing to do with kids. It's got
nothing to do with kids at all.
Why are you talking about kids?
There's [ __ ] kids around this area
that talk to me and they've heard all
the stuff I've said about kids. So, stop
using that as an excuse to justify your jealousy.
You know, it's [ __ ] ridiculous. Now,
I woke up Greavves. Yeah, I was having
some mis calls by this [ __ ] uh [ __ ]
by this [ __ ] um Jamie Thompson.
this [ __ ] Jamie Thompson.
Yeah, it's jealousy. It's nothing to do with kids.
Actually, I wasn't alone Christmas. I
was actually with my friends on Christmas, actually.
You know, stop talking about kids.
[ __ ] kids, bro.
Anyways, let's talk about you. You're
going to be alone for Christmas. Let's
talk about you. This isn't just about
me. We're talking about you fat ugly
people. You're going to be alone
Christmas. We're going to stop talking
about you people. It's that time of
year, lad. It's that time of year, man.
You're going to be alone for Christmas
with no family and no dinner this year.
Let's talk about the future. Let's talk
about you people.
Let's talk about you.
You little Mongs.
[ __ ] you live in London. If you lived
in London, you'd be on my door. Oh, this
is the same repeating. This is the same
[ __ ] with these people. God,
the same atmosphere with these people.
Why do you Mongs keep repeating the same
thing? When are you going to get off
YouTube and get money and stop being
skinn and stop repeating and change the
episode, man? Come on.
When are you going to stop repeating and
creating the same atmosphere? It's so
boring. This is why the community is
dead. It's the same repeating with you
disabled people. This is why people [ __ ] off
because it's the same repeating [ __ ]
every time with you people.
You say that we've got low IQ, but you
constantly coming on here repeating
every time I click on [ __ ] Timmy's
channel. Skin. skin. Timmy, your skin.
Your skin, Timmy. Timmy, Timmy, your
skin. You're all They all say that
they're smart on it. They all say that
you're smart on it. But they all repeat
the same [ __ ] Someone's not answered me
that yet. I've still not had an answer
for that one, Grezy.
It wasn't to fa. I'm not getting into
I'm not I'm not going over it again,
bro. We're not talking about last year.
We're talking about this year.
Yeah, we're talking about this year. So,
anyways, when are you people going to
get off of YouTube and get a life?
Stop living in the past. For [ __ ] sake.
It's [ __ ] boring as [ __ ] You people
are proper repeaters on here.
This is why I didn't come on the other
day, bro. And I won't be on tomorrow either. Same atmosphere.
Same [ __ ] atmosphere.
You can't go on a channel and have
normal talk. Rezy, what did you do
today? Oh, I done this today. What did
you do? I done this today. Nope.
There's not there's none of that on any channel.
It's just the same repeating.
Yeah, but why are you talking about
that? That was last year. Why are you
Why are you talking about that,
Kenny? You're going to be alone this
year with no family just like you was
last year. Do you know what I remember?
Do you know what I remember last year, Kenny?
Do you do you know what I remember last
year? That I went live and you was all
on my live stream.
I remember that quite well. I remember I
went live and you was all on my live stream.
Why do you people pretend that you don't
come on here at Christmas as well? Like
L. He pretends that he doesn't come on
here Christmas. You [ __ ] do. Cuz I
was live Christmas last year and you was
all on there.
You were all on my live stream.
I think Greavves was on there, too.
Why do you pretend that you're not going
to be on it Christmas, lad? You know,
it doesn't matter, bro. I was getting
three grand a month. I had my own house.
I don't give a [ __ ] what they left me
with or what they didn't leave me with.
It doesn't matter. I was I had I had
money. I was getting three grand a
month. I don't give a [ __ ]
But at least you admit it. L will say
that he won't he won't be on here
Christmas when he [ __ ] will.
But yeah, you need to stop uh blaming
kids for your jealousy, bro. That's
that's lame. Now, you need to leave the
kids out of it.
It's not about kids. It's got nothing to
do with kids. Oh,
it's not to do with kids. The kids [ __ ]
was said like 3 years ago. It's nothing
to do with kids. Don't blame [ __ ]
kids because of your jealousy, you
people in this community. Yeah, man.
And you need to stop bringing up kids.
You don't You don't go for people
because they go for kids, cuz they've
said stuff about kids.
You do it cuz you're fat, ugly, jealous
people. We monsters. That's why you do it. Yeah. idiots.
>> Yeah, I'm on Reddit now. Yeah.
Oh, here we go again. 28 living 28
living with your mom. What's there to be
jealous of? Ah, same old conversation.
You people are so boring, bro. They give
me headaches, Greasy.
Because it's just the same conversation,
the same jealous people.
That's why you'll notice that I'm not on
here as much now because it's just the
same [ __ ] with these people every time, bro.
It's just the same old [ __ ] same old
arguments. And it just goes to show that
they ain't got a life to just keep going
round and round in circles with in this.
I'm 28 and I live with my mom. Bro, I'm
28, younger than you, better looking
than you, got more money than you, got a
mom unlike you. It's the same
conversation. And then I'll ask you to
come in and show us your face and you
won't do it. So, what's the point of
this whole thing? I've explained a
million times how you're jealous.
Multiple, multiple, multiple times. You
people in your 40s, virgins, no money,
no life. I've seen what you people have
done on here multiple times. Look at
your lives. [ __ ] a 28-year-old, you're
in your 40s and you're still a virgin.
How are you going to talk about a 28-year-old?
A 28-year-old that's got a better life
than you. It's the same argument with
these people every time. This is why I don't
these ugly, jealous, narcissistic
people. This is why I don't waste my time, bro.
But it's self projection jealousy.
That's all it is with these people. And
I and I wouldn't say it if I didn't believe it.
You got people on here in their 40s
calling you single when they don't have
a girlfriend. It's just the same [ __ ]
with these people.
This is the same [ __ ] with these fat
ugly people creating the same atmosphere every day.
Same fantasies, same talking, same
repeating, same comebacks. It's the same
[ __ ] with them every time, you know,
same [ __ ] with them. And I know deep
down with these people, it is jealousy.
Think of it. It's like what Ronald Pump
said, you're better looking. You got
more money. It's the truth. It is the
truth. truth what he said cuz if these
people had a better life they wouldn't
be on here regardless of what they say
it is the truth and I'm getting a tattoo
by the way gre that since we're talking
about tattooing and [ __ ] when I talk about tattoos
I've proven you people have been on here
typing away even when I've not been on
here yes I have yes I [ __ ] have so
um you're better looking than them
you've got a better life than them and
you've got more money than them. Signed
by Ronald Ronald Pump.
That's the tattoo I'm getting.
Yeah, that's the that's the tattoo I'm
getting of what Ronald said. You're
better looking. You got a better life.
You got more money than them. And it kills them.
It's so true. It's so true. Even though
it took me two years to realize it, it
is the truth with them. Think about it.
You're younger. You're better looking.
You're not fat. You're not old. You're
not disabled like them. Think about it,
bro. How many times have these people
have asked them to come on camera and
they won't come on camera and show themselves?
They won't come on camera and show themselves.
But they won't show themsel. They They
won't come on camera and show themselves.
They won't come there and show themselves.
Yeah, you're on benefits as well.
You're on benefits. Self projection, same atmosphere
with these people. I'm on benefits.
You're on benefits. You ain't got a
girlfriend. You're ugly. You know,
you're forced enough to come in here and
start talking about other people. But
have you ever looked at yourselves?
You're on benefits. You're ugly. You
ain't got a girlfriend.
Look at yourselves. Look at yourselves
before talking about other people. Bro,
show me money. Come on here and show us
money. You You ain't got a girlfriend.
You're ugly. You're on benefits. Stop
talking about yourselves.
It's almost 2026
and you're still talking about
yourselves, putting yourselves down.
And that's what goes to show that it is
It is jealousy cuz if they weren't
jealous, they wouldn't do this. It shows
that it's jealousy for people like Jamie
Thompson and Terry to constantly be at
someone. It's clear as day jealousy. If
you look in the sky, right, you can see
that you can see the clouds. It's only
acts of a jealous person. There's
different acts of people in life, right?
And it shows that you've got something
they want. Think about it, right? How
much how long have these people been on
the internet now doing this? It's only
acts of a jealous person. There certain
There certain acts in life, bro. Right.
And it's Yeah. better looking, more
money, and a better life. It's the
truth. I know it's a hard pill to swallow, but
yeah, that's another thing you're saying
about how you've got a job, so why are
you wearing handme-own white trainers?
But I'm on benefits, by the way. By the
way, I'm on benefits. Terry's not on
benefits, but yet I've got I'll show you
my trainers in a minute that I'm wearing
tomorrow. But don't forget, I'm on
benefits, by the way. Terry said I'm on benefits.
One second. Let me just make this copper con. Uh, right.
So, if someone's on benefits,
why do they have more Why do they have
better trainers than you, bro?
>> [clears throat]
>> [ __ ] mad [ __ ] Bro,
>> you are jealous. You're definitely
jealous. Don't forget, Terry. I've seen
you. You're legit. You got shitty
trainers. You're ugly. You're an old
man, bro. You want to talk about a 28-y old?
And you want to talk about a 28-y old?
You not see what's wrong with that yet? Madness.
But you want to talk about uh a
28-year-old when we've actually seen
what you look like? [ __ ] disabled
people on here.
Why? Cuz when I come back to your area
last time, you didn't show up. Cuz I
went to your area last time and you
didn't show up.
Yeah. I went to your area last time and
you didn't turn up. That's why I've got
a pretty good excuse. Because I went to
your area last time and you didn't show up.
Yeah. Yeah. You made me go to your area
and you didn't show up. That's why.
So, yeah. Look at these trainers. How is
someone on benefits got trainers like these?
Look at them. Brand spanking new trainers.
Look, they're brand spanking new. I
think I've only worn them once or twice.
You can never a full trainer like that
because you're skinting skin flint. Just
like your virgin boyfriend,
Terry. Just like your virgin boyfriend.
You two should meet up and have a beer
and call it the two virgins.
The two absolute virgins.
Look at them trainers. You can never
afford trainers like that, mate. So,
anyways, um why didn't you turn up last
time when I went to your area?
Tell everyone why you didn't turn up. I
was going to smash your [ __ ] face and
then you know it in it. Why didn't you
Why didn't you show up?
H Why didn't you show up?
Why didn't you show up last time I went
to your area? You absolute virgin. You
know what? I'll meet you and the virgin together.
No. Why didn't you show up when I went
to your area? I went to your area and
you didn't you didn't come out. I was
going to smack your teeth down your
throat, bro. I was going to take that
mask off you and I was going to spit in
your face, bro. I was going to violate
you, mate. And I was going to make you
swallow my spit. Yeah. [laughter]
You like that, don't you, Grezy? Come
back. Come back in the morning. Nope.
I'm not coming back in I'm not coming
back in the morning because the last
time I went to your area, you didn't
show up. You had your chance. You know
how I live. [ __ ] off.
I was going to [ __ ] unmask him like
you know you know how mask you know how
Kane got unmasked you know in WWE where
they take his mask off. I was going to
unmask him. I was going to make him
[ __ ] swallow my spit bros. Yeah.
Trust me. Yeah.
You don't know what I'm like now. I'm a
filthy [ __ ] I'm a filthy [ __ ] Greasy. Yeah.
I can't leave Greasy without content.
The poor [ __ ]
in it. Greasy. You poor [ __ ]
Uh, bro, I went to your area last time.
You didn't come out.
I went to your area last time. You
didn't come out.
I came to your area. You didn't come out.
Well, it'll be free, Triple, if you come with us.
But Triple H, you're another one as
well. I I came to Newcastle three times.
You didn't come out. So, I don't know
why you're laughing.
I don't know why you're laughing, Triple.
Cuz I went to your area three times. You
didn't come out. I went I went to
Newcastle three times. Your area.
Oh, you're boring, Terry. You're boring,
man. Stop it. I went to your area last
time. You didn't come out. Stop it.
I tried to meet Triple H three times.
You didn't come out.
Yep. It's been cancelled. Yeah, because
you people are not worth it.
You people are not worth it. Yeah.
I Triple H. Yeah. What would you do if
if Bomb became your kid's new daddy?
What would you do if Bomb became your
your your child's new daddy? You'd have
to fill him in then, in it, bro. You'd
have to fill him in. You'd have to fill
You'd have to fill him in.
You know, you'd have to You'd have to
fill him in, mate.
Then you would have to in it. [ __ ] that.
And it [laughter]
What did you say, Triple H? You'd feel venom.
You'd feel venom. Didn't you say triple [laughter]
[laughter] trip that he'd feel better? [clears throat] Bless you.
Bless you in life. [clears throat] >> [laughter]
>> Oh, that's funny, lad. That's very funny.
Yeah, but we all know why he did that,
didn't it? Didn't we, Dusty? I used to
go hard on him as well.
It's all self-reflection with these people.
Look at what he ended up looking like,
bro. But I can't even hate him cuz he
actually got me he actually got me laid
in Manchester. So, I can't even say anything.
No, I can't even say too much about Bomb
because if I didn't go in Manchester the
second time, I wouldn't got laid. He got me laid. So,
he don't he doesn't actually understand
that he got me laid
that good Friday when Ed Sheeran was
playing. Do you remember?
He got me laid, bro. Cuz if you didn't
wind me up, I wouldn't have went there.
Do you remember that day, um, Greavves?
Everything went quiet. There was no
plans and I thought, "This little cunt's
pissing me off now." And bam, do a video
in, uh, do a video in Manchester.
You remember that, ain't it, Grezy? The
good old days.
Yeah, you remember that, don't you?
[clears throat] Those are like the LT
days, isn't it? Yeah. This little [ __ ]
was winding me up, bro.
just [ __ ] bomb. So then I went to
Manchester and then he didn't show up. You remember
I was Yeah. See, I'm not scared of
anyone. See, I put myself at risk a lot
of times, Dusty.
I put myself, you know. Yeah. A lot of
times, bro. A lot of times
I went live round Manchester. I waited
for bomb the second time.
Anyone could have come and killed me, bro.
But wasn't scared.
I'm not scared, you know,
mate. I went to your area and you didn't
come out. Stop it.
I went to your area and you didn't come out.
And then he got me laid as well.
It is all bi It is all biased, Dusty. It
is all biased because I went to Mark's
area two times and the [ __ ] house did
not come out and no one ever said
anything about it. No, they are biased.
They are biased.
They are definitely definitely biased.
And only three or four people said the
thing about bomb and law J is no, they
are definitely biased because one of the
people that took the biggest L on here
was Mark Samson. And he was still
allowed to come on here about 13 times
doing the [ __ ] before people called him
out. No, they're definitely biased.
The Mark Samson thing never got brought
up once. That was the worst. That was
the worst. That was the worst L someone
could have ever took
and no one ever said anything.
I was live in a park so there was no excuses.
So that but no, they are definitely
definitely biased. They're biased with a
Trevor Dawson one.
They're biased with a nonsleg thing
because he didn't come out of his area.
He didn't come out once. They are
biased, are they, bro? That's why I
don't meet anyone on it.
They are biased, lad. I'm surprised that
Mark Samson, he took probably even a
worse Elden Bomb.
You make yourself cornflakes. Really, mom?
No, not true. My mom wanted to move
house. My mom even said on the live
stream the other day, anyone's welcome
to come here. My mom's even said
anyone's welcome to come here. So, no.
My mom moved cuz she wanted to move.
So, yeah. Get your facts right.
[ __ ] That's literally what my mom
said the other day. No,
no, no, no, no, no. My mom wanted to move anyways.
>> And it was a good thing cuz it made me
money all them years.
So you actually helped me to be honest
in a way. You actually helped me because
you made me money.
You made me all them thousands for them
years when I happened to work. So yeah,
thanks. Thanks for that.
I mean that's not the case. But even if
it was the case, well you made me
thousands. You made me thousands mate by
ear even. So yeah. So yeah,
do you remember when all of that was
happening at the housey?
Someone could have died that day.
Someone could have actually died. And
you think it's funny,
you know? O Terry, I think you and the
virgin bastard needs to meet me.
You know, you and the virgin bastard
that's never had sex need to meet me.
You and the virgin.
What do you think, Terry? You and the
virgin himself, the pack of virgins.
Like you know a pack of bags is a pack of virgins.
I'll have you both. I'll have both of
you [ __ ] virgins.
I'll both I'll bite your [ __ ] ear off
like Mike Tyson.
You and the virgin would be a great
would be a great show.
Me versus you and the [ __ ] big
virgin. What do you think we the biggest
virgin going? Why don't he meet me now?
I don't understand.
I guess you can't meet an adult. I guess
you can't meet a grown man. Maybe.
I tell him that you're a [ __ ] virgin yourself.
I say virgin. I said, "Yeah, you are the
[ __ ] virgin. You're a virgin cunt."
That's what I say to him.
I know you are the big virgin. And we'd
be like walking around with each other
to each other. You know what I'm saying, lad?
Bro, listen. Stop it, Terry. I went to
your area last time and you didn't come
out. You're not about that life. Just
stop it now.
It's embarrassing. It's really, really embarrassing now. [laughter]
Who calls a lot of that LT [ __ ] on here,
Grezy? He had beef with quite a few
people, didn't he?
who calls a lot of this LT [ __ ]
because he's an absolute virgin. That's why
because non legs is an absolute virgin
and I've already you do not know where
that nickname even comes from.
It It goes way back. It goes way way way
back with him. Do you want to Do you
want to hear the story, Greasy?
It's not it's not a long story, but I'll
tell it again if you want. It's only
quick. It goes way back. You know,
people have a name and it sticks. You
know, even when he does finally get
laid, he'll always be that virgin, you know. [snorts] [laughter]
Yeah. So basically when I used to meet
him I used to say that oh yeah I got
with an escort I got with an escort and
I got with an escort and uh you know
um basically I I told him about the
stories and he would not have it for
love nor money. Now obviously me being a
17year-old kid I was thinking why the
[ __ ] does this guy keep dismissing my
struggles? And I was like oh it's
because he's the virgin. He's the virgin
that's never had sex
>> and the way he used to go on about Sher
Cole and yeah, he's he's definitely
definitely a virgin. Definitely
definitely definitely a virgin, mate.
I don't [ __ ] know everything at 17,
though. I didn't know he was projecting
his virginity onto me. Big virgin.
Big big big virgin, mate.
Big big big virgin, mate. Big virgin.
Big [ __ ] virgin, mate. Yeah. Yeah.
And I don't And and again, Greavvesy,
I've never ever met anyone since who
didn't believe I used escorts.
Yeah. Never ever met anyone that never
believed it. Only that virgin. So I
found that strange why. Yeah. I found
the whole thing strange why you wouldn't
believe someone's paid for sex.
Probably because he was jealous because
he was a virgin and he didn't work
properly. But again, I don't know. his
fingers or something. He
>> I didn't know he was a big virgin. The
biggest virgin in town. The biggest Jesus Christ.
Is that you? You got caught in the act.
Right, let me have a little look.
Nope. Never happened. One second.
All right, let's just turn away.
Okay. I mean, I can go to bed with I can
lie next to my mom in bed right now.
Does that mean I slept with her?
I mean, does does that mean I does that
mean I slept with her if I lie next to
my mom right now in bed? No, it doesn't.
Would that would that mean I slept with
her? I want to see porn. I want to see
what I put up. I want to see all the good stuff.
I want to see all the good stuff, mate.
I want to see all the good stuff. I want
to see I want to see dick and mouse and stuff.
I want to see I want to see I want to
see proper proper sex.
You know, like like in the vid like
vintage, you know. I I want to see sex.
No, it's not come on now, Grezy. It's
not come on now. It's not come on now.
It's not come on now, Greavvesy.
It's not come on now because at the end
of the day, I put a porno up. Not not
[ __ ] me in bed with someone. I
actually made a porno,
you know? I put a porno and he got his
whole channel banned. I don't give a
[ __ ] about two absolute virgins lying in
a bed. I want to see some action. I want
to see some abs. I want to see some action. You know,
One second. He's not blocked, is he? I
want to see some proper action.
How to [ __ ] a disabled woman.
How to [ __ ] a disabled woman. Wait,
you're not blocked, are you? No, you're not blocked.
Why are you on that virgin channel?
One second. Let me unblock you. No,
you're not blocked on that one. You're
unblocked on this one. Okay, you're I'm
blocked on both of them now. I know why
you're blocked, mate. Take an L, bro.
Listen, I put a porno up.
Yeah, I listen. Let me let me let me say
this clearly to you. Yeah, >> I
have put a porno up. Porn.
You know what porn is? Porn. Not lying
in bed with someone. Porn.
A porn video. And I've been in bed next
to loads of different women. Bro br.
I put a porno up. Right, right, right,
right, bro. I put a porno up and I had a
woman admitting to sucking my dick and
and sleeping with me in bed. What he's
put up is is no comparison.
It's It's no comparison.
You're all biased. You're all biased. I
love that, you know, Grezy. I love it. I
love it. Right. So,
you you you go on, right? This is how
you know it's biasness on here because I
don't even know why I waste this. This
is what makes me think, Grezy, there's
no point coming on here with these with
with you bias people. Because think
about how many people call me a virgin,
yet I've been in bed with what, multiple
different women, put a porno up, and now
you're saying I've took an L because
someone shown me in bed with someone.
Does the biasness on it ever stop?
They're so biased.
You know, it's [ __ ] mental.
Jesus [ __ ] Christ. You're [ __ ] biased.
I'm I convinced I'm convinced this
community loves nons.
And why why do you keep saying that you
you slept with Aisha boot? You you went
absolutely nowhere near that girl.
You like that little saying? You went
absolutely nowhere near that girl
sexually. You went absolutely nowhere
near that girl.
Aisha is a Muslim. You went absolutely
went nowhere near that girl. Aisha is a
Muslim which she practices. He goes to
mosque. She does Eid. Did you come
anywhere near her? Back off. Back off
you. Back off you burning C.
Yeah. What about when I was putting a
porno up and showing me in bed with women? You know,
biased. That's fine. I'm not going to
block you. I know what you people are
like. You're biased on here.
Yeah. This is why this is my main
problem with this community, Cory, is
the biasness. That's why I take breaks.
I don't block anyone, though. That's completely fine.
Yeah, it's biasness. Definitely biasness
on here. Definitely.
Definitely. Definitely. I think they
love nonsense on here, bro. It's a pedo community.
Yeah. Facts. What? Me proving I've slept
with women and me me showing a [ __ ]
video. Yeah. I hate facts, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Even though you call me a
virgin even though I proved I've had sex. Biasness.
Anyways, I'm coming off here tomorrow
anyway, so I won't be back. They're
biased on here. That's my main problem
with the community is the biasness,
Cory. Nothing else. It's the biasness.
And it makes you really think that they
it is a pedo community. It is a proper
It's a proper bias pedo community, which
is probably why you don't go on it much.
I wasn't on here yesterday. I was on it.
No, I won't be on here tomorrow either.
I've got stuff to do tomorrow, lad. Yeah.
Proving what? Proven I've had sex.
How have I proven I've had sex?
How has nons proven he's had sex? Same
question to you. Well, cuz he's So him
lying in bed next to a woman proves he's
had sex, but me getting a blue job
[ __ ] isn't prove I've had sex.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Congratulations. Give
yourself a clap. You biased nonslover.
Nah, they're proper pedos on this
community, bro. They're proper proper
pedos on this community. You're wasting
your time with them, Cory. They're
biased nonslovers. Proper proper biased non-sl.
They're obsessed bias nons lovers.
Yeah. Yeah. Having a girlfriend. Yeah.
Of course, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Like all of
the women that I was in bed with. The
[ __ ] That never meant anything, did
it? Nah. Nah. Nah. No. No. Yeah. I'm I'm
a virgin, aren't I? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. You're You're right, bro. I'm a
complete and utter virgin. Yeah.
But you know what? I don't even know why
you come on this channel. You might as
well go on your boyfriend's channel
since you like to suck you. Even Kin
will tell you the bias.
Yeah. And lying in bed next to a woman
isn't sex. Yeah. And lying in bed next
to a woman isn't sex. Same same thing
back to you then. A [ __ ] is more
closer to sex than someone lying in bed
with a woman. Lying in bed with a woman
isn't sex. Same same thing back to you
then. Same thing back to you. [ __ ]
biased non-slavver. Anyways, I'm off
here tomorrow. Anyways,
they're starting to give me brain damage again,
right? Brain damage again. They're
they're giving me brain damage again,
bro. These jealous people are giving me
brain damage again.
Giving me a sore head, Grezy.
They're giving me a sore head, lad.
I do know what sex is. Yeah. something
that you've never had and you're never
going to lose your virginity.
Yes. Yes, I do. Something that you will
never experience cuz you're like a
virgin. And I've also I've made a uh
I've made a song for you, by the way.
It's a WWE theme uh a theme tune, but
I've added you in with it.
The virgin song dedicated to the biggest
virgin himself. You I might sing it one
day if you're lucky. I might sing it. Yeah.
This exactly what you are.
Alltime virgin. Oh, he does sleep.
Yeah. Lying in bed next to a woman doesn't uh
doesn't uh doesn't prove you've had sex.
That doesn't prove you've had sex.
Uh a blow a [ __ ] doesn't prove you've
had sex, but lying in bed next to a
woman proves you've had sex.
Wow. These people are really biased
nonslovers with jealousy, man. They need
to get a life. Honestly,
yeah, I know, bro. I'm proper. I'm Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Proper.
It doesn't matter if they live together.
I live with my mom. It doesn't mean I
have sex with my mom.
He's not alone. Anywhere near that girl.
Just like a Shabbout. I mean, I live
with my mom. Doesn't mean I have sex
with my mom. No. I mean, okay. Good for
you. Have you have you put a porno out
there yet? Come back when you put a
porno out there
because you're say you're saying that
you live with someone. I live with a
dog. It doesn't mean I had sex with a
dog. I lived with my sister. Doesn't
mean I I had sex with my sister. Yeah.
Yeah, I love I love the biasness on
here. That's what makes me know that I'm
just wasting my time.
That's why I come off here for like two
three weeks because of the biasness.
That's the only thing. It was only the biasness.
The biasness with these people
time and time and time and time again.
That's why I come here for a couple of
weeks. Grievy was no other reason. It's
cuz they're all biased. Yeah.
You know, but guess what? Do you know
what? I I don't mind entertaining you
though, Terry. You know, ugly,
lonely little man. You're living your
worst life. I don't I don't mind making
you I don't mind you loving things
better looking than you. I don't mind
you jealous people. I don't mind giving
you entertainment. You're living your
worst lives. So, I I'm I'm more than
happy to, you know, come here and stuff.
You all hate me cuz I'm younger and
better looking than you. Ronald Pump was
right all along.
I seriously think this is what the
problem is, Grezy.
I genuinely think it's cuz you're
younger and better looking than them.
Like, all all jokes aside, I generally
generally think that.
I generally generally generally
generally do, bro, because of what they
do on here. It's only because of what they do.
I generally think it's because it's only
because of what they do, lad,
you know. It's only because of what they
do, not what I think of myself. That's
why I think that.
Yeah. You have kids and the misses.
Yeah. I'm a millionaire, bro. And I
ain't got a hole in my ass.
Yeah, they're definitely jealous, bro.
Definitely definitely jealous.
definitely jealous. These people here
are even though they say that they're
not and you're this and you're that
they are they are definitely jealous on this community.
Definitely definitely jealous
because of uh the amount of people I've
got obsessed with me and dedicated to
stalking me and stuff
and it's what they do on here. It's what they do,
not what I am, it's what they do on here.
So, but like I said, I'm changing the
content up anyways. I'll be doing some
traveling videos and I'll be disabling
the comments and disabling the thumbs up and that
and I'm going to make them watch a life
that they'll never live since none of
these people want to meet me. I'm just
going to annoy them that way and I'm
going to stop going live.
What do you think of that greasy? I'm
just going to annoy them that way. Yeah.
Going to stay in some nice hotels. I'm
just going to annoy them that way. Simple. Yeah.
So then there's nothing they can do
literally but watch it. There's nothing
they can do but watch it, you know. So yeah.
Do you remember? Do you remember that
channel that goes on Timmy's skin? It
says to It says to Timmy skin, nothing
else but skin. [laughter]
Is it funny, Grezy? No.
[snorts] Yeah, you'll meet me tomorrow.
You're boring. You're boring. You're
boring. You're boring. You're boring.
I don't think this is about kids. Griezy,
what do you think it's to do with? I
don't think it's about kids. I think
these people would do what they do anyways.
I think I don't think it's about kids. I
they're jealous of the fact that you're
younger and you're better looking than
them and you've got freedom.
Uh not necessarily just about money.
That's what I think it is with these
people. It's nothing to do with kids.
Nons has proven to be a nons multiple
times and no one says anything. It's
nothing to do with kids. That's what it
is. You're younger. You're better
looking. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Basically.
Yeah. You've had more life experience
than these people.
Yeah. Yep. Yep.
It's not It's got It goes from It goes
more than kids, Grezy. It goes more than kids.
Yep. I've seen it. I've seen it. I've
seen it. And you know what I think? Do
you really want to know what I think?
Do you really want to know what I think?
You really want to know what I think? Anyone?
You You really want to know?
You you you you really want to know what I think? Absolute virgin.
That's that's what I think. I think he's
an absolute virgin
again. Until you provide a porno,
then I'm not interested. I want to see a
porno. I want to see sex. If you've had
sex, prove it.
Prove it. I I want to see dick. I want
to see dickat. I want to see it like the vintage phone, you know. [snorts]
Yeah, I'm self projecting, bro.
Yeah, I'm self projecting, lad. I've
already proved I've had sex. I've
already proved I've had sex. I've shown
me getting a [ __ ] me lying in bed
naked next to women, women admitting
they've had sex with me. I've already proved it. Biased [ __ ]
Biased. Biased. Biased [ __ ] I've
already proven it.
I think I've still got some videos. Actually,
I think you're an absolute virgin if I
didn't know any better. Jesus Christ. Yeah.
Yeah. Self projection. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. [yawns]
Yeah. I'm Yeah. I'm projecting. Yeah.
I've never put a porno up.
Yeah. I've never had sex. Yeah.
I [ __ ] that 19year-old about three times.
[ __ ] sig. The one in Manchester been
I I I have I I have had sex, mate. I [ __ ] have.
Well, if that's the case, why is he the
one that's obsessed with me?
No, they're not. No, they're not.
He's the one that's obsessed with me cuz
he's the one that's jealous of me. I'm
better looking. I've had more women.
I've got more money. No, he's the one
that's jealous of me. I mean, he's got
two channels dedicated to stalking me.
I mean, the evidence is there that he's
the one that's obsessed and jealous.
Let's just point that out there, lads.
That he's got two two channels obsessed
with me. He's definitely the one that is
obsessed with me.
He is definitely the one that's gen
obsessed with me. The evidence is there.
The evidence is is in black and white.
I've already proved I've had sex.
You absolute virgin.
He's done. Oh, there we go, Terry. We
know. We know. We know. We know that
you're not about that. Bigging up
someone grassing. And this is how LT um
calls you out. We know that you're not
about that life because you're biging up
someone grassing. We know you're not
about that life. Just like I went to
your area and you didn't come out. We
know you're not about that life. We know
it's all you're just a [ __ ] because
you're biging up someone calling the
police. You're not about that life.
People that are about that life don't
big up glasses. And yes, I'm on bail,
bro. I don't want to talk about that
virgin. I put posters up of him and made
him cry to the police. I'd accept being
on bail. At least I didn't get run out
of my area by posters.
I didn't get run out of my area by
posters. He did. I'll take the bail,
bro. I'll take the bail. I think it's
voided now. Anyways, I don't mind, bro.
I put up posters and run him out of his
area. I stopped him going to an event
for 3 weeks. Lovely. I don't mind
getting I didn't mind getting nicked. I
made him cry to the ble to the police. I
made him go running to the police
crying. I don't care. Simple, bro. You
can You can do whatever you want.
So, that's how we know that you're not
about it. That's how we know that you're
not about it. That's how we know that
you're not about it.
Because you're bigging up someone
grassing. That's how we know that you're
little wet wipe. Even LT sniffed you out
on the emails. That's how we know that
you're not about it.
You know, I put up posters of you and I
had you go into the old bill about me
crying. I made you go to the police cuz
you couldn't handle me on YouTube. You
couldn't handle me. Grezy, I've got ADHD. You know,
do you know?
Do you know?
No, I've got evidence of what he's done.
Bro, he hasn't restricted me. I'm still
talking about him. I'm still calling him
a virgin. I stopped him going to his
events for 3 weeks cuz of me. Do you
think anybody would stop me going somewhere?
I stopped him going to an event cuz he
couldn't control me. He couldn't handle
me. He had to go to the police cuz he
couldn't handle me. I'm unstoppable. I
was owning him so badly.
So badly. He was so much of a loser he
had to go to the police station. That's
the biggest L someone can take.
That's the biggest L. When someone can't
handle someone on YouTube cuz they're
bullying him that badly. He's so much of
a loser. He had no fight left in him,
Terry. Just like you, you little monk.
No fight left in you. You're so much of
a loser that the only thing you could do
is run to the police. Hold that L,
[ __ ] You could handle me. You
could handle me. I'm too much for you.
Think about it, Timmy. Come on, man. I'm
too much. I can't even be I can't even
be calm down.
I'm I'm unstoppable. You had to get the
police involved. You couldn't even own
me yourselves on YouTube.
I'm I'm unstoppable. I was owning the
lot of you. For somebody to feel the
need to be so much of a loser virgin
that they have to go to the police,
you've owned them. You've got to them so
badly that they've had to get a crime
refuge. A sambber. Yeah.
Yeah. Terry, I could I couldn't be
stopped. I could have The ownage was so
bad they had to get the whole deal involved.
The ownage and the ass whooping was so
bad. I literally got a plane out and
whooped his ass. You know, you know,
you know, you got owned so badly. You're
so much of a loser you had to go to the
police. No, but seriously, that is loser
[ __ ] though, getting owned in YouTube. I
told the [ __ ] many times, "Leave me
alone, Greavves." I gave the warning. I
gave the [ __ ] warning to this [ __ ]
virgin [ __ ] to leave me alone. I said,
"Leave me alone, you virgin fucker." And
then I started getting like [ __ ]
calls and [ __ ] and I was like, "No,
that's it. [ __ ] that.
Play with fire. You get burnt, mate."
Yeah. You wish you little grass, Terry.
And you know, the fact that you keep
talking about this shows you're not
about it. If you was about anything, you
would have come out when I went to your
area last time. You're not about that
life. The way that you're talking about
grass and it shows that you're not about
it. And that's why you didn't come out
last time because you knew you was going
to get [ __ ] up. You wasn't on no
[ __ ] uh probation. You knew you was
going to get [ __ ] up. That's why you
didn't come out. You wasn't on no
probation. You're not about that life.
The way you're biging up grass in it
shows that you've never been about that
life. LT knew. LT knew you he he sniffed
you out straight away. You know,
mate, you can't handle me. I'm too much.
I'm too much. You have to get the police involved.
Imagine that, Greg. You stop being so
much on YouTube, so out of control. You
have to get You have to get the police.
You have to get the police involved.
No, it's just cup stains, bro. It's just
you know. But come on, Timmy. He was so
much of a loser. I had him run into the police, you know.
You're so much of a [ __ ] loser with
money and women and looks and everything
that you you have to get involved. You know,
I'm out of control, mate. I've got ADHD.
I've got ADHD, mate.
Look, this is the face that you went to
the police over. I'm not exactly
intimidating or or anything like that,
but you know, I had you run into the
police over me.
Hold that hell, mate. Hold that. Thank you. [ __ ] [ __ ]
You're [ __ ] virgin, can't you? Yeah, Virgin. Yeah, Grezy,
you enter the police. I'm unstoppable.
I'm out of control. Is it, Greavvesy?
I'm out of [ __ ] control,
Greavves. I'm out of control, lad.
I'm out of control. [snorts] over YouTube. Triple H.
The window is going in over YouTube. [laughter]
Yeah, I'm actually the first person it
happened to. [laughter]
I'm the first person it happened to, you know. Oh [ __ ]
Do you remember,
Grezy? The windows went in.
The windows went in, Grezy. [laughter]
Yeah, the [ __ ] windows went in, mate.
Yeah. It's so funny. Yeah. Because [laughter]
because you know when I was subleting
that house. Yeah. When I was subleting
that house, there was somebody staying
in that room, but for whatever reason,
he wasn't in that room that night. I
don't know why. I don't know why he
wasn't, but the the the bed was next to the window,
Grezy. The the bed was next to the
[ __ ] window. Greavvesy.
So, anyhow, he he was in
Whoa. He probably He won't He probably
won't be here today.
He probably wouldn't be here today. Grey,
it's not funny. It's not funny. It's not
Remember the ebite got stolen. [laughter]
Yeah, that was that was that was like a near-death experience,
you know, grievy. A near-death experience.
It's not funny, bro. Someone could have got killed.
Someone could have got killed. Imagine I
was with my mama that day. Greavvesy,
imagine the day. Yeah. They said they
were coming and I was with my mama.
Is that cute, Greavvesy?
If I was with my mama. Huh? See? [laughter] Yeah. [snorts]
Madness, isn't it?
You said that's stupid, isn't it? Reg
just having a child for the sake of
having a child, is it? And it's ditching
it. You said that's stupid, isn't it? [laughter]
Yeah. You said that's stupid, didn't you?
Gez is a funny [ __ ]
Gez is a funny [ __ ] mate.
Because he'd already found his mother. Yeah. Mad.
All on the same website.
You can watch Mickey Mouse on.
Yeah, but money going to court wasn't
YouTube, was it Greavvesy?
Yeah, but I don't think the court thing
was over YouTube. [snorts] [laughter]
And to think if he didn't come on it,
he'd still be with Kaye.
He'd still be with Kaye. Yeah.
What do you think to that? Greavves. Mad.
Yeah. backfired bad.
It backfired cuz if he went to prison today,
we would have been that would have been
because of me, wouldn't it? Technically,
I said, "Yeah, come on this community.
It's going to be great.
This community is going to be great.
You'll love it. You'll absolutely love
Yeah, I said Monty, you all love the community.
Yeah. N is N G my mama Greavvesy.
Was N G my mama? [laughter]
You lost everything over YouTube.
Yeah, but he had his chance to get off there.
They were calling social services.
Where was my mama?
This is my mama.
Is this my mama? Greavves. Hey,
is that my mama?
A taking a baby away from its mama. Yeah.
All right. Do you remember when got
nicked and he's and he got his devices? See, Squeezy,
I am. Yep. I'm still stalking her. Well and proud.
I love it, Kenny. I love it.
Um, yeah, Belly got nicked
and he lost his device over YouTube,
Grezy. And he and and a normal person
would think maybe it's time to get off
of YouTube now. They took my devices.
Let me start fresh. Not him.
Not him. Nope. He bought a new device
and then came back on YouTube the next day.
Why, Greavvesy? Is it from all distress?
It might be from all distress, lad.
So why why is the hairline receding then Greavvesy?
Because you already found your mama.
Found your mama.
You kind of brought it on yourself
though. This YouTube thing is it
grieves. You kind of bought it on yourself.
Yeah, I like it. I didn't like her friend's tone.
I didn't like her I didn't like her friend's tone
about she was going to shoot me. Yeah, right.
Yeah. Yeah. But what about LT? Was he
the root cause? Cuz he started messaging
them, didn't he? Nah. No, mate. Yep.
It's okay though. I'll just wait.
You You'll wait. Yes. Until it's been made.
But wait until it's been made.
That's like us with the [ __ ] GTA,
isn't it? Yeah. That's like [ __ ] us
with the [ __ ] GTA, bro.
That's what she gets for being a little [ __ ]
You'll never forget me
once you meet me, Grezy. You'll never forget.
You'll never forget me, matey.
You'll never forget me.
Just like that South American [ __ ] AZ.
Yeah, just like that self [ __ ]
American [ __ ] a [laughter] [clears throat]
full of laughs.
Uh, she didn't reject me. I already
[ __ ] her and had her body. Uh, she
didn't reject me, but yeah, she's a [ __ ] anyways.
That sounds exactly what a s would say.
Well, oh, white knight. The [ __ ] didn't
reject me. I already [ __ ] the [ __ ]
and see her saggy body. I just don't like [ __ ]
Wait, did that South American one reject
me? No, cuz you don't even live in
England. I just don't like [ __ ] women.
Uh, no it wasn't.
No, it wasn't. And I already had her body.
Nope. Wasn't about wanting or not
wanting. You're not going to be a [ __ ]
and get away with it.
Simple. It doesn't matter who you are
where you live. You're not going to be a
[ __ ] and get away with it. Think about
it. I already had her body. So why would
I give a [ __ ] if I already had someone's
body? I just don't like [ __ ] I just
don't like [ __ ] Even if I don't
want them. Simple
as that. And I will go out of my way to
[ __ ] with any woman that's a [ __ ]
Yeah, that's not what happened. Anyways,
we're not getting into that again. You little repeater.
We're not getting into that. Anyways,
again, repeat. I've already explained this.
So, we've already explained this, but
yeah. Again, uh Tracy, whoever the [ __ ]
you are behind that account, believe it
or not, right, they're all unbiased
people that aren't in sales.
I had her body. I don't give a [ __ ] if
she wants me or not. I had her body.
I had her body. So why would I care, bro?
I just don't like [ __ ]
Yeah, that's what she said cuz she
caught out being she got. Bro, whatever.
I'm not explaining it again. I'm not
explaining it again to you. I'm not
explaining it to you again, bro. Say
what you want. Think what you want. I don't care.
Oh, by the way, you know, somebody can
be unbiased and not be a incel. By the
way, you do realize that someone cannot
be a white knight and a s and not be an
incel. You do realize that. You know,
of course he did the absolute virgin mad. >> [snorts]
>> You know what? I am going out tomorrow
and I'm going to be doing these approaches
and I'm going to be and I'm definitely
telling you I'm going to find someone to
dine and dash.
I'm going to find someone to dine and dash. Yeah.
D I'm going to find someone to dine and
dash. That's my promise to you, Dusty.
I'm going to really [ __ ] someone up,
bro. It might take like a week. I'm
really I'm really back on this now, bro.
I'm really back on this now.
I've got the pictures on my device, you know.
Yeah. And then and they're going to be
[ __ ] and they're going to get nicked.
I'm going to die in a dash, you know.
Yeah, because he's a [ __ ] virgin. Cuz
he's an absolute virgin. He's only
messaged two of them. He's only know two
that I've been with. Triple. He only
knows two, lad.
It was only two.
Yep. I heard I heard I heard.
He only messaged two. He doesn't know
anyone else. The [ __ ] virgin.
The absolute virgin.
It's cuz he's a virgin and he's too ugly
to get anything normal himself. But it
was only two people.
You went absolutely nowhere near that girl.
You've absolutely You went absolutely
nowhere near that girl, Aisha. You know,
you've seen me in bed with many women.
You've also seen me You've also seen me
have a [ __ ] with a woman.
But again, you're biased, so that's
fine. But you went absolutely nowhere
near that girl.
You went absolutely nowhere near that girl.
Yeah. Nowhere near that gal. Sexually.
[ __ ] her on a park bench. Get real
good. You didn't [ __ ] nothing, you little virgin.
[ __ ] park bench.
No one's seen me in bed with many women. Really?
Should we go down memory lane with
Goldilocks and the Free Bears?
Goldilocks and the Free Bears.
Do you want to go down memory lane with
Goldilocks and the Free Bears?
I'm pretty sure we have. I can list them
out if you want.
19year-old Nottingham Manchester Sig no
bro really no
really no really no
You've never seen me in bed with any of
them. Okay, Mr. Biased
biasness on here.
Why are they so biased on this
community? Can I ask you this? Why you so biased?
That's what makes me think it's jealousy
on this community, Steven Howard. This
is what makes me think it's jealousy
with these people.
No, I'm not telling that story again.
This is what makes me think it's
jealousy with these people. And we're
not even just talking about women. We're
talking about for we're talking about meetups.
We're talking about meetups.
Well, actually, I was 25 at the time, so Yeah.
I mean, I was 25 and she was 19. Yeah. Yeah,
I'm thinking it's jealousy with these people.
And it's not just about women, it's
about everything. I've listed you many
examples on how they're biased.
The women, what they see, uh, [ __ ] like that.
There's definitely jealousy on here, bro.
Definitely jealous on here. >> [snorts]
>> I was 25 and she was 19. Yeah, she was
boring though. She didn't suck my Willie
the first time I met her. She did the
second time though, Dusty.
She didn't suck my Willie the first time
I [ __ ] her Dusty in the hotel, but the
second time she did.
Bit boring, isn't it, Dusty?
Yeah, she didn't suck my willie the
first time. UK, but she did the second
and the other times after that. Yeah.
Yeah. Peter Belly's Willie.
Why is it revoling?
Oh, it's revoling now.
Why is it revoling, lad?
Yeah, I can three times and the rest of
the times I just got my I just got a [ __ ]
Yeah, I was horny after the club. Yeah. [snorts]
>> Maybe Charles Lee Ray done it. Um, no.
Depends how much you've tried with the
dating scene. With me, no. For anyone
else who hasn't really tried,
maybe. But for me personally, no.
Because of how much I've tried and [ __ ]
No. Oh, are you a struggle dismisser?
Wonder why you can't get a woman. A
woman. I've already had women. Biased.
Biasness again. Every time you're
biased, I'm just going to keep bringing
up how you're biased.
Biasness. And you're a struggle
dismisser as well.
You're also a struggle dismisser.
I love that when you say no wonder you
can't get a w a woman even though I've
put up like a million approaches where
they've been [ __ ]
Good old struggle dismisser.
Peter belly. My channel wouldn't be what
it is without struggle dismissers.
I've literally shown you messages where
women have been [ __ ] Struggle dismisser. ignorant.
Her friend was telling me that she's got
anxiety and stuff.
She was telling me that her friends got
anx Her friend was telling me that she's
got anxiety and [ __ ]
She said Charles used to abuse her. [ __ ] good. [ __ ] good, lovely, lovely.
Oh, that's lovely.
Yeah, that's lovely, bro. Yeah.
No, it's definitely women that are the
problem and other people prove and other
people's proving that
women are definitely the problem. That's
why you can go on 102 different channels
of men and they'll get the same [ __ ] by
women. Nope. It's definitely the women.
And also another thing is you keep
defending women is not going to make
them like you. Just throwing that out there.
So, nope. Uh women are definitely bloody
the problem. Uh cuz if you go on other
people's channels, you will see women
act the same [ __ ] the same [ __ ] way.
Nope. Definitely women.
I've noticed it on the Ed Struggle uh
the Ed Matthews um thing as well when I
watch Ed Matthews. Nope. Nope.
Definitely the women. They're definitely
definitely the women
and other people in London. It's
definitely definitely women.
Definitely definitely definitely
definitely definitely definitely the women.
Definitely definitely definitely the
women. It's 100% the women.
I don't understand, Dusty, how they can
still say that women aren't the problem.
And I've put approaching videos out
there. Delusional, bro. Autism. Autism
to the max.
You don't think I'm the problem? It's
already proven to be a gender thing.
Um, somehow Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Do you want me to explain?
Just because I've had women, it doesn't
mean I'm going to lick their asses and
don't think that they do any wrong. I'm
not a white knight. I'm not a s like
you. I'm not a white knight and a s. I
don't need to lick women's asses. I
could have had a million women. I'd
still say they're [ __ ] and they're [laughter]
cuz I've met women. I know what they're
like. Doesn't matter how many I've been with, you know?
And it's not somehow. I've shown me with
women. Again, it's not somehow. I've
shown you. I don't need to I don't need
to lick women's asses. I'm not a loser.
Only absolute losers defend women.
Virgins. Only people do that.
You know, the only people that defend
women are virgins that don't get women.
They're the only ones that stick that
stick up for them. You know,
well, I don't have respect for women. I
hope they all get raped.
Well, I hope they all get raped. And
tomorrow, I'm going to be approaching to
the maximum and the next person that I
come across, I'm ding and dashing them.
So, now I'm motivated even more than ever.
I'm going to find one to [ __ ] over. Definitely. Yeah.
Well, I hope they all get raped. And
that's me saying something and I'll say
it here right now.
And you watch what I'm doing tomorrow, bro.
You watch what I'm doing tomorrow. Yeah.
Watch, bro. Yeah. [ __ ] this.
Yeah. It's not funny, mate, when this
person is going to get nicked because
they can't pay the bill.
Watch, bro. I ain't going to stop. Trust
me, brother. I'm not going to stop.
Give these [ __ ] back of what they've
gave me over the years.
You know what I mean, Grezy?
Well, I will be getting one tomorrow.
I'll go out every I'll go out every week
until I get one.
I'll go out every week until I get one.
I'm not going to stop.
I am going to do it as soon as I find
someone. I, like I said, if it all
fails, I'll just go with the tenant.
I'll just go with the ex-tenant
and [ __ ] the tenant over. As long as
they're a woman they're getting [ __ ] over, Grezy.
As soon as I find a woman that will
meet, I'm I'm [ __ ] them over. Simple.
It doesn't matter who they are, what
they look like. Black, white, mixed
race, I don't give a [ __ ]
what they are. They're getting [ __ ] over.
You like that, Grezy?
I might even blackmail one as well.
I might even blackmail one.
I'm not going to let these [ __ ] women win. Yeah,
I might order a McDonald's
groovy. I'm not sure.
No no no no no. Yep.
Yeah. But it's going to come cold, isn't
it? But yeah, I'm just going to die and
then dash someone.
I want to make them pay for all the [ __ ]
they've done to me over the years.
I really want to give these [ __ ] some
back of what they gave me over the years. Bro.
Uh, let me have a little look,
Grezy. Let me have a little look what's
on the menu.
Let me have a little look what's on the menu.
I only had fried chicken earlier.
There's some burgers here.
I get maybe like a burger or something.
Oh gosh darn it.
Should I get like a burger? Do you think
there's a Grinch at McDonald's?
No, that's not true. Let me have a little look. Oh gosh.
Oh yeah, [laughter]
the grits mill. What's that all about?
What? You get a free pair of socks.
What the [ __ ] bro?
What the [ __ ] is that all about? Yeah.
Oh, I might get that and then wear the
socks tomorrow when I go out and about.
What is it? It's a big M though, is it? One second.
Should I get a nine nugget meal or a Big
Mac meal? Big Mac meal.
Yeah, it is a dead meal.
Big tasty is nice. Yeah.
No, I tell you what I like. I like that
Philly steak one. No, no, no, no, no.
One sec. They might not have it anymore.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Damn it. No.
That's a cheesy chicken.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I hope they ain't took it off the [ __ ] menu.
I think they've took it out the [ __ ]
menu, the [ __ ]
They've took it off the [ __ ] menu,
Oh gosh darn it.
Oh gosh darn it, Grezy. Uh,
I just I might just go Burger King. [ __ ] it.
Okay with you, boss.
I always get the same thing from Burger
King all the time.
I'll get it tomorrow. McDonald's. I'll
go to McDonald's tomorrow in Grey and get it.
No, I always get the bacon double Cheese
XL. It's the same as what uh Bomb used to get.
Bacon Double Cheese XL.
I always will get the same as bomb
because that I like cheese and bacon and
that's it. Is it?
I'm a Muslim.
I don't want a cola.
Oh, did you get a Coke as well? Why?
Coca-Cola cost 18 p more. I'll have that. £12.
So, it's £14 for this meal. Should I get it?
Well, I'm not from Kent, so I can afford
it. Yeah, I'm not from Kent, am I? So, I
can afford it.
Yeah, there we go.
See, if I was from Kent and not London,
I'd have to think about it a bit more
because of the finances, you know.
So, is that okay that I got that burger?
I prefer Burger King.
Would I be getting my vitamins from this grey?
Would I be getting my vage for this? [laughter]
No, she's asleep.
I [ __ ] hate these women UK asylum. I
want to make them pay for all the bad
things they've done to me and put me through
and keeping me sexless and [ __ ] I
really want revenge.
It's playtime tomorrow. It's playtime.
I'm getting revenge.
And they're probably out there now
sucking other people's dicks and giving
them sex. These scumbags probably going
for people in prison. UK asylum.
It will never change, bro. Never change.
Have you ever been with someone UK
signing that don't give you sex? Uh,
sorry. That gives you sex but don't give
you a [ __ ]
I've had it before where they haven't.
I have. I've had it where they haven't
gave it low job.
Um, yes, I have once. Yep. [ __ ] madness.
Oh, [ __ ] It's a madness, bro.
What does one do, though? What does one do?
It's sad, isn't it, Dusty?
Sad. It's got to be this way.
I generally think women are evil, bro.
I generally think they're evil.
I honestly wouldn't be [ __ ] going out
tomorrow if it weren't for my sister, bro.
I am really really done. Like you
believe me in it, Greasy. I'm really really done
cuz I shouldn't have to try again. I
shouldn't have to go out trying again.
I shouldn't have to be going out trying
again. You get me? Why does someone like
me have to try? I should have to try.
Uh, they my mom dismisses it.
No, I'm not I'm not accepting it.
We can't let these [ __ ] women win. Do
you remember her, Quezy? Don't let these
[ __ ] women win. Huh?
They just dismissed my struggles.
Well, I don't speak to my sisters about
it, but yeah, they just dis My mom just
used to dismiss my struggles.
They just dismiss it.
So, you can't really talk. It's
basically you can't talk to anyone about
it. Basically, you can't talk to anyone
about it because they just dismiss struggles.
So, you can't actually speak to anyone
about it. It doesn't matter who they are
because they just dismiss it and then
defend a woman
cuz I told um you remember that one that
I had going on a wild goose chasey the
one that was being a [ __ ] the one that
was being passive aggressive that I was
going to die in a dash and my mom found
out about it and no matter what I told
her that she done she weren't having
none of it. It didn't suit her.
Uh she weren't having none of it. I said
that she was being a [ __ ] and she
weren't having it at all at all at all
as the tenant would say. So then I
thought, well, if they're just going to
keep dismissing your struggles, [ __ ]
him, is it? So yeah,
lay need the struggle dismisser.
Yeah, they dismiss your struggles, lad.
Because their excuse is going to be
you're too young for them.
cuz their excuse is going to be that
Well, you can't get f, you know, in
Thailand, you know, the women that
you're going to be getting in Thailand
are people that are in their 30s. You do
realize that? So, you can get a you can
get a relationship there, but they're
going to be in their 30s.
So, you can't get anyone that's in your
30s here. You can't find no one there.
It doesn't matter what age they are.
If you go to Thailand now, you can get
someone in their 30s.
Yeah. You get someone in their 30s easy
that wants a relationship. But bro,
you're not getting a 30y old here.
You're not getting a 40y old here. Trust
me. Trust me. They're full of [ __ ] as well. So
lady doesn't eat curry.
You don't need to pay with Thailand.
Yeah, but there's Oh my god. You can go
on Tinder and the women come to you and
you don't even need to pay them. There
are women that you don't need to pay.
There are people that want to be in a
relationship with you.
There is. Trust me. Ant-Man's got a girlfriend.
He's got a girlfriend.
And he doesn't pay her.
He doesn't pay her. So
maybe I can become like Johnny Sins. Greavvesy,
you don't know who Johnny Sins is, do you?
Nah, I can't watch him, bro. I can't watch him.
I can't watch that Johnny Sims. It's too fake.
It has to be old vintage porn.
I was dead, man. I like interracial um porn.
No, he's a porn star.
No, he's a porn star. Greavves.
Uh, it's not even natural, bra. It's not
No, no, no, no, no. It's not even just
because you can't get laid. It's because
we don't want to deal with stuck up
[ __ ] that think they're better than
you. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. It's
not even just that. It's not even that.
You can you can you you okay? You can
stay in England and keep dealing with
these women [ __ ] their attitude and have
no respect for yourself or go somewhere
where you're treated like royalty. I I I
know what the option is.
You know, I I I know exactly. It's a
no-brainer for me. You either want to
stay in in this country and deal with
these stuck up [ __ ] that have got attitude problems
or you leave.
So it's it's that's even worse than
going to a third world country. So I
don't know why you're laughing at it.
I don't know why you're laughing.
Anyone that's got respect for themselves
will just jump on that plane and leave. Simple.
Someone that's willing to put up with
their [ __ ] over and over and over and
over and over again has got problems.
But don't forget, Grevy, they Well,
actually, they consider you weak, don't they?
They consider you weak, Grezy,
if you give up, don't they? If you want
to deal with If you don't want to deal
with toxic women anymore, they call you
Yeah. They call you weak, don't they?
But if a woman wants to give up, she
made the right choice. Cuts. Yeah.
from nons legs on clinch channel. By the way, [snorts]
this is just self projection. Very very self-p projection.
Yeah, this is self projection, bro.
This is self projection.
All right, there's a lot of
self-reflectors on this community,
Grezy. A lot of self-reflectors.
Oh, the burger's out for delivery. The
burger's out for delivery. I can't wait.
I can't wait. Greasy. You know
what would you do if you was me, Dusty?
Well, I just stay in now and save money.
I don't see the point in going out.
Yep. I just don't see the point in going out
if I'm honest. Yeah.
We can't let these [ __ ] women win. Grezy
Dusty, we can't let these [ __ ] women win.
Dusty, what would you do if you was me
with the this womanship?
Seek out revenge.
Would you seek out revenge?
I would seek out revenge. Me? That's
what I'm doing.
I'm seeking out revenge.
Well, what would you do?
What would you do then?
Oh, do you remember that account when I
used to say um them [ __ ] were laughing
at us, greasy, and then they thought I
said them [ __ ] were laughing at you and
then they changed it to them [ __ ] were
laughing at us.
No, not me. I hold grudges.
If I ever see that USA isn't he mate,
that's what they get, mate.
I ordered myself a burger cuz I was hungry.
Didn't see you there, Laney.
Oh, I need to go pee actually before I go downstairs.
Do you reckon one of my punches are hard? We've
reckon they're hard my punches.
They [ __ ] are.
No, I don't move on me.
That hurt my mouth, by the way, doing that.
Yeah, that hurt my [ __ ] mouth doing
that, mate. You reckon one of my punches
could knock someone out? I reckon.
Oh, I should really wear my gown. I
haven't worn my gown today.
You remember when me and Timmy was
fighting Grezy? [laughter]
You like that, didn't you? When they
come in the door, I had to rush back. Do
you remember when they come in the door?
They said, "Oh, we're coming in your
door." And then I was at my mom's. Do you remember?
And I was like, I'm [ __ ] coming back,
mate. I'm coming back. You remember?
You remember, Grezy?
[laughter] Did you like it? Yeah.
It's funny, is it?
Yeah, they Yeah, they said that they were isabelle.
Yeah, he was pretending to be Isabelle.
I remember that time. Crazy. Yeah. [laughter]
Yeah. I remember that. You're right. Captain. >> [laughter] >> Yeah,
I just want to [ __ ] throw you, man. I
want to throw you. I want to [ __ ]
throw you, you virgin [ __ ]
Yeah, I'll get him right that [ __ ]
elbow the virgin [ __ ] in his face.
You went absolutely nowhere near that
girl. You went nowhere near Aisha. You
went absolutely nowhere near that girl.
You went nowhere near that girl. Do you
like that, Grezy?
You absolutely did not have sex with
her. Aisha is a Muslim and she does not
do any of them things, you know.
Oh, one minute away. One minute away.
Hurry up. I'm [ __ ] starving. Christmas.
I think I should get a free £10 today.
They give you a bonus at Christmas. The
benefits gre extra 10 quid.
So that might pay for this, you know.
Bro, it's cold out there, man.
Oh my god, bro. It's cold out there, man.
Holy [ __ ] Yeah, man.
Hopefully that Oh, bro, it's cold. Oh my
god, it is cold out here.
Where's the skin [ __ ] [laughter] six? Yeah. >> Nope.
>> One six. Yeah. >> Yeah. What's up?
>> Thank you, Captain.
I got the goods.
What fun is that?
Hopefully the burger is still warm.
Fingers crossed. Fingers crossed.
It seems bad. Oh,
that [ __ ] [ __ ]
for a while on my channel
day before last. Yeah.
One second. Can you hear me?
I'm having this burger. It's skin.
It don't even taste that good, bro.
didn't get my um money.
This is um this is uh
Hopefully. Yeah, this is Burger King. I
prefer Burger King than McDonald's.
But the best burger place is Gourmet
Burger Kitchen, hands down. Oh.
I was watching Cal Freezy, Dusty. Do you
know Cal Freezy? I was watching Cal Freezy yesterday.
I was watching Cal Freezy's video
and he had the Reaper burger like I had.
He had a Reaper burger like I had and he
even said it was the hottest thing he's
ever had. I told you it's hot, bro. I
told you that Reaper burger will kill you, bro.
That power line of reaper will kill you.
I had more than one bite though. I beat health really.
Burger is nice.
Five Guys is good. Dusty Five Guys with
a milkshake is good, but it's overpriced.
Leaves. I think you come on here to mock me, do you?
I hope you don't mock me.
All right. Hopefully. Do you reckon that
Ricky Millington will meet me? Dusty,
imagine me and Ricky Milling up having a beer.
Yeah, there's a bully in there.
>> Yeah, man. Don't bully me. Stop it. Mhm. Please be
my favorite of him is Kieran. Kieran's my favorite.
He's not biased at you people.
Yeah, he's not biased like you people.
He does. He doesn't suck the dump st's
dick. He's not rectile dysfunction dick.
That's what I like about.
He doesn't suck dick.
He ain't been on it for a while.
No, he's not. He's right about all of
you. You're biased when it comes to
nonsense. You're definitely definitely biased.
You're so far up his ass. It's unreal. He's right.
Yeah, Rocky Roy. Yeah. Yeah, he's right
about you though. You are biased.
Definitely biased on you,
but you admit it anyways.
You're definitely biased.
Definitely not something. Definitely.
Definitely. Definitely. Definitely. Bias.
He's another virgin. Well, then he'll be
like your boyfriend then, would he?
Well, then if he's another virgin, he's
like he's like the open version then,
isn't he? He's like your best mate.
Yeah. Well, then he's like your best
mate then, isn't he?
Well, then he's like your best mate.
Takes one to no one, doesn't it?
Like your virgin boyfriend
with a disabled girlfriend.
So, do you reckon Ricky Millington will
meet me or not?
Do you reckon Ricky Millington will meet me?
Yeah. I hate the fact that he's got a disabled girlfriend.
Yeah, bro. You got me.
Yeah. Yeah. He hates the fact that I've
been with normal women. He's the one
that's obsessed with me. I'm not the one
that's obsessed with him. Again, biased
nons lover. You're saying that Kieran's
a mong, right? But he can see through
what you people are doing. Your biasness.
This is why he doesn't come on here.
That's one of the reasons I won't be
coming on here after uh after this live
stream for a little bit.
It's the dick sucking and the biasness.
I'm sick of seeing it. You know, Dusty,
it gets very tiring seeing it. Very, very tiring.
I don't want a disabled girlfriend.
I've got more money. I'm better looking.
I've never had to resort to disabled. I
don't know how much clear I have to make
it to you. [ __ ] me.
I don't want a disabled girlfriend that
don't sleep with me. I'm not jealous of
that. I don't hate someone. He hates me
cuz I'm better looking than him. Again,
his YouTube channel gives him away,
bro. He's the one obsessed with me. I
don't want to be with a disabled girl
that don't sleep with me. If I was ever
with a disabled girl that don't give me
sex, I would go up the [ __ ] wall.
Ain't no jealous of some fat ugly [ __ ]
that don't [ __ ] him.
Disabled by the game. You're biased. You
two are jealous of me. So you'll be in
it together. And that's why I'm quitting
YouTube is because of the biasness. It's
the jealousy and the biasness. That's
why I'm coming off it next year. I can't
wait cuz these jealous people will never
leave me alone. The jealousy towards me.
This is why I come off of it for three
weeks. The jealousy towards Peter Belly,
it needs a break from, lad.
Yeah. And I've also had more women than
you and him combined, and none of them were disabled.
And I've had more girlfriends than him,
and more women than him, which I've
shown on camera. Shouldn't you be on his
[ __ ] channel sucking his dick?
Shouldn't you be on his channel sucking
his dick, lad?
If I've been called a bun and I've had
more girls than him, that's saying
something then, isn't it, lad?
Yeah, they're all stinking. They're all
people that are jealous of me. And I
mean it. And that's why I come off of
here for ages.
I know. I've told you it's jealousy.
It's cuz I'm younger and better looking.
They can't even deny it anymore.
Yeah. They can't even deny it anymore.
They can't even deny it anymore. That's
what happens when you're younger and
better looking and you stumble across
this community. They'll find problems with you.
They'll pick problems with you.
Oh, uh, saying that.
Yeah. Well, you're going to Well, you're
going to watch it again. You're going to
watch it again. You people are jealous
of me. You're going to watch it again,
and you're going to keep watching it cuz
you jealous people need to [ __ ] get a life.
and stop being jealous of people just
cuz they're younger and better looking
than you. You're going to watch it
again. You're going to keep watching the episode.
Yeah. Also, another thing is one more. I
wanted to say another thing about this
Mark Samson. 28. I've had more women
than you. I'm younger than you and
better looking than you. You're in your
40s and you've never had a girlfriend.
Self projection. Just like what Pat
Mustard used to do. 28. Yeah. Not 48 and
never had a girlfriend like you. And
every time I say this stuff about you,
it's facts. Every time I say this stuff
about you, I'm 28. I have had a
girlfriend and I've had more women than
you. You're [ __ ] middleag. You can't
afford decent trainers. And you're ugly.
Look at yourself. [ __ ] the 28-year-old.
Look at the 40year-old who's never had a
girlfriend. Look at you, [ __ ] boy.
Look at the [ __ ] Terry with shitty
trainers who's never had a girlfriend.
[ __ ] the 28-year-old. Stop self projecting,
bro. You're in your 40s and you've never
had a girlfriend. [ __ ] the 28-year-old.
Look at you. This is what I had to say
to another person. This is literally
what I had to say to another person. You
don't have a girlfriend. And I tried to
say it in the most clearest way I
possibly can. You don't have a woman.
You don't have a girlfriend. You are
ugly. You are a ma. And no matter how
many times you tell these jealous
people, bro, they still don't get it in
their thick head. And another thing,
yes, I have had a girlfriend anyways.
And I'm not, yeah, yes, I have had a
girlfriend. And again, we're not
self-reflecting on me anyways. These
people have never had a girlfriend. They
don't have a woman.
So stop self-reflecting your [ __ ] onto me. Anyways,
also another thing is when that Mark
Samson thing happened, I don't think
Monty was on YouTube.
No, I think he was on YouTube actually.
So, they've been biased for
When did I start saying stuff about
kids? I can tell you exactly when this
was. No, they were biased about
they were biased ages before that, bro.
when that Izzy thing was going on.
Yeah, that was ages ago. Yeah, they like
I said to anyone on here, bro. Yeah, he
was on YouTube, but I don't think I said
anything. Anyone who's watching this, if
you're younger and better looking than
these people, they'll pick problems
because of jealousy. This is a community
for the fat, ugly people that ain't got
a life. So, if you're younger and better
looking, they'll find problems with you.
This is what they do. They'll pick out
problems because of jealousy
and become biased. And and this is what
I warn any anyone that thinks about
coming on this community, Dusty. It's
the truth because I they've been biased
with that Mark Samson thing for the
longest, bro. That's why I don't fight
people. That's why I don't meet up with
people. You know, I could easily meet
that guy today and smash his [ __ ]
face in. But I wouldn't even waste my
time, waste my energy, waste my money
because we all know I'm better looking
than all of you people. I'm better
looking than all of you people. And
that's enough to get you people jealous.
I'm better looking than all of you
people. And that's a fact. So whether
I'm ugly, good-looking, average, guess
what? I'm better looking than all of you people.
And that's enough. So eat that dick, brother. Yeah,
you just try to bring other people down
to your level. But the thing is, all of
the people on Lord J's, all of the
people on Lord J's, they're all on the
same level. You see these people?
That's why they get on with each other.
Yeah. Terry, you're boring. I've already
gone to your area and you've not met.
You didn't meet me. I've already gone to
your area and you didn't meet me.
Yeah. And no one cares about your
opinion. No one cares about yourself
projecting opinion. Come on this
channel. Right. Listen, bro. Listen.
Join my join my um live and show your
face and tell me that I'm This is self
projecting again. You come on here right
now, show your face and tell me what I
look like. Until then, shut the [ __ ] up.
Right. Most women's opinion, I've been
with more women than you, bro. I've been
with more women than you. So, how how
does that make up? How does that how
does that work? I have been with more
girls. I've had more girlfriends than
you. How does that make work? I've been
with more women than all of you people
in this community combined.
Again, self projecting from you fat ugly
people time and time again.
One second. I'll put a link up.
So, why is someone that's ugly had more
women than you? Can you explain it? So
that must mean you're seriously ugly
then, bro. And you've seen me with women
as well. You've never had a girlfriend.
Why have you never had a girlfriend?
It's not owning, it's facts with these people.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Right.
I'll put the link up. Why is this not
working? Hold on. Come in and tell me.
Come on and tell me what you look like.
Come on. Show me what you look like,
bro. Come on,
bro. We've seen me with more women and
girls than you. Where's your girlfriend?
Where's your girlfriend? Come on. The
link's up there, you little self-reflector. Come on.
Where's your girlfriend? And that's what
I always say to these people. Where's
your woman? Why have we never seen you with women? Come on.
Oh, fantasy stories. I knew it was you.
You got bullied by Pat Mustin. I knew it
was the bun.
Big up PJ. You're
got bullied by Pat. Big up. Big up boy.
Run away from boy. Pat busted. Bullied
you good, didn't he?
>> No matter how you run, you're still unattractive.
>> I've had more girls than you. More women
than you. Virgin boy. You're still a virgin.
>> You've never
Yes, I have had a girlfriend. Where's your girlfriend?
>> Where's your girlfriend? Where's your
girlfriend? Where's your girlfriend?
Yeah. Yeah. Where's your girlfriend? I
ask you a quick question.
>> Where's your girlfriend?
>> Quick question.
>> Where's your girlfriend? Where's your
girlfriend? Tell us where your girlfriend is.
>> Where's your girlfriend? You can't answer it.
>> Very, very brief question.
>> Where's a woman's G-spot? PJ, where's the woman's
>> Got ugly Irish. Where's your boyfriend?
>> Answer the question. Where is the woman's G-spot?
>> Where's your girlfriend? Ugly boy.
>> That question.
>> You keep calling people a M. Where's your girlfriend?
>> You're a virgin. that question.
>> Where's a woman she spun? Where is woman?
>> Girlfriend. Where's your girlfriend?
>> Why can't you answer that question? DJ,
you don't have a girlfriend. So, a
single Irish man living with his girlfriend.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. For happy. I don't
have a girlfriend. You're right. You ran
away. You're correct. TJ, you're
correct. I don't have a girlfriend.
Where's woman's G-spot?
>> What? Yeah, because you're Why don't you
have a girlfriend?
>> Where is a woman's G-spot,
>> bro? I'm not explained to a virgin when
you're a virgin.
You want me to put the porno up again?
Bro, how can I be a virgin when have me
in bed with women? [ __ ] idiot. The
guy is a [ __ ] clown. And another
thing is, right, we are not even making
excuses for you, bro. No one's going to
go to Ireland and meet you when we've
seen you run away from Pat Mustard, you
[ __ ] [ __ ] You've run away from pot
mustard, you [ __ ] Anyways, come in
and show your face. You can't show your
face cuz you're ugly.
The moment one of you people come on
here and show your face and you're
better looking than me, come back to me,
bro. You can't do it. See me.
See me. See, the thing is, M, listen to
me. M, right? I can go on this black
guy's channel right now and call him
ugly. Call him stinking. Call him this.
Call him that. But guess what, bro? If
he puts the link up, I can show my face.
You can't show your face cuz you're ugly.
That's something I'll always have
against you, you little m. And stop
telling people to go to Ireland, bro.
You ran away from Pat Mustard. It's
embarrassing now. Like, it's really,
really embarrassing. No one's going to
go to Ireland to watch you hide again,
bro. Like you did with Pat Mustard.
We've seen you run away from Pat Busted.
You [ __ ] [ __ ] You absolute [ __ ]
Everyone remembers it, but they probably
won't bring it up because why they're
biased. So, yeah. biased people on here.
Yeah, they're biased people on here, is
it? So, uh yeah,
you're a really sad bastard. And you're
supposed to be like my age as well. And
you and you're still doing this after
running away from Pat Mustard. Jesus
Christ. You really are a sad bastard,
aren't you? But the thing is, you can't
show your face. But it's okay though
because all of the people fantasy
stories that haven't shown their face in
the past that's been docked have all
been ugly and you're no different.
So I mean you projectors have been shown
time and time again what you look like.
Bro, you can talk about women all you
want hating me. Bro, I've been with more
women than you would ever have
hotliners. Do not make me put the videos
back up all over again. You sad [ __ ]
You sad [ __ ] [ __ ]
You know, you're not. Yeah. And I'm
stating facts about you. You're an old
[ __ ] that that can't afford new
traders. That's facts. And I went to
your area and you didn't come out.
That's facts. Let's talk about facts.
You're little. You got shitty traders.
You're old. You're ugly. You didn't come
out when I when I went to your area.
These are all facts. You didn't come to
my area and I didn't come out. You have
never been to my area and I didn't come
out. I went to your area and you didn't
come out. I went to your area and you
did not come out. Let's start talking
about facts, [ __ ]
[ __ ] hell, man. So, yeah.
>> Why did you run away from that mustard?
>> I still can't believe you couldn't
answer that question. That's mental. Your age.
>> I could answer it, but I'm not answering
your question. Self.
>> No, you couldn't answer it, PJ.
>> Your self-reflecting question.
>> But I have a simpler question. I have a
more simple question. I have a more
>> Describe a describe what a [ __ ] looks
like. Describe what the [ __ ] looks like.
>> You're a virgin, so you would know.
There's no point explaining to a virgin.
So, you don't need to explain to me sex education.
>> Okay. So, explain it. Explain it. PJ, explain it,
>> bro. I put a porno out there.
>> What does it look like? Explain it.
>> I'm not answering your questions.
>> That's insane. You are without a doubt a
virgin. Without a shadow of a
>> virgin. I'm a virgin. Really, bro? These
people are [ __ ] disabled, bro.
Honestly, I'm a virgin.
Yeah. Anyways, I'm coming off of this
after this live stream anyways and I
won't be back for a while.
These people really are [ __ ]
I'm a virgin. Okay, bro. Yeah.
>> Yeah, I'm a virgin.
These people are a waste of time, bro.
Is it really are a waste of time?
I'm a virgin, man. What the [ __ ] bro?
All right, Greavvesy, are you still there?
Oh, you still Yeah, this person's
dismissing my struggles again.
Steven Howard Greavvesy.
Yeah, it's still dismissing
Dusty. It's still dismissing struggles
because people that don't dismiss
struggles are are are thrown back by
stuff you show them.
Yeah. Yeah, it is. Look, I don't think
you need revenge. Honestly, dude, you
need therapy. I don't even mean this in
a dorito way, but you'll clearly have a
lot of anger inside you, especially
towards women, regardless of whether you
feel they deserve it or not. Make it
less unhealthy both of you and women you
might date later. Yep. dismissing my
struggles because anyone that doesn't
because I told her about some stuff that
happened and [ __ ] Yep. That's dismissing struggles
because they don't seem thrown back by
what you're showing them which is which
is dismissing struggles
which is dismissing struggles
because they don't say anything about
anything that you show them which is dismissing struggles.
That's the whole point of dismissing struggles.
They dismiss anything that they do.
Yeah, it's dismissing. Yes.
Whether you needed therapy or not,
Dusty, why do they dismiss people's struggles?
Why do they Why do they do it, bro?
Why do they dismiss people's struggles?
Because they don't believe what they're
writing. But I don't know why they say
it. Because they don't believe it.
Yeah, I'm a virgin, bro. Okay.
Yeah. Yeah, I'm a virgin. Even though
I've proved I've had sex many times.
Yeah, I know I'm a virgin. Anyways, why
do they just miss people's struggle? Why
do they just miss people's struggles?
Come on, Dusty. Give me a completely
unbiased unbiased opinion. Come on.
Yeah, women hate you as well. Fantasy
stories. They hate you as well.
Yeah. Well, you would care if I was a
woman. Well, well, they'd care about my
struggles if I was a woman. So,
I mean, if I was a woman, they'd care
about my struggles.
Yeah. Women hate me. But guess what? At
least I've had their bodies. At least
I've had sex out of them. You've never
had sex. Fantasy stories. Bro, if you
really want to speak some truth, come to
London and say it to my face. You know
how I live. Come on, bro. If you really
want to speak some truth or speak the
truth, come to London, bro. I'll meet
you anywhere you want. No one's going to
go to Ireland when we know what you do.
We've seen it with Pat Mustard. I will
meet you anywhere in London you want.
London's a fun place. You know what?
I'll make the exception for you. I would
make the exception for you. Yeah, they
hate you as well. I know, bro. But I've
been with them. I've had sex with them.
At least I've been with women unlike
you. At least I've had their body. At
least I'm not single like you.
single virgin like you. I could be a
single virgin like you, bro. It could be
worse. I could be so hated that I'm a
single virgin like you. Hated by women
like you are, [laughter]
bro. I will 100% smash your face in on
February. I will 100% smash your ugly
Irish face in that past that rusted
thing annoyed me, bro. I will knock the
[ __ ] out of you. You I bastard. You
[ __ ] Irish [ __ ] Yeah, I will 100%,
bro. 100% knock the [ __ ] out of you. But
let's face it, you're not coming to
London because you done the same thing
with Bomb. You done the same thing with Bomb, bro.
The same thing with Bomb.
You've done the same thing with Bomb.
You said you was going to Manchester.
You're not going anywhere, man. You're
not going anywhere. And I'm not going to
you because we saw what you done with
Pat Mustard. Well, if you can't even
meet a fat old man, if you if you can't
even meet a fat old man, bro, you're not
going to meet me. Yeah. Simple.
You're not about that life. Stop it.
Uh because when I went to your area, you
didn't show up. Stay out of this. Uh
because when I went to your area last
time, you didn't show up. That's why I
won't meet you. Because I went to your
your virgin area last time and you
didn't show up.
You called me out. I went to your area
and you didn't show up. Waste of [ __ ]
time. It took me ages to get there as
well. You [ __ ] [ __ ] out. You little
Listen, Terry. Right. If you really
wanted to meet me, you'd come on my
door. You'd come on my door. You would
come on my door. Especially since you
pussied out last time. Shut up. You're
not about it. I went to your area and
you didn't show up. End the story.
That's that. So, take that L.
He's not coming to [ __ ]
Right. He's not coming to London.
He's an absolute virgin. Yeah.
Let me put the link out again.
>> You can say women hate me when they hate
you more. You're single and a virgin.
They hate you. What the [ __ ]
They [ __ ] hate you. They're leaving
you single and you've never been with a
woman. That's worse than me. At least
I've been with them and you're [ __ ] a single virgin.
There you go.
But I'm off after today anyways.
Oh, your b. How about you get the Uber
here? How about you get this Uber here
right now and I'll stay up for you. How
about you get the Uber here now and I'll
wait for you. Come on.
Come on. And you, Sam, you absolute virgin.
Come on, Sam. You [ __ ] Irish virgin
[ __ ] who women hate you. No girlfriend,
no sex life. [ __ ] virgin. Come on.
You Irish leprechaorn [ __ ] Yeah.
Come on. You like that, Dusty?
You [ __ ] [ __ ]
You [ __ ] Irish [ __ ] who's hated by
women. Never had sex. No girlfriend. I
can say girlfriend more than more than I
can I can say it better than these
[ __ ] you know. So, if you want to
get an Uber here, I'll wait for you.
I'll stay up if you want.
You're virgin, can't you?
[ __ ] you [ __ ] virgin. You know
the [ __ ] is this?
>> So no excuses for February Munter.
>> Yes, you Irish mun that got bullied from
Pat Mustard. I love you. You Irish
virgin [ __ ] with no girlfriend. Okay, so
>> you [ __ ] Irish [ __ ] No girlfriend,
no sex life, no money. Run away from Pat Mustard.
the 12th of February 17th. Are you available, mother?
>> Are you bringing your girlfriend? Oh,
you don't have a girlfriend cuz
>> Yes or no? Are you available at that date? Mother,
>> yes, I am. You Irish mondon.
>> Yes, I am Irish manta with no girlfriend.
>> You will be there as Who you coming
with? Who you coming with?
>> Okay, let's make it simple. Okay.
>> Are you live in London? I will crew up in London.
>> You don't have a girlfriend cuz you're a bunch.
Listen up. You will be at a set location
with your camera on. Can you do those things?
>> Yes. Yes. Yes.
>> Okay. Pick a date between the 12th and the 17th.
>> The 12th.
>> Will I arrive on the 12th? You [ __ ]
>> Yeah. I want you as soon as you get off
that plane, you Irish single bas.
You ain't got one. You're ugly cuz women hate you.
>> 7 p.m. Mother.
>> I can show me kissing a woman. Where's your girlfriend?
>> Yes or no? 700 p.m.
>> Come on, you Irish banter.
>> Can you do 7:00 p.m. on the 12th? >> Yes.
>> Can you go live at a set location if I
prove I'm in London?
>> Yes. Yes.
>> Okay. So, after I b after you get your
face smashed in, can you also explain
why every time you fought you've run
away like a coward and cried?
>> Okay. On one condition,
>> I can. Yeah.
>> Okay. So, why did you run from a
12-year-old? I can I can follow mother apologizing.
Why did you run away from Pat Mustard?
Why did you put your question?
>> Why did you say sorry to Pat Mustard without me
YouTube for 2 years? Why?
Why have you never seen you in London?
Why have you got no girlfriend? Why are
you scared to say I'm going to waste my time?
>> Why do you run away from
you got a girlfriend?
Peter Belly owns it.
>> But we've got it locked in though. 12th
of February at 700 p.m. in central London.
>> You said sorry to Pat mustard and you
12th of February at 700 p.m. in central
London and you go live.
>> Why did you say sorry to Pat and run away?
>> You bottling mother. Are you bottling
it? Yes or no?
>> Irish bully victim. There's no chance.
>> Let's have it confirmed. 700 p.m. on
February 12th, Central London. >> Yes.
>> You go. You will go live.
>> Yes. [clears throat] Yes.
>> Okay. I'll remind you at the time. Okay.
You're getting bullied on camera once
again. All right. M. >> Okay.
>> People won't forget. Have it locked in.
12th of February. Mter's getting happy
slapped on camera. >> February.
>> You will put your camera on and you will
stay live for an hour in central London
and get bullied.
>> You know what's so funny, bro? I can't
believe I've been showing your face
after running away from Pat Mustard.
>> This is why it's funny. This is why it's
all funny, bro. Because the guy ran away
from Pat Mustard and he's coming on here
like he's like he's big.
This is just not even It's just
ridiculous. You ran away from Pat
Bustard, you little single bully victim [ __ ]
Women hate you, bro. Women hate you.
They hate you more than they could ever
hate me. And that's why you're single
and you've never been with a woman.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
I'm coming off of this [ __ ] um from
tomorrow. Anyways, Cory, lad, for a
little bit. Same atmosphere.
It's the same people doing the same
[ __ ] It's the same atmosphere every day.
I think this is worse than [ __ ]
Reddit, you know, bro.
I think this is worse than Reddit.
It's the same repeating people.
It's the same repeating people every day.
Every [ __ ] day.
So yeah. Why did you run away from Pat
anyways? What's What's up with that?
>> Why did you say sorry on camera? The prime.
>> Well, you said sorry without even
meeting him. That's even worse.
>> He made you a fact. Yours is a lie.
>> He made you He made you run off of
YouTube for a year.
>> But Monter, the difference is I'm saying
facts, but video evidence you're saying.
>> I'm I'm saying YouTube. You ran away
from Bat Mustard. That's facts.
>> Why did you say sorry the prime on camera?
>> That's facts. That's facts.
>> You're ignoring it though.
>> But the thing is
But I've met people. I've met people
though. Yeah, but I've met people. You
>> said sorry though.
>> But I've met people. But I've met
>> Who have you met?
>> Who have you met on here? Who have you met?
>> Terry, Timmy tried to meet Arsenal. Mark
tried to meet bullied and you got
bullied by them.
>> Yeah, I got bullied. Okay.
>> Beat you up on camera.
>> You need to understand. You need to
understand. You ran up on camera. What
are you talking about?
>> You ran away from Pat
>> and Prime grabbed you by the throat and
he said sorry. You ran away from Pat.
There's no chase you down the street.
>> You know that guy. You know that guy was
You know that guy was stalking people
for and you ran away from him. You ran
>> You're talking
facts are you are a coward.
>> All of these things that you're
listening is not a bigger L than what you do.
>> But Low
is bigger than all of
>> you got bullied and forced to say sorry on camera.
>> Bro, you got
Okay. And what did I do? And what did I
do the next day?
>> Nothing. You said on YouTube. You ran
off of YouTube for a year.
>> You said sorry on camera. That's the ultimate power.
>> You ran away from a fat old man.
>> So you're aditting on your power. So what's the
>> So you're aditting your power, PJ.
>> Listen, listen, listen, Terry. Right.
>> Get the Uber here.
>> Never let a man make me for you right
now. Get here now. >> Yeah.
>> You have zero balls, PJ. You are pushy,
lad. Yeah, at least I didn't get bullied by >> Pat of February.
Never could that fat man bully me off
YouTube like you. But then again, but
then again, the soft every single person
on YouTube are soft. PJ Billy G. Bomb Billy Gull
Manchester made him run away.
>> Never happened, mate. You got bullied by
Pat Mustard. Everyone remembers.
>> He did get bullied by video.
>> No, mate. No, mate.
>> No, it's not. It's on video.
>> After all the [ __ ] he does, you ran away.
>> Prime made you say sorry on camera.
>> [ __ ] Irish.
>> Crime made you say sorry on camera.
There's video of it.
>> Irish. Irish [ __ ] and you're supposed
to be strong, you
>> but you're a known [ __ ] PJ video
evidence showing your [ __ ] shitty. You're [ __ ]
>> You know what I'm saying, bro?
>> Prime 12year-old brother chased you down the street.
I'm wait I'm waiting for you to come.
You know, I'm waiting.
>> Even Terry bullied you. He beat you up.
>> I went to Terry's area and he didn't
come to get him off you cuz he went to
Terry's area and he didn't come out.
Yeah, but Terry poop and you asked the
guy to jump in cuz you were scared.
>> How about you and Pat? Oh, you ran away. Sorry that
>> Okay, but bro, but listen, it doesn't
matter. You ran away from a pat fat old man.
>> You're making things up and I'm talking reality.
>> I'm better looking than you. I've had more.
>> But you're not though.
>> Okay. Do you want to do you want to
upload your face?
>> Do you want to upload it now? Who's
>> A woman will never call me a
>> bro? Listening and you ain't got a
girlfriend on numerous
>> you ain't got a girlfriend and you're a
virgin unattractive PJ where
>> you have a weird shaped face and you
ain't got a girlfriend you're ugly
massive eyebrows prove you're ugly at
least I've been with women so why have I
been with more women than you
mindset no more women than you
no social life I'm so ugly no life
experience no education
That's you. Yep. Keep talking about yourself.
>> You don't your tea.
>> That's you by yourself. And you run away
from Pat Mustard. You speak for themselves.
>> At least I've been seen with women and
I've had girlfriends unlike you.
>> You haven't. You haven't. You'll see.
>> At least Irish ma
woman you've shown.
>> Why have we Why have I been seen with
women and you haven't b every time?
Let's go the evidence.
>> Woman reject. Why have we seen with
women and we ain't seen you with women? You >> mish.
Answer the question. Why have we seen
>> Why have we seen me kissing women,
[ __ ] women, but we ain't seen you
with women, you ma? You Irish m of a man.
>> Is that a hypothetical or can I answer?
>> Yeah. Answer.
>> Okay. My answer is we've only seen you
with one [ __ ] That's a fact.
>> Uh, do you want me to put the videos up?
I We've seen me kiss about three or four
different women. We've seen me in bed
with different women.
>> No, that's a lie.
>> We've seen me in women.
>> So, it's a bit maden probably 200 women.
At least 99.9%
of you think and M has had more women than you.
>> Say a lot about your looks then, isn't it?
>> But you have a lot about your looks.
>> You've never had a girlfriend ever.
>> I haven't had a girlfriend. You've never
>> Ever had a girlfriend?
>> You've never had a girlfriend and you've
never had sex. But you're defracting
from your girlfriend. You've
>> never had a girlfriend. Everyone has
seen me on here with multiple multiple multiple.
>> Okay, let's go.
>> Why have we seen me with women, but
we've never won by one month or do you
have a job?
>> I win. See how you don't win when you're
not talking about
>> Do you have a job? Yes or no?
>> I've got more money than you will ever have.
>> Answer. Answer me.
>> No. No. Turns. You go then I go. Do you
have a job?
>> You don't have a job.
>> Do you have a job?
>> Reflection. Every self-reflection.
So, I'm going to assume you don't have a job.
>> Answer it then.
>> You're a spaz.
>> Okay. You don't have a job. Next
question. Go on.
>> But that's not a question. That's
[snorts] a statement.
>> Yeah. You're asking me a question and
I'm answering it. You don't have
>> Okay. So, what's the answer? Do you have a job?
>> You don't have a job. [laughter]
>> But that's not an answer. That's a question.
>> Do you have a job? >> Yes.
>> Okay. What's your job?
>> But you just skipped over my turn. Now
it's my turn. Do you have a job?
>> Because you don't have a job. So, you're
asking me if I've got a job. You don't
have a job. If I answer Okay, say say I
answer your question. Will you
[clears throat] promise the answer to my
question would be yes or no?
>> Okay. Okay. Ask me another question. Go on then.
>> Do you have a job? Yes or no?
>> You don't have a job.
>> But that's not yes or no.
>> Okay. No, you don't have a job.
>> Yeah. Okay. So, you have no job. Okay.
>> I don't have a job. And you don't have a
job. And you don't have a job.
>> But that's not a question.
>> No. No. No. I'm I answered your question
and I'm telling you you don't have a job either.
>> That's a statement. That's not a
question. Why you ask but why are you
asking me if I have a job when you don't
have a job?
>> Because you're
saying a statement. That's not a question.
>> What's the next question then?
>> Okay. So, what's your girlfriend's name?
>> You don't have a girlfriend. Self
projection. You don't have an answer.
>> You've never had girlfriend. You're too ugly.
>> That's why you call me. No. Motherfirmed
you have no job.
>> We have now confirmed you've never had a girlfriend,
>> bro. Have we? We've never seen you with
a woman. So, that's already two down.
So, let's go for number three.
>> You don't. But you're job. Listen,
you've never had a girlfriend.
>> What's your level of education?
>> I don't understand what you're I don't
understand what you're what you're
getting at. You don't have a job and you
don't have a girlfriend.
>> That's a lie, though. That's the problem
is you've admitted to my question. I
have them here.
>> But we know that you don't have a job or
a girlfriend. We've never seen
>> How do you know that?
>> Hold on. Where's your girlfriend? [laughter]
>> Repeat yourself.
>> You see, you don't have a girlfriend.
>> Repeat the question. You sp
>> Where's your girlfriend?
>> In my bed, sleeping.
>> Oh. Oh, really? Can Can we hear her? Can
we Can we see her?
>> Yes. I will walk up to her and I will
say, "Hey, wait, make up a second. I'm
talking to this random incel on YouTube.
Would you mind confirming that you're a
woman to him, please?"
>> Yeah. Don't forget to
Don't forget to tell her that I've had
more women than you. Even though I'm
will say, "Hey, Jame. I'll say, "Hey,
wake up and tell this guy who's a random YouTube spot." >> Yeah.
Yeah. Your connect. You need to sort
your [ __ ] Wi-Fi out, matey.
That's your lack of experience in life.
>> Because you would do that. You would go
speak and try and get her to speak to
YouTube spastics ever bullied me off
YouTube, I'd kill myself, bro. That is [ __ ]
>> So, can we go back to questions?
>> [ __ ] If Pat must ever run me off a YouTube question.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And
>> do you get disability benefits?
>> Uh, no. But you do.
So, you don't get disability benefits?
>> No, but you do.
>> But you've confirmed you don't have a
job. So, how do you get 1,200 a month? I
>> I have ways of making money.
>> But you said you don't have a job, though.
>> Do you sell drugs?
>> Don't you don't need to know what I do.
>> But I do know you claim disability
benefits. You get
>> No, I don't. No, I don't.
>> But confirmed that your mother confirmed
you get. You're just like nonslegs. Two
virgins. Two absolute
>> Peter. Your mom has confirmed you get pip.
>> Two absolute virgins.
>> Are you ashamed that you get disability
benefits? Are you embarrassed by that?
>> Absolute virgin. Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
>> Why are you deflecting? Are you ashamed
of that? Are you embarrassed?
>> No. Are you Are you embarrassed that you
ran away from Pat Mos? >> No.
>> Really? That's pretty embarrassing. That
is really really
>> Is it my turn? Because I actually have a
real question, not a hypothetical.
>> It's not hypothetical.
>> You pay benefits for disability.
>> How hypothetical. You did run away from
Pat. Should we go back on your whole
channel? How's that hypothetical?
>> Because you're talking [ __ ] You're a
>> You How am I talking [ __ ] You ran away
from Pat Mustard. How's that talking [ __ ]
>> Okay, explain.
>> Uh, okay. Well, he called you out
several times and you didn't meet him
and then you ran off YouTube for a year.
How's that talking [ __ ] You ran off.
The problem is you talk about
hypothetical. I talk about reality.
>> That's not hypothetical. That is
reality. You ran away from Pat Mustard.
You are known as the man that ran away
from Pat Mustard. And you always will
be. You always will be. How is it hypothetical? [laughter]
>> I think you're embarrassed. You get
disability benefits. That's what I think. >> Hypothetical.
>> I think you're ashamed. Did you claim disability?
>> You know the definition of hypothetical.
You do hypothetical means. You don't
know what it mean.
>> Can you spell it though? Can you spell that word?
>> Yeah. And I can tell you what it means
because you obviously do both. Spell it.
>> I don't I don't need to. I know what it means.
>> You don't know. Just like you didn't
have to explain what a Clinton look
like. You didn't have to explain what a
Got is. You don't know the answer cuz
you're know what hypothetical means. Yeah.
>> No. Explain it to me.
>> Well, you obviously don't know what it
means because you actually
>> You're correct. You're correct. Explain it.
>> That actually did happen. Explain it and spell it.
>> That is actually hypothetical.
>> Such a [ __ ]
>> You're an absolute idiot. You're
>> life come to Ireland and you want me to
come to 29 years old. No girlfriend had
more women, no friends, no bad
personality and mindset.
>> There's many videos of you being bullied
online. You're a known. You're unattractive.
You have disgusting greasy skin. That is
you. Yep. That's you. I got kicking you.
That's you. Yeah. Keep talking. That's
you though. Literally went away. Don't
forget. Don't forget. You don't have a
job. You confirmed it. That's number one.
>> Don't forget you ran from Pat. You got
you run away from you get disability
benefits. You have confirmed that.
That's number two. >> Yeah.
>> You have name one friend.
>> Girlfriend. I'm better looking. I never
ran from Pat. I ain't got a speech
impediment like you. You can't even talk
about PJ things are true. >> Okay.
>> They ask you a girlfriend. When do you
have a girlfriend? When
>> bro, it doesn't matter.
>> Oh, it doesn't matter. Just like it
doesn't matter that you don't have a
job. Just like it doesn't matter.
Explain what a Clint looks like. Just it
doesn't matter that you have no explain
to [ __ ] You're a literal [ __ ]
>> Okay. Yeah. Really? Am I
>> going to answer any questions? I've
answered all of your questions, but you
can't answer one because you're you're
ashamed of yourself.
>> But the problem is you don't have a
girlfriend. You don't have a job. You
run away from Pat Mustard. This is why it's laughable.
>> But the thing is, you're lying. I'm
telling the truth.
>> You're not You're not telling the truth.
You don't How am I lying? You don't have
a girlfriend. You don't
>> Okay, let's go one by one. Okay, we'll
go one by one. We only can
He'll ask questions. It only be yes or
no. Okay. Stop putting down the yes or
>> You need to stop calling yourself a monk
with no girlfriend. Ask the question.
You keep putting yourself down like
that. We know you're never embarrassed.
>> We know you've never had a girlfriend. [laughter]
>> You're ding from your own life.
>> Why are you talking about yourself like
that? Stop putting yourself down.
>> Have you ever had a job?
>> Stop calling yourself.
>> Have you ever had a job? M stop self-reflecting.
>> Women call you more
than I have.
>> Everyone on YouTube called Jim Hunter
plus many women
>> and and and
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But guess what? I've
had girlfriends. You haven't. You
>> You haven't had a girlfriend ever in
your entire life?
>> I think it's funny that a M has had more
[laughter] women than you. Okay. Okay.
Let's go by Let's go by your logic then.
Yeah. [clears throat] Do you think that
if if I'm a M and I've had more women
than you, then you must be the M
>> if you want to talk about logically, right?
That's not logic though.
>> You're telling lies.
>> People have seen me with women multiple
times, but that's a lie.
>> We have seen you with one transgender
woman and we have seen you be
>> Okay. Really? Really? Really? Yeah. Okay, bro.
>> Really, bro?
>> That's a fact.
>> Call me a m. You're calling me a m. I'm
better looking than you.
>> But you're not though unattractive.
>> You're very ugly. You have bad skin,
greasy hair, punch back, bad nose, faty
face, and even your personality adds up
to that. You have a bad personality.
>> You have no job, no charisma.
>> Put your camera on. Put your camera on you.
>> Put your camera on and it will show that
you're all of these things, ugly boy.
But you won't do it.
>> Fantasy stories. Here's the thing,
right? I stumbled across if I if I
stumbled across another community and
they were telling me to show my face, I
could cuz I'm not ugly like you. So the
fact that you can't do that ugly that
you are the b cuz you can't show your
ugly face. Simple. You're not.
>> So do you think you're attractive,
>> PJ? Yes or no? Are you attractive? Yes
>> Am I what?
>> Are you attractive?
>> Am I attractive? I'm better looking than
you and I'm willing to prove I'm more
attractive. Yes. More more than you. Yes. Yes.
>> Okay. But do you think you're attractive
compared to every man else on earth? Do
you think you're attractive?
>> Do I think I'm attractive to I don't
[ __ ] know. I know. I'm better looking
than you, you ugly [ __ ] And that's enough. [laughter]
>> But it's not enough though because even
reality women hate you. Stupid questions
for I'm better looking than you cuz
you're a bun and you got women hate you.
Why do all women hate you? Like every
woman you approach laughs at you reason
you've never had a girlfriend and you've
had sex. Why do they hate you? Why have
you never been?
>> You're confirming that women hate G.
>> Bro, women hate you. They hate you.
>> But you're confirming women also hate G.
And you're hypothetical. Women also hate you.
>> No. No. Women definitely hate you. You
don't have a girlfriend.
>> You just said women don't have a
girlfriend, bro. Why am I sexing up
women? Which is correct. They hate me.
They They definitely hate me in
>> Bro, but they hate you. They don't like
you. They don't want you
in your head. They don't like you. They
don't want you. They hate you. You're ugly.
>> You're deflecting your own problems.
>> So, you've you've got a girlfriend, >> correct?
>> Really? Can we hear her?
>> No, you will never hear with more women
than you. I've had more
>> I've had more exist online that regular
women don't want to speak to you in any format.
>> Bro, listen. Let me tell you something.
Women don't like you. They don't want
you. Get that in your head. Listen, no
matter what you're saying about me, all
of this white night and sing ain't going
to make you lose your virginity. You
don't want to be 80 in that bed thinking
you're still a virgin and women hated
you all along. They don't [laughter]
like you. They don't like Irish ugly
people that ran away from old men. Think
about it, bro. If you actually had your history,
>> reality speaks for itself.
>> And there's hundreds of videos of women.
>> There's also loads of women that I've
been with kissing in bed with as well.
>> Your [laughter] face on Reddit and
>> No, they didn't. But guess what? I've
been in [laughter] bed with women. I've
been in bed with women and kiss women.
You ain't had that. So they definitely
hate you. They don't want you
>> ugly. Any evidence of women calling you
ugly to your face? Why is that?
>> No one called No one called me ugly.
>> They did. She called you a mother to your face.
>> No, they didn't.
>> She called you a mother.
>> But then if they called me a mother to
my face, does it not make you think
that's weird that I've been with more
women and you're still a virgin then?
>> No. I say a lot about you. That would
say a lot about you. That woman seen
your gross hunchback and your ugly face
and said, "Mother,
>> that's a regular reaction. I've had a
girlfriend. You loser."
>> No matter how much you say, it doesn't
change the fact that you don't have a
girlfriend and you're a
>> You've never had a girlfriend about
yourself. If I start about that, you'll
deflect. I'll ask you a simple question.
>> Videos of me kissing.
>> I'll ask you a simple question. When did
you have a girlfriend?
>> A woman. Why is
>> This should be simple. This should be
simple. When did you meet your
girlfriend? When did I meet my
girlfriend? Bro, you don't have a
girlfriend. You keep self-reflecting again.
>> That's my point though. It should be
simple for you. The answer I keep saying
you when did you meet her? You can't answer.
>> You don't have girlfriend.
You can't answer. I
>> don't have a girlfriend
>> and you can't answer.
>> Because you don't have a girlfriend.
>> You realize every single You realize
every question's been self-reflecting.
You realize that?
>> No. PJ, that's your that's how you get
around it. You see everything.
>> You're telling me So you're telling me
you've not seen me kiss women in in a in women's beds?
>> What I'm saying is you've never had a
>> No, no, no. Is that what you're saying?
>> What are you saying? Have I ever seen
you kiss a woman?
>> You So you've never seen me kiss four
women and in women's beds?
>> I've seen you kiss a very unattractive
[ __ ] I have seen that.
>> You've only seen me kiss one woman? Really?
>> Well, I've kissed four and I've been in
their bed. same concept about you cuz they [ __ ]
>> women and you're 20 years old.
>> They [ __ ] with an Irish woman.
>> Absolute insanity.
>> 28 years old and four kisses.
>> I've had about 400 kisses. Slept with
more women than you. Never run away from Pat.
Not a single woman can date you because
you have a bad personality. Oh, you've
never had a girlfriend. You had a
girlfriend. You have no personality. >> Unattractive.
>> Coming from a single virgin that's never
had a girlfriend.
>> All facts, BJ. [laughter] Everything I
just ain't got a girlfriend, that has
never had sex. Yeah. Good one, bro. Bro,
listen. So, why can't you show us what
you look like? Anyways,
>> did anything I say was it a lie? Did I
say any lies there? Everything you said
was the truth about yourself. [laughter]
>> Was it the truth about you? You might
>> Was it the truth about GPJ?
>> Put your camera on Put your camera on.
Put your camera on. Put your camera on.
>> What I mean? Are you
Bro, so you're trying to say you're better.
>> Are you embarrassed by your life? Yes or no?
>> Show Show us your face.
>> Are you embarrassed about your life?
>> Show us your face. Show us your face. I
want to see I want to see something embarrassed.
>> Can I see your face? Come on.
>> Why would you fix your life? Why can't
you get up? Why get in better shape? Why
can't you wash your greasy face?
>> And why don't you fix your posture for your hunchback?
>> Why [clears throat] don't you stop
running away from fat busted?
>> Why are you doing a fake laugh? Are you embarrassed?
>> A fake laugh. I'm laughing at you.
>> No, that's a fake laugh cuz you're
trying to deflect the fact that you're ugly.
>> I don't need a fake laugh. It's coming from [laughter]
>> It's coming from the stomach. It's I'm
laughing at you. It's not though.
>> I just can't believe how you ran away
from Pat Mustard and you have the nerve
to show your face on here again.
>> I think you're embarrassed.
>> I think you're embarrassed that you claim Pep.
>> All you Irish are the same. All you Irish.
>> No. Are you embarrassed? You claim Pip.
Yes or no?
>> You're talking about yourself.
>> Yes or no? Are you embarrassed that you claim Pep?
>> You claim PIP.
>> Yes or no? Are you embarrassed? You claim PIP.
>> I don't claim PIP.
>> You do claim PIP, though.
>> No, I don't. This sounds like that
mustard son. Everyone, this sounds like
you confirmed you're on benefits, correct?
>> He sounds like it.
>> You confirmed you get benefits though, correct?
>> I don't get pipped.
>> You get benefits though, right?
>> No, I work.
>> What do you work as?
>> I I uh What do I work as? I'm a delivery driver.
>> For who?
>> I deliver pizzas. Pizza Hut.
>> Okay. How did you get that job?
>> I applied for it online.
>> What? What's your tax bracket?
>> You don't need to know that.
>> Okay. What's a P45?
>> Yeah, exactly. So, you've got no job. That's confirmed.
>> No job.
>> You don't know anything about
>> You claim you get 1,200 a month. How do
you get [snorts] that with no job?
>> I work for Pizza Hut.
>> But you don't. You just confirmed that's a lie.
>> No, I work for Pizza Hut.
>> Okay. What's your salary?
>> Well, how much do you get a month?
>> I would say
I would say about two grand after taxes.
>> No, you don't.
>> How much do you get?
>> Well, that's pretty [ __ ] then, isn't it?
Two grand after taxes.
>> Correct. How much do you get?
>> Sorry. And you're bragging about that.
>> No. How much do you get?
>> I just told you how much I get.
>> How much?
>> You I get £1,200 from Pizza Hut
>> after tax? >> Yeah.
>> So, you get below minimum wage? Yeah.
>> How is that possible? That's illegal.
>> It's I do get that. It's not by the books.
>> So, you get paid cash and ham at Pizza Hut. >> Yeah.
>> That's also illegal. They're a franchise.
>> Oh, well, no one's going to find out.
>> No, cuz you're lying. Correct.
>> No, I'm not lying.
>> Because you're on benefits.
>> No, I'm not.
>> You get PIP?
>> No, I'm not lying. No.
>> No, you are. You just confirmed it. You
just confirmed you get PIP.
>> You don't even work, bro.
You get because you're a [ __ ] Good
night. Sleep well, Hunter. Good night.
>> See you in February. Anyways, this guy
is so boring, bro. He is so boring.
You got to laugh at these people. [laughter]
You got to laugh at these people. Is it >> [laughter]
>> I can't stop laughing at that accent.
You know what it is, Greavves? It's the accent. [laughter]
It's the accent. You can't stop laughing
at the accent, in it.
[ __ ] stupid ugly Irish [ __ ] talking
about me. He says that he's seen me kiss
one woman. This is what I mean. They're
biased on here, bro. They're [ __ ] biased.
Oh, women hate you as well. I said the
same thing to Dusty when he was trolling
me. I said, "Women hate me and they hate
you as well.
Oh yeah. This is why women are repelled
by you. I said, "Oh, but it's okay for
them to want sex. It's okay for them to
want one night stands and hookups."
Double standards. Is that double standards, Greavvesy?
I don't even know why I said that. Oh, I
thought you were going to sleep.
Do you remember when this [ __ ] idiot
said he was going for a lad's holiday in Manchester?
He said he was going for a lad's holiday in Manchester.
This guy is full of [ __ ] He ain't going
to no London, mate. Who the [ __ ] goes to
London in February? Guy's a bullshitter,
bro. Guy's a bullshitter.
Yep. He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
Jesus Christ. Yeah, I got owned. No, I
didn't. Anyways, Terry, come here in an
Uber. I'll wait for you. Come here in an
Uber and I'll wait for you. I I'll stay
up for you if you want. I don't mind
staying up if you want to get an Uber.
Yes, you are.
Why is it double standards or not?
Dusty, is it double standards or not?
I said to this person on um
Grievy, Dusty, is that double standards?
She says that if you want sex, it will
make women repelled by you. But what
it's okay for women to want sex and have
sex? seems a bit hypocritical to me.
There's people out there that hook up with men.
I think that's a bit uh that's a bit
double standardy, isn't it?
They're s They're such hypocrites, bro.
They're such [ __ ] hypocrites.
They [ __ ] are in it. Yeah.
Double standards. No. Dusty Grezy. Is
that not double standards?
Is that not double standards?
So, it's not okay for a man to want sex,
but it's okay for a woman to want sex.
I don't know. I think that's double standards.
Yeah, I think that's double standards. Me?
No, Gre, I'm asking you. Is it double standards?
They're making excuses for women again.
I just want the answer. Is it double
Sanders or not?
It seems like it's double Sanders, bro.
Yeah, it seems like proper double standards.
It's making me not want to go out
tomorrow, bro. Greasy. It's making me
not want to go out tomorrow, lad.
It's really making me not want to go out tomorrow, bro.
All of this tomorrow. Think about it, bro.
I thought you was going to sleep. It's
hard to stop bullying you. Honestly,
it's like an addiction.
>> Yeah. Well, guess what? You don't you
>> actually an addiction though. Bullying
the mon is so enjoyable. That's actually insane.
>> You do realize that you don't really
bully anyone. You just make a fool of yourself.
>> Yeah. Do you ever think I mean I mean I
come on here I mean I come on here every day so
>> yeah. Do you ever think back
people that are bullied come back for
more over and over again?
>> Yeah I do.
>> Of course they don't.
>> I mean you ran away from Pat Mustard
when he bullied you. So you would know,
wouldn't you? Yeah. Do you ever think
back on what prime done to you? You
>> can't even take your hand.
>> Listen, whenever you're by yourself and
you look in the mirror, do you ever
think back on what prime done to you? >> Um,
no. Cuz I didn't run away from Pat
Mustard. But you
>> don't think about that. You don't think
about him grabbing you and making you
say sorry and thousand people seeing it?
>> No. No. No.
>> Not once. Not a single time.
>> No. So,
>> you don't feel embarrassed by that?
>> No. Do you feel embarrassed by running from Pat?
>> No. Cuz it's a lie.
>> How is that a lie? You literally
everyone saw you run away from Pat. What
do you mean it's a lie?
>> Cuz it's a lie.
>> So you didn't say I'm sorry, Pat Mustard
on a video. No. >> No.
>> You're full of [ __ ] mate. Everyone saw you.
>> Is there a video of you being made to
say sorry on camera? Yes or no?
>> Yeah. When I was caught off by God.
>> Caught off guard.
>> Yeah, I was caught off guard. Yeah, I
was. Yeah. Yeah. [laughter] And your
first instinct was to say sorry, was it?
>> So why are you why are you making up
stories to London?
>> Why are you coming up? Why are you
making up stories that you you're
>> Were you scared?
>> Just imag scared.
>> I'm not scared of anybody.
>> Then why'd you say sorry?
>> I'm not scared of anybody, mate.
>> Why did you run away from Pat?
>> Why'd you say sorry?
>> Why did you say sorry to Pat?
>> Why did you say sorry?
>> Why did you say sorry to Pat Mustard?
>> Because you're deflecting. You're ashamed.
>> You know what? No, I can probably get it
up right now. One second.
>> Do it right now. Let's see it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Let's do it. Because what I can do right
now is I can get a video of you saying
sorry to Prime, then run off like a [ __ ]
>> Why do you laugh at everything?
>> I can also get a video of you being
chased by a 12-year-old. I can also get
Laura J embarrassing you at your front
door. You've got
>> I also have a video in the There's a
there's a there's a short where it says
Pat wins. Why does Pat win?
But Munther, I'm talking facts.
>> No. No. Why does Pat win? It's running
right now. It says Pat wins.
>> But M, I'm talking facts.
>> What does he win? What does he win? [laughter]
>> I'm talking facts.
>> What does he win? If you type in TJ and
crying and you will see you said sorry
to another man trying not to cry.
>> He bullied you. He bullied you.
>> Oh, mother. Listen, life. Monter
needs losers and you fulfill that bracket.
>> Why don't you come to London next week?
>> We need I am of February.
Why would anyone go to London? Why would
someone go to London in February? You
don't make sense.
>> Job opportunities.
You'll never understand.
>> You'll never have a job, PJ. You'll
never have friends.
>> You're a loser.
>> Who else Who else do you watch on here?
>> You are a loser.
>> Who else do you watch on here? Good
loser. You will have nothing. You will
never travel for work. You will never
travel to meet friends. All you will do
is travel by yourself like an incel.
That's all you've ever done.
>> You went to Amsterdam by yourself and
had a Burger King. That's all you did.
>> Self projection.
>> That's a fact though, PJ. That's a literal fact.
>> Oh, just self I don't have I don't have
the energy for the self projection, man.
>> Oh, it's facts, though.
>> It's not. It's not. It's self
projection. It is though. It is facts
It is fact. PJ,
>> you can't say that accent.
>> You don't have any friends. You don't
have a single friend in this world. >> Serious.
>> A man joined Lord Jay's and confirmed
you got bullied in school.
>> Imagine that. Someone's
confirmed that you got bullied in school
and had to leave early.
>> Where's your friends? Where's your
>> Living life unlike you.
>> Yeah. Okay.
>> Unlike you, M. everything.
>> If you had any friend, we [laughter]
would know about it. If you had a single
friend, we would know about it. Just
like anytime you get a kiss, you video
it because you're an intel.
>> You will never have a friend.
>> Life has passed you by, M. And you'll never recover.
>> Self addiction.
>> Reality speaks for itself.
>> Yeah, man. Self.
>> Reality speaks for itself, M.
>> Stories is 100%. Who is this [ __ ]
>> Yeah, bro. Who Who are you?
>> Okay, he's 100% right. No, he's not
right, bro. I just don't have the energy
to keep arguing with a self projector.
>> No, I thought that was one of your in agreeing me.
>> What is What is right? I'm better
looking than you. You ran from You never
had a girlfriend. You don't have a job.
These are all things about you.
Okay. Am I lying by saying you're scared
to show your face?
>> Okay, let's go question my question. Am
I lying when I'm saying you're scared to
show your face?
>> TJ, can we go?
>> Am I lying when I'm saying you're scared to show?
>> Can we go question my question? Yes or no?
>> Show your face.
>> Yes or no? Can we go question by question?
>> Can we go question by question?
>> Yeah. Yeah. And I'm going to start.
>> Okay. So, I'll start first. I'll start
>> Show us your girlfriend.
>> Show us your girlfriend now.
>> Name me one life experience you've had.
>> Show us Show us your girlfriend now. >> No.
>> Yes. Cuz she doesn't exist.
>> No. because you're a creepy incel on
YouTube. You have no understanding of women.
>> You have zero understanding of women, DJ.
>> I've been with the only women who've
ever been in your company. You have
tried so hard to video them because you
want to prove to strangers you're not a
women. I've listen.
>> You haven't though, mother. You haven't though.
>> I [laughter] that accent that accent,
bro. I can't, bro. I can't take I can't
take you serious with that accent.
>> Why do you trouble by yourself?
>> Take it serious.
>> I can't take the accent seriously.
>> No, I think you're embarrassed. I think
you're doing your fake laugh cuz you're
embarrassed by these questions serious.
>> Just like when you aditted to the job.
>> That's all I'm saying.
>> That's what I'm saying.
>> You're a skit and silly lives your mommy.
You know what I'm saying? that you got
bullied by Pat Bust. You had a girlfriend.
>> But guess what? I've had a girlfriend.
>> You've got more money to be. Let's play the money.
>> Let's play the money game right now.
Let's play the money.
>> Let's play the money. Billy G,
>> I'm still here.
>> Billy G,
>> Billy G.
>> One second. Fantasy story. Listen, you
fat ugly American [ __ ] He's not right
about me. I just can't be bothered
arguing. I'm not the one that got
bullied from Pat% right,
>> bro. He ran away from Pat incel,
>> bro. You're an incel. You're Look at
you. You fat ugly American.
>> [ __ ] loser.
>> You are a loser.
>> Look at yourself. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
Listen, bro. You're saying about all of
these people bullying me, but I'm still
here. What does that show you? That
you've never bullied me.
>> That means you're a bully victim.
Because you've never bullied me. Because
I'm still here. I'm willing to meet you.
I'm willing to meet you. Listen, I'm
>> Okay. 12th of February at 7 p.m.
>> Smash your face in. And I'm going to
smash your face in.
>> You won't though,
>> cuz history has proven that you're a coward.
>> Would though
take you serious?
>> Harry put you in a headlock. Tiger
pushed your face in the mattress. Lord J
came to your front door. The
>> You couldn't even show up to a fight.
And you can show up to a fight. And you
can even show up to a fight.
>> And you can even show up to a fight. And
you can show up to a fight.
>> EJ, you're an incel. Like
>> I'm an incel that's had more women than
you. Yeah. Make it make sense. An inel
that's had more women than you.
>> An incel that's had more women than you.
I know. Make it make sense.
>> Inel that's had more women than you. I
know it. Make it make sense.
>> The other thing is Yeah. The other guy
that joined, I've had more women than
both of you fat incels.
>> You're getting the reality,
>> bro. Do you want me to really start
putting the women up I've been with
again on video? You want me? You want me
to embarrass you again? Relax. Embarrass you again.
>> Don't be embarrassed by your life.
That's your life.
>> I'm embarrassed by my life. I didn't run
away from Pat. >> Okay.
>> I didn't run away from Pat.
>> So, let's simplify it. Have you had a girlfriend?
>> I have. You haven't.
>> When did you meet her?
>> It doesn't matter when I met her.
>> It does matter cuz it's a lie.
>> Okay. Well, show us your girlfriend then
if it's a lie.
>> What's her name?
>> It doesn't matter what her name is.
>> It does matter cuz it's a lie.
>> The accent again. Where's your girlfriend?
>> In bed sleeping.
>> Okay, wake her up. We want to [ __ ]
see the ugly [ __ ]
>> But why would she speak to an insult online?
>> I don't want to tell her that she needs
to [ __ ] up.
>> I don't understand the women.
>> Cuz I want to tell her to I want to tell
her I want to tell her to go get raped.
I want to tell her to cuz I want to tell
her to go get raped.
>> Of course she would.
>> I wouldn't tell her to go get raped.
You're an insult. But you're up. Wake
the [ __ ] up.
>> No. Because you're an incel.
>> You're a mother. You're an incel. You
will never ever have a girlfriend.
>> You're laughing at, bro. I'm laughing.
Bully me here. Come on. You're supposed
to be bullied.
>> You need to try harder. You need to try
>> People called you an incel on Twitter.
>> You need to try You need harder. You
need to try harder. You're supposed to
be bullied. And I'm laughing at you. And
I'm laughing at you. I feel bad for you.
[ __ ] You're funny.
>> I genuinely feel bad for you. Honestly,
I genuinely feel bad for you,
>> bro. You need to feel bad for yourself.
If you got bullied, that's the biggest L
you could ever take. That's the biggest
L you could ever take, bro. A lot of
people would love to get him.
>> A lot of people would have loved to get
their hands on him, you know.
>> But you're ranting again, mother.
>> No. [laughter]
>> You ran away. You absolute virgin. You
absolute virgin. You ran away from bat busted.
>> You ran away from busting.
>> Never had a girlfriend. You're supposed
to be bullying me.
>> All these women you've approached,
hundreds, probably in the thousands, and
not a single one has decided already
been in a relationship you benefit yourself. >> Unattractive, PJ.
>> It's all facts about you. You carry on,
bro. Carry on talking about yourself.
I'm not interrupted.
>> Yes, you're unattractive. You can sell.
You got no job. You're ugly. That's you.
Keep talking about yourself.
>> Keep talking about yourself.
>> You need to reflect cuz if you keep
talking about yourself have to reflect.
If you reflect it on your own life, I'm not scared.
>> I'm not scared on your own life.
>> I'm not scared to show my face.
>> I'm not scared to show my face. You are.
You're scared to show your face cuz you're
scared to show your face.
>> Scared to show your face cuz you're
ugly. You're talking about my face, but
you're scared to show your face cuz
you're ugly. You're scared to show your
face cuz you're ugly. Just like Pat
Bustard, you can't show your face cuz
you're ugly. And that's not a lie, is
it? Come on. Come on, [ __ ] If you're
really good-looking, show your face. Come on.
>> Show everyone. Show everyone what a good
looking man looks like. Show everyone
what a good man.
>> PJ, why are you almost crying? Relax.
>> I'm not crying. I'm not crying.
>> We're stage, right, PJ? We're age. PJ,
how old are you? Why can't you show your
face if you're not a mj?
>> How old are you?
>> Why can't you show your face if you're
not a ma? Let's
>> go back and forth. Show your face if
you're not a mre.
>> You're self-reflecting. You're selfing.
>> You're selfreflecting.
>> I'm self-reflecting.
>> How am I self-reflecting?
>> Stop looking in the mirror. Stop calling
yourself a M. Get away from that mirror.
>> I'm 26. You're
>> Get away from that. Get away from the
mirror that conversation cuz you're
embarrassed. Get away from that mirror.
You're embarass. Get away from the
mirror. Mitch, you're embarrassed.
>> Get away from that mirror. You
>> You're a dirty hunchback in [laughter]
a dirty Irish [ __ ] that ran away from Pat Mustard.
>> You're a dirty [ __ ] that ran away from
Pat Mustard with no girlfriend, no sex
life, ugly looks, no money.
>> You hit 32, it's too late. Will you be
live with your mommy till the end of time? >> Yeah.
>> At least I've got a mommy that loves me.
Your mom's probably a prostitute [ __ ]
men for money.
>> At least I've got a mommy. Not like you.
Your mom's probably selling her ass on the street. [laughter]
>> Where is your mother?
>> Isn't your mom an actual junkie though?
>> But Venom called her a junkie. Your
boyfriend called your mom a junkie.
You're a face
>> and you didn't know nothing about it.
two absolute virgin
called your mama chunky and you ran away. [laughter]
>> Two absolute virgins.
>> Why burger boy? Why do you keep leaving? Bro,
>> you're a bully victim. PJ, bro. Just
stay with him.
>> One of your bullies. PJ, he's one of
your bullies. Everyone bullies you.
That's the problem.
>> So much that I come on here.
>> Okay, I'm going to leave. I'll let this guy bully.
>> You need You need to stop bullying me, bro.
>> American guy. Enjoy bullying the mon.
Yeah, bully me. Please don't leave.
>> Yeah. What have you got to say, man?
>> Why do you have a credit rating of zero?
>> Why? Why do I have a credit rating of zero? >> Yeah.
>> Um because it's fun. Why do you sound
like a fat ugly bastard? Oh, left.
Jesus Christ. I can't take that accent serious.
I really, really can't take that accent serious, bro.
I can't take that [ __ ] accent serious. [laughter]
Did you ever take an accent like that serious? Rezy.
That is really funny.
Pack of virgins. Them two pack of It
>> I'll give you one chance and I'm going.
Question by question or I'm leaving.
>> Okay. Can I start?
>> Yes. But only one rule. It has to be yes or no. >> No.
I mean the question be yes or no. You
[ __ ] All right. Go. Your question.
Your question first.
>> Okay. Can we Can we see your girlfriend? >> No. >> Why?
>> My turn.
>> No. It's my turn. That's the rule.
>> Okay. Why is your credit rating so bad?
>> So, you said it's yes or no question.
>> Okay. Why? Okay, that's a good question actually. So,
okay, you've won that one to be fair. Okay, [laughter]
>> fair enough.
>> That was a fair point. That was a fair
point. That was a fair point. Can we
change the rules? Okay. Can we any any answer?
>> Absolute bird.
>> Any question? All right. So rephrase
your question. Rephrase your question.
>> You're an absolute virgin.
>> That's not a question. That's a statement.
>> I know it is. I know it's a [ __ ]
statement. I [ __ ] know it is. It is,
isn't it? It is. Yeah.
>> So that's your final question. Is that
your final question?
>> Is that your final question?
>> You even said it's a statement. You even
said it was a statement. Yeah.
>> Okay. So I have an actual question.
>> Why is your credit rating so bad?
>> But that's not a yes or no.
>> Yeah. We've changed the rules.
Um, well, it's not.
>> It is. We've seen it, though. >> Okay.
>> It's below 100.
>> Why did you run away from Pat Mustard?
>> But you haven't answered my question then.
>> I have answered your question.
>> I have.
>> Why is your credit so bad?
>> It's not.
>> It is. It's below 100.
>> It's not bad.
>> It's below 100.
>> It's not bad. I can get a phone contract
if I want.
>> But no, you're below 100 though. That
means I can get phone contract. If you
have bad financial choices, that means
you're be skinned forever cuz you're a [ __ ]
>> Okay. So,
why'd you run away from that bustard?
>> I didn't.
>> There's a there's a video where it says
that you said he won. You want me to put it up?
>> Yes. Right now.
>> Okay. One second.
>> Yeah. So, there's a video of me on
camera saying Pat, you won.
>> On your channel saying Pat wins. Yeah.
Pip work coach. That's you.
What's my channel? Do you hear my voice
saying those words?
>> Everyone's seen it, mate. Everyone has seen it.
>> No. Like, I'll give you an example.
There's a video of you saying sorry, the
prime on video. That's irrefutable. Correct.
>> Well, you ran. Okay. Well, you ran away.
>> Is there a similar video for me doing those things?
>> Well, you ran away for a year. So, yeah.
>> Incorrect. That's another incorrect. You
You come off of it for over a year. But
the problem you have is you mistake
evidence with your opinion.
>> No. So you didn't come up with it for a year.
>> I've been off YouTube many times. I have a life.
>> Yeah. Because Yeah. Because Pat must bully that.
>> But how though? [clears throat] How's that possible?
>> Because it is.
>> Give an example of bullying. >> Uh
made you run off of YouTube.
>> You're an absolute bastic. He said he >> bro.
>> He offered to meet you and you made up
every excuse and he ran off of YouTube
for a year. You got bullied.
>> Incorrect. Made up lies.
>> But I'll back up my statement. I'll give
an example. I'll give an example. PJ.
Okay. Lord J went to your door and
insulted you and your mom and you ran
inside and closed the door. That's on
video. That's irrefutable.
>> Several charges to kick the door in my
face and he
>> But that's irrefutable.
>> At the end of No, I was standing in
front of my mom.
>> No. No. You closed the door and you ran away.
>> No, I didn't close the door properly.
Watch the video back properly if you
want to. You watch. And another thing is
I tried to meet him again after that and
he would put his camera on.
>> But there's video evidence. But see what
I mean? You have a counter argument. You
have a counter argument, but then
there's video evidence.
>> Yeah. And there's also there's also
evidence where the where the door didn't
close properly and he could have kicked
the door in my face.
>> Okay. Okay. They want me to play the
video. Play the video. Play the video.
Play the video. play the video. So, go
on channel. Okay, I I'll tell you how
people do. Okay, go type in YouTube Lord
Jesp's door and watch the video. The
video is right there.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Watch it. Watch it. And you
can see where the door didn't close
properly and you could have easily
kicked the door in my face.
>> Why did you close the door?
>> You did. What do you mean? Why did I
close the door?
>> Yeah. Why did you close the door?
>> I was standing in front of my mom. You [ __ ]
>> So, why did you close the door?
>> I was standing in front of my mom.
>> Why did you close the door?
>> Why didn't he meet me when I tried to
meet him in the other area?
>> Why did you close the door? Why didn't
he put his camera on?
>> Because you were scared.
>> Central London.
>> He closed the door cuz you were scared.
>> Yeah. Scared? Yeah. Really?
>> Yeah. That video you evidence.
>> If I was scared, Listen. Listen. If I
was scared, I would have opened the door.
>> Yeah. Do you remember exactly what
happened? Do you remember exactly what
happened? I looked through the window.
Do you remember what happened? And I
said, "What are you going to do? [ __ ]
off." And I stood in front of my mom.
I'm not scared of people like you.
>> I'm not an Irish far away from you. The second he
>> I didn't need to do anymore. I didn't need anymore.
>> I didn't need to do anymore. I told
>> him the word fear.
>> I told him to [ __ ] off.
>> Oh, okay. Let's move on. Okay. What about the
>> Another thing is And another thing is
ask yourself this, right? Why didn't he
give me a part two like he did with
Timmy? Cuz he knew that he's not
>> scared of LT. Because he was scared of
>> So you admit he's scared of LT.
>> Obviously he's scared of LT. He's scared
of me. He made up some [ __ ] story
about me when I tried to meet him. But
listen, you you're still a [ __ ] No
matter what he whatever he did, you're
still a [ __ ] and you bottled it.
>> But guess what? At least I never run
away from Pat mustard like you.
>> But that's a lie though.
>> That is that I know it's not a lie. It's
not a lie. No,
>> it is a lie though. It's not a lie.
>> I tried to I tried to leave at least
>> Wait, Lord J is not scared of you. Why
would anyone be scared of you, mate? You
Why would he be scared of you? Same the
same reason you won't go live in the
February cuz you'll be scared that I'll
turn up. That's exactly what [laughter]
>> this guy thinks people scared of him.
>> No, you're scared of me. You are scared
of Okay. So, what you're So, you're not
Wait, wait, wait. So, you're not friends
with L J. >> No.
>> Why not?
>> Cuz he's a [ __ ]
>> Okay, whatever. Well, no one's scared of you anyways.
>> No, but you're scared of everybody though.
>> Okay. Okay. Look at big bad Franco.
Franco made all these threats to me.
>> Really? Oh, Timmy just uploaded. I want
to get Timmy on here. Timmy owns you in it.
>> But the reality is PJ, you're the
biggest [ __ ] out of everyone.
>> Yeah, really.
>> Timmyy's just on a video. [laughter]
You and Timmy, you and Timmy are absolute virgins.
>> Timmy is the only one more of a [ __ ]
than you. He's the only person on here. >> Really?
>> He is the only person you could beat up.
in this entire community
>> because he
>> Well, you could you probably beat up him
as well, but doesn't matter. Timmy came
to meet you and he brought back up and
you're a [ __ ] How bad Timmy?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I [ __ ] her mom and her
little [ __ ] though. She liked it. [laughter]
>> You're an incel. Ask second question
though. Why you Why don't you Okay, one
second. Why don't you go out Why don't
you go at nonsle legs?
>> I don't care about him.
>> Why? He's a nons. You said you don't like nons.
>> Cuz he's a boring nons.
What do you [laughter] mean he's a
boring n? Yeah, but you can still go at
him. You can't just go for one person.
That's not fair. You know,
>> you're because you're an artistic spaz
and you react.
>> No, but he would as well if you
>> been bullied. That's why you've been
bullied for the last four years.
>> So much bullying. I keep coming back
laughing at you for more.
I know. But all right, here I have a serious question.
>> You know when people you know when
people bully people, they don't they
don't come back for more. You know that.
>> Okay, I'll I'll call you PJ. Make you
answer. PJ, you I have one serious
question for you. Okay. How does it feel
that all those videos with your name
will be online forever, forever and ever
and ever. And anyone who ever searches
your name will see nons pussyard.
>> It feels [ __ ] lovely.
>> Surely it doesn't. was funny. Lovely. Is
that right? Lovely. Yeah, Timmy's loving it.
>> But Timmy's a Timmy offered kids
alcohol. Timmy assaulted a woman on a
bus. Timmy's a pedophile. He's an actual known pedophile.
>> Timmy Timmy claimed he worked at an all
girls school, which is a lie. Which only
means he has fantasies about working at
an all girls school, which confirms he's a nun.
>> Yeah, but you are a nun as well. I'm not
though. You're just getting words.
>> Based on what though?
>> You are.
>> Based on what?
>> Cuz you like little girls.
>> But that's your disgusting brain. Cuz
you're a pedoo. That's your That's how
your brain works. [clears throat] >> Ped.
[laughter] That accent is funny.
>> Your life's funny to be fair, PJ. Your
life will never get better. You're >> I'm
>> I'm going to get the Sideman on you if
you don't stop.
Your life is destitute. You will never
What would you do if I get assignment on you?
>> You will never have a girlfriend. You
will never have your own house.
>> You will never travel the world.
>> Have a friend group.
>> Have more friends than you.
>> You don't. Do you have no
>> What countries have you been to? >> Countless.
>> He's not blocked.
>> I've been to Okay. What? Okay. What What
countries? Go on. Um, Italy, Belgium,
Jamaica, Spain, Portugal, Poland,
[ __ ] Denmark, Copenhagen or sorry
cities. I could go on and on. There's so
many I struggle to actually say them.
That's the problem.
>> You've never been to America.
>> Have you been to America?
>> No, I'm just saying you've never been, have you?
>> What's the relevancy of that? You
haven't been to any of those cities I
told you because you're
>> I've been to Bel.
>> You went You went on one Where did you
go in Belgium?
>> I went to Brussels. You saw that.
>> Okay. What's the airport? Describe the
airport to me.
>> I I went by the train. You [ __ ] Don't you remember?
>> Oh, of course she got the train. Cuz
you're a spa. You can't fly.
>> I went to Belgium. I went to Belgium before you.
>> And did you go by yourself? >> Yep. >> Why?
>> Because I prefer solo traveling. Because
you've got no friends.
>> Well, you never solo traveled. >> Huh? >> Ever.
>> So, where world have you travel to?
>> Solo travel. >> No.
>> I've been to America, Australia, Dubai.
>> Incorrect. All lies.
>> No, it's not lies. I' I've unblocked
Timmy, by the way. Why is he not joining?
>> Cuz he's a [ __ ] He knows if he joins
you he'll get terrorized cuz he's a pedoo.
>> Pedu. I like the way you say that. Pedu.
>> Yeah, because you're a nons as well. You
identify with Timmy. You're in the same bracket.
>> What would you You didn't answer me.
What would you do if I got the Sideman
on you? I know them. You know.
>> Ah, Timmy. I don't I don't answer. You're
>> Why? Cuz you you need to fix your Wi-Fi
victim. That's all it is. You're a bully
victim. That's all you ever will be. PJ,
you are a bully back then. That is
>> you know all of this. You know all of
this. Yeah. You know all of this that
you're doing. It's not going to change
the fact that you got bullied by Pat.
>> But PJ your entire life bullied.
>> You know,
I have a serious question. I have a
>> When Prime bullied you, were you
embarrassed? Be honest.
>> Um, no. Because he never bullied me.
>> Well, he did. He grabbed you by the
scruff. I still I still can't believe
you're going on about that video, bro.
>> Prime grabbed you by the throat and made
you say something.
>> You're still going on about that [ __ ] video, man.
>> Cuz it's important you
>> I don't even save anymore.
>> Listen, what I'm going to do, I'm going
to do you a favor. I'm going to hop off
so Timmy will join cuz Timmyy's scared
of me. Timmy, you're a fat n. All right,
PJ, you're a monster.
>> Why? Why is Timmy watching? Why was
Timmy watching? Why did you see the
video Timmy? [laughter]
I want Timmy to come on. Timmy.
Yeah, he is a He is a repeater, bro. He
is a repeater.
Is Timmy coming on? I want Timmy to join.
I saw Timmy the other day live in the
pub. Greavvesy. He was saying, "Don't
[ __ ] with me." He was showing his face
like this. I've had enough. Yeah, I was
dead, bro. Yeah. [laughter]
Timmy Elg is on the same website you can
watch the sideman
Oh, is that Timmy?
Why is Timmy not coming in?
>> If it helps Timmy join and Timmy, I've
contacted Optical Services to send a
recent video of you being a fat strokey
pedo [ __ ] Timmy offered kids alcohol
and Timmy assaults women on camera and
your family will be told without Timmy
and you'll do nothing about it because
you are finished on here you fat ugly >> bastard.
So anyway, contact optical services on
Monday morning to me. They'll get my
email about you dirty pedo [ __ ] See
he's not blocked. So why is he not coming on?
He's not coming on, is he?
No, I'm not doing a bet. Uh, Dusty,
I'd be in bed all day tomorrow if I had
it my way, but I've got to go out and drink.
I wish I could stay in tomorrow.
Oh, are you coming into me or not? [laughter]
Hey, look who's here. Grievy. Look who's here. Grievesy.
>> Look who's on. Look who's on. Hello.
Hello. Can you hear me? [laughter]
>> Timmy, why is he being a [ __ ] pratt?
>> Bro, you were reacting to him. Listen to
me, bro. I've been doing this for 10
years, right? This is a fiber [laughter]
cable. You are You shouldn't get round
up with him. You should have said,
"Mate, why were you lying about your
watch? what you said was three grand [laughter] to yourself
and you're finished Ladies and gentlemen, [laughter]
you come to [laughter] Birmingham and
I'll punch your head off that Irish on
your face. You're going to be [laughter] a little ning.
You're a bullshitter and you ran away
from Pat mustard. You ran away from Pat
Mustard. You little [ __ ] You ran away from Pat.
You [laughter] little [ __ ] [ __ ]
Come to come to England in February and I will
have to come to the UK.
>> You're a [ __ ] woman and you're a
virgin. I'd rather be a woman. [laughter] Why do
virgin do nothing about the situation?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Why don't we come to the UK? I'm not
going to come to the UK.
[laughter] You're going to say,
mate, when I get your address, mate,
[laughter] you will be lad.
You can't you've got no friends, no
women, no relationship with anyone. You
couldn't ban anyone from anywhere, mate.
From a little [ __ ] [ __ ]
you, Sam Jones. Sam Jones is going to
ban me from the one who
am I this? Oh yeah, you're [ __ ] nuts
as well, mate. I'm going to call you on
mate. I'm going [laughter] to go [ __ ]
up. Let your hand go out when I come to address.
>> I will be in Ireland, mate. And you're noticing
anyone, mate. You can't you can't show your [laughter] fantasy. [laughter]
Even even strong.
You have no women, mate.
Yeah, we're back in the UK, mate. I'm
doing I'm doing
You're going to do nothing, mate. You're
going to do nothing. You little clown.
I've seen your picture, mate. Even PJ [laughter]
would knock the [ __ ] out. You going to
knock yourself out, you nons [laughter] you none,
mate. cuz I will get you a dress room
and I'm going to
[ __ ] out of you.
>> I will knock the [ __ ] out of you, mate.
If you come to here in February, trust me,
>> I will knock the [ __ ] out. Yes,
[laughter] I [ __ ] know. You little
You're a [ __ ] slug. So why did you So
why do you So why you about to
Why are you lying about your virgin?
the [ __ ] is on the back of that gone a woman.
We don't care. We just want fantasy. Why
you ABOUT YOUR WOMEN?
AND THEN you got you got owned by the [ __ ] virgin.
You got the yes no game. You got the yes
woman. Yeah. Anybody
I'm not talking to you about sexual education woman.
No, you answer my question. That's
yours. Why you answer? Because you're
over. Why are you No, you can't answer my question.
You've never had
a vagina in real life. Yeah. I'm a virgin.
Why don't you get your mom to [laughter] get to
I will not clean you ON THE JUST GET THE
[ __ ] TO the UK. [laughter] >> [laughter]
>> punch your face.
It's not your country. It's not your
country. Can I get your address? [laughter]
Stop talking [ __ ] Stop talking [ __ ]
Yes. You I'm bad. I'm bad. You're
[ __ ] virgin. Not you. Okay, lad.
>> You're fine, [laughter] bro. You're fine.
>> Yeah. I'm ger
to UK so I can put you in
nothing but your [ __ ] bullshitter.
>> Are you coming to the UK? [laughter]
Answer my question. Are you coming to
the UK? Are you coming to the UK? Yes or no?
We don't give a [ __ ] about
we don't give a [ __ ] about fantasy [laughter] UK.
>> Have you got a hard on? Have you got
hard on? Yeah, I'm finished now. Got
on. Yeah. Have you got a hard on now?
Have you got a hard on? Is your dick
hard now? Yeah.
>> Why you mention it on YouTube? Anyway, any any
February so I can pick the look I want
to leave this hangout in February.
I'm going to give a [ __ ] bank in
England [laughter] about PJ being a
[ __ ] You PJ being a [ __ ]
>> That's correct.
>> Oh my god.
blah blah blah blah. Are you going to
answer my question?
Is he going to answer [laughter] that?
>> Are you going to answer my question now?
Question. Are you coming? Are you coming
to me in blood so I can put you in the
co? Yes or no?
>> One second. He's just talking over
people to me.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no. Just answer the
question. bring him back on and I just I
don't give a [ __ ] because he talks
because he knows if he comes in February
who knows I will put him in the back of an ambulance.
>> Why can't everybody just play any PJ PJ
the biggest [ __ ] on here? He's the
biggest nons woman beating [ __ ] on here
ever going and his mom has to do you
know what to his mom PJ cuz everyone in
wants him dead.
>> Have you been under drink today?
No, I just want watch time fantasy if he
comes to [ __ ] London cuz he ain't
going to come. You do realize this guy
talks more [ __ ] than [ __ ] me.
>> You're banned slug. You're
>> I'm no one gives a [ __ ] what you say.
Fantasy. You're going to ban no one. You
live with your mom because you can't go
[laughter] to a m You can't ban no one.
You live on this internet because you
got no friends and you're Yeah. I'm
banned from a [ __ ] [laughter]
I'm banned from I'm banned from the
Cardier [ __ ] Kings and [ __ ] bread
[ __ ] Okay, I'm banned from the
[ __ ] I'm banned from banned because
[ __ ] fantasy said Sam Jones and I'm
banned. I'm banned from a ret. So the
[ __ ] tells me I'm banned from
yeah okay. I put it in their hand and
made them drink it. Okay. So
why don't you come to the UK? It's the crime.
>> But you're already banned. You're
already banned from my country. You
>> can't come to the UK. You're a coward.
History, mate. You You're an embarrassment.
I'm leaving this handout because all you
do is repeat yourself because you were
toss a clown.
Finished by a little virgin. Yeah.
Finished by a virgin. Okay. Virgin away.
Run away. Run away slug. Slug. You fat
fat nons. That's insane. [laughter]
>> He's [ __ ] falling over in the
background. You fat ny [ __ ] Road Elders
is getting [laughter] in the yard
and your brother Chris is a [ __ ] like you. Byebye.
>> You're two absolute virgins.
Two absolute virgins. Grezy. >> [gasps]
>> Two absolute virgins. Grezy, if you want
to know my opinion, Grezy.
[ __ ] absolute virgins. The lot of them.
They're absolute lot of them. Absolute virgins.
Two absolute virgins.
Yeah, this all [ __ ] this all started
from [ __ ] Timmy watching me in it,
Grezy. What's Timmy doing on my channel?
Do you reckon Monty's going to see this, Grey? [laughter]
Do you think Monty's going to see this?
Two absolute virgins. Absolute virgins.
You remember when Timmy said that he
spent £400 drinking?
Easy. He said he spent £400 drinking.
He's talking [ __ ] in it.
He's talking [ __ ] ain't greasy.
[ __ ] abs two absolute virgins. One sec.
Two absolute virgins. Why? Timmy,
I've got a bone to pick with you. You
never guess who's been talking [ __ ] about you.
All right, Timmy.
Nons has been talking [ __ ] about you, Timmy. [clears throat]
>> All right, then PJ. But PJ, can you just
not let down because I can't ask you that
>> Timmy, you know Nons was talking [ __ ]
about you earlier in his life and that.
>> Oh, [ __ ] nons legs. He's got no life. He
just sits in his house all day [ __ ]
talking [ __ ] He's got three watchers,
probably red star, [ __ ] fruit ding
and that. I don't give a [ __ ] PJ. I'm
unlike you. It's a fiberactive cable,
mate. Right. Nsgs. He's got no life,
right? I could find N legs. I know his
social club where he drinks. So if he
wants to try it with me, I'm I'm a
different cat of fish to you, Peter. I own him.
>> Yeah. Yeah. He was saying he he was
saying he was saying that like you're a
gambling addict's virgin and [ __ ]
>> I'm a virgin for 20 years. So how can I
be a virgin if I shatter from 19?
>> That's what he was saying on his live
stream. Well, Shaunie can only go with
Mingus because he's got no confidence to
get a fit bird in his [ __ ] lifetime,
right? You can't, right? Shaunie just
sits there all day obsessed with you cuz
he's got no [ __ ] social life. No
meaning. I mean, why do you think he's
got Cuz he's had no quality of life. PJ,
he stood there. I mean, PJ the DWP got
hold of him. He's got a lot of
explaining to do that one.
>> Yeah. And Timmy, do you know the thing? [laughter]
>> Anyway, PJ, the thing is Timmy, even if
you reported him, if you reported him to
me, I wouldn't I wouldn't say anything
about it. I wouldn't care. Like, you know,
>> PJ, I know this, but PJ, I know the
social cluby dream. I'm not like you.
I'm very a lot smarter than you. Don't
take it personally. But
>> Timmy, do you think do you think you
could have him in a fight though?
>> I think anyone can bang Sean in the
fight. He's he's a troll. But if you
[ __ ] went to fight, you'll phone the
police. Hello, I'm the victim. [laughter]
>> THE POLICE WILL SAY, "Fuck off you."
>> Oh, Timmy, mate. He's a virgin. >> Yeah,
>> PJ, let's be honest about the situation.
You're a virgin, too.
>> I'm a v. How can I be a virgin?
>> Because you don't shut up about women.
You constantly talk about them nonstop.
>> So, what did you say? He's going to call
the police and do what?
>> Well, come on. Let's be honest. If I
went to meet Sha and punched him in the
face, you played the victim and phone
the police and make out he's done
nothing wrong on social media.
>> Yeah, cuz he's a [ __ ] cuz he's an
absolute virgin coward to me. You know this.
>> Johnny has got nothing in life. He sits
there and he's mentally obsessed with
you. What sort of a life is that? Waking
up in the morning being obsessed with a virgin,
>> you know? Yeah.
>> But I'm talking about you, by the way,
>> Jimmy. I've I've proved I've had sex.
How can I be a virgin?
>> Peter, everyone knows you're a virgin. [laughter]
>> But Timmy, I've proved I've had sex.
>> Look, look, Peter. PJ, if even you are a
virgin, let's be honest about the
situation. It's not the end of the [ __ ] world.
>> So, should me and you go and fill that,
you know, nonslegs in them.
>> Cuz I'm I'm on it if you want it.
>> Why can't I thought you meant to be a gangster?
>> Yeah, but [ __ ] it. He's talking. He was
talking [ __ ] about you as well.
>> I don't give a [ __ ] It's a fiberact.
You could talk about me all day tomorrow
and I wouldn't give two shits. I'm not
like you, PJ. This is not my real world.
>> Why Timmy? Do you know how to do you
know a woman's G-spot?
>> Do you know Do you know how to lie that
you're not a virgin? [laughter]
>> What? No, Timmy. You know what a G-spot is?
>> I'm not talking to you about sex
education. When you lie that you say
you're not a virgin. Every [ __ ] on the
internet knows you're a virgin.
>> But that doesn't [laughter] matter.
>> You are a virgin, PJ. You
>> I'm a virgin.
>> Let's be honest here, PJ. It's not the
end of the world if you a virgin. Who
gives a [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I'm a virgin, man. Don't tell any
no PJ, you are definitely a virgin. You
get rattled over being rejected.
>> Yeah, I'm a virgin, bro. Yeah, I know.
Don't tell anyone, though. Yeah,
>> I have to tell anyone. You taught the
whole world, mate.
>> Yeah, but you need to fill that [ __ ] nonslegs in
>> cuz you go at me at me and Monty. You go
at me and Monty, but when nonslegs is
[ __ ] talking [ __ ] about you, you
don't say anything.
>> Yeah, [laughter] but I don't watch nons
legs, so why am I going to give a [ __ ]
Everybody knows what he's done on the
PlayStation, everybody knows what he's
about. And if people speak to him, then
they can't have no authority to call
anyone a bacon. It's like people
speaking to Ding what he said about Daz
Be's [ __ ] daughter. And people are
making out he's a saint. These people
are bit serious past the point of
hypocrites. PJ, you just got to laugh. I mean,
>> this is why I don't understand. They go
for Monty, but they don't go for nonslegs.
>> Yes. Because because the reason why they
don't go for nonslegs because you come
on the P you come on the internet. Let's
be honest about this agitated [ __ ]
talking [ __ ] about women.
>> Yeah, but even if I even if I left, no
one would still say anything.
The thing is ding like the thing the
thing with nons miller and that like
they go on about bacons but they love
talking to bacons like ding who said
that they want to rape a 14y old girl. [laughter]
>> It's not funny PJ. No it's not PJ. No
it's not. [laughter] PJ if you laugh
I'll come and knock you out if you're
going to laugh at sick [ __ ] like that.
>> You're laughing yourself.
>> I'm not laughing PJ. It's a difference.
Can you hear me laughing? No, but you
used to you used to laugh at the
gambling industry. That's ridiculous. [laughter]
That's not But that's not talking about
14y old rapist, is it? The gambling
industry is a complete different subject, PJ.
>> Yeah, but how can you laugh at the gambling industry?
>> What the [ __ ] are you on about? The
fantasy stories is like you have lost
the [ __ ] plot to a degree.
PJ, the fantasy stories industry and
what Grape said about a 14y old girl is
two completely different subjects.
Have you played roulette lately?
>> You know I played roulette yesterday,
PJ. It's the most stupid.
>> I don't watch our videos. You don't even
put full videos up.
>> PJ, you do watch my videos. Stop bullshitting.
>> No, I don't.
>> The reason why people don't go for
Shorty and you know this is because you
suck. You do your stacking, then you
start ruffling on about you've been
rejected and this one told me to [ __ ] up
and all this and all that, right? That's
why people are going for shorty because
it gets to you.
I'll come if I come off YouTube. Well,
here's the thing, Grezy. If I come off
YouTube, will people start going for
him? No, they won't to me. No, they won't.
>> I think you [laughter] have you seen
Mass Mill's post. Have you seen
smackhead smack that smackhead Stacy's
dad me? There's a lot of people
>> he's a virgin.
>> There's a lot of people PJ what have
gone for Shauny. I think you haven't
been doing your studying properly.
>> No, they haven't. No, they haven't. Not
nowhere near as many people that go for
Monty. Listen, not not nowhere near as
many people that go for Monty.
>> PJ St. Stacy's dead beat. Mom's gone for
Shauny. Um there's other I mean Mass
Miller's done several post on Shauny. I
think you're a bit delusional PJ.
>> Tammy's an actual virgin though. Like an actual virgin.
>> We all know PJ's a virgin and you are as
well mate. More lawn you got.
>> Okay. Simple question to me. What woman
>> No, no, no. Don't simple question. You
can't answer yours.
>> What's a simple question?
>> No, no, no. I answer
No one's answering your questions until you learn.
>> Yes, I'm a virgin. By the way, did you
see so? So, why do you like
why do you lie compulsively then going
to PJ that you're no?
Answer your question. No, no, no. Too
many questions. It's my turn to answer
too many questions. No, no, no, no, no. I'll just
I haven't finished the question yet, M.
I haven't finished the question. [laughter]
That's how thick you are.
No, no, no. You're the slug. You're the
one who's only 6:00 in the morning making out
with your [ __ ] mom.
You're a single [ __ ] virgin.
You're a virgin. Yes, I'm going. So,
I've had sex with the same 30 years. I'm a virgin.
>> Women had a prostit
[laughter] I'm a I'm a I'm a virgin
fantasy. Does that play your rocket?
>> Yes, it does. Thank
>> two absolute virgin.
>> Okay, no problem. Yes, I'm a virgin. Now,
>> what does a clip look like? What does a
>> No, no, no, no. You haven't even
answered my question yet. Why are you
lying that you've got a Message which
everybody on the internet knows you haven't?
>> But that's not a question. That's a statement.
>> Yes. No, it's a question. Answer the
question. Why are you lying that you've
got a Message?
>> But that's an unfair question.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no. Just answer the
question. Why are you Why are you being
shitty that you've got a business when
Why do you Why do you
Why do you rate that you've got a job
and you're on here 24/7 asking you
>> anyway? I'm not I don't talk about 5y
old girls. Are you coming dead?
>> You said you were coming in February.
Are you coming? Yes or no? No one gives me
no one cares
for 10 years. No one gives the [ __ ] yes.
You are you are like
you are you are a stock record. You are a record.
You are you are a stock record. You are
a stock record fantasy. No one cares
fantasy. No one cares. I care that you
care. If you care that much, I'll come to
you. Well, come to
I'm banned from a virgin.
>> Yes, you're banned from Ireland. Have
you heard stupid?
Have you heard of the [ __ ] Have you
22 England and no one cares about finish.
No one cares about finish. No one cares.
[laughter] I'm a virgin.
>> I'm going out later.
>> I'm going to move my mic until you stop
having a panic attack. We can get
talking about the fights. Are you coming
to the UK? Are you coming to the UK? Are
you coming to the UK? No one cares about me.
You're a [ __ ]
You're a [ __ ] [ __ ]
No one [laughter] gives a [ __ ]
>> Can you just answer my question? Are you
coming to the UK Birmingham? No one
gives a [ __ ] about you.
IC just a woman.
>> You're a woman beater.
>> My mama.
>> Yo, Timmy thought a woman had a
prostate. He's a [ __ ] virgin.
>> Timmy, why can't you answer what a [ __ ] looks like?
>> No, I don't want to answer your
question. I want to know how you can I
want to know the UK in February so I can
put you in a coma. So you
full of [ __ ]
mate. You're going to ban anyone. You've
run away from
You must have owned you massively. You can't
you must you're going to do nothing.
You're going to do nothing. You're going
to do nothing. Stop talking.
So you're triggered about me. You're
triggered about you're triggered over.
You keep repeating yourself. You keep
repeating yourself. Answer my question.
>> PJ, PJ, will you kick him out?
>> No. Kick him out, PJ. Thank you, PJ.
Well, he over talks. Are you coming,
this is all I want to know, to the UK in
February so I can put you [laughter] in
a coma. No one gives a [ __ ] about Tim
Aldridge rowing on a bus doing what he's
doing. No one gives a [ __ ] about Tim
Aldridge doing what he does. We care
about fantasy. Is are you coming to the
UK in February so I can put you in
Yeah. Hello. Right. So, let him back on
now. Doesn't answer a question. PJ, keep
him out. All we want is yes or no. Is he
coming to the UK in February? >> Okay. [laughter]
>> No one's interested in this [ __ ] No,
no, no. Kick him out. Kick him out. AJ's
not going to answer the question. It's a
coward. [laughter] It's a [ __ ]
coward. Right. One more chance. Fantasy.
Are you coming to the UK? Yes or no? No
one gives a [ __ ] about Tim Eldridge.
We've won a fight.
[laughter] Let him back in.
>> Let him back in. If he doesn't ask your
question this time, ban him. It's a
[ __ ] waste of that one.
>> Listen to him clap in the back.
>> Oh my god. Pick him out, PJ. He's a
[ __ ] He's a [ __ ] PJ. He's a
[laughter] [ __ ] PJ, we all know that
he's been silenced for five, six years,
but he's been in the UK. So let him talk
about let him talk about Eldridge 24/7.
Let him talk about Aldridge cuz he's
going to do all that [ __ ]
>> Oh Autumn, how are you mama?
>> Anyway, anyway,
>> let's have a talk. Why do you give a
[ __ ] about Shaunie? Cuz you he does
trigger you, PJ. Let's be honest about
the situation. He does.
>> I trigger him. He makes videos.
>> No, you don't. PJ
makes But listen to me. For someone to
make community post to someone every
day, they must be triggered.
>> Yes. But you give them Can I talk to you
like an adult, PJ? You give you give
them a reason to do it. That's right.
Cuz you non-stop going, "Oh, Sean's a
virgin. Sean skinn." Sean said the more
you keep doing that, look, all these
post what fruit can do on me. I do one
or two to take the piss and that's it. I
laugh at the [ __ ] So why can't So why
can't you? But yeah, because he is a virgin.
>> Yeah, but PJ, you you you do get rattled
over some basic nuts. It's unbelievable.
>> And you do get rattled over in PJ. You
get very rattled.
>> You hear me? You do, PJ. The Do you know
Do you know how to beat Sean? Ignoring him.
>> That's the only way we're going to beat
him. Yes. Really? And if he keeps doing
it on your
>> Yeah, but you don't have But Timmy, you
don't have people obsessed with you.
>> Yes, I do. I've got mass many videos
about 80,000 videos a day on me. Do you
see a movie react? No. I take the piss
out of a movie and then that's it. I
don't go crying every day. Mass has done
this and mass mills done that. I ignore
them PJ. But you say you the only life
you've got. You go live when you gamble.
You're live every day. You talk about if
you really say YouTube's not your life,
then prove it to everyone and don't come
live every day and don't do videos every day.
>> Yeah, I have. But that but Smoky Beast
still comes on here every day, isn't it?
>> Yes, but PJ
God, who gives a [ __ ] what anybody else does, right?
>> You know, you know, Timmy, you know that
you know that Smoky Beast skin, isn't it?
>> No, he's got a few quid. Look, PJ, who
gives a [ __ ] who's got me? Listen to me,
PJ. I'm trying to help you here. Who
gives a [ __ ] about Banger being on here
every day? We all know this is Banger's
life and Banganger is the only thing
Bangers got to do.
>> I want to know why they're on here every day.
>> Because they've got nothing in life, PJ.
What part of [laughter] that don't you
understand? Like [ __ ] on here every day
talking the same [ __ ] about you cuz he's
got [ __ ] all in life. >> Yeah.
>> And that JF you've seen that Jo account to me?
>> I don't know JF. To be honest to you, JF
is going to Thailand, PJ, and you've got
a bit of a grunch against your bonnet on
that. Who gives a [ __ ] if JF's going to
Thailand? Why does all this bother you?
>> What are you talking about?
>> It does bother you. 12minute video
[ __ ] talking about JF going to
[ __ ] Thailand. Who gives a [ __ ]
>> Yeah, because he's a [ __ ] weasel, Timmy.
>> But who cares, PJ? He's got an opinion.
Who [ __ ] cares? I hate these people
on TV on um uh YouTube to me.
>> But PJ, why do you give a [ __ ] You say
YouTube's not your life, but you're
getting triggered what other people
think. People talk about cause me a
nons, cause me a boss wanker, cause me a
bum beater. Do you think I'm going to
give a [ __ ] No. Do you think I'm going
to go on about it tomorrow? No. My day
goes on, PJ.
>> Yeah, true.
>> But you But but you you compulsively go
on about it because it does bother you.
You're a bullshitter. M
>> you won £100 the other day, didn't you?
>> I won about450 this week. Let's start in
a minute. Why do you let these people bother you?
>> How did you win it?
>> We'll talk about that in a minute. Stop
switching the subject. Why do you let
these people bother you?
>> They don't bother me. They're repeaters.
>> They do. Oh, PJ, they do bother you cuz you don't
>> They don't. They're repeaters. They're
>> PJ, have you ever considered you repeat yourself?
>> Yeah, but not as much as these people in
it. Yes, you do, PJ. Saying you not been
a virgin for the past [ __ ] three and
a half years.
>> They [laughter] are repeaters though, Timmy.
>> But PJ, you've been repeating and saying
not been a virgin for the past three and
a half years.
>> Listen, Timmy, every time I go on your
channel, every time I go on your
channel, Timmy, it's the same skin. It's
just repeat same repeating people.
>> PJ PJ groups called me skin all week. Do
you think I'd give a [ __ ] why you bother
me if someone calls you skin?
>> Autumn is my mut's my mama to me.
>> Hello, Autumn. Look, but PJ, I'm trying
to help you here. You think I'm taking
the piss? Why does it affect you that
someone calls you skins?
>> It doesn't. It's just self-reflecting.
>> But it doesn't bother you, PJ. Cuz you
ramp rage and you go [ __ ] in sterics,
>> right? Listen, Timmy, you want me to ask
me a question, right? Ask me this,
right? Ask me I I I'll answer you a Go.
I'll answer you if you ask me. Ask me
ask me this. Yeah. Why do these people
call you skin? Ask me it.
>> Because they call you skin, PJ. Cuz they
want a reaction. And
>> no, no, no. You don't. Ask me the
question. Ask me the question.
>> Okay. Why do people call you skin, PJ?
>> Because they're skin. [laughter]
>> But PJ,
>> whether you like it or not, maybe it's
not true. Calador the other day showed
on camera. 17 grand PJ is not skin. In
your world, it might be skins, but in
the real world, PJ, it's not skins.
>> Timmy, if these people weren't skinned,
they wouldn't be on here every day. Do you not
>> PJ? and PJ they're skint because they've
got nothing in their lives apart from
this. They don't go out and spend any
money. That's why they've got that's why
they save their DWP sitting the house
all day calling people virgin single cuz
they're [ __ ] single and you know got
to stabilize themselves. What part of
that don't you understand PJ?
>> I do. I do understand it. I do.
>> No, you don't. You don't PJ because you
your right your your world is money. You
are mentally obsessed with money PJ.
Right. It's beyond chronicle.
>> Yes, you [ __ ] are
>> right. And you and you get triggered
more than you. Where with me, PJ, I
don't give a [ __ ] shorty has got
[ __ ] 10 million, 50 million, 25
million, whatever. Right. I mean, people
call me stink, but people know nothing
about me. They don't know what I've got
in the bank and that. And I just I laugh
at them. PJ, I don't understand why you
can't do the same.
>> How much do you have? [snorts]
I'm not talking about I just want
everyone to think I'm a skin because I
get my dick gets hard over it. [laughter] Did
>> you hear that? Timmy, you've got
>> But you do and why you obsessed with
this grim? You do know he trolls the
[ __ ] out of you. You [ __ ] [ __ ] >> Grey.
>> Yes, he trolls the [laughter] [ __ ] out of you.
>> How do you know?
>> Have you seen his videos? Are you that [ __ ] spasticate?
>> Yeah, but it's not malicious. Yes, but
he's still trolling you. [laughter]
[ __ ] [laughter] hell, PJ. You going
about shorty and he's trolling you as
well. What planet are you on? Timmy. Hello.
>> No link. It's a no virgin zone.
Okay, I'll put it's a no virgin zone.
Nons is not joining. He wants to join,
but he's not joining to me cuz it's a no virgin zone.
>> I don't I don't care if he I I don't
care if he does join PJ. It's a [ __ ]
cow to me. You're the one who's scared
of him, not me.
>> I'm a coward. You mentioned the police
over me cuz I put up posters. You
[ __ ] loser. You [ __ ] virgin rat
looking loser can't.
>> No, he's not coming up because he's
trying to get the police involved. to
me. He's the police involved.
>> PJ PJ is winning here cuz you don't let him on.
>> I I made him go cuz he's trying to get
the police involved. You [ __ ]
>> The final heir because he comes on a
hand gaps. The police are going to come
and arrest you. I've never heard any so much [ __ ]
>> I'm not allowed to contact him. It's by court order.
>> Oh, but surely he didn't say. If you got
any evidence on this, P James, you can
>> Yes, I do have evidence. I'll show you
it tomorrow if you want. Yeah, I'll dig
it out. Yes, I do have evidence. Please
do. I will do it because that will make me off.
>> And and I said I said to him, Timmy,
listen. I said, if you message me on
WhatsApp, I'll let you on. So if he
tries to call the police, I've got
evidence where he's contacted me to me.
You know how these things work, right?
>> You know what I mean?
>> PJ at the end of the day, right?
>> Yeah. But you even said that he's got no
life and that to me. YOU EVEN SAID LIFE.
HE s he sits there waking up in the
morning like Master does with me
thinking about you. He's more interested
in a virgin in his own real [ __ ]
life. And he's a [ __ ] virgin himself. Timmy.
>> Yeah. So, you heard it from him. You absolute virgin.
>> PJ, right? PJ, he tried saying Timmy.
Timmy, he tried saying that he [ __ ] a
girl on a on a car uh a park bench. That
never happened. I knew the girl. Timmy,
she's she's Muslim. Muslim. But PJ,
Muslims do have sex before. Oh, you wrong.
>> But she didn't [ __ ] him. She didn't [ __ ]
him. She She went nothing. He went
nowhere near that girl to me.
Even Even if he did, why is it bothering you?
>> Because he's an absolute virgin lying
about someone that I know.
>> But if he did, do it. It's It is
bothering you, PJ. Cuz you sound rattled
in your voice.
>> Because I can't believe he's he's almost
31 and he's never had his leg over and
he's still a virgin.
>> PJ, he has had his leg over.
>> He has not had his leg over. He's the
biggest virgin going like you are.
You're both two virgins. Two peas in the absolute virgin.
>> If I If I If I say I'm a virgin, would
that make you happy? Yes,
>> mate. You two are hacker virgins.
>> I If I If I call myself a virgin, would
that make you happy? Yes.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Okay. I'm a virgin. Are you Are you excited?
>> So, wait. You So, Monty's a virgin. Yeah.
>> Monty's always been a virgin.
>> So, Monty's a virgin. But that [ __ ]
nons from out of London, eh? That
[ __ ] nons virgin. You're biased.
>> Well, what the [ __ ] does bias mean? Can
you explain? Cuz I don't think you even
know what the meaning of the word means.
>> Of course I know what bias means. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Well, so what does what does it
>> you [ __ ] you pair of virgins? Absolutely.
>> No, that no bias doesn't mean we're a
pair of virgins. PJ, try again.
>> You are a pack of virgin. >> Yeah,
>> that does not mean Boris.
>> No, but you you are virgin. No, you do. You do.
>> But but PJ, I'm trying to help you here.
Why are you [laughter] bo you bothered
about this [ __ ] cable? Why are you
bothered about what Shorty says about
you? Why are you bothered about what
this joke? Why does it really bother And
it does bother you, PJ. Don't
>> Yeah, but you even said that if you
fight him, he'll call the police. That's
what you said to me.
>> Because that's what he does. But one day
his corruptence will come and he'll get
Nick patrolling and you'll have the last [ __ ] laugh.
>> Yeah. I just think he needs to get laid.
I've always said to him he's going to
die a virgin.
>> I'm not being funny. You say Sean's
obsessed. You're just as bad as him.
You're obsessed with him.
>> I can't watch somebody I used to meet be
a virgin. Be a virgin.
>> Come on. Come on PJ. Let's talk. I'm
trying to like PJ. Are you actually
going to act your age or you going to
act like a 5-year-old for the rest of your life?
>> He's an absolute virgin. I am acting my
age. I am acting my age.
>> You know, you're actually old,
>> Timmy. I'm actually my age, lad. Come on.
>> So, but let let's have a talk. You gone
about Shaunie being obsessed with you,
but you're just as bad as him cuz you
said you said he is obsessed with me.
>> But you're obsessed with him. You're
both as [ __ ] bad as each other.
>> Yeah. I just think he needs to get laid.
Bit like you Timmy.
>> I think I I think what you need to do
the [ __ ] up, ignore him, and let him
make a patter of himself. >> Yeah.
And that's the
>> You haven't been One second. One second.
One second to me. One second, bro. You
haven't been nicked because you didn't
show the police what you done. You
absolute virgin. The last time you tried
to call the police, they told you to
[ __ ] off cuz they've seen your Virgin
Channel. See, the thing is, Timmy,
right, when he was reporting me to the
police, they didn't see his virgin
channel. Now they've seen his virgin
channel. They don't act now. Do you see
what I mean to me? because they're not
going to react to him because they'll
say to him, "Look, mate, you you're
poking the bear. You're winding him up."
And they'll tell him to [ __ ] off the se.
>> Do you remember nons?
>> You're not a victim, you absolute
virgin. You're not Hey,
listen. You're somebody that got owned
on YouTube. One second, Timmy. One
second, Timmy. You got your ass a good
old whooping and you had to call the
police. You got your ass a good
whooping. Think about it, Timmy. All
right. If you got your good old whoopen
and you had to run to the police, you'd
be taking a hell, would you?
>> Of course.
Would you call the police over YouTube
to me? I
>> I've had to call the police over YouTube
cuz someone called the police over me.
And I would never call the police over
this [ __ ] And you know what the police
legs did cuz he couldn't handle me. I
was saying he could handle you say get
over this. Jesus Christ.
>> No, Timmy. Listen, listen. I know
someone I know someone called the police
on you, but in his case, he I was too
much for him. He couldn't handle me.
>> Do you know me? Oh god. Can you calm
down, PJ? And take a deep breath,
please. Yeah, cuz you're very excited.
You [ __ ] rattled your anxiety to [ __ ]
you up tonight.
[ __ ] virgin. I [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Go on.
>> The The police don't give a [ __ ] about
your social media. They get fed up with
it, PJ. I want to do an event for two
weeks to be I'm I'm the one that made it
happen. I made walk around. Do you
remember the posters, Ty? Do you remember?
>> Yes. It's your dick very hard now. PJ,
if you got a massive rocket,
>> but you don't remember the posters, do you?
>> I remember them well, PJ. And no one
gives a [ __ ] Okay. Well, I'm talking
about the police.
>> He did give a [ __ ] cuz he went running
to the police like a little [ __ ]
>> PJ, I'm trying. You know,
>> I'm trying I'm trying to explain to you
about the police and social media
because I've had people call the police.
The police get better with social media.
They get better with people calling the
police social media. >> God,
>> you say you don't suffer from anxiety.
[ __ ] hell. You're all over the place. You are.
>> Jimmy, would you do posters of someone?
>> I got the mental age of a [ __ ] 5-year-old.
>> No, I stopped you going to that event
because of the posters. I I swapped him
going to an event because of posters to me.
>> Yes. Okay. Is your dick that hard now?
Can we shut up about it?
>> Would you ever do posters to me?
>> I just said cuz I haven't got the mental
age of a [ __ ] 5year-old.
>> How did you see when I done it then?
Where did you see it?
>> You put it all.
>> Did it make you laugh? Did it [laughter]
>> No, I just thought it cuz [ __ ] idiot
you were to be honest.
>> Yeah. To me. be honest.
>> Of course I love social med
you you stopped you second [laughter] to
me. You stopped going to the plow and
harrow cuz of me. You abs a virgin. You
went to the police station because I
gave your ass. I gave your ass a good
whooping. You couldn't handle the Peter
belly. It was too much for you. You had
to run to the old bill cuz your virgin
ass got a whooping. You [ __ ] virgin.
>> One second Timmy. I wish I could go back
to meeting you when I was younger. Not
you, Timmy. Right. When you used to call
me a virgin. I'll be like, "Look at your
[ __ ] self, you skinned virgin. You
shitty little Kent wanker in your little You
not so big." One second, Timmy. You're
not so big for a man, are you? You
[ __ ] skint virgin. And you shitty
little beds. I'll be just as bad as you
now. Come on, you [ __ ] virgin [ __ ]
Come on. Come on. Come on. You little
bed sick grand a month boy [ __ ] with an
ugly girlfriend you can't sleep with.
Come on. See, I'm like you, Timmy. I'm mad
>> PJ. PJ, you're don't take me seriously.
You're taking it very seriously tonight.
When I was shouting at
>> projecting your virgin onto me cuz
you're a [ __ ]
>> When I when I was when when I was shown
at fantasy stories, you do know that was
acting PJ. I'm an actor.
>> I'm not actor. When I'm telling him he's
a big version, you are
all of these sex stories. All of these
sex stories that he's made up to me.
Absolute made absolutely made up to me,
>> you know. But who gives a [ __ ] Why are
you obsessed with it? Surely. Why does
he Why does he affect your life?
>> He needs to stop pretending he's had
sex. He's He's a classic.
>> So, so, so because he pretends he has
sex. That affects your everyday life. Yes.
>> Well, I just find it pathetic, Timmy. I
knew that I
>> Timmy, he didn't have sex with her. He
literally never had sex with her.
>> But, but why is it affecting your
everyday life? How is it affecting your
everyday life? He does because you're
going on about like a long playing record.
>> Timmy, it's okay for him to be a virgin.
I don't care. But just stop lying.
>> PJ, it's not the end of the world if
you're a virgin. How many times I got to
tell you this?
>> Yeah. Same thing to you, virgin boy.
There's nothing wrong that you ain't
your dick suck. You're just not any
girl's cuppper. You certainly Britney's
cup of tea. Oh, you know he's some girl. You
>> And you had you saying you've got no
autism. [ __ ] hell. Jimmy, listen to
me. You know, you know his dad was 42
when he met her his mom that his mom
that was 14. You do realize that?
>> Yeah. Yes.
>> No, you you do realize that, right?
>> Yes. I've heard about this 14y old thing
you did with the internet. I don't give
a [ __ ] about that, PJ. I'm not
interested. I'm trying to talk to you.
Why does this website trigger you?
>> So, you don't care about nons then?
Yes, I do care about nons, but I don't
care about you know when he went you
know you know HE WENT TO COLLEGE OH god
mention 80,000 times gives a [ __ ] everyone knows
>> no but you don't know yeah but listen to
me right you know when he went to
college right he he got
>> everyone knows everyone knows
>> but that's where this whole thing comes from
>> you say you don't repeat yourself but
you've been repeating for the past years.
>> Let me just say no. No, no. You don't
know about the shovel cole thing to me.
You don't know.
>> Yes, PJ. Yes, I do.
>> He was like, I like shovel co. I like
co. He went into college the next day,
right? And I was like, I'm not gay. I
like co. He was copying. He was a
copycat to me. And
>> how can you got busted being a copycat? Copy.
>> And you say you have and you and you say
you haven't got autism. I think you're
being copy. I don't copy the crowd.
>> Of bell boy, listen. You're a little rat boy.
>> You won't dare [ __ ] do videos of me
talking. You will not dare do a video
talking my name. I dare you to do a
video talking my name. You do a video
talking my name. You rat ugly little
virgin [ __ ] on the ground a month. Do I
dare you to do a video talking my name?
One second, Simmy. Leave it. Leave it.
One second. Yeah.
>> Just cuz you mate. Just because you got
caught out with a copycat trend with
Sher Cole, you absolute virgin. Don't
project your gayness onto me just
because you're getting bullied. Call copycat.
>> Have you finished now, PJ? Have you
finished now? So, this is where this is
where Sha's winning. You've just gone on
for the past 40 minutes constantly about
Shauny, but you make out he's obsessed.
We've been going on about him for 40 [ __ ] minutes.
>> Yeah. And I bet you won't message me on
WhatsApp. And I bet you won't message me
on WhatsApp. Another thing, I bet you
won't And I bet you won't message me on
WhatsApp. He's not allowed to message me
on WhatsApp, by the way, Timmy. He's
banned from messaging me on WhatsApp.
That's what he told me.
>> You told you you've told us all about
30,000 times, PJ.
>> Yeah, he can't contact me. He's not
allowed. It's part of the It's part of
the conditions. He's not allowed to
contact me, mate. That's why he won't do it.
>> So, here's the thing, Timmy. You say you
don't like, and I'm telling you about a
nons. PJ, we all know about the shorty
thing. The reason why I say I don't care
because I've heard it about 50 billion times, PJ.
So, you agree that he is a nons?
>> The whole internet does. They only like
him because it affects you. You're
[ __ ] rattled like you're doing right now. >> Yeah.
>> But listen, I But you don't know that he
said Cheryl car was attractive to fit in
with the crowd.
>> Everybody knows about Shauny Dlex. the
reason why they go with him because it triggers you.
>> What part of that don't you understand?
>> Yeah, but he was saying he was saying
>> he was saying that um he was saying that
if I don't like Sher Co, I'm gay. Timmy,
you have And you don't copy the crowd.
You don't copy the crowd.
>> He was follow He was following the crowd.
>> So were you. Grimsy Grimsy Grimsy. Oh,
you're my new best friend. I said so I
don't so so Timmy I said if you don't
find if you don't find an attractive if
you don't find how how am I a nons
exactly everyone knows you're a nons
Timmy everyone knows he's a nons grimsy
grimsy I've had a new cup of coffee on
Grimsy I've got a new and you make out
you don't go with the crowd you're a bit
of a fant listen to me he's asking how
am I a nons he is a nons he is a n
>> come on PJ come on come on PJ you have
said some sick [ __ ]
but he's asking how He's asking how he's
a nod. He is a nod to me.
>> PJ, why are you This is why you say you
got their autism and you're going about
I've got a laugh, man.
>> Boy, suck my dick. Rat boy. B boy. Suck
my dick. Rat boy with no teeth. >> Virgin.
[clears throat] Have you Have you Have
you ever Have you Have you ever
considered having some therapy
>> when you messaged me on WhatsApp? Virgin
boy with a rat face. I think we got [laughter]
>> So Jimmy, why have you not Why do you
not go out nons legs for being a nons?
That's a bit hypocrite.
>> I've I've already set my mind on [ __ ]
nonsex. But I'm not like you, PJ. I
don't need to repeat it 56 billion times.
>> Timmy, come on. Come on. Come on. Okay, Timmy.
>> I I don't know the kid. I'm not going to
attack him. So I don't know him. He can
talk about me as much as he wants. I
don't give a [ __ ] and [ __ ] you over this M
>> yeah but Timmy so but you go Monty man
for being announced but you don't got him for
>> I know I I go at Monty man and I explain
I go to Monty man because he's a [ __ ]
appalling father like the [ __ ] mother
Kaye he [ __ ] swore at L told him to
[ __ ] off doing some recording things
make a [ __ ] to the go to the fridge
to cook her own [ __ ] dinner which all
the evidence on the Patel's channel this
is the way Shaunie hasn't got
commitments like Mongol has Mongol
[ __ ] up massively by putting his whole
[ __ ] life on social media and treated
his mom. I mean, at the end of the day,
the only reason why he sees the well, we
call them Nathan's miners. The only
reason why he's seen Nathan's miners is
because his mom's got them in care. If
his mom wasn't at the responsible adult,
he said that he wouldn't see him.
>> Yeah, but Timmy, he said that he was
chatting he was chatting up a 15y old.
>> He said it himself, Timmy.
>> PJ, we are we're talking about Sea.
You're on Mongol now cuz you you keep track.
>> We're talking about nonslegs. He said
that he chated up a 15y old. Yeah, but
you just Yeah, but you just said, "Why
do I go to Mongol?" And I'm explain why
I go to Mongol because the way you
treated his [ __ ] miners was [ __ ] appalling.
>> Yeah, but so you've got no problem with
someone chatting up a 15y older.
>> PJ, I've said my mind on him so many
[ __ ] times. I'm not like you. I'm not
alone playing [ __ ] stuff record and
go on about the same [ __ ] I say it once
and it's end of subject.
>> Okay. Can I Okay. Can I ask you a
question, Timmy? Yeah.
>> Come on.
>> Do you think listen listen to me Timmy Timmy?
>> Do you think right a 25year-old and a
16y old is right
>> PJ? No, but it's in the law. I don't think
>> but nons were saying it's it's nons were
saying it was fine.
>> Yes, but it's not illegal PJ cuz when
they pass 16 it's legal age.
>> Yeah, but it's 18 and above. No, but
Timmy 18 and above. 18 and above. And
why why I say that to me is because when
you're when you're 16, you're still at
school. So I'm always 18 and above me.
>> Yes, PJ. PJ PJ, I agree with you. 16 and
25 is wrong. I'm not disagreeing with
you, but it's not against the law, PJ.
That's what I'm trying to explain. But
>> it's always better to stick to 18, you
know. It's always better to because
Timmy because Timmy cuz Timmy the thing
is the thing is Timmy you can't you're
still at school at 16, aren't you? So
you know what I mean?
six form at 16 or college or having a job.
>> Yeah. And and you can't [ __ ] you
can't um you can't [ __ ] um buy
alcohol and stuff.
>> No, I know that. But PJ, this is why
people get pissed off you cuz people try
to help you and all you do is talk about
[ __ ] Shaunie like he's your [ __ ] boyfriend.
>> You know, I don't I done a lot for him,
you know. Listen listen to me. I've done
a lot for that kid.
>> Yes, but listen to me, PJ. adding a lot to people.
>> You know, do you know do you know he had
he had a stepdad that used to beat him
to me? He had a stepdad called [ __ ]
David Campbell. He was from Leeds.
Horrible [ __ ] Horrible horrible [ __ ]
And and I helped him and everything.
>> I went around the house and you know
what I'm saying? >> Yeah. >> Right.
>> And and and this is how
>> PJ PJ, what I'm trying to say to you is
this, right? Why can't you just get on
with your life and do something in your
lives and moaning about the same
pointless [ __ ] like [ __ ] ding like
[ __ ] banger like Mr. being all them
who are manchilds that are meant to be
grown men. Why can't you get on with
your life? Why are you rattled over this shell?
>> Yeah, David Campbell.
>> Listen, Timmy, I know a lot about him. I know Timmy
>> I don't give [laughter] a [ __ ] if you
know a lot about him. I'm trying to help
you here. Why don't you get on with your
own [ __ ] life? Why are you obsessed
with this individual and you got the
cheek to say he's he's obsessed with you.
>> He's got a whole channel dedicated to
me. He's got a whole channel stalking me
to me. I've been my
Yeah, but Yeah, but you do exactly the
same. You You both need to [ __ ] grow up.
>> There was a Scottish lad in uh in
college called Jack and he used to bully him.
>> Yes, but PJ, we're not talking about
we're talking about
>> Do you remember Do you remember when you
used to say Chev was attractive to
>> Oh my shoot me
talking to Timmy.
>> Yeah, go on Timmy. He wanted to follow
the crowd. Bless him.
>> He wanted to follow the crowd, didn't you?
>> But you want to But you're exactly the
[ __ ] same. You can't talk.
>> No, I know the second maid. And it
Nothing I say about you is made up,
mate. Everything I say about you is the [ __ ] truth.
>> PJ, right? I'm trying to help you there.
Where are we going to go on this? Where
how you going to move on in life? You
going to come on YouTube every day
moaning about women and moaning about
[ __ ] Sean? How are you going to move on?
>> No, I don't mind.
>> You're doing You've been worried about
him for the past hour, PJ. [snorts]
>> And you know you have. Your silence
gives it away. >> No,
>> I'm trying to help you here. I'm I'm not
I'm not bullying you, PJ. I'm trying.
But I You're that autistic. You don't
let you don't listen to anyone.
>> You know what? Do you know what he
needs? You know what he needs? One second.
>> Here we go.
>> I reckon he just needs to get himself I
think he needs to get himself a little job.
>> A little
>> I think you need to [ __ ] I think you
need to [ __ ] get off social media. Sis s
a little job I think a little job would
do you the world of good. One second to
me. I'm being serious.
>> I think a [ __ ] psychology will do you
some good. PJ Triple H will get you a
little job. Triple Triple H will get you
a little job. Nonss. I know Trip R was
was saying he would get him a little job.
>> Oh god, you are obsessed with Shaunie
and yet you make out he's obsessed with you.
>> I just want him to get to lose his
virginity. I want him to lose his I want
I'm supporting him. I want him to
finally get laid,
>> you know. Once he gets a job and that
sort himself out, he might get laid, [snorts]
>> you know.
>> Are you finished now? Are you finished >> Yeah.
>> Good. So where we gonna go,
>> you got you got you got he got bullied
by a guy called Jackary.
I don't know if I can quote you anymore.
This right where
>> I forgot the other I forgot the other
guy's name, but I know that the first
one was Jackie. It was a long time ago,
but they were definutistic people, but
this is probably the most autistic
person I've come across. Anyway,
>> you're born on the You're You're born on
the 26th of August.
>> Have you,
>> Timmy? You're born on the 26th of August.
>> Who gives a [ __ ] if I am or not?
>> It wasn't the other night. It was days
ago. Yeah, that's your birthday to me.
>> Yes, we know that, PJ. Everybody knows
that. Can we get to
>> What are you doing for your What are you
doing for next year's birthday?
[ __ ] staying off this fiber cable.
Put it that way.
>> Timmy, you're funny, [ __ ] You are. I
forgot the other name. Who is But I
don't know the other name. [snorts]
>> All right, PJ, I'm trying to help you.
Like, listen to me. Don't talk to Sean.
Listen to me. Where are you going to go
in life? Where are you going to go in
life from here? I'll
>> go I'm going to go to I'm going to go to Orington.
No, no, no. I'm I'm trying to You going
to come off YouTube? You going to give
your head a bubble? You going to see a
psychologist? Or you going to talk about
Sean for the rest of your life?
>> I'm going to go to Openington,
>> right? PJ, do you want to be a winner or
a loser? Cuz at the moment, you're being
a [ __ ] loser.
>> His nonsle's a loser.
>> Yes, because he's obsessed with you and
the only thing he's got in life is
[ __ ] Virgin Peter.
>> I don't want to be I don't want to be a
loser like him. It's like it's like
Steven Har Steven Harwood which is fruit
king. Ding. He's a loser cuz he's
obsessed with slugs.
>> Call you a loser. Oh, look. He says
look. Look at this. Timmy, read this. He
told me come to Orington and I'll call
the police. You absolute virgin. Come
on, Timmy. You've got to say that. He
says if I go to his area, he's going to
call the police.
>> Oh, let him call the police. I just
laugh at him. Go to his area. Let him
call the police. And they'll tell him to
[ __ ] off when they see how obsessed he
is with you.
>> Yeah. The virgin. I have to show the
virgin channel. There's two virgin
channels to me.
>> The PJ I don't watch short cuz I don't
give a [ __ ] about people going on about
you 24/7 cuz everybody knows you're a
virgin. Everyone knows you live with
[laughter] your mom.
So why not watch somebody repeating history?
>> Especially when it's coming from a
virgin themselves like him, the biggest virgin.
>> Why am I going to watch somebody when
everybody knows everything about you, PJ?
Yeah, I'm a virgin even though I prove
I've had sex.
>> So, do you know this is why Timmy, do
you know this is why people don't prove
themselves to you anymore? You know,
this is You want to talk serious? This is why
>> people prove they've got more money.
They prove they've had sex and you still talk [ __ ]
>> PJ, why you got to prove yourself to a
bunch of people on a fiberact? Why does it matter?
>> It doesn't. I'm just saying
>> it does matter cuz you've got to prove
you've had sex in front of anyone on the
internet because you're that [ __ ] sad
and insecure. It's untrue. You are
triggered. What that cable tells you?
>> 13 grand. You showed your daddy's life
savings four years ago and you don't have that.
>> Who gives Who? Oh my god.
>> I showed seven grand of my own money and
you've never shown 13,000 of your own
money and you ain't got money.
>> PJ PJ, who gives a [ __ ] if Sean's got 50
grand? Why is it bothering you? you that
13 grand was your daddy's that you can't
show now. I'm just saying to me. He's
bringing up because he's typing to me. He's typing.
>> Why you Why are you bothered? Cuz you
are bothered. You are absolutely
vasselled that Sean's got money and
you're money obsessed.
>> He ain't got no [ __ ] money, mate. He
lives in a bed with no bed.
>> He's absolutely got no money.
>> God. God. God. Can I Can I Fin could
show 50 grand. I wouldn't give a [ __ ] PJ.
>> But you do.
PJ, you you are the you are the version
of the old slug and it's embarrassing. I
used to be obsessed with money and it
all it does is do do nothing but ruin a man.
>> Why are you bothered about if someone's
got a pri more than you? Your jealousy
PJ is chronicle. >> How?
>> But you're jealous that Sean's got money
cuz you know you you shut up about it. [snorts]
>> I have a big bed with my girlfriend and
you're still a virgin. Oh my
>> Timmy, listen. Timmy, what [ __ ] This
community is [ __ ] mad, isn't it?
>> This community is full of big [ __ ]
babies, PJ. What part of that don't you understand?
>> Yeah, it's true.
>> No, I just It's like being in the post
cuz he's crying his eyes out. I'm going
to doimmy laugh at the bastard.
>> Timmy, how's your How's your dick
feeling from the um [ __ ] the other day?
>> That's a bit of a personal question,
isn't it, PJ?
>> No, but you Well, you had sex the other
day, ain't it? And you said it was so
>> PJ I have sex every day with sex god.
>> So you had sex today? >> Yes. >> Really?
>> Yes. It's called masturbation?
>> No. When did you
>> When did you have sex with a woman? >> Today.
>> Really? Who?
>> The milk lady. >> [laughter]
>> Where did you
>> No, last I last time I had it was last
Saturday. PJ, I met some.
>> You know what though? You know what it
is? Do you know what it is to me? Yeah.
I'm not being I'm not I'm not even
lying. Yeah, Timmy.
>> I think nonsex's girlfriend fancies me. [snorts]
>> Why don't you get in there then?
>> I don't know. Cuz she's a bit of a [ __ ]
>> So are you. So you make a great couple.
>> What you want me to get? I don't think
she can handle my big dick. PJ,
>> I don't think non girlfriend could handle me.
>> Well, you wouldn't know till you ask her
out, would you?
>> She likes me. I think she has a crush on
>> Well, why don't you get in there instead
of talking about a step instead of
talking a good game, do something about it.
>> Really? What? And get her pregnant. And
so she's carrying baby Peter bellies.
>> Oh god, we don't have a [ __ ] PJ in
the old one's bad enough. Why is that? [laughter]
>> Because you say you've got no or cuz you
say and you've been rattled over Shauny
for the past hour. You say that you're
not obsessed with money, but you're
jealous that Shaun's got more money than
you and it really bothers you. You say
that you're not a virgin, but you talk
about being rejected every [ __ ] day
of the week. I mean I mean
>> I could I could touch her lady parts.
>> I'm good at touching lady parts. think
you've ever touched the ladies part, PJ.
Let's be real.
>> I touched the ladies part.
>> I spoke to your prostitute and cuz
obviously I had a very good chat with
them and they said you were
>> No, but hold on one second. One second.
Hold on. Virgin boy, she's going to have
to say that to save, but deep down she
likes me. Even Even Ricky says it. He
She's going to listen, Timmy. She's
going to say all of these bad things
about me when she's with the virgin, but
that's not what she thinks. Do you know
what I mean? Timmy,
>> you say that you're well. [ __ ] hell.
You need to see a therapist. This
surely's really got you by the ropes. Any
>> So Timmy, how how much was you in to win that 400?
>> I'll be honest with you, PJ. Tuesday I
took out £400 and I went home with 690.
>> Right. Yeah.
>> Next 500 and I came home with about 650
something stupid. I was aboutund
something up. Then I lost a bit on the
way home. So I was 70 up. Yesterday I
made about over about 1601 170 about
bought drinks. I went home with £110
profit. But I'm not gambling anymore,
PJ. I'm happy in my little pinch cuz I'm
not greedy anymore. You can't win big
anymore. The industry is [ __ ]
>> Next week.
>> So I'll be doing a [ __ ] ding two
pound a day doing Cash Beast.
>> Are you out drinking today?
>> No, I haven't even drank, PJ. I the only
reason why I overshout fantasy stories
is because he overshouts me because you
see with you he won't overshout you
because he knows you a [ __ ] He knows
with me if he comes to England he knows
he's going to be in the back of an ambulance.
>> Do you remember when you run away from Ben Gregory?
>> I didn't run away from Ben Gregory PJ
cuz this is what you do before I
practic. I had an autistic girlfriend
called him. I don't know how many times
you had it. I took the piss because I
told her I was going shopping and I went
to the bookies and I took the piss. I
own it. And she kept ringing me and I
kept ignoring her and then she phoned me
when I come out the book saying I'm
parked on double red line. Right. So I
ran to the car panicking that she
couldn't find a parking space. I didn't
know why the [ __ ] was recording me
cuz I would have [ __ ] done something about it.
>> Timmy, you know when you said you can't
win big anymore? Yeah. On the [ __ ] on
the on the damning. Yeah. Yeah. But what
if you put what if you put 400 pound
online roulette? You couldn't it?
>> Yes. But PJ, I don't want to put I don't
like that online roulette. It's the most
rigged piece of [ __ ] going.
>> Yeah, it's worse than anything today.
>> That that have mercy. Roulette has done
my [ __ ] stacking recently. That's why
I don't play anymore.
>> When did you not do you play recently,
>> PJ? I played it six months ago and I
lost about a grand in 10 minutes.
>> How did you get a grand?
>> I'm not telling you my [ __ ] income,
PJ, cuz YouTube is not my life like yours.
Woman is coward. You You ain't You was
You're jealous. Oi, you're jealous that
I got with USA, is he? He There was this
American that I got with and he got and
and Virgin Boy Nons got jealous to me.
>> But you But do you know why? Do you know
why Sean trolls you? And I can answer
the question, PJ.
>> He got jealous. He got jealous. You
wanted a bit of a fight. He
>> He's trolling you because you keep
reacting to it, PJ. What part of that
don't you [ __ ] understand?
>> That's no.
>> Yes. Yes, you do.
That's why tram trolls you. That's why [ __ ]
>> So when you when you when you when you
No, Timmy. Cuz even if you don't react,
they're still going to do it. You know that.
>> Yes. But PJ, who gives it to me?
>> Can you listen to me for once in your life? Listen.
>> Right. Stop the autistic attack and
listen to me. I will leave YouTube
tomorrow. A mass mill will carry on
talking about me for 20 years, PJ. But I
won't give a [ __ ] But I won't give a
[ __ ] cuz I won't be seeing it.
>> These people have got nothing in life.
What part of that don't you [ __ ]
>> Yeah, true. That's true.
>> So, so PJ, if someone talks about you
for the rest of your life, why does it
bother you? Why can't you look at and
go, you're the winner because they're
going on about you and you're sitting in
the background. And I was like, we
didn't I will read his post in a minute
and I'll just laugh myself to sleep.
>> That's what this is. This this this
YouTube to me is a game. It's a game of
grown men, right? And I used to be one
of them, right? And Toasty was right
back in the day and Joe Scott was right.
I was a big man child.
>> Wait, I don't know.
>> Timmy, Greavvesy. Greavves, are you there?
>> One second. Greavves, are you there? One
second. One second. [laughter] No, no,
>> Jimmy. You know, um, listen, you know,
nonsex, you know, I know a lot about him.
>> About this for the past hour, PJ, let's
talk about it again cuz he's born in the [ __ ]
>> His dad, you know, his dad,
>> right? Yes.
>> You know, his dad changed his name, isn't it?
>> No, I didn't know that, PJ.
>> So, his name he's he's his original name
was Mick Goldsmith and then he changed
his name to Mick Jonathan Robinson. And
do you know why he changed his name?
>> And do you know why he changed his name?
>> I've just I've just said why?
>> Cuz he got caught with an underage girl.
>> That's really made my day, PJ. Thank you
for letting me know that. That's really
made my day.
>> He used to be a brick layer. He used to
be a brick layer. He went to Germany and
he was born on the 1st of September.
>> He was born on the 1st of September and
he used to travel for work. He didn't
like kites. He still flew. He didn't
like He didn't like going on planes to
me, but he still went on it cuz, you know, working, >> right?
>> And he used to be like into like rock and roll.
>> Um Yeah. And he kidnapped a girl before,
>> right? Okay. PJ mind.
>> And you think you think that's on? You
>> PJ he lives in he lives in Cryen.
>> PJ, the world is full of Romans. You
expect me to fight every wrong in the
world? There's about [ __ ] 8 billion
people. PJ, this this is why I don't
look too much into social media cuz I'll
end up like you and Good Vibes and
Banger completely [ __ ] rattled. PJ,
as long as it doesn't affect me. As long
as it doesn't affect me, why should I get involved?
>> Yeah, he lives in he lives in uh Cuden.
>> PJ, if I go through social media
incidents, I'll end up dying through stress.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> And he has he likes the guitar. His dad
likes the couture. Timmy, have you ever
played a guitar?
>> Yes, PJ, I have played a guitar.
>> Yeah, he used to collect um guitars and
stuff. He was very very bad cocaine. Uh
Timmy, he was very bad on the cocaine.
He gambled. He gambled everything. And
>> so was I. So So was I bad on the
cocaine, PJ. I've given you up for three
months. So why are you judging people on
cocaine? Cuz I struggled with that.
>> His dad was a proper cokehead.
>> So was I. So, how does that make you a bad per
owed [ __ ] drug dealers money?
>> But but but PJ that gives a [ __ ] about
Sha's dad. Let's be honest.
>> Yeah, but being a cokehead, Timmy. Come on.
>> But come on. Come on. You say Sha's
obsessed and you've been going on about
Shaunie for the past [ __ ] hour and a half.
>> Yeah, cuz he's been in the chat.
>> Yes, but you don't. But it's PJ Ding was
in my chat. I just I wouldn't go on
about ding for two hours. I just wind
him up. A panic attack and I'll just
play my tunes. Why do you let these
individuals get to you?
>> We know how you get your money, Jimmy. You sublet.
>> I sublet. What the [ __ ] are you on
about? I live on my own. You [ __ ]
>> But you get your money from subleting.
>> How can I sublet if I live on my own? You did.
>> But you used to sublet. [snorts]
>> Who's told you?
No, I'm saying you did it.
>> So where's the evidence?
>> I'm guessing.
>> So there's no evidence. So why are you
making up [ __ ] then?
>> No, but you did used to know it. [snorts]
>> Where's the evidence again?
>> Money Mike told me.
>> See, Money Mike told you to jump off
Mount Everest, would you do it? >> No. >> Exactly.
>> You did. You did. You did use the sub. It
>> And I don't think Money Mike told you
that. I just think you're being a bit of
a fantasist now, PJ.
>> No, Jimmy, he did tell me that he used to sublet.
>> No, if PJ if he's tell you that, he's
taking the piss out of you like the
internet. The whole internet does.
>> So, what do you work?
>> PJ, I'm not discussing my personal
fiberactic cable means nothing to me,
right? I'm not like you as to tell
everybody about my sex life, tell
everybody about old Shauny's dad or tell
everybody about Shauny's [ __ ] cocaine
habit or Shauny's PlayStation. I don't
give a [ __ ] PJ. I come on here for a
laugh and a bit of a wind up and a bit
of drama and that's it. I'm not
interested in Shauny's life. I'm not
interested in Shauny's dad. He's got £18
million. I seriously don't give a [ __ ]
>> Jimmy, I've got £300 to last me a month.
What do I do?
>> £300 a year for work. 300.
>> What the [ __ ] have you done with your money?
>> I done my sacking.
>> No wonder you've been rattled over Sean
for the past hour and a half.
>> I'm only joking. I'm I'm only joking.
I'm only joking. [laughter]
I wanted to see if you'd believe it.
>> PJ, I wouldn't give a [ __ ] if you had 10
grand or 300 quid. What's wrong with
last a month to me? PJ, £300 of money
you've got to last a month would be
disgraceful. You should be on about You
should have about [ __ ] £300 per week.
The amount of tax payers money you love.
You get a lot more [ __ ] money than
used to [ __ ] be on universal credits.
>> Yeah, but Timmy, you you're benefit yourself.
>> No, I'm not PJ. I'm self-employed. I
don't give a [ __ ] if the internet calls
me a liar, PJ, because again, it's a
fiberactic cable mass.
>> But you're on Yeah, but you're on
benefits as well, aren't it?
I'm on PIP. That's the only benefit I get.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying, isn't it? [laughter]
>> You get you get housing benefit, carers
allowance. You [ __ ] play the system
like a fiddle. You do.
>> No, [laughter] I don't. No, I don't.
>> Yes. You [ __ ] You told everybody you
claim carers allowance for your system
to get an extra 60 quid a week.
>> No, no, no. I never said that.
>> Come on. You your family played the
system like butter wouldn't melt. >> No. >> Yes.
>> Yeah. I know I know all about your dad,
Mick Jonathan Robinson.
>> Oh, guess what? I I I even know nonsive.
Next. Um I even know
>> I know I know [laughter] I know nons's
mom's name. Do you know what it is? And
you just say you're not obsessed with sugar.
>> Do you really know what it is?
>> No, I don't. [laughter]
>> You want to know what? What do you know
what it is?
>> I don't care, PJ. How many times do I
got to tell you this?
>> Okay. Well, you don't want to know. I'm
trying to tell you about the guy and you
don't you know
>> I don't give a [ __ ] about Shy. I don't
give a [ __ ] about Mass Miller. I don't
give a [ __ ] about [ __ ] Ding. I don't
give a [ __ ] about King of Belfast
showing his [ __ ] 199 picking out his
great content. I don't give a [ __ ] about
[ __ ] Shagger going. I don't give a
[ __ ] about Travidor calling me single
even though he sits on YouTube all day
wanking over this cuz no woman's next to
him. I don't give a [ __ ] about Discord.
I don't give a [ __ ] about any of it.
I've got a real life PJ. I come on here
because I like taking the piss out of
people like you who take this to heart.
Yeah, you are able.
>> Well, you choose to [ __ ] cry like
babies so I get entertainment out of it.
>> You remind me of Jimmy Savo sometimes.
>> What the [ __ ] I can't believe you even
thought of that name. That just you call
you're calling Shaunie a bacon and
you're mentioning Jimmy [ __ ] Savo. [laughter]
>> Yeah, he's like Jimmy Sav.
>> God, PJ, I need to go to bed and it PJ.
It's like [ __ ] 10 to 14. For the past
two hours, all we've talked about is [ __ ] Sean.
>> No, you have to you have to stay up.
>> I'm not talking about Sean for another
two hours. I've got better things to do.
This has been the This has been the
biggest hours of my [ __ ]
>> Can I come to your house on Sunday for a sleepover? >> Can't. >> Why?
>> Because you were going about Shauny all
night and I can't be asked to talk about
[ __ ] Sha all night. We can have a sleepover.
>> But talking about Sean, no thanks.
>> No, not that [ __ ] version.
>> You know what I [snorts] mean?
>> PJ PJ, you've been you've been going
about Sean since I've come on the
Hangouts pretty much. [laughter]
>> Wait, why do you meet Monty again?
>> Why would I want to meet that sick?
>> I don't know.
You had a fun You had a fun You had a fun night.
>> No, I didn't. No, I didn't have a fun
night out with him. He [ __ ] brought
speed. He was [ __ ] I told him to [ __ ]
off many times. He's like, "Timmy,
relax." I was like, "Mate, get away from
me, you [ __ ] weirdo." Right in the
arcade because I was [ __ ] waiting for
Mike cuz I didn't want to be nowhere
near the [ __ ] prick. >> Yeah,
>> it's Do you remember when you said
Timmy? Do you remember when you said I'm
going to knock him out? Remember, I'm
going to knock him out. Timmy, you said
that, didn't you?
>> PJ PJ, I'm not being funny. About 99.9%
of people on this community I could
knock out. [snorts]
>> Yeah, but you said it. I'm going to
knock him out. You remember the video?
>> Of course. I was going to
>> I beat you. I beat you. I beat you in
the fight, Timmy, didn't I?
>> You've beaten no one in the fight. PJ,
who was Okay, Timmy, who was stronger,
me or Monty?
>> Right. I'll be honest to you, right? If
I teached you PJ to punch first before
being anxiety and none of this [ __ ]
[ __ ] you got caught off guard, you
just get to the bottom grabs you. You
should have punched him even then. That
was the lame most [ __ ] excuse I've heard. PJ,
>> why nons legs? Are you still there?
>> I need to tell you something.
But listen, who's more who's stronger?
Who's more stronger? Me or Monty?
>> I don't know cuz I haven't seen you all.
I I mean PJ, why don't you just go?
>> Listen to me. You have to be honest. You
have to be honest to me. I beat Tiger in it.
>> You did in one way cuz I pulled you off
him. Yes. If I wasn't there, I think he
You could have beat him. Let's be
honest. But but the one thing what Tiger
did do to you and I'll give him this. He
put you in a dirty mattress. And
>> but listen, Timmy, why did you put him
up to that? You knew he weren't going to win. PJ,
>> PJ, he wanted to go on your own free
will cuz he lost his mom at the time and
you were slagging off his mom. That's
why he went down.
>> I wasn't mom. I've never argued.
>> No, I wasn't.
>> I think I think you've got a short I
think you've got a very short memory. PJ
>> Well, you was with Tiger the other day, wasn't you?
>> Course [clears throat] I was with Tiger
the other day and I wasn't with him on
Thursday. That was a different Can I meet you?
No, cuz we don't want to talk about 5 hours. >> Huh?
>> We don't want to talk about Sean for 5 hours.
>> No, we're going to like the casino now.
>> We don't want to talk about Sean, though. [snorts] >> Okay.
>> We see when me and Tiger meet, we don't
talk about YouTube, PJ. We don't talk
about Lord J. We don't talk about our lives.
>> Tiger used to Tiger used to
>> used to what? He used Tiger used to talk
about um YouTube all the time with Mike
in it. Mike told me like back in the day
he always used to talk about YouTube. [snorts]
>> No m I've seen Tiger now for about three
weeks. We've not once discussed YouTube.
We've gone back in the olden days now.
We're not interested in this. We get on
with our lives PJ. We've said we've lost
too many years being like fuzzies by
being menchild. And I look back on it PJ
and it's purely embarrassing. Mhm. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, Timmy, we need to Timmy, do you
know what? We need to get revenge on women. Jimmy,
>> I thought why I want revenge on women. I
haven't got an issue with women. You're
the one who's been rejected, not me.
>> No, I just don't like them cuz they're
[ __ ] to me.
>> No, you don't like them cuz you get rejected.
>> No, I just don't like them cuz they're [ __ ]
>> No, you get rejected. Just [ __ ] only.
It's not the end of the world.
>> You didn't help me with that [ __ ] in
America, Timmy. Do you remember when all
of that was going on? I messaged her
family. You didn't help me.
>> PJ, she told you to [ __ ] off and it was
hilarious. I'm not going to lie.
>> Yeah, but you remember when I was
messaging her family to me.
>> She said, "Well, I don't take this
offensively, but you can [ __ ] off." [snorts]
>> Yeah. No, no, no. The other one. The
other one. The other one from two years back.
>> I don't know what the [ __ ] you want about, mate.
>> The one when I was messaging a family to me.
>> You think that's funny? That's not
funny, PJ. That's just being a [ __ ] >> [laughter]
>> Why? Why?
>> PJ, if I message your family, you go you
go up the [ __ ] roof.
>> Yeah, but she cry about [ __ ] Yeah.
You cry about VR doing it, then you do
it to others. You're a hypocrite.
>> Yeah, because Yeah, because Yeah,
because Timmy, them [ __ ] were laughing at us.
>> So, okay, because you can't go on about
VR doing it to you when you do it to
others. Two bombs don't make a boy, PJ.
>> Yeah, but she was being nasty, bro.
Yeah, you don't contact someone's family
because you can't handle your fiberactic cable.
>> Yeah, but you messaged me, but you've
messaged my sister.
>> I messaged your sister because I did it
for your wellbeing because you were
going to get your head caved in because
you kept mentioning miners 24/7. I
didn't do it, PJ. I did it because I was
trying to get you off the internet for
your [ __ ] safety. [laughter]
Remember, Timmy, do you remember when
you when people's messaging your family?
>> My family don't give a [ __ ] PJ. They delete it.
>> I just
>> Yes. And they deleted it, PJ, cuz it's childish.
But you found it funny.
>> What do you mean? What do you mean I
find it funny, PJ? PJ, I don't give a
[ __ ] because it's just a bunch of
[ __ ] children throwing their toys out
the pram. I don't find it funny. I find
it funny. make this [ __ ] so goddamn serious.
>> Yeah, but Timmy, the thing is, yeah,
>> it's not funny,
>> PJ. I don't laugh at it all. Don't get
me wrong, but I laugh when Banger goes
on about you 24/7 and Sean and that I'm
thinking you're all grown [ __ ] men
and you behave like [ __ ] toddlers.
>> So, Jimmy, you know your you've only got
one brother, is it?
>> Where we going on this? I'm asking you
how. So, how come your brother your your
brother don't have autism then? But you do?
>> I don't know, PJ. I'm not Jesus [ __ ]
Christ, am I?
>> You're not faking it, are you?
>> How can you fake it when you've been
diagnosed at 2 years old? You pr?
>> Because your cuz your brother doesn't
seem to have it. So, that's weird. No,
>> I don't know, PJ. I'm not a scientist.
I'm not an expert. So, you're asking me
questions I [ __ ] can't even answer.
So, I just hope you're not faking it.
>> How can I fake it, PJ? What the [ __ ] are
you on about? I r the back of my head. I
make myself look like a plunker in
[ __ ] public. How can I fake that?
>> Well, at least you're not in a
wheelchair, is it?
>> Not everybody has autism in the book.
You You're saying you There's There's
this guy that I knew. He was in a
wheelchair. He was born at in a
wheelchair and he died at like 26.
Well, it's what how what's that got to
do with autism?
>> So, how how do you how why do I reckon
you dive at young age?
>> I don't know. I'm not like I said, I'm
not am I I'm not a psychic.
>> Yeah, it's weird, isn't it?
>> Of course, it's weird if he's died at
26. It's a long age for him to go.
>> I hope you don't die soon. We need you for contact.
PJ, if I die, I don't give a [ __ ] mate.
I'm I'm I'm at that stage at life now
where if it happens, it happens. I've
lost my family and I've only got little
my life as far as I'm concerned.
>> You lost your family on YouTube.
>> No, like my family died of cancer, PJ.
That's what I mean. I thought PJ I've
experienced losing family at a young
age. You haven't? You still got your nan
and granddad. You still got your parents.
>> No, no, no, no. My my nan's dead and my dad's dead.
Oh, sorry. Your dad died. I didn't mean
like that. But PJ, I've got no
grandparents. I've lost my uncle, my
dad, and everything. PJ, I'm at that
stage of life now where I'm comfortably [ __ ] numb.
>> Yeah. Well, you got your mom.
>> Yes. That's the thing. What keeps me going? [snorts]
>> And I don't have um I don't know if my
granddad's dead. I think he might be
dead. I don't know.
>> What do you mean? How do you What do you
mean you don't know? You should know
that. You should contact
>> because we don't talk to him. We don't
talk to him so we don't but he's like he
would be 89 so maybe he is dead. There's
a good chance he is dead.
>> You normally can. Yes. I mean PJ I'm not
going to go into all this tonight but look PJ
you need to sort your life out mate. I
know I'm I'm I'm sorting my life out PJ
and I've got a long road to go. I'm not
going to be a hypocrite saying I'm going
>> The thing is the thing is the thing is
the thing is to me yeah with great power
becomes great responsibility.
PJ, I've known that saying for years, but PJ,
>> where did it
>> you have
great saying that's great
responsibility. I don't know where
exactly where it come from, but I've
heard the saying for [ __ ] years. PJ,
answer the question. Are you going to be
on YouTube all day tomorrow moaning or
you going to do something in your life
and fix your life?
>> I'm going for tomorrow
>> cuz I won't be on YouTube all weekend,
PJ. I've got a life and you won't.
>> I won't be.
>> I tell you what, Timmy, I tell you what.
As soon as you go live, you'll see the
same people smoking beef. You'll see the
same spastics in it.
>> Yes. Because they've got nothing in
life, PJ. How does that
>> Yeah, I know. [laughter] That's what I'm
saying to you. That's what I'm trying to
say. That's what I'm saying. Because
they've got nothing.
>> Yeah. But but but obviously I'm not
going on about it. You [ __ ] are.
>> You know,
>> PJ, we all know that the Lavry boys
speak the same [ __ ] every day. Why is it
affecting your life? It doesn't.
>> It does cuz you're [ __ ] going on about it.
>> Okay. Well, want to be on YouTube tomorrow.
>> I don't give a [ __ ] who's on YouTube
tomorrow. PJ, I think he's
>> I don't think you're ever going to come
off YouTube. Are you
>> PJ? The way this community is going. No,
cuz it's laughable. [laughter]
>> Really? Whereas people like there's
people like you that talk the same [ __ ]
and make a complete pratt of yourself on
a daily basis. No, I can't come off.
>> You reckon you reckon um
>> I mean you got and you got you got
fantasy talks ut
will be on here Christmas
>> Lord J will be on here till he dies
>> until he die. the only life he knows.
>> The only life he knows. [laughter]
>> Yes, because it's the only But you'll
never leave YouTube because you're
Samador and everyone. These people mean
everything to you. You rrestled over.
Yes, they do. You've been You've been
moaning about Sean for the past two
hours [snorts] talking about Sean's
talking about talking about Sean's life
story in the whole internet. Don't give a [ __ ]
>> It's very funny, is it?
No, it's boring.
>> It's what?
>> It's boring.
>> Yes, boring. >> Really?
>> Yes. Really?
>> No. I hate women, Timmy. They're [ __ ]
evil [ __ ] man.
>> I know you hate women cuz you've been
repeating this for the past [ __ ] four
years. We all know you hate women cuz
you've always been rejected. [laughter]
>> No, but No, they just can't. They're
just evil [ __ ]
>> Yes. You call them evil [ __ ] because
you've been rejected. [laughter]
>> No, because of what they've done to me. To me.
>> Yes. Cuz you've been rejected. That's
what they've done to you.
>> No. [laughter]
No. Not at all. Not at all to me.
>> Yes. It is PJ. It is.
>> No. I just don't like them.
>> You don't like them, PJ? Cuz he's still a virgin. [laughter]
>> This guy is an idiot. This guy
>> I'm not an idiot. It's the [ __ ]
truth, mate. Everybody in the [ __ ] UK knows you.
>> You know what you should do, Jimmy? You
should try and meet a woman and get You
should try to meet a woman and get one
pregnant for a laugh.
>> Why would I woman PJ?
>> For it to be funny.
>> Why would it be funny?
>> Cuz then they to make them pay in it.
>> To make them pay for what?
>> Being nasty.
>> No, women are very nice. PJ, I have a
lot of good time with women. I like the
sex. I like their personality. I like
their charisma. Not all of them are
good, don't get me wrong, but you can
say the same about males. You don't like
females, PJ, cuz not one female in the
universe has ever let ever given you sex.
>> Timmy, why don't you go and get one pregnant?
>> I don't want to get a woman pregnant.
What planet do you live on? You are very
autistic, aren't you?
Yeah, but why wouldn't you want that?
>> Because I don't want a kid. I'm 41. I
just want to get on with my life, PJ. I
don't want kids now. It's too late for me.
>> No, it's never too late,
>> PJ. I don't want kids. And I like my own
income. I like my own company. And I
like having different women. One week I
like to have a Chinese blood. One, one
week I like a Pakistani. One week I like
a Portuguese bird. One week I like a USA
bird and one week I like an Australian
bird. I'm not interested in a relationship, PJ.
>> So, when did you last have sex with one?
>> Saturday. And I'll end up having sex
tomorrow when I go out again and I'll
start talking to him.
>> You've used a prostitute before, isn't it,
>> PJ? Of course I have. That's a stupid question.
>> Yeah, I have as well.
And I didn't do it with her because she was ming.
I was pissed as a [ __ ] I didn't get hard.
>> Yeah. But didn't you do it in Amsterdam?
>> I've never been to Amsterdam. I don't
know what the [ __ ] you on about.
>> You said before you went to Amsterdam. No.
>> No. I tell you where I've been. I've
been to Switzerland. I've been to
Portugal. I've been to Ireland. I've
been to Northern Ireland. I've been to
Scotland. I've been to Wales. I've been
to France. I've been to Belgium. I've
been to Finland. I've been to Italy.
um Pra Prague and um
yeah, that's it really. That's all I've been
like. Do you remember when I went to
Amsterdam to read the videos? Did you like them?
>> Yes, I remember it very well. Yes.
>> You said I went to France to gamble in it.
>> Have you been to France, PJ?
>> No, I've been to Belgium and Amsterdam.
Do you know what?
>> I went to the Belgian casino. Have you
ever gambled in France?
>> No, PJ. I go on holiday to have a
holiday, not to gamble. >> Mhm.
>> I don't go on holiday to gamble, PJ. I
go on holiday to get laid and get sunburnt
and party. And
>> you went to Cypress, didn't you?
>> Yes. And I got very high on ecstasy.
>> Yeah. But you don't like flying. And
will you do it again?
>> Well, if I had to go back to Cyprus and
have the time of my life, yes, I would.
Even though I don't like it,
>> I'm thinking of moving out to Cyp. I'm
thinking of moving out to Cypress, PJ, >> really.
>> No, I'm being deadly country anymore. I
don't like Britain.
>> It's [ __ ] in it.
>> It's a crap country, mate. This
country's gone down the pot now.
>> The women are [ __ ] in this country,
too. But you're going to call them [ __ ]
wherever you go because you're going to
give you're going to be rejected worldwide. PJ,
you've been rejected by Americans.
You've been reject.
You're not going to put a bird in
America, PJ, cuz one of them told you to [ __ ] off.
>> You know, I've been to America.
>> Stop lying.
>> I went to America, Jimmy.
>> Why do you lie so much? No, you haven't.
I have. I went when I was 16.
So, have you got any evidence on this?
>> No, I'm joking, man.
>> I knew you were bullshitting the evidence.
>> I've been Australia. I've been Australia, though.
>> No, don't lie.
Got any photos of you being You got any
photos of you being in Australia? >> No,
>> because you're [ __ ] lying.
>> Yeah, but you can we you should
immigrate to Australia. >> [laughter]
>> I don't want to go to Australia, mate. I
don't like tarantulas. >> Really? >> Yes.
>> Birmingham's a [ __ ] dive.
>> Birmingham is a [ __ ] hole. The whole UK
>> You You live You live in Syo, >> PJ.
>> That's where you used to live. That's
where you used to live in it.
>> Yes, PJ. I live everywhere, PJ. Like,
you live in London, right? But you know
PJ I've got I've got many places I go a
lot of people nationwide. [snorts] >> Yeah.
>> Don't forget PJ I've been on here 10
years. I know a lot of people around
this country through social media. >> Really? >> Yes.
>> I'm really going to [ __ ] a woman over
today, bro. I'm going out drinking. I
really want to meet a woman to [ __ ] over.
>> Yeah. Well, you do get kicked out of
Lever Spoons for attacking more Australians.
>> You saw that. You like that video,
didn't you, Timmy? I went down with, didn't we?
>> I thought you was a prat, mate. I ain't
going to lie. I thought you was a prat.
>> No, but you don't [snorts] trying to copy me.
>> You No, you liked it, didn't you? You
liked it in it,
>> PJ. PJ, the reason why I did what I did
was because she called me sexist. I've
never been called sexist in my life. I
don't like lefties. I'll be honest with
you. I can't stand lefties. And because
she was a lefty, I lost my head. And PJ,
there's a difference of you and me. What
I did was completely wrong. Right. And I
I'm not proud of what I've done. You are
proud of what you do. And it's not a
good place, PJ.
>> Yeah. But they deserved it, isn't it?
>> So why did them Australian birds deserve
it? Cuz they were just having a meal,
minding their own business, and you
didn't get your own way toys out the front.
>> But she wasn't going to be Maui. You
went up to her and approached her
without her without her say so. You did
it on purpose so you could get a video.
>> I didn't do mine on purpose. She called
me sexist and I reacted.
I should have been the better man and
walked away and I reacted.
>> Yeah, but you know these people Yeah.
They were making excuses for the bouncer
to me. The bouncer started on me and
then when I defended people make excuses
to I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not being
I'm not being I'm not being funny. If I
was a bounce and I saw the way you doing
them women page, I'd have lost my job
and punched the [ __ ] light out of you.
>> You hit you hit a bounce um like a month
ago as well.
>> Yes, because I hit him because he
grabbed me viciously cuz I was trying to
get in the casino. He said no and I said
something about oh you've been sent oh
you know only people I can't remember
what I said but he thought I was being
offensive towards his culture and he
grabbed me and I wasn't. And I was
taking the piss out the casino and then
I [ __ ] grabbed him back and well I'm
not I've been knocked out by a Welsh
guy. I've been humiliated so many times.
There's only so much crap a human being can take. [snorts]
>> You know PJ [clears throat]
you've not at that length yet PJ and
it's like that woman train thing. You
[ __ ] you you were scared to approach
you like Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You should
have read in her face. If you make out
you're this gangster and put her straight,
>> bro. I was half asleep. I told her she's
an ugly crackhead.
>> I said it more than once. I said it more >> Yeah,
>> because you was half asleep. That makes
you a [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I said what I had to say, bro. I
said what I had to say. I didn't need to
say anything more. >> Okay.
>> They're idiots. But
>> I've got to go I I've got to go to bed,
PJ, cuz I've got to be up at 9:00 cuz
I'm in a routine. So, what are you doing tomorrow?
>> Getting pissed.
>> So, you're going out drinking? >> Yes. >> Where?
>> I'm not saying PJ, but I'm going to a
magical place where I'm meeting a bird
for I've done off a website. PJ, I get
dates PJ cuz I'm the god sex man on the
internet. Right. I am not telling the
dating sites I [ __ ] like you to give
the trolls ammunition, but I Can you
meet me tomorrow? >> No. >> Why?
>> Because cuz I'm out with family tomorrow.
>> Why don't you go over your mom, P? Why
don't you go over your mom, PJ, and do
some constructive about moaning about
Sean all [ __ ] day?
>> I'm going to try and meet some women
tomorrow to [ __ ] over.
>> But don't get kicked out, PJ.
>> Mate, I'm I'm gonna be on one tomorrow,
Jimmy. I'll be on one.
>> Yeah, but PJ
PJ, you obviously haven't took my advice
out to pull a woman. You what you do is
you go up to them and go, "You look very
attractive. Can I buy you a drink and
they say no?" Then get the hint that you
they're not interested and you move on.
>> Yeah, but they need to pay to me.
>> Oh god. You Why do they need to pay to
Cuz you've been rejected all your life.
>> No, they just need to pay. They're not
nice people in general.
>> Pay for what? Because
are you are you mentally well or not?
>> I am. Yeah.
>> You're not because like Hitler. You're
the Hitler towards females. You want to
see every female exterminated because
you've been rejected so many times.
>> Timmy, I've been with women.
>> You're like a [ __ ] Dalek. Want to
destroy every [ __ ] woman on the planet.
>> I've been with a woman.
>> Yes. And because you've been rejected by
everyone, you're like Dalek Peter. I'm
going to call you Dalek Peter cuz you
want you are like the
>> Dimmy Timmy, I've had sex.
>> Why [snorts] are you lying,
>> Timmy? You're an idiot.
>> PJ, everyone knows you haven't had sex.
You moan about women every [ __ ] day.
>> Yeah, I moan about them cuz they're
[ __ ] and I want revenge.
>> No, you moan about them because you're
like a Dalek and you've had no sex and
you want revenge. I'm going to call
You had sex. So you had sex last Saturday?
>> Yes. PJ, why are you so interested?
>> Do you have sex every Saturday?
>> I don't. No, not every Saturday, PJ. I
do go stages about three or four months
without it. But I'm not like you. I'm
not desperate. I can live without it.
>> You can't live without sex, Timmy. You
have sex all the time.
>> Yes, I can. Yes, I can. PJ, you'll be
>> So, you'll be getting a [ __ ] today.
>> P. I don't even know what I could be
dead tomorrow. I don't plan my days. I
don't know what's going to happen, do I?
>> You sound like a [ __ ]
>> The [ __ ] are you on about now? [ __ ] hell,
>> Jimmy. Why do you sound like
>> Why are you a Dalek?
>> Why do you sound like a
>> I'm going to I'm going to call you Dale
to every woman exterminated. >> Really?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to call you Dalek PJ.
>> Yeah, but Timmy, you're a virgin.
>> You're a Dalek.
>> Yeah, but you are a virgin. Yeah.
>> Do you know where the Daleks come from? PJ.
>> Doctor Who? >> Really?
>> You've never seen Doctor Who?
>> Yeah, I have. Yeah.
>> So, how can you not know about Daleks?
>> Oh. Oh, yeah. I think I do know what you mean.
You're talking about that brown.
>> NO. [laughter] NO. WHAT THE [ __ ] are you
on about? No. The big metal [ __ ] tin
things with one little pointy eye and
they got this little [ __ ] god. What?
They shoot people mixer cement. Not what
they call like a mixer.
>> You you watch Harry Potter in it?
>> No, I don't. That's one thing I can't.
>> How do you know what it is then?
>> Because it's advertised everywhere.
>> How How do you work? What do you mean
[laughter] it's advertised everywhere?
>> Well, ITV I advertise it all the time.
[ __ ] BBC, dude. Every [ __ ] knows
about Harry [ __ ] Potter.
>> Do you have a wank over it?
>> You are you in the head or not?
>> Yeah, but do you have a wank over Harry Potter?
>> Are you [ __ ] that disgusting? No, I do not.
You are not normal, mate. No. No wonder
no woman wants you. If you go around
having conversations, do you rank over
Harry Potter? You are not a well kid. [laughter]
>> You have a Harry Potter.
>> I think he's thinking [ __ ] hell,
Peter. Get a grip. [laughter]
>> You You are one disturbed kid, aren't
you? Deep down. [laughter]
How [clears throat] How do you work that one out?
>> Well, you are disturbed because who's
going to think on a in an everyday
conversation who has a rank with Harry Potter? [laughter]
>> We need to get revenge on these women. Timothy,
>> I don't want revenge women. I love
women. I love who they are.
>> Timmy, you can't Timmy, you can't
afford. Timmy, you can't afford a flagship phone.
Oh, you Dalek Peter because you just
want women exterminated because you've been rejected.
>> You can't afford a flagship though. Is
it Timmy? If
>> I say I can't afford a flagship, will
you get Will you stop getting excited?
>> Yeah, but you can't in it.
>> If I say I can't, can I go to bed cuz I'm tired?
>> No, I like you here with me, Timmy. I
don't want to feel left out.
No, PJ, cuz I've got a life and like you
going to be moing about [ __ ] Sean all day.
No, I'm going to be I'm going to be I'm
going to be moaning about women tomorrow.
>> You do that anyway. [ __ ] hell.
>> What do you mean? Huh?
>> You moan about women all the [ __ ] time.
>> You don't hear me moan about women.
>> Yes, you do. But up about them.
>> Yeah, but you never hear me moan about women. Oh,
>> [ __ ] hell. The whole internet knows
you moan about women.
Yeah, they're going to pay for what they've done.
>> Oh god, you really are. You You do need
to be locked up. You are like You are
like Hitler all over. You are >> Nah.
>> You know where do you know where Hitler
was? Hitler was from
>> Germany. Yes, we know. But originally he
wasn't from Germany. He was from
Austria. I can't pronounce Austria.
>> How did How do you know?
>> Is it?
>> Because I study history. PJ. He wasn't
originally from Germany. He was
originally from I can't pronounce it,
Austrian or something. I'll come back to
me in a minute. But he was the prime
minister of Germany. >> Oh,
yes. And do you know why America got
involved in the Second World War? >> Why?
>> Because Japan attacked them. >> Mad
they were with. >> Yes.
You went to Germany where
>> I've been to every
uh bit Berlin and they do [ __ ] good stellar
[ __ ] about 20 when I was 22 around
there. It was years ago with PJ. [snorts]
>> You're crazy.
>> So are you. You're a [ __ ] Hitler. You
want every woman dead. Good job. You're not
>> I'm going to have to think about [ __ ]
women over tomorrow. It's depressing.
It's very depressing to me.
>> Yes. PJ, you PJ, you've been going on
about this for the past [ __ ] you
know, half an hour and you say you don't repeat yourself.
[ __ ] hell. Do you know what? I I
don't know what I'm going to do with
you. You've got serious issues.
>> These women are going to pay for what
they've done to me. You watch.
>> Yes. Okay. PJ, can I go to bed now?
>> I'm going to do a video tomorrow owning
a woman. Is that all right with you?
>> Yes. Yes. You do what you want to do.
I'll go to bed.
When are you putting a gambling video up again?
>> Probably tomorrow, PJ. I'm going to put
a long one up tomorrow cuz I've got a
long one to put up.
>> Yeah, Timmy, I saw you in a pub a day
ago with 100. You won £100.
>> Yes, you did. Yes, I did. And
>> yes, I know.
>> Why did you do [laughter] that?
>> Anyway, PJ, I don't know. Look, PJ, I've
got to go to bed, mate. I'll catch you
tomorrow. All right. Just don't do
anything. Don't do anything stupid. even
though you're not going to listen.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay.
>> See you later.
>> See you, Ken.
Oh, we [ __ ] own that fantasy, bro. >> [laughter]
>> O trip. It's the same people on here
every day, isn't it?