Where the [ __ ] is this [ __ ]
I need to brush my teeth.
Come on. You come on you virgin. Virgin.
Come on you virgin ta.
Washing my hair. Ready for the fight. I'm waiting. Come on.
Come on. You virgin. haircut.
You like this?
You like my little hair music? >> [snorts]
>> Heat. Heat. [snorts] >> [snorts] >> Okay. Copycat.
You're under arrest
on suspicion of being a copycat.
for suspicion of being a copycat.
Do you imagine there was such a crime? I
think it should be crime crime.
What do you think? Anyways,
where is this cotton?
Where the [ __ ] is this?
[ __ ] hell. Crazy, bro.
put some food in a bit. So,
don't try and come back on here,
right? Don't be coming back on here
saying that you've won.
I'm going to give the [ __ ] until 4:00
just to be nice. So, he's got absolutely
no excuse then.
Yeah. I don't want this [ __ ] having any
excuses, bro. You know, so you've got
until 5:00 to post a video,
but going by what you were saying
yesterday, I don't think you're going to meet anyone
saying that people's got their jeans on
tick and all of that. Same same
self-reflecting [ __ ] So, yeah, I don't
think they're going to they're going to
be meeting me, bro.
Let's be real here.
You [ __ ] lushing it. Waiting for the
money to drop. Greavesy. Waiting for the
money to drop. It doesn't matter how
much the money is, does it,
Grezy? As long as that As long as the
little money's going to be dropping,
doesn't matter, does it?
I want to go get a roast dinner. I'm
[ __ ] hungry, bro.
Yeah, the agreement was five and he but
he doesn't live in London and he hasn't been on. Yeah.
Yeah, but he hasn't been on. That's what
I'm trying to say. He hasn't been on.
I get two I get £250 in a couple of days. Grezy £270.
That's lush, isn't it, Grezy?
I get £270 in a couple of days. Is that lush?
Absolutely lush, isn't it?
Got some longer dropping. Greavves.
Is that lush?
Yeah, it is.
It's lush, isn't it, Grezy? Is it lush? Yeah.
Is it lush? Greasy.
I want to work some mad hours, bro. Be
depressed as [ __ ] bro. Yeah, just for
one week. Have some nice load of money
dropping and I'll be waiting. I'm
thinking I'm going to play some pool on
a Tuesday. Um, Grezy,
I think I'm going to play some pool on a
on a on a I'm going to play some pool on
a week on a weekday to get better at it
cuz I like Paul. I got my ass whipped
yesterday. So maybe on a Monday,
Tuesday, I'll just go for a couple of
hours and uh play some pool with a nice
with a nice coke.
Don't really want to, you know, I'll
even play myself, you know, just to get
better at it.
You know, it's 1 pound50 a game.
I could even go today, but I'm not
drinking today. I'm not drinking today.
So, and I'd be tempted to drink. You
know what I mean? Greasy.
No, I'm not doing that. I'm going for
some food. So,
Is this [ __ ] [ __ ] coming or what?
Yeah. One second, baby. I'm listening to
your voice now.
Yeah. This guy was saying, my friend was
saying that, oh, there's other there's
other there's other men out there that
don't need anyone.
And I said, "Yeah, there's other men out
there, but other men haven't tried or
tried like me. That's the problem.
That's that's the that's the whole problem."
You know, some of them might want to be
single. Some some of them might not have
tried. Some of them might have tried,
but not nowhere near as much as me.
That's the problem with it. That's the
problem with it, bro.
I'd go as far saying I've tried more
than anyone in the [ __ ] world. To be
fair, I'd actually go as far as that
saying that. So that's what what the problem is.
That's what the problem is. You understand?
It's not like you've gone out once a
month for, you know, you've been trying
for years. Anyways, where the [ __ ] is this [ __ ]
See what I mean with these people in
here? They're [ __ ] immature, bro.
Got my shoes on.
See, they're [ __ ] maturing people on this community.
You nasty virgin.
You nasty skinned virgin, [ __ ] you. You right. You sure?
I'm not fine. I need some [ __ ] dinner down me. Okay.
You haven't left the oven on, have you, man?
You need it because you done that last time. Come on.
Can I go now? Grezy,
I said 4. What's it? 4:30. Can I Right.
Can I go now, please, Captain? And get
this roast dinner.
I'm standing by the [ __ ] door, bro.
Can I Can I go now?
Obviously, I have to run it by you first.
Can I go, man?
Cuz I'm getting really hungry now. Huy,
can I go now, please? Breezy.
I know this little [ __ ] was trolling,
bro. Little [ __ ]
This little YouTube [ __ ]
when he was trying to say, "Oh, if you
say so, it's not what I say." So, I
[ __ ] know. So, about you people in
this community. I don't I don't think I
know. [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
Still nothing on the channel.
See? Still nothing on the channel.
Still nothing on the channel. Greasy
glass of water.
The battle of the two virgin versus
the two virgins go headto head.
You're an absolute virgin.
You nasty virgin.
The two virgins go headtohead.
It's a main event. The two virgins.
I'm just having a glass of water. But
what's going on? Is this [ __ ] meeting me or what? Huh?
Is this [ __ ] meeting me or what, lad?
Before I go the other direction. Come
on. Cuz by the time I get there, it's
going to be about five.
Little [ __ ] Little [ __ ] lord. less embarrassing.
What? Me or him? Uh,
what? He's embarrassing on me.
Well, I'm embarrassing or is he embarrassing?
Well, I'm waiting. It's I'm I'll get
there for about five. It'll take me
Yeah, it will be about five till I get
there. So you come on here trolling,
pretending to be somewhere else. It just
shows that you got no life. It just
shows that these people ain't got a life
what they do on here. I knew it was he
was dodgy anyways when he was saying
about oh these people do it for
reaction. And I said that they don't do
it for reaction. And he said if you say
so. I don't say so. I know so.
But I didn't pay no mind. I know. So,
another [ __ ] loser ain't got a life
in YouTube. Got to get off it.
Yeah, I was getting lots of nutrients
after I met USA. Um, Grezy, I latched on
to a lot of new boobies. I had about
five boobies that year.
I would I I had a lot of boobies that
yearly. I used to latch on to get
vitamins, especially when I was younger.
I need vitamins, don't I, Grezy?
Yeah. Well, they're not claiming victory
because I won't be able to get there for
five. So, if he doesn't come on now
showing him on that train, I it won't be
a victory cuz I won't be able to get
there for five.
So, we planned for five. So if he leaves
it any later
than quarter two, he's lost because I
won't be able to get there by 5.
So he's had all day to show do community
post and show trains and he hasn't.
So he's lost. He's lost.
be able to get there for five if he's
leaving it later.
I have to wait for a bus and get a train. [ __ ] mongos.
Look at that red car.
I know to go for a roast or get I'm
going to go for a roast. I'm definitely
going to go for a roast. Definitely
going for a roast.
Right, I'm leaving in a minute anyways.
So, don't show up and say that you've
won because you haven't won because
you've kept quiet.
I mean, you can't be traveling an hour
if we don't know that you're there. So,
no, you haven't won.
You know, this is what I'm scared this
cunt's going to do. He's going to show
up there and say that he's won.
Well, he hasn't won anyways. We all
know. But they all will buy us on it
anyway, so it doesn't really matter. I'm
leaving in a minute. Loser.
I'm not waiting till 5. I want to go get
some food. I'm not waiting until 5.
I'm not waiting until 5. He's had all
day to come on here. He's not blocked.
Everyone knows his channel. So, no, I'm
not waiting until 5. I'm hungry.
and the place I'm going is nowhere near
me. I'm not waiting until 5. I wait for
a little bit longer
and that's it. So yeah, [ __ ] losers.
[ __ ] M, bro. You knew you know he's
not going to meet, bro. Like all the
things that he was saying yesterday. You
your jeans are on tick.
Your jeans are on tick. T t
your jeans are on tick, you know.
Yeah, it's going to take me about an
hour to get there. Buses and trains. So
if he comes now, him showing I'll leave
and I'll go that way. Otherwise, I'm
going the complete other way.
I'm going to go the complete other way. Oh yeah,
but you can tell he's not meeting. He's
a keyboard warrior by what he was saying
yesterday about the money jeans being a
bun. People like that don't meet people.
People that say the same repeating [ __ ]
self-projecting don't meet people.
You know, people like that don't meet people.
[gasps and sighs]
M when I'm better looking than you.
Change the record, bro. It's boring now.
Change the record. It's boring now.
So, an ugly woman that I didn't approach
called me a month of years ago because
she's insecure. Okay, bro. How many
women have I bullied over the years? How
many women have I made go to the police
over me? I think I've more than got my
revenge on these [ __ ] in one way or another.
So, can we please in 2026
think of new sayings and new words? I'll
stop going on about women and these
people stop repeating.
Crazy. Is that too much to ask?
You know what I'm saying? How many women
have I bullied? Think about it, bro. How
many women have I used and walked out on
and made and made look a [ __ ]
you know? Let 2026 be a new year.
Let 2026 be a new year, bro.
It's not a new year with these people.
It's [ __ ] repeating. Mr. Mcoo and his
ugly little matesy.
Mr. Mulo and his ugly little mates.
And his ugly little mates. Voila.
Mr. Mians, ugly little fell.
I don't want Indians. I want to roast them.
What people used to say that, Grezy.
If you tell me Mr. Mcoo will absolutely
make a comeback. If you tell me what
people say that,
what people say that music Oh, ow.
>> I'll do a Mr. MCU video for you.
What kind of people say that?
Uh, is it a question?
Why? Why have you put a question mark? Huh?
Why? Yeah, but how why a question mark?
>> Yeah, but it's not a question, is it?
It's a fact.
>> You like it when Timmy comes on you and goes nuts?
>> Maybe. Yeah.
Okay. Yeah. Well, people used to say to
me, "If I don't find Beyonce attractive, I'm gay."
Why do they used to say that, Grezy?
Back here in about 2010, they said, "If
I don't find Beyonce attractive, I'm gay."
Even I told them I didn't like black women.
They said I was gay and stuff.
They said I screw loose. Why do they say that?
>> [clears throat]
>> Let me have a look at the cinema. Is
there anything on in the cinema?
Let me have a little browse.
Yeah. Do you ever legs? I'll never
forget that day you went back to college
saying, "I like sh
little back then as well." Copycat.
Oh, what's this? Five Nights at Freddy's. Oh,
what's that? Is that's a horror film, isn't it? H
What's that? That's a That's That's
definitely a horror, isn't it? That's out.
So, we got that one. [groaning]
There's another one coming out New
Year's Eve or I think it's Christmas Eve.
Yeah, that looks good at Five Night at Freddy's. I might
I can't watch it now cuz I'm hung over,
so I wouldn't enjoy it.
I can go and watch it tomorrow, though.
One second. Let me see if I'm There's
one called The Maid or something.
Yeah, that Freddy looks good. I could go
today. How h how hung over am I?
I'm a little bit hung over.
My already started. Oh wow.
I reckon I'll go tomorrow because
tomorrow is Monday and obviously there
won't be any couples.
Yeah, I think we'll do it tomorrow 100%.
We'll go for a roast now and then we'll
we'll go to the cinema tomorrow. Okay
with you, boss.
Grezy. Okay with you, boss.
So, it's definitely a horror before I
click on this trailer and watch it. I
think I've heard about this.
Okay with you, boss.
Yeah. And obviously, there's not going
to be no couples tomorrow cuz it's Monday. Fingers crossed
cuz I just don't see it as fair.
You know how there's there's there's
there there's you see you get to see
people in relationships whilst you suffer.
I just don't think it's fair, Grezy. I
don't know about you. I just don't think it's fair. So, um yeah. you virgin.
Yeah, I am a bit hung over. So, I'll
wait. I'll go get this roast dinner up.
I'll wake up as fresh as a baby.
Uh, I'll wake up as fresh as a bubin grievy.
And um, yeah, go to a cinema tomorrow. I
might even get a little hot dog. Triple
H has made me fancy hot dogs now.
Oh, I've been waiting so long for a new
horror film to come on. So,
I could go now, but I'm just going to be
too tired. But
ooh, that sounds lovely.
Oh, I want a roast dinner, bro. But I
don't know if I can be bothered to go there.
A roast dinner is sounds a lot lusher,
doesn't it, Grezy?
No, fish and chips is too greasy cuz I
was drinking. I like fish and chips, but
it's too greasy, bro. Cuz I drunk
yesterday. So, what do you think? Fish
and chips or a lovely roast. Greasy.
I think a lovely roast. I haven't been
there for ages. It's going to take me
ages to get there, bro. Yeah.
Uh, what do you think, Greavvesy?
No, I'm going in a minute. Uh, Timmy,
I'll be back later. You can join later
and come back.
What do you think, Grezy?
Oh, I could get a nice curry.
No, I think a roast dinner. I haven't
had that for ages. No, I'm going to get
roast dinner. We said roast dinner.
And the deal was this guy doesn't win anyways because
it's it's going to take me ages to get
there, but I think it's worth it. I
haven't had a roast for ages. Greasy. So
anyways, as I was saying, as I was
saying, this guy hasn't won Greasy. No
matter what he comes on here and tries
saying, he hasn't won. No matter what he
comes on here try saying, he hasn't won
because the reason he hasn't won Grezy
is because um the deal was he had to
show him on the train before I made
moves. So he hasn't won. So if he tries
to go like if he tries to do a video, he
hasn't won because the deal was he had
to show him on a train prior to me traveling.
So even if he tries showing up now, we
said that you I said you show me you're
on that train and I'll make troubles and
we should get there at the same time. So
even if he tries coming back on it, he
hasn't won. So
not that he is going to do that because
you're just a little keyboard warrior,
little [ __ ] Like I said with these
people, just wait for them to get doxed.
Rezy, all you got to do, right, is wait
for one of these people to get doxed.
That's all you got to do. Like no
reaction, no videos. Just wait for them
to get doxed.
That's all you got to do. Just wait for
them to get doxed. Go on their door and
see what they're saying. Just be like a
little watchdog, like king. That's all
you got to do. Just wait your turn.
Everyone's got their turn.
Like Joseph Farra if if Joseph Ferrar if
his address went out there I'd go in his
door. I'd go up by Newcastle and go in
his door and say, "Well, what what you
say now? You got all of this to say
behind the keyboard
that only my mom hates me and all of
these things." Come and say it now.
I would, bro. I honestly [ __ ] would.
I'd say, "What have you got to say now?"
Cuz if you got something to say on
YouTube, you can say it to my face, can't you?
So, are you going to watch this Five
Night at Freddy's 2? Wait, is there a Is
there a first one? I hope there's not a
first one, is there? Cuz I haven't
watched the first one. And then I
probably need to watch the first one.
I haven't watched the first one.
No, Grey. I haven't watched the third
one. The first one.
I didn't even know there was a first one.
I hope there isn't.
Yeah, there is. I didn't see the first one,
but I just watched the second one.
I can just watch the second one, can't I?
Let me try and watch the first one today
in bed before I go to sleep and then
watch the second one tomorrow.
Grezy, okay with you, boss. I'm sure
I'll be able to find it on the internet
somewhere to watch it. Is that okay with you, boss?
Is that okay with you, Captain?
Obviously, I have to run it by you
first. Okay with you, captain.
You remember when I said, "Can I go out
and get a woman pregnant for?" You said,
"That's not okay with me, boss." Not
okay with me. You said that's stupid.
You can't have a kid with someone and
leave them there. Is it Greasy? That's stupid.
The person on Reddit said, "But yeah,
but then you have a kid."
I said, "Yeah, well, I'll just leave the baby."
You can't do that. They said, "I can."
Yeah. Anyways, this guy
is not coming. keyboard warrior.
No. Do you know what he's gonna say,
Grevy? I'll tell you exactly what he's
gonna say. He's going to come on here
later saying, "I made you wait. I made
you wait. I made you wait." But not
really. I don't mind saying waiting a
little bit. Not really.
Traffic's probably died down now. That's
what That's what they're going to say.
They're not going to say that they've
won, Greasy. I know these [ __ ] idiots
on here and what they do, lad. They're
going to say, "Oh, I made you stay in. I
control you." And [ __ ] That's what
they're going to say. I bet you any
money that's what he comes and says. Do
you want to bet? Do you want to bet Grezy?
I know these people, bro. What they do on here?
Right. I'm going to get Ro anyways. Yeah. So,
I'll see you later. Yeah,
I'm going to get some popcorn. I'm going
to get some popcorn on the way back to
watch this uh wedding thing.
No, I'm leaving, bro. I'm going. I'll be
back later. Yeah.
Right. You can join for 5 minutes, but I
need to get going, bro. I really need to get going.
I'm really hungry and I need to travel.
What the [ __ ] I just tried sending you
a link. It didn't let me. What's going
on here then?
There we go.
Mom, I'm going to the cinema tomorrow.
I'm going cinema tomorrow
and I want you to come with Oh, what is that? Elf.
Elf is under telly.
Oh gosh, I remember you. You look elf.
Elf is on the telly. Oh gosh.
Right. Are you joining Timmy or what?
Cuz I need to go, lad. I'm starving.
It's [ __ ] raining now as well.
>> You all right, Captain?
We're coming to London and >> what? >> Hello.
>> Are you coming?
>> Yeah. You come to London. I'll give you
I I'll give you the money. Yeah.
>> Yeah, I can hear you.
>> I can hear you just about. Yeah. Are you
coming to London? I'm not going to get
this bloody roast today, am I, Greavves?
Oh, gosh darn it.
I don't think I'm getting this bloody
[ __ ] roast today. Am I mate?
It ain't happening today.
What [laughter] are you doing? Are you
coming to London?
You absolute virgin. >> [laughter]
>> Right, I am I am out of it. Yeah, cuz I
need to get this roster now and I'll be back later.
See you. Peace. See you.