Yep.
It was all [ __ ] wasn't it? I knew
it, mate. I knew it was all [ __ ]
[ __ ] idiots on this community, bro. I knew it.
I knew it was [ __ ]
People that say them words like, "Man,
uh, can't pay for your jeans and shit."
They're they're just little cowards that
will never meet you. It's just the same person.
I knew it. I knew it. I knew it. I knew
it. I knew it. I knew it. I knew it. I
I knew that was going to happen. [ __ ] idiot.
Idiots on this community.
Yeah, I knew that. I knew it. I knew it. >> Yeah.
[ __ ] tired. I am
Yep. I knew it, bro. I knew it was [ __ ]
People like that will never meet you.
people like that will never ever meet you.
I'm off here tomorrow anyways. So,
in case anyone wants to make up rumors It's
It's always a cycle when you're in this um country.
Always when you whenever you're in this
country, you're always contining that cycle.
Sad. Sad. Sad.
just sad in it, bro. This country is
sad. I need to go. I don't even I can
watch this film, bro, before
sleeping. I'm [ __ ] tired, bro. I feel
That's the one here. Yeah. [ __ ]
I'm about to have a shower, you know.
Yeah, I'm going to have to have a shower once.
Well, I'm going to wait out until next
week anyways. I said I'm going to go out
next week even though I'm depressed.
Yeah, still got
difficulty. You're always in a cycle
when you're in this country.
[ __ ] hell, bro. It's so bad. When
does it end? People really say
Yeah, I was in the shower.
Yeah, [ __ ] him.
Tell him if he's got a problem. He knows
where I live.
Oh [ __ ] this is making me more cold.
Yeah, I was just in the shower, Captain.
no reply from that number. UK, so I
never £160 gone. Nothing.
£160. No date.
Uh, next week. This week. next week. Uh,
same old. You would have thought at 28
now, bro. [ __ ] would have changed. You
know, you you would you would have
thought at 28 years of age.
But, you know, we've been doing this now for years.
This is depressing, bro.
But yeah, another weekend gone. Nothing, no change. So boring.
Yeah. The more you think about this, the
more you the more depressed you actually
get when you think about your
experiences and the fact that nothing's
changed. It's really bad, is it?
Yeah. I wanted to stay in bed and do
nothing. The more I think about my
experiences, but I've got to go and do stuff tomorrow.
It's so bad, isn't it?
It will never change. It will never ever
ever change all women. I don't know how
people can sit there and say that it
will be on me. You're just a cycle in this country.
It's always the same thing though. It's
always the same thing in this country.
It will always be the same thing in this
country with women. Bad experiences.
Nah, I'm going out next week and I'm
probably going to give up the life again
cuz I called it. I said I'm going out.
So, I'll be giving up with life again. I
need to go cinema tomorrow first thing.
I need to watch this film before I
sleep. So, then I'll be giving up with
life again. Get the money out the hair.
Get the money worth out the haircut and
just stay in bed again and be depressed
waiting to die. Seems like that's a better option.
So, yeah, that's that. Depressing as
[ __ ] Nothing but bad experiences all
your life. Bad, bad, bad. Never changes
either, no matter what you do. That is
bad, bro. That's why I didn't want to go
out yesterday, but I had no choice.
That's why I didn't want to go out
yesterday, bro. Cuz I knew it was going
to be the same thing as it would always
be the same thing.
I've already made a change. I've
traveled. I've approached. I've used
dating apps. I've already changed time
and time and time and time and time and
time and time and time and time again.
No changes. So, no, I'll continue
feeling sorry for myself and give up my
life. It seems like a a lot better um solution.
I'll continue keep feeling sorry for
myself because it's warranted.
So, that's that. I'll keep doing it. At
least that way you know your place in
life. So, you feel better cuz you know
your place in life because you know it's
never going to change you. So you keep
thinking it's going to change you.
You're making yourself worse. At least
if you give up and you stay for 2 months
or 3 months and you leave, at least you
know where you stand. This is why I
didn't want to go out yesterday cuz I
knew where what was going to happen
again and again and again and again and
again and again and again. Which is why
I don't go out now. I was basically
forced into going out yesterday. So, you know,
so that's that.
It's so bad.
I want an early night today, but I need
to watch this film before I go to sleep.
Yeah, I won't be on it here tomorrow
anyways. I'm busy. So,
and yeah, that guy was a no show today.
So yeah, you're never going to meet
anyone. You're never going to have a sex
life. Accept it, own it, and leave.
That's all you can do. Well, there's no
point thinking about something that's
never going to happen. I went out approaching yesterday.
You know, same old [ __ ] Make believe me a headache.
Same old [ __ ] Got a number. Didn't even
have the decency to reply. Huh? How much
money are we in now? How many times have
we approached now? And it's the same thing.
Yeah. People on Reddit keep telling us
that we're going to keep meeting people
that people keep people on Reddit keep
telling us meet. You're going to meet
someone. It's just the same old [ __ ]
over and over and over again. It's the
same old regurgitated [ __ ] time and time
and time and time again. You know, it's
regurgitated. That's all it is. Same
stuck up people playing the same games,
same old [ __ ]
Just like it's going to be next week
when I go out. Just like it's going to
be next week when I go out. It's going
to be exactly the same the same experiences again.
You know, we all know it now, bro. Come
on. It's boring.
And the reason, and then you want to
gamble to get a buzz. This is what I
mean. It's you're always a cycle when you're here.
You're always in a negative cycle.
That's probably why I gamble today and I
still have the alcohol in me because you
get depressed from the women and the
alcohol and then you want to gamble and
then you're around in circles again.
This is what this is the cycle you see.
This is the cycle that you're in.
Yeah. Well, you're delusional. If I was
going to find someone, I would have
found someone by now. You're delusional.
So, what you think don't matter. If I
was going to find someone, I would have
found someone by now. Again, 6 years of trying.
again. 6 years of trying and dating
women is not healthy either. Trying to
date women is not healthy. Alcohol,
gambling, trying to date women, it's all
negative. That's why I I stepped away
from it. That's why I didn't want
anything to do with him again. But
people on Reddit kept saying you're
going to keep you're going to meet
someone. How many times for how many
years have you been saying the same thing?
Let's let's let let's put it let's put
it bluntly now. How long have you been
saying you are going to meet someone?
Seven years? Eight years.
13 years. How long have you been saying it, bro?
Right. Okay. And I'll repeat myself
again since you claim that you don't
listen my struggles. I've been trying
for seven years. Right. I've been trying
for seven years. I tried yesterday.
Start explaining. You're saying that
you're not dismissing my struggles.
Okay. Well, I tried yesterday. I didn't
find someone. I tried two weeks before
that. I didn't find someone. I haven't
had a date. Right.
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] about other
people in a better way or a worse way.
I'm talking about me. Stick to the
subject. I haven't had a date since
April. I have been out a million times
since April. Stick to the subject. Don't
compare people that are better than me
and worse than me cuz I don't give a
[ __ ] about them. We're talking about me.
Stick to the subject, right? You say you
hate other people comparing. I haven't
had a I haven't had a date since April
and I've been out. So, if you haven't
had a date since April,
no, no, no, no. Because there were no
positives. It's not negatives. It's
reality. They're not It's not negatives.
It's reality. I went out yesterday and I
kept getting the boyfriend [ __ ] that happened.
It's reality. It's not a negative.
There's a fine line between being
negative and being real.
The truth is not negative. It's the truth.
You know, that's that. So,
you're not ever going to meet anyone.
Just like on Saturday when I go out by
myself, you're still not going to meet
anyone. You can't even get a reply back.
You can't even get a [ __ ] date. You
know how you know you want to talk about
relationships? Yeah. How how how hard it
is to maintain a relationship. And if
you can't even get a conversation out of someone,
you're not going to meet anyone. If you
can't even get a date, you're not going
to meet anyone. If you can't even get
anything but I've got a boyfriend,
you're not going to meet anyone. These
are all signs that you're not going to
meet no one. Because if you was going to
meet someone, you would have already met someone.
Simple as that. If you was going to meet
someone, you would have already met
someone by now. It would have already happened
if you was going to. That's that.
Right. Okay. So now you're just dism
okay. Right. We go around and around in
circles now. End the conversation. I've
explained it to you about 25 times and
you're still telling somebody that's
tried more than anyone in the world that
if I don't try, I'm not going to meet
someone. End the conversation now.
Anyways, right. Wait for Greavves here
and then tell him about this Franklin.
Yeah, cuz we're just going round and
round and round in circles. So, um yeah,
you're talking to someone that's tried
more than anyone in the world. So keep
remembering that before you before you
write that. Right. Wait one second.
You're saying if I don't Okay. So why
haven't I met someone now then? Okay
then. So why haven't I already met
someone? Considering I've tried more
than anyone in the world. Can you Can
you give me a Can you give me a
situation of how it would happen?
Okay. Can you give me a situation?
So you're going to go out next week,
right? Okay. And all of the bad things
that women have been doing to you for
years is going to stop.
You really want to do you want to put
money on it? Right. I'll be out Friday,
Saturday. I'm going out cuz I said I'm
going out. Do you want to put money on
it? Cuz I could deal with winning some
money. No. One second. You said that if
you don't if you keep trying, you're
going to meet someone. Okay. So, why
haven't I already met someone? You're
saying that I haven't No, you're saying
that you don't dismiss my struggles,
right? I've tried more than anyone in
the world. So, why haven't I already met
someone? Cuz I like the word trying. You
said that if you don't try. Okay. Well,
I have. You know, I've tried more than
anyone in the world. So, why haven't I met someone?
So, can you explain it? I I'll be very
very very excited to listen to this. If
you don't try, you're talking to someone
that's approached women all over the
[ __ ] country. Why haven't we already
found someone? See, the thing is, right,
it's all well and good you saying these
things, right? Oh, you're going to meet
someone. You're Bro, we've been hearing
it for seven years. We've been hearing
the same thing for seven years now. More
than seven years, but on here we've been
hearing it. So,
when would you meet someone? Give me I'm
I'm I want to know.
You know, I assume you don't do the
lottery. No. So, you're going to go out
one day and all of these women that
[ __ ] you over is going to is suddenly
going to change. [ __ ] delusional. How
delusional can someone actually get in
their head? They're delusional. You're
never going to meet anyone. You're going
to continuously keep having bad
experiences, continuously keep being
depressed when you keep trying in this
country. That's all that's ever going to happen.
That's all that is ever going to happen.
Nothing else will ever change. Nothing
else will ever happen because you would
have already met someone by now.
You would have already met someone if
trying worked. You would have already
met someone. You're still saying the
same [ __ ] You know,
you can approach a million women, you're
still not going to meet anyone at this
point. It really doesn't matter if you
try, you don't try, cuz you're still
never going to meet anyone. So, there's
no point you even trying. The only thing
that's going to happen is you're going
to get, "I'm I have a boyfriend. I'm not
interested." or you're going to get led
on. Nothing else will ever happen. I
know it and you know it.
And I wouldn't have went out yesterday
if I wasn't forced to go out.
So, I'm not even contradicting what I'm
saying. I'm not even contradicting it
cuz if I generally thought that weren't
the case, I'd be out approaching every
day. Got the confidence, not scared to
do it. I would be approaching every
single day or every week or twice a
week, whatever. I would be doing it
every week at the very minimum, but I
don't because I know there's no hope.
So, if you know there's no hope for you
and you accept it, you can move on with
your life. If you can't do that, then
you're always going to constantly be
depressed, depressed, depressed,
depressed, depressed. So, the that's the
that's the thing. Might be a hard pill
to swallow at first, but that's it. Oh,
we're just talking about women in this
country and [ __ ] and how you're never
going to meet anyone despite what you
try. Anyways, moving on from that now.
But yeah, this guy didn't meet. He
didn't put any videos up. Another little [ __ ] house.
Yep. Another little [ __ ] house, mate.
[clears throat and snorts]
This is what I mean with these people in
this community. I'm going after I'm gone
tomorrow anyways for a little bit. Won't
be live for a while. Look. Yep.
What I mean?
So yeah, you definitely definitely will
never meet anyone.
You definitely will never meet anyone.
It doesn't matter how many cuz cuz the
thing is like I keep repeating to you
repeating to the brick wall. You haven't
had a date since April.
You can barely get a conversation out of
someone. It's not automatically going to
change for you or me. So,
you know, like, so it's like it's it
doesn't what you're saying don't even
make any sense.
I went out yesterday. All I got was I
have a boyfriend. That's like the the f
well towards the end it was like the
first word. So, it's not all of a sudden
magically going to change and not be the west.
You know, look at that gambling. I
gambled today. I didn't even lose any
money. It pissed me off.
So, I was better off like just [ __ ]
I'm better off I'm better off just doing
nothing, bro, and just saving money and
just just doing nothing or whatever.
Just just doing nothing. Just just
basically doing nothing. But I'll go out
next week if you want me to and I'll
prove it to you again that it will never change.
I don't mind. I've already had my
haircut. I can prove it again if you
want, you know.
Yeah, it was mad, bro. £44. Jesus
Christ. I won't be going there. I used
to go there all the time. I was
expecting it in the 30 bracket. 30 pound
Yeah, I was I was expecting to be the 30
bracket. That is mad.
So, yeah, I won't be doing that again. Um, yeah.
Never [clears throat] again, bro. I
didn't mind paying like 30 32,
but that is mad. I'm not paying that
again, bro. I had to pay it cuz I
already ate it. Can't put their price up. So, yeah,
I'll be watching this film soon and
going to bed.
Same old that £170 on a weekend and got nothing.
Good old England.
I'm going to probably try and get a
couple of hours before I watch this
movie cuz I'm so hung over. Yep.
I wish I just stayed in bed yesterday,
bro, and done nothing.
Yeah, it is. I know. But I had to pay it
because I already ate it. >> Yep.
I know. If I knew that, I wouldn't have
[ __ ] got it, would I? Cuz it cuz it's
a place I've been to before. So I was
expecting it to be I've been there like
a million times. So I thought, "Oh yeah,
it's going to be like 32 33. Yeah, it's
not too bad. Just it's just society, you
know." But 44, I was like, "What?"
I was like, "No, no, check that again."
So yeah, you're always going to be
depressed in this country, women, whe
that's why I just don't do anything
nowadays. There's no point doing
anything. You might as well just stay in
bed and do nothing.
We went out yesterday. Look, we
approached even the people that we
didn't get the numbers from.
It will never ever change.
Never change. Just like what Ant-Man said.
This guy said, "If you you'll meet
someone if you keep trying." And I've
explained to him, "Look, if that was the
case, why haven't I already met someone?"
If that's the case, why haven't I
already met someone?
If that's the case, if trying if you
meet someone trying, then why haven't I
already met someone? He's struggling to
he's struggling to answer the question, Dusty.
Then by by your logic, I should have met
someone by now. No.
[ __ ] idiot, man.
I was thinking of these people in this
community, bro, when I was on the bus
back. I'd love to get my hands on one of
these people, bro.
Like that Joseph Ferrar. I'd love to get
my hands on one of these people. I'm
sick, you know, bro. Very, very sick.
Very very sick I am, bro. Yeah.
when it comes to these people.
So, I'm very sick when it comes to these people. [snorts]
Now, I'm hung over as [ __ ] and I'm going
to have problem sleeping now, you know. Yeah.
It's a jewel.
I'm really thinking the suicide, bro.
I'm not even joking.
This is depressing, bro. This is really,
really, really, really depressing. Yep.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] depressing, bro. Very
very very very very depressing. Yeah,
we can pray that we go to bed and not
wake up. [snorts]
That's the only thing we can
Yeah, definitely. Bro,
I am [ __ ] in my head, bro. I'm [ __ ]
tired, man. I won't be able to sleep either.
I don't think I'm going to wear my um actually
I'm in I'm in the room. Huh? [ __ ] cloud. lovely.
Nice fresh top.
Hopefully we can go to sleep and not
wake up. That'd be lovely.
Done everything I wanted to do in my life anyways.
It actually made me worse. See, if I
didn't go out yesterday, I think I would have calmed
It's depressing, bro.
I can't believe another year, same time
this year and you're still depressed.
Still nothing's changed.
We hear a lot of people say a lot of things. Nothing changes. Morning
cinema tomorrow bro
probably just be staying in bed.
I don't want to be in public.
Yeah, I want to be in public, bro.
Depression in it. Yeah. Slow [snorts] depression.
Yeah, it's just the same people doing
the same [ __ ]
Oh god, man. Timmy skin. It's just the
same people doing the same [ __ ] bro. Damn. Yeah.
Why are these mods so power hungry on here?
They're so power hungry.
They got like no life outside of Reddit.
It's truth, man.
No life outside of Reddit.
They've got no life outside of Reddit,
bro. These mods all to
all to do with power.
It's all to do with power. Ready? Yeah. Yeah,
they b people to feel powerful. It's [ __ ] pathetic.
No, no, Link, but I can't be bothered
talking to anyone. >> [sighs]
>> I just said to this guy, I don't care
about other people. I don't compare
myself to others.
Someone said, "I know your struggles,
bro, but there's people way worse than
you doing better." I said, "Don't care
about other people. That's a bad
mindset." No, that's a realistic mindset
because comparing yourself to other
people is a waste of time.
Comparing yourself to others.
I don't compare myself to others. If
anyone knows me,
because I don't compare myself to others. That's why
Waste of time
cuz comparing yourself to other people
doesn't change anything.
Just depressed, bro. I went out yesterday.
Yeah. Feeling rough, depressed.
As it won't change my situation, neither
will complaining. Neither will trying.
So yeah, complaining won't change a
situation, but neither will trying. Even
bettering yourself don't work. Again,
dismissing the fact that, you know,
neither do dating apps. Neither do
dating apps work.
Complete waste of time.
We're just going round and round in
circles. No, I didn't win. I got my ass whooped.
Yeah, you're right. The what the You're
right. Nothing works and the world is
against you. Again, dismissing my struggles,
which is what these people do. What
you're talking is crap. What you're
talking is [ __ ] Cuz I've been trying
for years and years and years and years
and years and years and years and years
and years. So, what you're talking is
absolute crap. And if you wasn't
dismissing people's struggles, you
wouldn't be saying this stuff. So yes,
the world is against me. Yes, if you
want to put it that way. Yes, they are.
Now [ __ ] off.
I wasn't with lady anyways.
You're still telling me to work on myself.
Still telling me to work on myself.
Uh, I'm going to end up killing myself,
bro. I really am going to end up killing
myself. I swear to God.
This is depressing me now, bro.
It changes nothing. Stop telling people
to work on themselves.
Stop telling people to [ __ ] work on
themselves. This is what's making me
want to kill myself. These people
telling me the same [ __ ] over and over
and over again, bro. You know what I'm
saying? Hearing the same [ __ ] Keep
trying. Work. We've heard it all before.
I've been hearing this for years and
years and years. This is what is
annoying me, bro. It's not going to change nothing.
It won't change nothing. Working on
yourself don't work. [ __ ] off.
Can't. You know what I'm saying?
Won't change anything.
You know what I'm saying? Just let
someone kill themselves. That's what I'm
going to do. I'm killing myself, bro.
I'm killing myself before this before
this new year. I'm telling you, I'm
killing myself, bro. 100%. 100 million%.
[ __ ] suicide is the only way out.
Stop telling people to keep [ __ ]
working on themselves.
I'm just going to go into a manic
depression again, bro. I'm going to go
into a manic depression where I won't
want to go out, where I won't want to
get out of bed. Cuz this is what this
gets you like, bro. You don't
understand. This is the [ __ ] this gets
you like. I I went out yesterday, bro,
cuz I got forced to go out. I got forced
to go out, bro. I literally got forced
to go out. I had to go out. Like, I got
forced in a way where I got forced to go
out. I didn't want to go out. I woke up
and said, "I'm not going out. I'm not
going out." I got forced to go out.
That's the only reason I went out.
Same [ __ ] happened again.
We're s we're hearing the same thing
again. Go Jim, work on yourself.
We've heard it all before, bro. We've
heard all of this [ __ ] before.
What? It doesn't matter what my physique
is. Stop making excuses for women. It
doesn't matter what I am, bro. It
doesn't matter what I am. [ __ ] fat,
skinny, fat, muscly, skinny, lanky,
ugly, goodlooking, [ __ ] whatever the
[ __ ] it is you are. It's not going to change.
Do you understand? It is not about me.
It is not going to change. It doesn't
matter what the [ __ ] you are, what the
[ __ ] you look like, it is not going to [ __ ] change.
Oh my [ __ ] god. Stop reversing it
back onto me again. And I don't know
what it is with these dudes that do this [ __ ] you know?
I don't know what it is with these dudes
that do this, bro.
Don't worry about where I live. Said,
"What country do you live?" Don't worry
about where I live.
Why do these people tell you like, "Oh,
just go gym for yourself. Oh, just look
good for yourself." Stop telling people
to work on themselves for women when it
ain't never going to change. It's never
ever ever ever ever going to change.
They're always going to be stuck up
[ __ ] Doesn't matter what you are.
It doesn't matter what you are. You
know, if you're going to give advice
like that, you should be telling people
to do that just to do that. Stop telling
people that they need to do that to get
women because it ain't going to change.
No matter what someone does, it's never
going to change. Stuck up women.
So stop. Yeah. You keep telling yourself
that, Triple H. You keep telling yourself that.
Yeah. And I'll win the lottery next
tomorrow, won't I? Just stop saying the
same [ __ ] over and over again. If you're
going to give advice, give advice for
the person to improve. Don't tell them
that they can't get anyone because
they're not doing these things.
Don't say, "Oh, well, you're not meeting
anyone because you're not going to the
gym and you don't have a physique." And
that's [ __ ] stupid.
Oh, you live with your mom or you don't
have a job or no no no.
[ __ ] off, man. Come on. Just stop lying
to people. You're going to give advice.
Give it give them advice for themselves. You know,
you're never going to meet anyone ever.
I know it and you know it. Simple.
Yeah. I've been hearing that one for
years as well. It will happen when you
least expect it. Yeah. Yeah. The West is
suddenly going to change, isn't it?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So, the when you'll go
out one day and all of the things that's
been happening to you for seven years is
going to stop. Yeah. Yeah. Of course. Of
course. Of course. Yeah. Of course it
will. Yeah, of course it will. Yeah.
Yeah. Of course it will. Yeah. Cuz one
day you go out one day. Yeah. And all of
these women are going to be completely
different as they've been for seven
years. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Of course. Yeah. Sure.
Yeah. I really, really, really believe
it. Someone that's traveled up and down
the country since the age of 22,
obviously go to different places every
week, met more than enough ample full of women.
Again, I've put my approaches out there
and I put my messages out there. If you
want to dismiss that, that's your
problem. I'm not even answering that
question. I put my messages out there
and I've put my approaches out there. If
you weren't so ignorant to dismiss
people's struggles, you wouldn't even be
ask you wouldn't even be asking me that question.
Again, dismissing people's struggles.
This is a big thing uh to do with gender
that no matter what you tell people
women do, no matter what you show, they
just dismiss it. That's why I never tell
Laney anything. I refuse to have an
argument with her. I refuse to get into
any confrontation because all that's
going to happen is they dismiss it. So
everything that you say gets dismissed.
So I never get into any kind of debate,
any kind of argument. I don't tell her
any experiences cuz it's unhealthy cuz
all you're doing is talking to people
that is just going to keep dismissing your struggles.
You're asking me right now a question
when I have put up several different
approaching videos where the women have
had attitude, been stuck up, women have
led me on, and you're asking me, do I
think I'm the problem?
One second, bro. Let's let's make this
make sense. I have shown you where women
have said they've had boyfriends
straight away. I have shown you where
women have gave attitude. I have shown
you where women have led me on and the
whole text was there and you're asking
me do I think I'm the problem, not the
women. Do I really need to answer you that one?
Do do I really really really need to
answer that question? Come on now.
Why you don't cuz you you you will
learn, Grezy. You do learn,
right? Again, I'll repeat myself. I put
approaches out there and I put messages
out there. I'll repeat myself again for
people that apparently don't dismiss my
struggles. I put approaches out there.
Out there, I put messages out there. You
keep dismissing them. Back to Greavves's
question. How am I going to learn if I
don't compare myself to other people? Um,
well, you get your No, no, no, no. Me,
me talk. No, no. It's like talking to a
brick wheel with you people. I have
shown you evidence, evidence of what
women have done to me and you keep
ignoring it. I have shown screenshots. I
have shown approaches and I'm talking to
a brick wall. You're ignoring my
struggles just like you're ignoring my
struggles. You're you're telling me I'm
It's like talking to a brick wall. I
have literally shown you black and white
evidence like the Felix cat of what
women have done and you're telling me
that I'm talking to a brick wall. You're
you're saying that it's like talking to
a brick wall. I have literally shown you
black and white evidence that you keep ignoring.
I have shown you black and white
evidence and you're still typing away at
me. Grezy. Anyways, on to you. How would
you learn if you don't compare yourself
to other people? You learn from your own
experiences. You learn from getting
better experiences. That's how you
learn. You don't compare yourself to
other people because comparing yourself
to other people is not going to change
your situation. So whatever whatever
people do is not going to change you.
you or you you or nobody else comparing
is a waste of time. It's a complete and
utter waste of time. So you will learn
by your own experiences.
Is that is that what makes sense? I
think it makes sense.
It's not going to change your situation.
So no matter how many people you compare
right again I'll repeat myself. I have
shown approaches. The third time I'm
repeating myself now apparently for
people that know this much this much of
my struggles. I have put approaches out
there and I've already answered that
question. The one that you've just
answered. I have put approaches out
there. I have put messages out there. I
have messaged someone today and they
haven't replied back. Somebody that I
met yesterday. What do you want me to
do, bro? Get a gun to their head and
make them reply. See the thing is you're
constantly constantly constantly trying
to blame other people but the women when
it is the women that are the problem.
And that's exactly what my videos have
shown. You have been shown black and
white evidence of women being the
problem and you're still not having any
of it. Which is basically what I'm I'm
what I say in most of my videos. You're
being shown black and white evidence of
what women are doing and you're simply
denying it cuz they're women. When we
all know if I was sat here chatting [ __ ]
about men, you wouldn't be saying
anything. It's the truth. It might sound
repetitive, but it's the truth. And you
know it's the truth.
You've seen what they've done. I put I
literally put messages up there even
when my microphone have broken and
you're still making stuff up,
you know. Well, yeah, you need I have
figured out you need to leave the country. Simple,
you know. I'm talking to this guy on
[ __ ] Instagram telling me to go to
the gym and get a better body. Not for myself,
but I don't know why he's saying that
because you're still never never going
to meet a woman.
You're never going to meet the woman.
You're never going to meet a woman. So,
he should be telling you to do that for yourself.
Don't tell people that they're going to
meet a woman because you you're you got
a better body and you got cuz you're
not. You are not.
So stop saying that [ __ ] So So
yeah, and you're still saying that women
aren't the problem. I mean, I I tell you
exactly what happened yesterday, Greasy. Yeah.
The first approach I done, I tell you
the first approach I done, I went and I
spoke to someone and they were
unenthusiastic. I walked away. Okay. The
other person said that they had a
boyfriend. Uh the other uh the other
person gave me their number. They said
drop them a message. Messaged them. They
didn't reply back. The other people just
said I have a boyfriend within 10
seconds. What are you supposed to do? If
people are doing that, what the [ __ ] are
you supposed to do? Huh? See, this is
what I mean. You're constantly finding
ways to try try to blame men. Even when
you're showing black and white evidence,
you won't have it. You know, I I don't
know what it is. Really, really, really
what it is. And we all know what it is.
I know what it is, you know, but you
constantly still don't think they're the problem.
Even when I've just told you what
they've done, it's [ __ ] madness, bro.
Idiots. Absolute idiots.
[ __ ] absolute clowns. Absolute idiots.
So yeah. But yeah, this person didn't
reply back. Anyways,
and also I've shown you multiple women
leading me on as well, which you never
really said anything about. But again,
it doesn't suit you.
That is strange as well cuz it's not
even this approaches that you've been
shown. You've actually been shown people
leading me on, but it doesn't suit you.
That don't suit you, does it? But a wine
and dash would suit you, would it? That
would definitely definitely suit you,
would it? Yeah, that suit you. If I went
out right now and I had a guy at a
woman, that would suit you. If I went
and died and dashed a woman, that would
suit you. But them leading me on, it
don't suit you.
It gets thrown in the It gets thrown in
the recycle bin. If that don't tell you
that it's a gender thing, I don't know
what will. It is clearly a gender thing.
You know, it clearly clearly [ __ ] is.
Come on now. You said nothing about them
women leading me on. You said nothing
about them taking the piss. Not a word
to ever been said. We're still waiting.
Why is that? Do you have selective
eyesight or I don't think it's selective
memory? I think is it selective
eyesight? I think I think that's a
better word for it. You've probably got selective eyesight.
You dismiss all the things that they do.
Bad. You just you literally dismiss all
the things they do. Even when you're
shown evidence, even if even if I was
wrong seven times and they were wrong
seven times, right? You never ever think
that they're wrong. Even if I'm wrong as
well. Why? I'm trying to really understand it.
It's not going to be the same in
Thailand. It's not going to happen.
It would never happen. Thailand is guaranteed.
It would not happen in Thailand, you
idiot. There's no there's no chance.
So then if I go to Thailand Okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay. And if I go to
Thailand and I go on Tinder and I find a
relationship, are you going to admit
that it's the women in the country then?
Yeah. Okay. So if I And you don't need
to pay Dusty. We've already been over
this. I've got a friend that lives in
Thailand. I think I know what it's like.
I've got a friend that lives there. I've
got a friend that's been there three.
I've got a time. I've got a friend
that's been there three times. Three
times. And he's living there now. I
think I believe him more than you, bro.
Anyways, I go to Tinder. If I go to if I
go to Thailand and I go on Tinder,
right, and I find someone, are you going
to are you going to admit that the women
in this country are the problem? Then
would you admit it? That's that's a
better question to you.
But yeah, you shouldn't compare yourself
to other people.
Would you compare yourself? Okay. Okay.
Would you compare yourself to people
that's got more money than you? No.
Would you compare yourself to people?
No, he's not telling the truth. I've got
a friend that lives in Thailand.
No, he's not telling the truth.
Anyways, I've got a friend that lives in
Thailand. He tells me all the time.
Anyway, so you wouldn't compare yourself
to people that's got more money, less
money than you. You wouldn't compare
yourself to people in any other way.
So why are you comparing yourself when
it's to do with women?
That doesn't make sense.
So yeah, and I've got a friend that
lives in Thailand.
And I've got a friend that lives in Thailand. So
Yeah. Anyways, so you wouldn't compare
yourself to them people. So why would
you compare yourself to people? You
wouldn't compare yourself to people
doing better than you financially. So
why are you comparing yourself to people
that have got girlfriends? It doesn't make sense.
I know better when I've got a friend
that lives in Thailand. Yeah. When I've
got a friend that lives in Thailand,
Dusty. Yeah. I would say I know better.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. When I know somebody
that lives in Thailand
and works there. Yes, I know better.
Yes. Anything English? Yes. Yes, I do. So, yeah.
I've got a friend that lives there.
Yeah. Okay, bro.
So, yeah. Why do you keep dismissing
what women do as well, Greg? You triple
H D people. Why do you keep dismissing
the leading on and [ __ ]
Why do you keep dismissing all of the
bad things that they do? Can you answer that?
cuz I I'm a bit confused. I don't know
how many videos people have done on it
cuz he doesn't come on this community.
He doesn't like these people in this community.
So yeah, and I've explained this
multiple times. You don't have to pay
for the women. I'm not explaining it
again, bro. I'm not explaining it again.
So anyways, moving on now because we're
going nowhere with this and you're
missing people struggling again.
But do you think that you're the problem
and not the women even though I've shown
all the things women have done? Even if
they weren't all wrong, [laughter]
but you don't dismiss people's
struggles. But you don't dismiss
people's struggles. Yeah, I've shown you
ample full of women leading me on ample
full of women with bad attitude, but it
doesn't suit you.
But it don't suit you. You have shown
ample full of evidence and then you dismiss it. [ __ ] madness.
And then you're asking me that question. Madness.
I don't think I don't think there's been
I I can't remember the last time I've
met an unbiased person. I have met them
where they say that you're a [ __ ] and a
woman's a [ __ ] No, no, no. But very
very unlikely. People do generally
defend people that's got a vagina.
Yeah. They just they just they just uh you know
they do just miss your struggles.
Definitely. Why do you just miss
people's struggles? I really want to
know like can you just answer why you
ignore that all the things that I put up
with what women have done. Don't answer
saying all this. No, you've been shown
evidence. You've been shown lots and
lots of evidence of what they've done.
You have been shown ample full of
evidence of what they've done. So why
are you asking me a question? Do I think
it's me and not the women when I've
literally shown you what a lot of them have done?
But you don't dismiss my struggles. Really, idiots.
I can't respect that. You know, people
defending women for just being women. I
can't respect that
because you're saying that I always
think I'm right, but you don't think I'm
wrong. You're only defending them
because they've got a [ __ ]
They've got a [ __ ] in between their
they've got a [ __ ] in between their
legs. So you you don't actually even
think I'm wrong. You're just saying it
because they've got a [ __ ] in between
their legs. That's that's what the
problem is, you know?
But yeah, whatever.
And it's not even just here. You can go South America.
No, I'm not answering your question
because you don't answer my question.
I've got an answer to your question, but
I'm not answering your question cuz you
keep dismissing my struggles.
You're a hater. A different opinion.
Dusty, I've shown you facts, right?
repeat myself for the fourth time again.
I have shown you where women have led me
on and been rude for the fourth time
now. Is there going to be a fifth time?
Mate, listen. It's not about a different
opinion when you're being proven what
these women have done. That's when it's
not an opinion.
You know, you're hat you're biased
because you keep dismissing all the [ __ ] they've done.
Keep dismissing all the bad things women
have done. And that's what's getting me
down. If these people keep dismissing
what I'm showing that they're doing,
that's what's getting me down. Keep
constantly feeling like the boy who's
cried the wolf. I've shown you what
they've done. I've shown you their
attitude. And you still won't have none
of it. You still are adamant that
they're not the problem. I've shown you
them [ __ ] me over and leading me on.
And you're still dismissing it. You're
still dismissing it. Still dismissing
it. Still dismissing it. And then you're
asking me questions.
Why do you think women are perfect? Just
answer me right here. No one's blocked.
Why do you people think women are perfect?
I'm I'm really wanting to know. Do you
think they're going to sleep with you by
defending them? Like, I want to know the
answer. I'm not blocking anyone. I'm
asking you how you can ignore black and
white evidence and pretend it never
happened. Unless you're thinking that
these women are going to sleep with you.
I'm wanting to know, bro.
Bro, you didn't even go to Waterloo
today, you little [ __ ] Shut the [ __ ]
up. You didn't do no videos. You didn't
go live. You little [ __ ]
You absolute [ __ ] Everyone knew about
you anyways. You little [ __ ]
Yeah, I caught on early about what you
what you were on anyways. You absolute little [ __ ]
Yeah, you didn't show today. You little [ __ ]
Yeah, you are a waste man. You absolute
little [ __ ] If you was there, why did
you do a video? You little [ __ ] Yeah,
bro. You couldn't even do a video. We
all know. We all know you wasn't there. You know,
people that talk like that don't meet
people. As soon as you start saying M
and all of this and all of that, we know
you're not serious. We know who the
serious ones are on here, bro. And you
ain't one of them. Yeah.
See you later anyways. You can have a timeout. [ __ ] out.
So, yeah. I just So,
well, you don't think that? So, why do
you people keep dismissing people's
struggles then? Okay. Okay. Okay. You
don't think that? Okay, fair enough. So,
why do you keep dismissing people's struggles then?
Okay. So, why do you keep dismissing
people's struggles then?
Don't say you're blocked. You're not
blocked. I'm trying to get to the bottom
of why you people keep defending women
for having a [ __ ] in between their legs.
Right. So, you don't you don't think
they're going to sleep with you? Okay,
whatever. So, why do you keep doing it?
I'm asking you. I want to know why you
keep ignoring the leading on the
attitude, the [ __ ] Why is it going
in one ear and out the other or in this
case in one eye and out the other? I'm
asking you why you're doing it. You
know, you you say people are being you
say that people get you say that people
are getting blocked, right? You can't
have your say. I'm asking you why you're
doing it. Why do you keep defending and
dismissing everything they are doing?
[ __ ] me. I should have to ask this question again.
Take I'm gambling again. No, I'm not
Idiots on this community. If you watch
my video properly, you would have known
exactly what happened. [ __ ] idiots on
this community. So, you're not going to
answer. So there's no point in this
debate in the future. Then if I want to
moan and I want to winge, let me moan
and winge. Cuz you're not answering.
You're not answering when I have
literally shown you black and white
Felix the cat evidence and you're still
dismissing it. So if you don't think
they're going to sleep with you, why do
you keep defending them? I'm trying to
think about this logically because in my
head it does not make sense. If a gay
man will show me evidence of what gay or
or a woman, I'd be like, "What the [ __ ]
Why do you continuously keep dismissing
it? I'm asking you a question.
Is it because they've got a [ __ ] in
between their legs and you think they're
going to sleep with you? I'm asking you a question.
You've been shown black and white
evidence and you're still blaming me
just cuz I'm a man.
So, you must be a white man then.
If you can't answer it, you must be a
white man. That's the only thing it can be.
You've seen approaches, you've seen
messages, you've seen five different
things of what they've done, and you're
still saying, "Oh, uh, do you think that
you might be the problem? Do you think
that you might be the problem?" Not
that, "Oh, I think you was wrong 10
times. I think they were wrong 10 times.
I think you were wrong in some of them,
and they were wrong in some of them."
Really, bro? Really? Really? You're
asking that question after the [ __ ] that
you've been shown.
My again I put my evidence up of more
with my experiences with women more
experiences that you would ever have. I
blame women for leading me on keeping me
single, giving me attitude, lying to me.
I blame them for all of them things.
Yes, I blame women for giving me them
experiences. I'm not denying it. You
just said that I'm You just said that I
think I'm always right. I'm blaming
women for leading me on, giving me
attitude, taking the piss out of me. I
blame women for that. Yes, I blame
women. Yes, I blame women for that.
Yes, I blame women for that. Yes, I do.
I do. I blame women for that. I blame
women. And just, bro, again, let me tell
you something. Defending women is not
going to make them like you. Don't even
waste your time. They don't like you.
So, this is another thing I'm going to
say to you, bro. Right. That defending
women is not going to make them like
you. Take it from me, bro. Like, you're
going to be 90 and on your deathbed
thinking that all of them times where
you defended women and dismissed
people's struggles, they don't like you, bro.
I feel for you to be honest. I don't
know how dumb people can be, you know,
like defending women. women don't like
you and you're still sticking up for
them. I feel for you as well because I
still don't understand why you do it.
Autism. Like I don't know. I at first I
thought it was autism.
I at first I thought it was people just
being autistic to be honest because I
don't understand why where the desire
comes from to defend women
when women don't like you. I don't
understand. They don't like you. They're
never going to sleep with you. And I've
probably been with more women than you.
And yet, when you find somebody
complaining or speaking the truth,
you're saying, "Oh, well, this that."
And then you start going on your high
horse and [ __ ]
I've probably had more women than you
have. Not even to sound immature. And
you're the one sat there defending them.
Really, bro? Really?
Just that's what I I just don't
understand it. I don't understand it. I
really, really, really don't understand
it. No, not more escorts. More women.
More women than you that weren't
escorts. Not more escorts. More women.
I've slept with multiple women that
weren't escorts. And I don't lick their
ass. I don't simp. Oh, women are
perfect. I don't do what you do. So, is
it autism? I'm asking you why you're
doing it. More. Not more escorts. More
women. I didn't pay. More women.
No. I don't tell lane. I don't tell,
bro. I don't tell people because they're
so stupid that they dismiss people's struggles,
you know. I don't tell people because
they're so dumb and sexist that they
dismiss your struggles. Why am I going
to tell anyone anything? Simps like you,
white knights like you.
It's mad how people that have had less
women than you will sit there and defend
women. It's got to be autism. I'm
telling you, it's autism with these people.
Where does that desire come from? We're
never going to get the answer, but I
think it's autism. I think these people
are autistic. That's why they do it
because it ain't normal. It is not
normal. Especially with with what's
going on in the in the world now that
they continuously continuously
defend women and women don't like them.
Like UK asylum, women don't like him. He
certainly has not had more women than
me. He certainly has not. And I'm not
I'm not doing that to be awkward. You
certainly have not had more women than I
have in any way. And you're the one
licking their ass when I'm saying I
don't like what they are doing.
Yeah. I'm the one that's autistic. No,
I'm not autistic. Again,
self-projecting. Never had autism in my
life. So, it just it just doesn't make any sense.
So, I'm saying I don't like what they're
doing. They are doing this. They're
doing that. They are doing this. I'm
disagreeing with things that they do cuz
I'm not a sexist pig. You are coming to
their rescue like Superman.
It's [ __ ] weird.
Someone having a [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm high rate being a virgin. Bro,
the only virgin is you. That's why you
keep defending women. It's because
you're the virgin. It's so obvious. The
only people that do this are people that
don't get women. The only people that
defend women are people that are
virgins. Cuz they're all so autistic in
their mind. They think that one day when
they keep defending women, they're going
to get women. Only people that do what
you do are virgins. It's autism. I know
it's autism. Women don't like them. They
don't want them, but they still defend
them. And after year after year after
year, the [ __ ] still happens, but they
still do this [ __ ] Why do you do it? I
don't I could understand defending
someone if they're generally in the
[ __ ] wrong. Someone's getting beat
up. someone I don't [ __ ] know. I can
understand these but these No, I feel
bad for you, bro, being a white knight.
Yeah, I feel bad for you as well being a
white knight and being a virgin. I feel
bad for you as well.
I hope you I hope you lose your
virginity. I really really hope that all
this singing that you've done today, you
actually lose your vcard, your
Valentine's card. You too, man. I hope
you lose your [ __ ] Vcard.
Finding someone's a bit harder, but I
hope you lose your Valentine's card.
You two as well, lad. You two as well. I
hope you lose your Valentine's card, man.
Yeah. So we can both be happy cuz you
definitely definitely need it.
Definitely definitely definitely
definitely definitely definitely need it, man.
Yeah, you can use you can use your
Valentine's card and I can find someone
because the way these people defend
women is not healthy. It's really,
really, really, really, really not healthy.
And then you'll tell them that women
don't like you. Women don't like you.
Women don't like you. And they still
defend women. It's like Dusty. Women
don't like him. He will still defend
women. Women don't like him. Women don't
want him. But they'll still defend women
till they're blue in the face. It's
weird. It's [ __ ] weird.
So so so weird that these people stick
up for random women. It's [ __ ] madness.
[ __ ] absolute madness.
So anyway, that's that.
But either way, it's never going to
change anyway. So it doesn't really
matter, does it? No thanks.
No thanks, bro.
I'm going to send my dick I'm going to
send my I'm going to send some dick
pictures to people. I think we
just to piss them off.
could be ignoring little [ __ ] again.
Oh, same cycle. Same same cycle.
Same cycle again.
Same cycle again. I'm doing it, bro. 100%.
I'm definitely doing it again. Yeah, I'm
definitely doing it again. I'm sending
my dick, bro, to these people just as a
nasty thing to look at.
I got a lot of people that don't live in
England, so obviously they can't get the police involved.
Yeah, man. I'm doing it. I think all the
[ __ ] they've gave me over the years. Yeah.
going to send some dick pictures just to
annoy people, you know. I done it to
someone in France cuz they kept being an ignory.
Yeah. I said to one, "I hate women." She
didn't reply. So, I'll send her my um
You know what? Uh,
dismissing people's struggles again,
Grezy. I don't refer to myself as a nice
guy. I hate that saying nice guy. What
are you talking about? The times where
I'm talking about how women contradict
themselves. I actually say normal. I
don't say nice. I actually say normal.
You're dismissing my struggles again,
Grezy. You're forgetting all the things
they've done. Reminder, friendly reminder.
all the things that they've done. Friendly reminder.
You know what? This conversation would
be so much better if I was chatting [ __ ] about men.
This would be such a much better
conversation if I was talking [ __ ] about
men, would it? Everyone would be
agreeing. It'd be such a such a great
conversation, you know.
No, I'm saying women contradict themselves.
They say they can't find a normal person
and then if someone is normal they say
they're not interested. Yeah. They
contradict themselves. Women contradict They do.
Yeah. They do contradict themselves. [ __ ]
I'm I I'm doing it in retaliation.
Right. Right. Right. Right. But I'm
doing it in retaliation.
We're just going around in circles, bro.
We're just going round and round and
round and round in circles.
round and round in circles. You're
giving me a [ __ ] headache.
They say that they can't find anyone
normal or they can't find anyone decent.
Yeah, normal people approach them.
They're not interested.
There's people they can find on the
internet that are normal and decent.
Even if it's three out of 300 people,
but they're moaning and complaining
about men. Yeah. They contradict
themselves. And what what's your point?
They contradict themselves.
They generalize men. They say they're
anti-men. Again, another double
standards. I met somebody at the Weather
Spoons before, outside the Weather
Spoons, and they're like, "Oh, I'm anti-men."
So, if you say you're anti-woman, you
never hear the last of it. So, yeah,
it's a gender thing. Any Anyways, that's
why I don't take it that's why I don't
take it to heart because I know that you
really don't think that I'm right.
I I I think that you really don't think
that I'm wrong. Sorry. Cuz if I had a
[ __ ] in between my legs, it'd be a different story.
which shows how biased it is. If I had a
if I had a [ __ ] in between my legs, it'd
be completely different. So, does that
not destroy your argument? Does that not
destroy your argument, bro?
Does that not completely destroy the
whole thing, Grezy? So me and you, we
can go back and forth, back and forth,
back and forth, back and forth, back and
forth, back and forth, back and forth,
forth. But me and you both know if I had
a [ __ ] in between my legs, it'd be
completely different. Does that not ruin
the whole thing? Does that not end the
Does that not end it all? I think that
ends the whole thing to be honest with you.
No, I'm sending them dick pictures.
Yeah, I'm sending them dick pictures.
That would teach them for [ __ ]
trolling me and leading me on. I've got
some people [ __ ] Yeah, they don't
live in England, so
[ __ ] [ __ ] And they're going to be
like, "Ew, a dick is gross. Ew, dicks
are gross." And then they're going to
get like pregnant in a year cuz they're
hypocrites. So that's another thing with
these women. They're very, very hypocritical.
Very, very hypocritical as well. That's
another thing. They're going to be like,
"Ew, a dick picture. Ew, a dick. Ew.
double standards again. Cuz if somebody
showed you their vagina and you said it
was gay, if if you said you didn't like
it, they'd say they would say they they
would say you're gay.
I don't think anyone has said a vagina
is gross. To be fair,
women say dicks are gross, greasy, but
then they get pregnant and they suck dicks. So
yeah, they don't want you either. They
don't want you. They don't want Dusty.
They don't want none of us.
If they don't want me, they certainly
don't want you. Yeah.
This is a gender thing. This is a gender
thing. This isn't a me thing. This is a gender thing.
I might just send them porn. I might not
even send them my dick. I might just
send them porn. I don't really want to
send my dick. I might just send them
porno. Grezy. Yeah, porn.
Yeah, I might just send them porn.
Yeah. And I've had women as well, funny
enough. And I've had women as well. So
again, I'm the complete example of
someone that's unbiased. And I've had
women as well. And I can completely tell
you that I am unbiased.
It doesn't matter who's had more women
or or not. That that doesn't really
matter to be honest. I've had women.
I've had women. And I'm saying this, so
what can you say about me? [ __ ] if
you've had more than me or I've had more
than you. That's all irrelevant. I've
had women and I'm telling you they're
[ __ ] and I'm telling you they're evil
and I'm not a virgin. And I'm not a
virgin. Yeah. And I'm telling you women
are [ __ ] I'm telling you they're
all the same. And I've been with women
and I've had sex with people that
weren't escorts. So what have you got to
say about me? That's the definition of
someone that's not biased.
These women Oh, they were just people's
numbers I got and they led me on. I
don't give a [ __ ]
to be honest. I made USA change her
number cuz loads of people on the dating
apps were sending her dick pictures
cuz I thought I Yeah, she changed her
number in the end.
So what am I, bro? Am I an incel? Am I a
virgin? Cuz I've been with women. I've had sex.
So I'm completely unbiased cuz I'm not a
copycat. I don't follow the crowd.
I do not follow the crowd.
I haven't had women. Okay. I haven't had
women. Whatever. Not getting into this
review. I've shown videos. Again,
dismissing what you shown. I've been in
bed with women. I've shown plenty of
different women. I haven't had women.
I've shown plenty of different women.
So, what you're saying doesn't make any sense.
Yeah. Okay. You don't think I've had
sex? Grow up. All I can say to you is grow up.
So now you're So what you're saying is
because I'm not a white knight and I'm
not going to lick a woman's ass, I've
not had sex. That's not the way that
works. You knew you do know there's a
there's a third thing. There's white
knights, there's simps, there's incels,
but there's also people that are
unbiased that's just sick of their [ __ ]
and speak their mind,
you know, that speak their mind.
I'm not one to go to [ __ ] college the
next day and say,
I'm not a copycat. I've got a mind of my
own. You know, when I speak my mind, I
don't I don't follow the crowd. Unlike
certain people, I don't follow a crowd, you know. Yeah.
Mistakes I'm making. H dismissing struggles again.
Dismissing struggles again. I put
messages out there. I put approaches out
What's What's a mistake? Saying, "Hi,
how are you?" and them saying they've
got a boyfriend.
Again, this is a gender thing.
This is a gender thing. This isn't a me
thing. This is a gender thing.
This is a This is a gender thing.
Yeah, I'm making mistakes by going and
asking somebody, "Hi, how are you?" and
them saying they've got a boyfriend.
Yeah. Okay. See, you're just dismissing
my struggles again. See, we're going
back to the same thing again. You say
that you don't dismiss people's
struggles, but you are
by strange men. Uh I'm not strange. I'm
not strange at all. I'm a normal person.
Thank you very much. So, um get your
facts right. So, yeah. Um I'm not
strange. I'm normal. Stop being a white
knight. Women are strange themselves. Strange?
But strange? Are you all right, bro? Yeah.
Yep. Whatever. Bro, they're [ __ ]
strange themselves. Remember, Dusty,
they don't like you. So, keep defending
them. They're still not going to like you.
Strange? I'm more normal than them. At
least I don't leave people on.
At least I don't leave people on. And
you're calling me strange. At least I
don't lead people on and have attitude.
[ __ ] why not? This is a gender thing.
I think we should all just stop talking
about this now cuz this has been proven
multiple multiple times that this is a
gender thing. This is 100% a gender
thing. So, I don't even know why I'm
still wasting my time on it. It's clear
that you you defend them just for the
sake of them being a woman. You can't be shown wrong.
No, he's [ __ ] strange his [ __ ]
self. He's about this. Dusty is behind
101 different accounts and he's calling me strange.
[ __ ] white knight. Again, women don't
like you, Dusty. Take it from me. They
don't like you. So, keep defending them.
It's not going to make them like you.
Women don't want you either, Dusty. They
don't like you. So, as much as you keep
white nighting, they're not going to
like you. They don't want Dusty Chop.
Trust me. Don't waste your time, bro.
You're better than that. They're not
going to sleep with you. No, I'm not
going to leave them alone.
Do you know what I'm going to do right
now? I'm going to send them my dick
right now just to piss you off. One
second. Let me get it wrecked. [ __ ]
this. No, I've got these. Never mind.
[ __ ] that. Get my dick out right now. One sec.
It's nice and hard.
>> One second.
One second, bro. I'll show you. Leave them alone. One second.
Leave them alone. Yeah. One sec.
I'm going show them my testicles as
well. One sec.
I'm definitely not leaving MB. I'm going
to show them my big dick. My big gigantic cop. One sec.
Takes a while.
I don't listen to people on YouTube.
My mom told me not to listen to [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm not stopping, bro. These
[ __ ] One sec. Almost there. We one second. Almost.
I [ __ ] am doing it.
One second. Swinging it about.
Just a negative reaction. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm I don't give a [ __ ]
One sec. We're almost there.
Yeah, here we go. Let me take this
picture and send a bit. Hold on.
Well, I've argued with these white
knights now for the past hour and 45
minutes and we haven't got anywhere here
now, Grezy. So, something's got to give.
One sec. Just swinging it about
2 seconds. It's not to its full potential.
Heated to the Pekka.
Heated the Pekka
isn't to its full potential yet. Right,
here we go.
Yeah, I'm sending it. One second.
We need to find Where's that one gone?
There we go. Two sex. One there.
Where's the other one? Let's finish one.
I'll send her it.
There we go. Send that insert.
Oh, here we go. I've got another one.
Got a couple of them. [laughter]
Four people now. Center two. [laughter]
There we go. Lovely.
Yeah, I sent it to them, bro. I sent my
dick to them.
There we go.
There we go. Lovely. It's about five people. [laughter] >> Yep.
>> There you go.
I saying to five people. I told you,
bro. I don't [ __ ] about.
I told you I don't [ __ ] about, bro. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah. Done to five people. My told me,
my mom told me that I don't listen to [ __ ] So
lovely. Peter the Pekka. They saw that straight away.
They saw the picture straight away.
Triple the other messages was lost at transit. Yeah.
I don't think I can send it to this
person cuz they're in England. These are
all numbers I got from approaching by
the way. France, Finland. This one lives
in England. So, I don't think I can do
it because they they might call the police. Yeah, man.
I told you I don't listen to [ __ ] I mean,
should love Peter the Pekka, bro. Peter the Pekka.
I sent them Peter the Pekka.
Peter the Becker. [laughter] [ __ ] [ __ ]
And they're going to get wide and dash
when one of them meets me as well. Yeah.
Yeah. Trust me. I can do it dirty. You
don't understand me, bro. You don't understand.
You don't understand me, though. Uh,
Gregy, I can definitely do it dirty.
I can do it dirty, man. I'm worse than
Timmy. I'll do it dirty.
Yeah, I'm worse than Timmy, bro. I'll do
it. I'll do it dirty, bro. Yeah,
Peter the Yeah, [ __ ] [ __ ] All the
[ __ ] they've gave me over the years.
All the [ __ ] they've gave me over the
years. Leading on the piss taken. [ __ ]
them, bro. [ __ ] them.
But that's only a little I'm a drinking
a cup of [ __ ] right now. And that's only
that's only the start, bro. That's only
the [ __ ] start. That's only the start, mate.
[ __ ] amount of times they keep
pretending they've got boyfriends, being
[ __ ] being [ __ ] [ __ ] them, bro.
I think they'll be grossed out by a
dick. I mean, they say they're grossed
out by dicks, but they're not really
grossed out by dicks. Cuz if people's if
people was grossed out by dicks, they
wouldn't be having sex. They wouldn't be given oral.
So, they're not really they're not
really grossed out by um they're not
really grossed out by dicks.
No, I'm saying Grezy.
So that doesn't make any sense.
I sent it to the Finnish one as well,
Greaves. You know the Finland is
I reckon I'm going to get myself in
serious trouble next week, bro. I'm
going to be out I'm going to be by
myself to next week. So I was with my
sister and her friends. So I'm going to
be by myself next week.
I'm going to [ __ ] spill some drink
over some [ __ ] I'm going to spill some
drink over some cunt's face. [laughter]
Just for you, Grevy. Just for you. Yeah.
Give them some back of what they gave me
over the [ __ ] years. Yeah.
No, I'm not changing the subject. These
[ __ ] women, we can't let these
[ __ ] women win in it, Grezy.
Remember that, Grezy? Yeah. Don't let
these [ __ ] women win,
mad [ __ ] Yeah. Don't deprive Greavves
of content, the poor [ __ ] Yeah.
No, I ain't changing the subject, bro. Yep.
teach them for being little ignoring
[ __ ] and leading leading on. Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ] Yep.
By the way, Joker, I've shown Triple H
where women have led me on and been
stuck up, but he keeps dismissing it.
By the way, he keeps dismissing all the
bad things I've done. Dismissed.
Dismissed. Dismissed. Dismissed.
Dismissed. That's all he does.
Just throwing that out there, Dad. Yeah.
So, what location we going to next week?
Central Liverpool Street.
Where we going to where we going to be a
pest? Where we going to be a nuisance?
Where am I going to be a nuisance?
You know, I'm going to be a [ __ ]
nuisance next week. Triple. An absolute nuisance.
No. Elephant and castle is dead.
Why? Why elephant and castle? What's
good with elephant and what's good about
elephant and castle
what's good about elephant and castle?
Why would I go there?
Triple I grievy. Why would I go there?
Yeah, but why that place? Peter By's got
a lot of history in Elephant in Castle.
Really? That's what that account said.
Peter B's got a lot of history in
Elephant and Castle.
Bro, these people don't get into my
head. I'm in their head. They're the
ones that are writing about me every
day. They're the ones that are stalking
me every day, bro. I'm I'm the ones that
are in their head.
I'm in their head doing this.
Cuz they're the ones that are thinking.
They're the ones that have to wake up
every day hating on me, bro. So, they're
in I'm in their head. I'm literally in
Do you really think these [ __ ] stupid
people like Jamie Thompson and nonsense,
bro? I'm in I'm on I'm in their head.
For them to keep doing what they do
every day, I'm in their head. So yeah, dismissing struggles.
Yeah, I sent him my Willie
in the winter because you can get depressed
and sexy frustrated. Winter's the worst.
See, in the summer you can go out and do stuff,
but obviously in the winter you Yeah.
Yeah, it's a bit different.
They're not winning at the moment,
bro. They've got a channel dedicated to
me, bro. They've got a channel. They've
got channels dedicated to me. They're
not winning. I'm winning.
I live in their head. I'm winning. They
have to come on here every day being
obsessed with me, bro. I'm the one
that's winning. They're the ones that
are stalking me on multiple different
platforms. Won't leave me alone. Bro,
I'm winning. I'm the one that's winning,
bro. Not them.
You might want to see this Jamie
Thomasson channel. No, I'm definitely definitely winning. 100%.
I'm winning because they're the ones cuz
I've got all of these middle-aged people
that are obsessed with me.
They stalk me from the time they wake up
to the time I go to bed. I'm winning, bro.
You seem to have locked me in. I was out
yesterday. Bro, these people do not [ __ ]
with my head. They don't do anything.
They don't bother no one. I've been on
here for years and they and they just
bore people. I'm in their head because
I've got these middle-wage people that
are obsessed with me. They don't have me
locked in. I was out yesterday. And when
I don't go out, it's because I don't go
out. They definitely do not have me
locked in and they definitely do not
affect my life.
So, before we want to get into that
again, let's not. They do not bother me
one little bit. These people on here,
these little clowns on here do not
bother me one little bit. Not one little
These little self-reflecting obsessed
people. I couldn't care less about them.
Definitely definitely don't have me
locked in. You can go out whenever I
want. I was out today. I was out
yesterday. Definitely definitely
definitely definitely not.
I affect their life though cuz they're
the ones that are obsessed with me every
day. I affect their life though. That's
the That's the difference. I affect their life.
I think you're underestimating how much
time this takes. Waking up, stalking
every day, bro. It takes time. You You
seem to be dismissing
what they do and and the [ __ ] they go
to. You don't understand the amount of
effort it takes.
So, here we go. L's bomb. Bonboy again.
LJ's Bombay has ended the chat. You
don't understand the amount of effort
and time it takes. And if you really
did, you would know that I I am [ __ ]
with their head.
But you don't seem to understand that
though, do you? You don't understand the
amount of time it takes for them to do
what they do. I'm [ __ ] with their
head, bro. You got old age pensioners.
Obsessed with you.
Yeah. This is LJ's bum boy. Uh, doggy G.
Yeah. This is his bum boy.
Yeah, I had a haircut last week.
Why? Why you asking?
Hello, Timmy. Timmy's got a bone to pick
with you. I don't know why you keep
calling yourself ugly, rat face, but the
only ugly one is you in this chat. So, I
don't know why you're calling me ugly
when you are the only ugly one here. But
Timmy wants to meet you,
Blooming Tragic. You're 31 and you're
still a virgin.
You're 31 and you're still a virgin.
You're talking about kissing that
[ __ ] 30 21. You're still a [ __ ] virgin.
You're absolute v. Oh, look at him. Look
at the white knight. Look at the white
knight. Say that is a bit weird. Look at
the white knight virgin.
White knight appears.
predator. Okay, mate. Okay, mate.
Timmy's after you, by the way. Timmy's after you.
Yeah. I'd rather be alone than be with a
disabled girl. be with a [ __ ] fat
ugly the wolf like what you're with. I
think I'd rather be gay to be honest.
Yeah, I'd rather be alone than be with
someone that's got special needs.
You don't even like her either. You
insecure little virgin.
I can understand if you actually liked
her. You don't even like her. [ __ ]
virgin. And you know you're a virgin as well.
You're alone in a bed sit with a fat
disabled girl. Ugly disabled girl. Ugly and disabled. [ __ ] virgin.
Kissing at 21 is tragic, bro. You've
never had sex. You're still a virgin.
And you're [ __ ] older than me. You're
[ __ ] older than me, you virgin
Rey, you're still there. The virgin [ __ ] >> [laughter] >> Yeah.
I had a roast dinner.
Timmy's after you, by the way. Virgin.
Timmy said that you're skint and you're
in a bed sit. He wants you. You know, he
wants you. Two virgins fighting.
Two absolute virgins fighting.
Yeah, he come straight away when I told
him that I was sending dick pictures to
women. [ __ ] white knight.
Look at you, man. You're still a virgin
at [ __ ] 31 and you're still defending
women when you're a virgin and they
don't like you.
[ __ ] madness. [ __ ] autism. But at
least he actually admits he's autistic.
At least he admits that he's autistic,
you know, which other people I don't
think they do. So, you know, that is
definitely definitely definitely autism
because with him, we know for a fact
he's not been with anywhere near as many
women as I have. None of the women that
I have been with has ever been disabled.
So, you would have thought that I would
have been defending them, but I I don't
follow the crowd.
You see, the thing is, I don't follow
the crowd. Like I've said a million times.
I'll never forget that day you went back
to college, mate, after taking a week off.
I I like Sher Cole. I like Sher Co. They
were all [ __ ] They were all throwing
[ __ ] paper planes at each other. I
like Sher Co. You're gay. They were all
saying it to each other. Greasy little copycats.
Yeah, he can screen record all he wants.
He doesn't bother me. He's just a
coward. I don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah, he's a stalker. He's disabled. I
don't care, bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
about any of these people. They can get
cancer and die for like I don't give a
[ __ ] about any of these disabled people
in here, bro.
You can screen record all you want. I
don't care. You've been doing it for
years. You little low life. No one
cares. Screen record all you want. You
don't affect me. None of these people in
here affect me.
I affect them, though.
sad, jealous, fat, ugly people ain't got
a life anyways. Yeah. So, yeah, back to
the autism thing as well. Yeah.
What's wrong with sending your dick
anyways? Don't women have sex? Don't
women get pregnant?
I don't I don't care if it's
unsolicited. They don't tell me what I
can and can't send.
Why? Cuz I hate these people in this
community. Well, not everyone, but a lot
of them. Cuz I literally hate these
people in this community.
I hate 90% of them.
You don't believe me, do you?
Even that Joseph Far, if he ever gets
out there, I'm going on his door.
I would be going on his door. I don't
give a [ __ ] if it gives them a fright.
I don't give a [ __ ] if it gives them a fright. Good.
I'm sure they won't find it that
disgusting, Dusty. Cuz if they do, they
won't be having sex again, will they? If
they really found dicks disgusting, they
wouldn't be sucking dick and and stuff. So, yeah.
I certainly wouldn't be finding a vagina
gross then licking a vagina, solicited or unsolicited.
That's what I'm saying. They're
hypocrites in many ways.
Yeah. I don't Let give them a fry. I
don't give a [ __ ] >> [snorts] >> Yeah. I like
I like I like
What I find strange is how any of you
haters on here think that you affect
anyone when the only people that are
being affected is yourself. I've tried
to explain this to uh the disabled
Joseph Ferrar before. I mean like yeah
they're saying things but they have to
sit here and do what they do every day
without failure. Do you not think that
that's maybe me living in their head?
But he's so disabled and and [ __ ]
that he doesn't even understand it. Like
it takes effort. It takes time. It takes
dedication to do what these people do
every day. So really, you're actually
affecting their life. You're actually
[ __ ] with their head. And no matter
how many times you explain it, he
doesn't get it cuz he's [ __ ] disabled.
It's a lot of time, a lot of effort, a
lot of, you know, and maybe they're
they're that disabled, they don't really
understand it, you know. So really,
you're actually getting in these people's heads.
You're actually getting you're actually
getting at them really. So yeah,
and they ain't made me lose nothing.
They've not made me lose anything.
They haven't made me lose
kids or a relationship or they've not
caused any long-term effect for me.
They've called the police on me a few
times. They sent letters, but I was out
my mom's before they even sent letters.
So, these people really haven't done
anything to me. Even when I was back at
the old house, I said, "You can send
letters. No one's moving." So,
they're just idiots on here. I mean,
no, it's not the sight. It's these [ __ ] women.
Yeah, it's these [ __ ] women, bro.
If I didn't go out yesterday, I would
have been fine.
I was forced. So,
I was forced to go out yesterday.
Yeah, Monty's live, bro. Monty's live. >> Yeah.
unsolicited dick pitches.
Calling the police. Boo.
Boo. Grass. Boo.
Boo. Talking about grassing.
What a loser.
Please over YouTube. Boo.
That ruins all the fun, doesn't it?
Grievously the old bill. Boo. Grassing talk.
Grasses. So many grasses on here, bro.
That's why I would never ever fully do
what I I I want to do and and do a video
like with a piss and that
I am going to do it, but I would never
do it on on video. Never. I'd whine and
dash on video. >> Yeah,
>> that's why I would never ever do it.
Never ever do it cuz these glasses on here.
But then they call other people glasses. Mine. [ __ ]
the [ __ ] idiots. Oh yeah. Yeah. Red star. What?
[snorts] Yeah. So, basically what I'm
saying is this Red Star just gone a new
channel. What they do every day, it
shows that you're actually affecting
their life. Well, they don't have a
life, but you're affecting them.
You're actually affecting them.
Shouldn't be on Shouldn't you be on your
boyfriend's channel sucking his dick, Lord J.
You little mong. You people will never
get me in a cell again, mate. I'm too
smart for you little grasses. So yeah,
basically if you see what this guy's
doing, you're actually affecting his
life. For somebody to well affecting him
again, they don't have a life. For
somebody to keep coming on YouTube,
every day they're doing what they do.
You're affecting them.
Screen recording, stalking. It takes time, bro.
This takes time, Joker. I'm affecting them.
I'm affecting them for them to be doing
this. I'm affecting them. >> Yeah,
bro. You people are going to be alone
all Christmas, bro. Yeah.
I am [ __ ] tired, but I'm still hung
over. That alcohol still in me. It's
[ __ ] horrible, Grezy. Horrible. [snorts]
It's horrible, bro. No, there's no starting fresh.
[ __ ] a lot of you. Isn't that right,
Grezy? You [ __ ] a lot of you.
When I get my revenge on women, I'll be fine.
I still haven't got my revenge yet. Cuz
none of them want to meet me. When I get
my revenge on them, I'll be fine.
Do you know what? I've got a bottle of
Coke in the fridge. I bought it today.
Right. When I finish it,
I'm going to I'm going to piss on it.
first. When I wake up, I'm going to piss
in it and throw it at some [ __ ]
I'm going to throw at someone all the
[ __ ] they've done to me over the years.
Yeah. No, I can't do that one. That's
No, it has to be a Mountain Dew. Small one.
Yeah. Or you could like add piss in
their drink or something. No, but then
you'd have to go on a date. That would
be nice. You could actually like say,
"Oh, get a drink." And then add like add
piss and [ __ ] in it and that. I'm I'm
I'm [ __ ] bro. You don't understand,
man. I'm I'm sick of what they've done
to me over the years.
The ghosting, the leading on, the
attitude, the [ __ ] I want to fight back.
I want to fight back. [snorts]
I'm really wanting to fight back, bro.
Drop me a message. You haven't replied
back. Why haven't you reply back?
So, yeah, I'm definitely getting revenge
cuz of all of the things they've done to
me over the years.
I want revenge.
Like that USA is thing. I weren't going
to stop, bro. I weren't going to stop.
Look at all of the [ __ ] that caused. Yeah. Oh.
What I find strange is none of you have
got any issues of what they've done to me.
Doesn't seem to register in your brain.
Madness. You don't have no problems with
what they've done to me. Mad.
leading on attitude, being [ __ ] being
As soon as you say you're going to throw
a ball, piss on someone, well, yeah.
Yeah. You got no problems with
with them doing what they do. Oh, yeah.
You have no problems them doing what they do.
But then when I say I'm going to do
something is crazy madness.
The sexist world we live in. E
it doesn't matter.
Okay. So if I die in a dash. So if I die
in a dash, you're not going to have a
problem with it. No, I want piss
bottles. I want piss bottles. I like
piss. I like piss bottles.
Nope. I'm focusing on getting on
revenge. I'm focusing on getting getting revenge.
No, I like it nasty.
No, I'm going to do it nasty, bro. I'm
going to do it nasty.
I don't want to focus on I just want to
focus on getting revenge
for all the [ __ ] they've done to me. Oh,
yeah. A mini water gun. That's a good
idea with a bit of piss.
Yeah, that Yeah, water. Water piss.
That's a good idea. Yeah, [ __ ]
They got some lovely a lovely un
unsolicited dick picture. Lovely.
That is funny. That is
That is funny, bro.
Really is funny. Yeah.
I just want revenge on them, bro, really
badly for all the [ __ ] that they've
done. I really want revenge, bro.
They shouldn't be able to live their life.
That's one of the reason why I [ __ ] with
that USA, isn't he?
They shouldn't be allowed to live their life
after all the, you know, [ __ ] that
they've done and that put me through and
that. [ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, that [ __ ] I [ __ ] with her family.
I [ __ ] with her exes. Yeah.
Yeah. I [ __ ] with her badly. Really
She can go. She can [ __ ] off.
She can go get raped. Yeah.
Yeah, she can [ __ ] off and go get raped. [clears throat]
Is that right?
I made a [ __ ] change.
The maid can't change her [ __ ] number. Good. [ __ ] lovely.
She deserves it.
I want to tap into her. She deserves it
for being a [ __ ] She deserves it.
Yeah, she deserves it.
I want it to happen to her. She deserves it.
Yeah, I want to tap into her.
Teach them some teach some manners, you know.
What do you think, Dusty?
These women are not innocent. They're
scum of the earth. What they do to
people. Scum of the earth.
It's coming a [ __ ] earth [snorts]
bad experiences with them. That's the
way you would think. If you've had bad
experiences, that is the way you would
think. That's the right way to think.
Yeah, that's the right way to think.
No, it's not normal. No, it's not
normal. They do the [ __ ] that they do on
purpose. No, it's not normal.
No, it's not normal. People don't just
change their mind like that. No, they do not.
No, it's not.
It's not normal. They do what they do on purpose.
[ __ ] off, bro. I'm getting revenge on
them. I [snorts] don't care what anybody says.
I really couldn't give a [ __ ]
I've already told you how I'm going to get revenge.
It's not normal. People don't change
their mind in a matter of an hour or two
hours whether they meet someone or not.
They do what they do on purpose. They
don't they don't it is done on purpose.
The [ __ ] they do.
Yeah, I just had to say to one, stop
being an ignoring [ __ ] Yeah,
stop being an ignoring [ __ ]
It's the truth, isn't it?
Nah, bro. Nah.
I want to send this one my dick as well. One second. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. Yeah, they don't change their
mind. Don't make excuses for the [ __ ]
Joker. Don't make excuses for the [ __ ]
Yeah, that's one thing you shouldn't do.
Don't make excuses for the [ __ ] lad.
Yeah. They don't make excuses for the [ __ ] man.
Yeah. Don't make excuses for them little [ __ ] Yep.
[ __ ] life, bro. You're born alone, you
die. You're born alone, you get bad
experiences, you die. It's important. Yeah.
Went out approaching women yesterday.
Ben, same old story,
same old sad song. Just was sending them
my dick pictures and [ __ ] I'm looking
to get revenge now.
I'm really wanting to get revenge on
these women now. The dick pictures, the
dick pick is just the start of it. I
want to give them back what they've
given me over the years. The leading on,
the [ __ ] the ignoring, the
attitude, the false hope. I want to I
want to give them back something, bro. Really?
So, I think I'm going to throw a piss
ball at him, bro.
getting revenge on these women for all
the [ __ ] they've done to me over the years.
And them getting raped as well. That'd be nice.
Not by me, though.
Yes, I have had that before. Yeah, when
I was younger.
No, I won't. And if they will get raped,
I'll be happy as well. They deserve it.
They're [ __ ] They're [ __ ]
But yeah, I have had um I have had that. Yeah,
they do deserve that. They're [ __ ]
They're scum of the earth.
They do deserve that. They're scum.
They're the scum of the earth. They do deserve that.
So yeah, no symphony for me.
Uh so yeah, I have had that sleep thing.
Yeah, when I was younger.
Yeah, I did. I used to get Yeah. years
ago. Why? I don't get it anymore.
I don't get anxiety anymore.
But yeah, I did used to get it.
It's not going to happen though.
Yeah, but they do deserve it, Tiny Tim.
After all the [ __ ] they've done to me in
the past, their attitude, the [ __ ]
keeping you sexless, keeping you single,
leading you on, making up rumors about
you. They do deserve every all the bad things.
I ship all the bad things that happened
to them. I love it, you know. So, yeah,
I just sent a load of them my dick.
unsolicited dick pictures.
I don't give a [ __ ]
I really don't give a [ __ ]
This is why I didn't want to go out yesterday.
Just numbers that I approached.
Just numbers I approached.
Yeah, it is getting worse. And it
shouldn't be getting worse. I shouldn't
still be having this problem with women.
I shouldn't still be in this position.
I shouldn't still be having the same
thing. When I went to get this roast
dinner today and I gambled, even though
I didn't lose any money in the end, I
got my money. I took the money out and
I'm thinking, bro, we're going around in
circles, man. What the [ __ ] We're still
doing this [ __ ]
You know what the [ __ ] You know, this
the same [ __ ] go out, get bad
experiences with women, hung over, get
food, feel like gambling. I almost fell
into the same cycle again. This is what
I'm saying, bro. It's the same [ __ ]
This is why I didn't want to go out yesterday. yesterday, bro.
Uh, I didn't do my sacking. I've
literally just told you I didn't lose
any money gambling. Open your ears. Open
And it is a cycle. Okay, I'll give an
example in this country. Go out, try to
meet women, get bad experiences, wake up
hung over, hungry, go get some food,
want to gamble, then you'll lose money,
then you'll be more depressed, and it
just goes round and round in circles
until you leave. It will always go
around in circles. And I am not going in
that cycle again.
I am not going in that cycle again, bro.
If I lost that £50 today, I would have
went straight back home and it took me
ages to get there. So, I just took the 50 out.
I don't gamble. This was my first time in months.
No, this was my first time in months.
Yeah, it was my first time in months.
Yeah, it was my first time in months,
bro. I don't. So, yeah.
So you're always going to go round in circles.
You'll always go around in circles.
You'll try with women, get bad
experiences, be depressed the next day,
gamble, whatever it goes around or want
to gamble, where years ago.
It never it don't help you when you lose.
That's why I was thinking of suicide. I
generally think the only way out is
suicide, bro. I think this is the only
way these bad experiences are going to
stop is killing yourself.
So that's why I don't I'm not scared of
dying in my sleep, bro. I want to die in
my sleep. It's depressing this life. I'm
still dealing with this at 28 years of
age with these women, these bad
experiences at 28 years of age. It's depressing, bro. No,
I shouldn't still be dealing with this
at 28 years of age, Ben. I shouldn't
still be going I shouldn't still be Yeah.
We shouldn't be going through these exper
I shouldn't still be having these
experiences, bro. We've done this a
million times. We shouldn't still be doing this.
No, I don't kill myself. I'm just I just
give up my life. I didn't want to go out
yesterday, but I got forced to, Ben. I
got forced to go out.
I would have calmed down by now if I
didn't go out yesterday.
>> I said to my mom, "Let me go. I don't
want to go out with my sister. It's the
same bad experiences with women. And
then we had an argument. Uh then we had
Oh, okay. The hangovers get to me now.
We have and I said, I don't want to go.
I don't want any more bad experiences
with women. Then my mom uh then the my
sister's friend come out and I had to go out.
I had to go out, bro. I literally had to
because her friend come around and we
all went out together.
So I was cuz I was going to let someone
down. I was going to let someone down
again for the third time.
The third time, bro. They were getting
sick of it. This is how bad it's
getting, bro. It just gets worse and
worse and worse. You know,
well, obviously you want a sex life,
don't you? Why you why you you should be
with someone? This is what I was saying
to my Italian friend. He said, "Oh, but
it doesn't know it doesn't m know how it
doesn't matter how much you try. They
have the final uh word.
They have Yeah, true. But you shouldn't
still be trying. You shouldn't have to
go out and try again. You've already tried enough."
You know what I'm saying, Ben? You
shouldn't have to keep trying and
getting more bad bad experiences, you know?
Yeah, I'll probably stay in bed tomorrow
to be honest, but [ __ ] this. I was going
to go cinema, but no, [ __ ] this. I'm
going to stay in bed. I think me thinks [snorts] Yeah,
I don't care about nonslegs. I don't
care about other people. Stop comparing
me to strangers. I don't care about other people.
I don't compare myself to strangers. It
don't change my situation.
Stop comparing me.
You don't compare myself to richer
people than me. You don't compare myself
to better people than me. So don't
compare about don't compare me to people
that have got girlfriends. You wouldn't
compare me to someone that's richer.
This is what contradicts itself, right?
You always say, "Don't compare yourself
to other people. Don't compare yourself
to other people. Don't worry about other
people. Don't compare yourself to rich
people. Worry about what you have." But
then they just [ __ ] compare you to
[ __ ] strangers with girlfriends. It
doesn't make any sense. So, can we
compare ourselves or not?
You will never get compared to anyone
else unless it's the dating game.
They literally strictly say, "Don't
compare yourself to other people."
[ __ ] off, man. [ __ ] madness.
I do really want revenge on women
though, bro. I really, really do.
That is mad. I like the cold.
>> That's what nonslegs kept saying when he
first stayed back in college.
And they're like, "Oh, we'll leave we'll
leave him alone. We'll leave him alone. I copy cat."
Well, my picture is a copycat.
He followed me out the balcony. Copycat.
I can't get over that. Why people copy
copy the crowd?
Nah, I don't have autism, matey.
I think these white knights have got autism, though,
because I don't understand where the
passion and the desire comes from to
defend women all your life.
I would love somebody to explain that to
me one day. Why these people sit there
and defend women the way they do?
where that passion and desire comes from.
I shall never know, but I don't think
we'll ever know.
So, we move on. Sh. I show up again.
Copycat with no mind of your own.
>> Copycat with no mind of your own.
You little copycat.
I'm a little copycat.
>> You're under arrest for suspicion of
being a copycat.
You're under arrest
for suspicion of being a little copycat.
Guilty or not guilty, Greavves?
Are you guilty or not guilty
of being a little copycat? Hm. >> Huh?
>> Are you guilty or not guilty? [snorts]
>> Following the crowd,
you little cat.
My name's not. Another little coffee can.
Yep. I'm not greasy.
My name's not greasy.
I'm not greasy.
I'm a little copycat.
>> No, I'm not focusing on other things.
They need to pay for leaving me single
and sexless and leading me on. I'm not
focusing on other things.
No, I'm focusing on other things. These
women need to pay off.
>> These [ __ ] women need to pay.
What do you mean no one knows? I've
already done madnesses on women, bro.
What are you talking about? Everyone
knows that. You people don't know anything.
You think you know [ __ ] but you don't
know anything. I just sent them my dick,
bro. I've been trying to find a dial and
dash for the past week. I've been trying
to get somebody to meet me. I've been
trying to bribe people to meet me for
the past week. So, what do you really
know, bro? What do you really know? Come
on. What do you really know? You say
everyone knows, but what do you know,
bro? You don't know anything. I've been
trying for the past week to get somebody
to meet me. They won't they won't do it.
I said I'll come to a state house. I'll
come to I've been trying my hardest, you
know, even with tenants and [ __ ] So,
bro, you really don't know anything. You
really, really don't know anything. You know, [snorts]
I'm a little copycat.
Yeah. So, what do you really So, what do
you really know, bro? What do you really
know? What do you really know?
H Come on. Like that one I had going on
a wild goose chase. Why did I make her go everywhere?
Why did I make her go everywhere? Cuz
she wouldn't meet me, bro. And go to the
restaurant. So what do you really know,
Joker? What do you really know?
How is it going to send me down? What?
Dining and dash someone.
>> Yeah, I don't think I'm going to get
sent down for dining and dashing
someone, you know? Yeah.
You're not going to go to [ __ ] prison
for [ __ ] diamond and dancing someone,
you silly goose.
I'm a little copycat.
I just ate all the sugar. Greasy.
My name's O Grey. I'm a little copycat. Oh yep.
You virgin [ __ ]
So anyways, yeah,
thanks for the free thumbs up by the Yep.
What did you just say? Did you just say
women are racist? Incel.
Don't say anything bad about women, Ben.
Don't say anything bad about women.
Do not say anything bad about women, you incel.
Women are angels. Do you know that?
Oh, you know, Reddit's being copycats.
They're trying to make people prove
their age. They're trying to make Yeah.
people prove their age, right?
They're trying to be a copycat. You
know, like the police thing, uh the
police thing, sorry, the um the porn
thing where you got to verify your age.
Now they're trying to make you verify
your age to go on stuff. They're being a little copycat.
Greasy. They're trying to copy.
Reddit's trying to copy. Have you seen it?
Greeny doesn't troll me.
Yeah, doesn't control me.
It won't. No, they're not interested
either. There's Turkish women here.
There's Greek women here. They're not
interested that are actually from there.
They were actually born. No, they're not
interested. I've met Greek women, Greek
uh Turkish women.
Yeah. Here that are actually from there
that actually was born there. And no,
they're not interested.
No matter where you go, mate. Finland,
Australia, America, Greek. They're [ __ ] everywhere.
There's Greek women here. They're not interested.
No one's interested. Yep. It's London,
bro. People come from all over.
Greek, Turkish, Albanian.
I've met them all, bro.
Obviously, I live in London, man. What
the [ __ ] They're not interested. They
want to leave you alone and sexless. They're evil.
And they don't they don't only do that.
They do a lot of stuff. They lead people
on. They give attitude. They act like [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. There's loads of people in London,
bro. You should know this. They're not
interested in this country.
Like what Ant-Man said.
So yeah, serious. I am serious.
I'm not going to lie, am I? So yeah,
depressing life ain't it, Ben? When you
think about it,
it is a depressing life, lad.
Never change. It will never change.
Never change, bro.
I don't know why that person didn't
reply me back. They said, "Take my
number. Drop me a message." They didn't
even reply back.
They didn't even reply back then.
I'm not enjoying it. I think it's [ __ ] depressing.
I don't know how you can enjoy it. I
think it's depressing.
It's really depressing.
Like you're going to have to be alone
for the rest of your life without sex. I
think it's pretty depressing me.
I think it's very very depressing.
There's no reason for it either, Ben.
You're not disabled. You're not blind.
You're not fat. You're not ugly. There's
literally no reason for it. There's
none. It's not like you've not tried.
There's no reason for it.
So, I don't know how you can enjoy it.
It's depressing. It's [ __ ] depressing, bro.
It's [ __ ] really depressing.
I think it's very depressing.
I was supposed to go out with my sister
yesterday, bro. Uh, sorry. I was going
to go I went out with my sister
yesterday, but I wasn't going to go out.
I changed my mind then, but I I kind of
got forced into going, bro.
I just wanted to stay in bed yesterday,
bro, and be depressed and give up.
But yeah, I had to go basically. So,
it's sad, bro. Now I got the same experiences again.
Oh, that one from Spain blocked me. I
sent her my dick, but she's blocked me
before I could send it.
See, there's no hope here, bro. There's no hope.
Even though people tell you there's
hope, there's no hope.
There's no hope here, bro. No hope.
Send this one my dick.
Yeah. You'll never be I'll never be
happy here, bro. I'll never be happy in this country.
Never be happy here, man.
So yeah, that's hurting it.
I'm [ __ ] hung over, bro.
I should have to be trying again, Ben. I
should have to be trying again.
I should have already met someone by
now. I should have a sex life.
Do you understand? I should have to be trying again.
I shouldn't even have to think about
going out and approaching a woman again.
There's I shouldn't have to talk to
anyone. I shouldn't have to do nothing.
I've tried I've done I've already done
put enough effort into it more than
anyone in the world. So, do you see my problem? yeah.
So I shouldn't have to be going out trying again.
People tell me, "Oh, you have to keep
trying. You have to keep trying." Why do
you have to keep trying?
No one's interested in this country.
So why why do you need to keep trying, bro?
[ __ ] My eyes are killing me, bro.
That white rum really has its effect, doesn't it? So Yeah,
>> I'll be in bed again alone. Depressed.
[ __ ] this life, bro. It's so depressing, man.
Is it? It's so [ __ ] depressing,
mate. I don't have time on my side. It's over.
I don't have time, Mom. I go to bed at
like 7:00 in the morning.
Life's not great. Life's depressing, bro.
I can't wait to die. It's depressing.
No, I'm not going to cinema tomorrow.
I'm staying in bed all day depressed.
No, I'm not doing nothing tomorrow. I
was going to, but
I'll be depressed
waiting to die.
No, I'll be depressed. I think I'll just
end up killing myself eventually, bro.
This is depressing, bro. The bad
experiences with women you got to think
about every day. [ __ ] that. I'll
probably just end up killing myself. I
ain't got no regrets, bro. I live my
life. I done what I've wanted to do. So,
I don't need happy pills.
I don't need happy pills. There's a
legitimate reason why I'm the way I am.
There's a legitimate reason why I'm the
way I am. I don't need pills.
I look 40. No, I don't look 40. No, I
[ __ ] don't. Anyways, uh I don't need
pills cuz there's a reason for it.
So there's not a no reason for it.
There's a reason for it. The bad
experiences with women, you don't need
happy pills. You need better experiences.
The doctor's not going to give you
better experiences, is he?
Yeah. You'll feel happy when you get
better experiences with women.
But that's never going to happen. So,
it's always going to be the same old
Well, I'm never going to go bored. So,
that's never going to happen.
That's never going to happen
cuz I'm never going to go bored. [laughter]
And [snorts] what's bored got to do with
anything? Why are you mentioning being bored?
If someone's bored, they're bored.
What's that got to do with finding life
hard? You [ __ ] silly goose.
Yeah, but I'm not going to end up bored. So,
doesn't matter anyways, does it? Who cares? So, yeah.
Yeah, it's the bad experiences with
women, bro. It's enough to put anyone
down and age them. It's enough to put
any [ __ ] down.
Oh yeah, but we know it's self
projection on here.
Well, yeah, there self projectors on
here. You know that? I know that. So, yeah.
Yeah. AIDS. That's all the bad
experiences with women.
Enough to make anyone depressed. >> [sighs]
>> So yeah.
No, I don't look fy, you idiot. I asked
people multiple times. I'm not using
hookers. I'm not using hookers.
I'm not using it cuz I don't need to use
it. I don't look 40, mate. I ask people
all the time how old do I look and they
say my age. So how are you telling me
that I look 40, bro? I ask people all
the time, how old do you think I am?
They say 23, 28.
You know, no one's ever told me I look 40, bro.
I don't look 40, you [ __ ] idiot. 40?
Do you know what 40 you are, man? was like,
"Stop the cap, bro." Because I shouldn't
have to use escorts, Ben.
I shouldn't have to use escorts.
There's no reason. I'm not old. I'm not
shy to talk to people. There's not
really no reason. But technically,
that's the There's only three ways it
will end, Ben. You either use escorts,
you go to Thailand, or you join the porn
industry. That that's the only way it's
ever going to end.
That's the only way this will ever end.
So you got three you got three options.
You either stay here all your life and
use escorts but you'll feel like you're
missing out anyways. You can either join
the porn industry or try to join the
porn industry or you leave the country.
What else? What else could you What else
can you do, bro?
Keep trying and think that one day
you're going to meet a woman that's
different. But me and you both know that
ain't going to happen.
There's no other option.
There really do not know how bad it is,
bro. It's It should not be this way.
I haven't had a date. And this is how
you know you're not going to find someone.
This is how you know you're not going to
find someone, Ben. Yeah. Because look at
You don't come on here much. I haven't
come on here. I haven't had a date since
March. I had three dates this month uh
this year and they were all in March or
maybe two was in March, one was in
April. I've not had a date since April.
So, the chances are you're going to find
someone is extremely slim because if you
can't even get a date when most states
don't even go anywhere anyways. You're
not just going to find randomly find
someone. It's not going to happen. It's
not possible, lad.
Yeah, you're talking about yourself,
bro. No one cares about you, bomb.
You're self projecting.
I think it was either March or April,
bro. No one cares about you, self
projector. That didn't turn up today.
No one cares about you, self projector.
Get put in timeout. Anyways, [snorts]
back to you, Ben. Um,
uh, yeah, it is April. Yeah. And there
was times where I spent like I went out
on a Friday, come out the Sunday and I'd
be spending £600.
Now I don't I don't I can't afford to be
spending £600 anymore. And I don't even
think it matters whether you can or you
can't. I think that the principle is
there's been times, bro, where I I I had
like £1,000. I'd go out and I'd be down
to like £400. I'm thinking, "What? Where
the [ __ ] did that money go?" No date, no
sex, no nothing.
this depression for two days afterwards.
It was March.
Yeah, I know. That's what I'm trying to
say to you. Now you don't get nothing.
That's exactly what I'm trying to say to
you. Now you don't get anything.
That's what I'm saying to you.
You get nothing now.
Nothing. No dates, no kisses, nothing.
That's how you know you're never going
to meet no one
cuz of how it's like now, bro. That's
how you know
I can tell you that year that I met I
met USA Izzy I met I was so bro I had so
many dates I had a couple of one night
stands I had kisses now
you get nothing
you don't get anything bad bro
you get numbers that lead you on if you're lucky
But yeah, it is that bad. It really is Yeah.
You used to be able to get dates and now
you get nothing.
And the amount of money you have to
spend and the time as well, it's not
good, bro. It's not good.
Yeah. Two years. Two and a half years.
Last year was good as well.
Yeah. 2 and a half years was good as uh
last year was okay as well. Now I can't get nothing.
So you're not just going to meet someone.
I I went out uh Ben last month. It took
me 50 approaches to get one number
sober. They had attitude problems.
They had attitude problems. They were
stuck up. Make believe boyfriends. It
was sober, not in a club. And I'm
thinking, what? And you still have
people telling you that you're going to meet someone.
I went out yesterday. This woman's like,
"Oh, drop me a message." Didn't even reply.
What's the [ __ ] point of it, bro?
Yeah, I was in my local area uh
yesterday, Ben, and it was no different.
They same boyfriend [ __ ] It was giving
me a headache, bro. I was actually out
the I weren't in central London. So
yeah, you just get bad experiences time
and time again.
That's all you get. Yeah.
So that's that.
And it annoys me, bro, when I go on my
phone and I see all of these numbers and
I'm thinking, bro, you got all these
numbers. You don't need to go out and
try again. One of these should be
meeting you. You should have to [ __ ] try again. You know,
you should have to, you know, try again and that So, but Yeah.
But yeah, hookers are your only way in this country.
Bad, isn't it? Very bad.
Yeah, I had like 1,700 pound last month,
but I spent some money, bro.
I spent on jeans. I bought some jeans and trainers.
So, I spent a bit. I just save up again.
Yeah, like I said, I might go out next
week cuz I had my hair done. I don't
know what I'm doing.
Don't know what I'm doing, bro.
It's very depressing.
Very depressing life. I was watching
porn yesterday. It was very depressing.
Yeah. He lives in Thailand. He teaches English.
Yeah. It's really bad, bro. Oh, [ __ ] >> [snorts]
>> I'm all scared of flying.
I spent £44 today on a roast dinner.
It was £44, lad. No, it wasn't. It was
mad, but I already ate it, so I had to
pay it. I went to this place that I
normally go to yet. It's not I was
expecting like £31, £32,
society being what it is. He said it was
£44. I was like, "No way." I hadn't been
there for a year. I know the people in
there and that like used to go there all
the time. It was out of London and I was
like, "Nah, it can't be £44."
But obviously I already ate it. I was
like, "What the fuck?"
That's more expensive than the Indian
restaurants I go to. Never again, bro,
for a bit of chicken, pork, and beef.
There weren't even any lamb.
I didn't have a good day with the
gambling. I don't care that I didn't
lose the 50. Just the gambling was annoying.
Yeah, they're doing that now. They're
doing the extra service charge. That's
what it is.
That's what they're doing now. I was
like, so I won't be there again. You can
get a whole leg of lamb for 40 [ __ ] quid.
You can go to the butchers and get a leg
of lamb for 40.
So, I won't be going there again. That's mad.
Yep. I can't eat a 30 lb t-bone. I can
have a 20 one.
Yeah, I can have a 20 pound T-bone, but
not 30, bro. What the [ __ ]
You mad bastard. Yeah.
Yeah, you do. Yeah.
Do you think you can live off £1,200 a month?
Disposable money, Joe. Can you can it
£1,200 a month? Joe says that you can't.
Yeah, you can. £1,200 a month.
Disposable money. Of course, you can
live with that. Yeah,
that that Joseph Ferrar is an idiot,
bro. He doesn't know nothing.
Yeah, he's an idiot, bro.
It's [ __ ] though. I used to get three
grand a month.
No, I don't sub at the house. That's
[ __ ] bro. I still have money though. I
still can do what I want. Is it is a bit [ __ ]
It is a bit [ __ ] though.
That is a bit [ __ ] But yeah,
is what it is. E
I don't know what I would have done,
bro, without like that house for like 3
4 years, bro. Cuz obviously I was in my
prime, you know? So
I don't know what I don't know what I
would have done, bro. I probably would
have ended up dead or something or
pulling a lot of [ __ ] in because I
wouldn't been able to afford to do what
I wanted to do
cuz okay let's say okay what did I used
to do before that I still gambled on her
house but I was never scared what do you
used to do you gamble yeah so what if
you lost all your money you're [ __ ]
for a month then the women problem would
be even worseer when you'd have to worry
about money you'd be [ __ ] bro
at least I'm [ __ ] 28 and [ __ ]
don't go out anyways yeah He would have been [ __ ]
Yeah, that's when I had the house, bro.
I don't I can gamble. I can afford to
gamble. I just don't want to do it. I
just like win football bets and just put
the money away and [ __ ]
Bit harder now, but is what it is, isn't it?
I I Yeah,
I miss the houses in the house and the
area. The money is just whatever, you
know. But yeah.
Yeah. The last time I played roulette,
except from today, I won 550 from 100
and I just took it.
couldn't uh Yeah. Golden bet. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I know, bro.
I don't think it was just the house
where I had loads of money. I think it's
cuz I won from gambling as well.
Obviously, it was the wins as well.
it was obviously the wins as well. But
Yeah, like me. I I bought I had 1,700 pound
last month. Don't ask me how I got it.
It was [ __ ] hard. But I found my ways
and I bought a pair of vapors and a pair
of jeans. Cost me over £400. I can't
wear cheap jeans.
I can't wear cheap jeans, bro.
But most of my money used to go on prostitutes, you know,
I used to spend on escorts, gambling, [ __ ]
clothes, the [ __ ] lot, bro. Yeah.
But now if I if I get back to it again,
like 1,800 pound, I'll be laughing, bro.
And you won't need something. If you
don't need something then Well, I always
need something when I have money. So
that's the thing. Yeah,
I spend a lot of my money on escorts,
prostitutes, traveling, hotels, [ __ ] like that. So
yeah, that golden bet. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
>> Yeah, it was good, wasn't it?
I was on USA's Instagram, Ben,
yesterday. She still got them big titties.
[ __ ] scumbag, [ __ ] [ __ ]
But the gambling industry is finished now. [snorts]
No, it wasn't. No, it wasn't.
You can live off £1,200 a month with no bills. Yeah. Pretty
easy. 11,200. Yeah.
Good old golden Nope. Not gambling.
No. No thanks.
Not after today. Lucky I got that. Lucky
I took the 50 out.
Should have. would have and I wasn't
getting over 3K. I was getting 3K. Why
would I stack it, bro?
When I was banging escorts, going on
dates, traveling, wearing designer
clothes. Why am I going to stack it?
What for like 3 years?
Stack it for three years and say, "Yeah,
look, I've got £100,000 with no life
experiences." Why am I Why would I do that, bro? That's ridiculous.
What is it? Well, how much is it?
I think it's 90 something,000
and say, "Oh yeah, I got 90
something,000. No life experiences, no
dates, no designer clothes, no
traveling." Why? Why would I do that?
That's [ __ ] what Red Star does.
That's what these That's what these
people on here do.
Why the [ __ ] would I do that, bro?
at 23 24 years of age.
That's [ __ ] ridiculous, man.
And I wasn't getting over 3K a month. I
think it was 2.8. Not that it matters anyways.
Yeah. [clears throat] So what?
No, they didn't stop it. YouTube didn't
stop it. I'm not getting into this
again. YouTube did not stop it, Joker.
And I'm not getting into it again.
I've already been with women,
Joker. YouTube didn't stop my income.
And I'm not getting into this again with
you. I've explained this many, many
times again. So if you want to think
that, think that. We're not going into
this conversation again.
Same old boring conversation. I've
explained it about 10 times. Yeah, just
like I use colana.
Just like this and that. I'm not
explaining it to you again. If I've
explained something to you more than two
times, if you want to keep making up
stuff, you can keep making up stuff.
If someone stopped my income, somebody
would be getting killed. Yeah. And I'm
not I'm not I'm not talking about this
no more. Simple. Yeah. If any of these
clowns stopped it, I'd kill I'd kill one
of them, bro. Look what I'd done to
nonslegs over £180 a month. Made a [ __ ]
[ __ ] scared to leave his house. Yeah. No
one would have ever stopped my income.
Not even a 10. Not even£10 of it, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. You understand?
It's not about being about something or
not being about something. Anyone would
be the same.
I said, "These people called me up and
said, "Oh, yeah, we've had complaints
and I I don't give a [ __ ] about 180, 200 pound."
They didn't stop it. These trolls didn't
stop it. If they stopped it, bro, if
they stopped it, why why did I have the
house for three and a half years? They
didn't stop it. If they stopped it, I
wouldn't have had that house for three
and a half years. They definitely
definitely did not stop it. They never
stopped any money of mine. And any money
they did try, I got all the money back.
Yeah, bro. Exactly. And they never
stopped it because it would have took
three and a half years. Everyone knew
where I lived. Everyone knew I was
subleting. So what? It took three and a
half, four years for them to stop it.
They can't get involved with a court
case. They did not stop it. They 100%
did not stop that money. Right. The
landlord was trying to get it back for
years and years and years and years and
years. Yeah. Before anyone on YouTube,
before anyone on YouTube, Before anyone
on YouTube, Before anyone on YouTube, I
don't need a hair transplant. I'm not
you. Before anyone on YouTube knew about
it, I had them coming on the door,
sending letters. It was nothing to do with YouTube.
So, yeah, you definitely definitely
didn't stop my income because one of you
would have been getting killed. And I
can prove that with the nonsex thing as well.
You 100% did not stop my money. The only
reason you're saying that is cuz I told
everyone what happened, right? And you
reported me. You didn't stop my money.
People on YouTube can't stop your money. Yeah.
So yeah, you definitely definitely did
not stop any of my income, mate. Cuz I
tell you what, it took you [ __ ] four
years to stop it, didn't it? It took you four years
banging prostitutes, spending money, you
know. Took you [ __ ] years then,
didn't it? If it [ __ ] if you stop
that money. What? Four years. It took
you four years.
It took you four years, bro.
Four years. Four years. Really? Four
years. Three and a half. Four years.
Three and a half years. Three and a half
years. It was three and a half years,
not four years. So, it took you three
and a half years to stop somebody's money.
You didn't stop my money, bro.
Never stop my money. Just like you're
saying that I use colada in it. Just
like I pay off all my things in it.
Yeah. You keep telling yourself that.
You wish, bro. You [ __ ] wish. So, yeah.
And bro, do you know what? Even if you
did stop the money, which you definitely
definitely didn't, I was living. I got
three and a I got three grand
for [ __ ] three years and a half
[ __ ] women traveling laughing to
work. So you really think if you stopped
it? I'd be like, "Thanks for the good
life." That's what I'd be like. I'd be
like, "Thanks for the good life." But
you didn't stop it. You absolutely did
not stop it. Because if you did, I would
admit it and I'd be calling out every I
would probably go for someone that I
know would meet me like Prime or I'd go
for somebody that I knew would meet me.
Definitely. Definitely didn't. You have
no You've done nothing. I've got no
long-term effects from these people on
YouTube. I've got no long-term effects.
I've already explained it to you and I'm
not explaining it again. Keep thinking
that you stop my money. You keep telling
me that I live I use huge use kana bro.
Just keep doing it. It's fine. You
clearly know everything when people
explain things to you multiple times and
it's none of your business anyways to be
honest with you. It's none of your
business. So at the end of the day if
it's been explained to you, right? Yeah.
Yeah. Exactly. You obviously know more
about people's lives than they know
about their own lives.
So at the end of the day, it's none of
your business. So, if you didn't catch
on the three times it was explained,
that's your problem.
Worry about your money. Worry about how
much you get.
Cuz you know the thing is, right? Yeah.
Who's going to be out next week drinking
having fun? I am. No one on here is.
You know, I could get £500 a month. I
could get 10 grand a month. Just, you
know, I'm I'm the one that's going to be out
drinking. I'm the one that's going to be
out at a restaurant next. Not a user.
£500 a month, 10 grand a 10 grand a
month. Does it does it really matter, you know,
and that's that, bro? You didn't you
didn't stop anyone's money. And why why
are you so concerned anyways, you know? So, yeah.
idiot talking like the landlord. Again,
I'm not explaining it anymore. Anyways,
that's your problem. If you didn't hear
it three times, that's your problem. The
only reason Red Star is saying that,
he's saying that because I told the
story and he's saying that he's done it.
It's for reaction and you're not getting
a reaction. If you if you don't know how
it stopped, that's your problem, bro.
You want to think I pay off for my
jeans, that's your problem, bro. You
want to say I'm skinn, that's your problem, bro. You know,
let me tell you something. I've not
lived on 1.2K for about 4 months.
Been more like two grand for the past
couple months. It's been about two grand.
Yeah. About two grand for the past 3, four months. Yeah. So,
no, you're not a hater. You're just talking [ __ ]
You're just talking a load of [ __ ]
Talking a load of [ __ ] bollocks.
Talking a lot a lot of bollocks.
And yeah, no one's going to sit who's
going to sit and stack up 90 grand for
three years. Waste your youth.
This is what makes me laugh, right? It's
like with nonslegs, even though that
wasn't his money, right? This is daddy's
money. But even if it even if it was 13
grand, it's the same with rice. Okay,
let's let's let's take Rice's worth. So
you've had no life experiences for years
and you got 13 grand. I'd rather the life experiences.
I'd rather life I'd rather the life
experiences and have two grand.
Then have£10 in my name.
You don't need to know that. But you
don't need to know how much. How much
money do I have now? You don't know how
much money I have.
How much money do I have right now? You
don't even know that.
So, um, so yeah, I mean, you could save
money, but you're not going to have no life experience.
We can't all be like you people fit, sat
in indoors, [ __ ] can't go out. Who's
going to do that? Who's really going to
do that? I mean, it's okay. It's okay
from January to March,
January to April. Don't get me wrong, if
you want to save for four months, three,
four months during the winter, you can.
But bro, who's really going to sit there
and save for three years just to show
money? I'd I'd rather the better life,
you know? I'd ra I' would rather the better life,
Who's really going to do that, bro? Who
is really really really going to do
that? And I did Stack Buddy for like
three months, but I'm not going to say
for three years.
Oh, look at me. I've got 100 grand, but
I've got no life experience. Not been on
a date. Ain't traveled anywhere. Oh, you know,
it doesn't make sense. You know, who
would do that? Who would really really
do that, bro?
Do you know what I'm saying? Who in
their right mind is going to actually do
that, bro? Reload.
Don't have 1.4 grand. You don't know
what I have. Wrong again.
You don't know what I have. Try again.
Don't have 1.4 grand. Try again.
And you're in your 40s, a little sadder
on YouTube that ain't even got £1,000.
Worry about your own life, self-reflector.
worry about your own life.
You people really are boring on it in
it. You've been doing the same [ __ ] for
years. You've been doing the same shitty
thing for years. Really, aren't you
start uh you did not stop my money and
I'm not getting into it again. If you
stopped my money, it would not take you
3 and 1/2 years to stop someone's money.
No, you reported it to the council when
they were already trying to get the
house back. You did not stop my money.
And you you should know about the
universal credit. Do you remember when
you tried to stop my universal credit
and I had you stop going out your
[ __ ] house? You silly little [ __ ]
You silly little ratfaced little [ __ ]
When you tried stopping £200 and I had
you stop going to your event for 3 weeks
because of me. When I had you run into
the police station because of me. So, we
all know if that kind of income actually
got stopped by you people, somebody
would be paying.
Somebody would be paying. Mate, you and
your boyfriend, if you ever stopped that
kind of money from me, you've already
paid for £200 for [ __ ] sake. I was
like, I'm not going to have this little
ratfaced ugly virgin [ __ ] skint in a bed
sit try and [ __ ] with me. Some little
ratfaced little [ __ ] [ __ ] You know
what I'm saying? I'm not going to have
some [ __ ] ugly rat looking [ __ ] that
can only attract disabled. [ __ ] with me,
you [ __ ] [ __ ] that can only attract
disabled. And you want to talk about me
having my first kiss at 21? Bro, you're
still a virgin?
Oh, you can't listen to me. Okay. Right.
Does somebody want to type what I said
about me stopping him going through
these events when he tried to stop 200 pound?
I love how you little self-reflected are
trying to talk about a 28-year-old when
you don't in your 40s living your worst
life. Is it part of your disability
where you just latch on to other people
but you don't actually look at your own lives?
And yeah, you might have reported it,
but you didn't stop it.
You didn't stop it. You were shook,
scared of the black woman. Yeah. Okay.
That's not what happened. Anyways, we're
talking about you. Stick to the subject.
I went to your area. I put up posters of
you. I made you shaking. No, that's not
what happened. Again, not repeating
myself. If you didn't listen to the two
Mate, I had you running going to the [ __ ] police.
I had you crying to the police screaming
you're not a fighter.
I owned you in your own area. I made you
go to the police about me.
You couldn't handle me. I made One
second. Let me type it to this little
virgin. One second.
again. Self-reflecting fits. 40. One second. Listen. One sec.
There we go.
Bro, you're in your 40s and you got
nothing. No one cares about you self-reflector.
No one cares about you 40y olds. You
40-y old bums that don't even leave the
house. No one cares about you 40y old
bums. No one cares about you 40y old
losers. What you think about people
lives being tragic or whatever, bro?
Like, know what I mean?
No one cares about what you fat, ugly
losers think. You're nothing in life. You're nobodyies.
You're absolute nobodyies. No one cares
about what you think being tragic or
not. You didn't stop offending any
event. Yes, I did.
Yes, I [ __ ] well did. You had to call
the police on me. You had to call the
police. You couldn't handle me, mate.
You called the police on me. Stop it.
You called a One second.
You couldn't handle the Peter belly. You
tried to get me killed. He tried to get
He tried to get me killed. I'm not a
fighter. You [ __ ] virgin prank. Yeah. Remember?
>> He's trying to get me killed. He's
trying to get me killed. I'm not a
fighter. I'm not a fighter. One second.
He's trying to get me killed. I'm not a fighter. Virgin. One second.
Woohoo. He's trying to He's trying to
I'm too much for you. I'm too much for
you and your ugly girlfriend. You can't handle me.
Brav, shut up. You 40-year-old loser.
Get gone bomb. [ __ ] loser.
I bought a fighter. I bought a fighter.
No black woman owned me on the train,
mate. Everyone heard it. You You make up
stuff. What was the one for the bouncer
again? Cuz you was at work, right? Yeah.
Yeah. I love it, bro.
Yeah. What was the bouncer one then? And
he was at work, wasn't he? Was the
excuse for that one?
What was the excuse when I was at your area?
Of course you called the police on me.
I bully you and your ugly girlfriend. I
can't be stopped.
Of course you do. You can't handle me.
You and your ugly skinned girlfriend.
You know what I'm saying? Ah,
you know, bro, you I stopped you going
to your events for 3 weeks. I stopped
you leaving your house. I had you
running to the police over me. You silly
[ __ ] You silly virgin [ __ ] [ __ ] other people.
You know, you virgin.
You [ __ ] absolute virgin. Virgin boy.
skin in his little bed [ __ ] with nothing
in it. You in your little council [ __ ]
I bet you love to live with your mom.
Oh, your mom don't want you. She starved
She starved you.
Your mom starved you. You little [ __ ]
You little [ __ ] That's why your
metalism is so [ __ ] up. Of course you
called it old Bill cuz you can't handle
me. I bully you too much. You little
[ __ ] gay lord. You little gay virgin.
Of course you call the police on me cuz
I own you. I destroy you and your ugly
girlfriend. The only thing you can do is
call the police. Cuz when you get your
ass a good whooping, ugly boy. Ugly rat
boy. You know when you get your ass a
good whooping, you have to go to the
police station. You know when you get
your ass a good whooping what to do,
son. When I gave your ass a good old
whapon when I stopped you going to events,
you had to go to the police
cuz I destroyed you. I gave your ass a
good weapon. [ __ ] the woman on the
train. I I owned you and I made you go
to the police
screaming that you're not a fighter. You
absolute virgin. Bro, I would actually
love to meet you and tell you how much
of a virgin you are to your face. All
them times you used to project that
virginity onto me. I'll be like, "You're
the virgin. You're the virgin. You skin
[ __ ] You didn't [ __ ] Aisha.
You do not [ __ ] Aisha. You didn't [ __ ]
nothing. You [ __ ] virgin. Just like
when them [ __ ] black people was
throwing [ __ ] water at you.
They don't want to see some [ __ ]
virgin walking around Stratford. They
can spot the virgin. Why do you think
every single time I say let's go out
drinking? Let's go out drinking, the
manager says it's a no virgin zone, no
virgins. No virgins.
No virgins. They don't allow virgins
like you. They don't want some [ __ ]
lanky ratfaced looking virgin [ __ ]
walking into somewhere.
You know what I mean, mate? Imagine some
[ __ ] Kent virgin, some skin [ __ ]
walking into your [ __ ] premises,
mate. You absolute virgin.
And then you say, "Oh, I dress like that
because I don't I I've got a unique
sense of style.
Oh, I'm unique. I'm [ __ ] unique.
I'm unique." See, he bans me because he
knows the truth.
One sec. One second. Let me type.
There we go.
[ __ ] virgin typing [ __ ] but he's not
letting anyone say anything back. [ __ ] virgin.
You know what? I should screenshot this.
Why am I not screenshotting this? One sec. Yeah.
One second. But I need to screenshot this.
I don't know why I'm not screenshotting
these things. lad.
My little evidence pack. That'll be
166 things I've got now. My little evidence pack.
My little evidence pack. You like that,
Grezy? My little evidence pack. This
court is going to be so lush.
Grezy, do you want to come to the court?
You should come to the court. My little
evidence. You should come to the court, mate.
You should come to the court if you want.
Do you want to come to the court?
Where is this evidence? Oh, it's
harassment. Yeah, it's called it's a
it's a it's called it's a it's a file called harassment.
Getting a [ __ ] from that ugly [ __ ]
That ugly disabled [ __ ]
[ __ ] that. No, thank you.
Still no reply.
This person got the same attitude.
I'm speaking to someone on Instagram.
They've all got the same attitude.
That all women aren't the same. Yeah, right.
Yeah, I screenshotted it, by the way,
and I put it on my little evidence evidence pack.
the [ __ ] I want. Yeah.
>> [clears throat]
>> That terrible co thing is so copying.
>> Yeah, I'm going to [ __ ] with these
women, bro. Really bad. You know,
[ __ ] virgin. Yeah, but do you know
why he he called the police? Cuz he got
he he got his ass a good whoop. Uh he
got his ass a good whooping.
He had to call the police cuz he got his
ass a good whooping. Leave him alone. Triple H. Uh yeah,
he got his ass a good whooping. How does
it feel red that I was subleting and
getting more money than you? [ __ ]
[ __ ] having a better life. Woo. And
you still didn't stop my money. And it
wasn't even you that stopped it. It's
like a million people reporting someone
to the police. How many times are they
going to get nicked once?
You ain't stopped by, buddy. and I had a
better life than you, which I'm happy about.
These people, do you know what? I don't
understand these people in here,
honestly. All jokes aside, how they can
be jealous with people that they don't even know.
Do you not find it strange like year in
year out? Yeah.
that they can be generous with pe of
people that they don't even know,
never met, don't know how they can sit
on the internet. See, this is what I'm
trying to say. Like, I don't think you
understand the severity of it when
someone's when someone's saying it to
you because I don't know, your brain
just don't work properly. Do you not
understand how how mad it actually is?
I don't think you understand it like a
normal person. That's why you sit there
and say, "Oh, they do it for a reaction
and stuff." I don't think you understand it, bro.
Sitting and recording. They ain't got a
life. They ain't got no money. When you
think about what you're doing Yeah. next
week, say you want to go out next week.
You're out and they're sat on YouTube
talking. I don't think you understand
this. I don't think you understand how
serious it is. That's why you laugh at
it. Oh, but I don't think you understand.
It's like what Joker was saying. Yeah.
He's trying to say that they're in my
head. It's like what I used to say to I
used to say this to Joseph. Yeah. I said
this to Joseph Har that Yeah. They do it
for reaction. They do it for reaction.
And I said to him I said to him that,
"Okay, but they're reacting to me."
I said to him, Dusty, that okay, but
they're reacting to me by posting about
me. And no matter what you would tell
him, it didn't process in his brain.
That's what makes me think a lot of
people on here were disabled. I said to
Joseph Fer, "Okay, so you're reacting
for a reaction. That doesn't make sense.
So he never really went in in through to
his brain because he's so disabled he
don't he can't even process it.
I'll [ __ ] I'll [ __ ] that burger up, mate.
That's [ __ ] He's never stuck his dick
up any girl. He went nowhere near that
He went nowhere near that girl.
You know, he went nowhere near that girl. You know? [snorts] Yeah.
They react to you for a reaction.
That Joseph [snorts] is another weirdo.
So they react to you
for a reaction. Doesn't that just defeat the whole
I didn't get the police involved, Dusty? He did.
cuz I gave him a good old arv
involved. He got the piece involved.
I gave him a good old ass weapon.
I gave him a good old [ __ ] ass whapon.
You couldn't handle me.
A good old ass whooping.
I gave him a good oldfashioned ass whooping.
You couldn't handle me. I didn't call
the police. I didn't saw it.
Just like USA is USA called the police on me.
Hey, buddy. I'm flying off to Vegas
tomorrow, sir. I hope you Why don't you
do the same thing? You're always like
telling us you want
>> [ __ ] off, you fat [ __ ] stalker. Leave
me alone, you jealous bastard. [ __ ] off.
something. Leave me alone.
I don't want you.
Leave me alone.
Peter Griffin, [ __ ] off.
Leave me alone. It's not my fault. I'm
better looking and younger than you.
Leave me alone.
Leave me alone. It's not my fault I'm
younger and better looking.
Stalker. This This hunt is an actual stalker, bro.
He is an actual stalker.
An actual stalker, bro.
But serious, let's let's talk about this
though. Seriously, how can these people
Can I ask you a question? If these
people have got this life and their
life's better than everyone and they're
not skin, where do they find the time to
sit on the internet all day stalking?
I just would like to know the answer to it.
UK asylum, Triple H, Dusty, if they if
they've got better lives than people,
why are they sat on here stalking every
day? Not even winging. No, I mean
they're not even live winging. their
lives stalking every day.
I don't know, man.
I don't have the time or energy for it.
I don't I think you underestimate how
much it takes, bro. I really really do.
And they don't do it for a reaction
because even if you don't react to them,
they will always do it. So, don't even
say you do it for a reaction because
they don't do it for a reaction. The
amount of times I explained this to
Joseph Farra. It's not about a reaction.
I can prove it again if you want me to.
It's not about a reaction, bro. It's not
about a reaction. They will still do it.
Even if you never went live,
that's that, bro.
You right, [ __ ]
PJ [clears throat] will be alone on Christmas Day. >> [laughter]
>> Definitely won't be. I'll be with my mom
and my sister. Sounds like projection with you.
>> You're a manta.
>> Yeah, you are m
>> self projection again,
>> bro. [clears throat] What is it with you
Christmas self projectors? What is it with you?
>> Smelly smelly Pete.
>> How am I going to be alone when I'm
going to be with my mom and my sister?
That doesn't make sense.
>> Smelly smelly Pete. >> Huh? Smelly Peter,
>> can you talk English, please?
>> Smelly Peter.
>> Yeah, really. Put your camera on. Whoa.
There's a lot of self-repent in this community.
skin. Remember triple eight skin. The
one has always on Timmy's skin
saying I suggest you wind your neck in. >> [laughter] >> H. Ah.
That Damon Thompson's a proper stalker.
Why are these people so jealous of me just
in before they're not jealous but then
they spend all their life?
They are jealous, bro. These people are
but you say they're not, but they
definitely definitely are.
Again, you don't understand the severity
of what they do.
I couldn't even with the USA easy thing.
Yeah. I was [ __ ] with her for ages.
Not all day every day, but I was [ __ ]
with her and I was like, bro, I was
like, no. At the end, I was like, I
can't do this anymore.
So, that was somebody that really, this
is someone that I met in person. Not I
wouldn't say I know them, but I met them
in person. These people have never met
you, right? And they're willing to do
this every day for years.
constantly [ __ ] with people on the
internet from the time they wake up to
the time they go to bed and you're
really saying that you're not jealous. I
had to wake up annoyed and [ __ ] [ __ ]
every day [ __ ] with that [ __ ] It
went on for a while but then I stopped.
That's what I don't understand. Like it's they can't
if they're doing this, bro, year in year
out. It's not co anymore. It's not like
they do it over winter. They do it all
the time. So they have to be jealous of something.
They have to. They literally have to be
jealous of something.
They really, really, really, really have
to. But they can't admit it to themselves.
I don't know what it is, Greezy. Is it
the fact that like
you're younger and you can go out and
meet women? It doesn't matter what they
do, but you can go out. I want to know
what what is it, Grezy?
Because it's not for a reaction.
So why why do they do it? It's not for a
reaction. Definitely not for reaction. Okay.
So, if I stop going live
for 6 months and I posted videos
disabling the likes and the comments,
when I go on all their channels in 6
months times, they would have left me alone. Yeah.
Think about what you're saying. So
you're saying they love your angle and
the things that you say. Okay. So if I
don't go live anymore and I just put
videos on this channel, so you're
telling me they're not going to do what
they do every day? Are you sure about
that? So they they definitely do it for
a reaction? Yeah.
So if I go back in six to eight months,
they're not going to be posting about me. No.
Are you sure about that?
Cuz I've ignored people for month like a
month before and I've gone back on their
channel and they're still doing it. They
will never find someone else. No, they
won't. Dusty, I don't think you
understand. There are some channels
there are some channels that are
dedicated to me. I don't think you
understand. There's channels that are
dedicated to loads of people, but
there's channels that there were four
channels that were dedicated to me.
They're not going to go for anyone else. Trust me,
they will. No, they won't. No, they
So, if I left, right, Red Star is going
to go for other people. Uh Jamie
Thompson's going to go No, bro. There
were accounts that only go for me. No one else.
They won't, bro. Maybe the fake accounts
might the fake accounts might go for
other people when I leave. But no, them
them they will never leave you alone,
bro. Even when you're off here, they
will never leave you alone. It's like
what Ronald Pump said. They will never
leave you alone, bro. They will I should
have listened to him. They will never
leave you alone. Whether you're on air,
whether you're off air,
the fake accounts might get bored of
mentioning you and then just throw Monty
or something, but the actual people with
the channels won't.
They won't. They will never stop.
They will never ever ever ever stop.
And even if they did stop, they will
wait until you come back. They will sit
there and wait for 10 years. They will
wait, Greasy. They will wait. Even if
they have to wait 10 years, you could
come back in 10 years and they'd still do it.
They'll wait even if it takes 10 years.
Did I mention she should have a glass eye?
How long have you been under the table?
Oh, not long. Just a week or so. Yeah,
like Undertaker at Wrestlemania. It gy
like the Undertaker.
Did you watch He got defeated at
Wrestlemania? Undertaker, Dusty.
He got defeated by Brock Lesnar.
I was watching it yesterday. I was
watching some WWE. Who's here?
Why was Nons's favorite
uh wrestler John Cena? Everyone else
liked John Cena. He said he used to like
John Cena, but that was everyone else's.
Why do you think he liked John Cena as well?
Why do you reckon he likes John Cena?
Everyone else likes John Cena, Dusty.
He seem to like him as well.
Why does he like him as well? Yeah,
until it's been made.
>> Yeah, it's not letting me. Oh, hello PJ.
You all right, captain?
>> Saturday, captain. [ __ ] long time.
>> Yeah, a long time a
>> PJ. You just need to chill out on like [ __ ]
>> I was watching Timmy Aldridge Joker.
>> Yeah, but you can't put them You can't
put yourself in those levels, mate.
You're [ __ ] nuts.
>> Yeah, but I like Timmy Aldridge.
Yeah, but you're massively
deteriorating, mate. You have to
remember when I first saw you, you were
young, like 21. Like, you're [ __ ]
>> Well, duh. People will do get older.
>> No, what I'm saying is you're
deteriorating. Like, you're [ __ ]
getting progressively worse.
>> What do you mean?
>> You're letting these [ __ ] like take
over your life.
>> They're not. I take over their life.
Well, you are the m fantasy stories. You
are the mun. Listen, Joker, do you not
understand that I live in these people's heads?
>> No. Before maybe, but now.
>> No, no, no, no, no. Do you know this
account? Okay, bro. Do you know this
account called Redot? >> Yeah.
>> So, you're you're trying to tell me that
I don't live in his head, bro?
>> He lives in your head?
>> No, he I live in his head. He wakes up
every day doing videos of me from the
time I wake up to the time I go to bed.
do not understand how much effort that takes.
>> These [ __ ] guys get you so angry.
>> Yeah, I get them angry as well.
>> You are a month of fantasy stories.
Anyways, I'll see you in February.
>> How old are you now?
>> I'm not even saying how old are you now?
>> Before you know what? Before you used to
annoy the [ __ ] out of people, but now
they are annoying the [ __ ] out of you.
>> No, they don't annoy me. I I love it.
>> So, how old are you now?
>> What? Me? >> Yeah. >> 33. >> Where?
>> But listen, age is a number. If you keep
yourself looking fresh and healthy, it's a number.
>> Do you remember LT?
Listen, L2 is like
that's what I'm saying, Pete. When I
first started speaking to you, like you
kept [ __ ] real, but now you're [ __ ] a
bit of a fantasy.
>> This guy's a troll, bro.
>> What? Me? >> Yeah.
>> Well, how am I trolling?
>> You are, bro.
>> No, Pet. I'm just saying before you kept
things 100% legitimate. Like now you're
letting all these pricks get to you and
it it's just a [ __ ] show. Really? [laughter]
>> That's funny, is it?
>> Yeah, but you can't call me a troll,
mate. I was one of the first people
trying to help you out back in the day.
>> You were supposed to meet me, but you never did.
>> No, listen. I tried to help you out back
in The reason why you were supposed to meet me,
>> TJ. No, the reason why N meets you is
because you [ __ ] them all over.
>> No. Do you remember Fraser?
>> Yeah, but that's what I'm saying. You
[ __ ] everyone over.
>> Fra is it? Always wanted your face.
>> Yeah, but Peak, no one wants to [ __ ] you
over like this. Why you going to [ __ ] them over?
>> You are mother, >> mate.
>> So, where you living? Where you living now,
>> mate? Yeah,
>> I'm still where I am. You know what I
mean? Like people, listen, I know you
won't understand this, but people can actually
hold down a job, pay rent, have a car,
like I mean, not everyone is a [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but but working [ __ ] though, is it?
>> No. And not not always.
Look, Pete, you're doing good for time,
you know? You just don't realize it.
It's everyone is [ __ ] all these
pricks are getting to you and
>> I need to ban these repeating we need to
ban these repeating people it just
repeated is it
>> yeah back in the day you're doing better
you're deteriorating quite a lot
and people like seeing your downfall
that's what you don't understand [snorts]
>> I think they do this cuz they're jealous
bro as well
>> do you know what it is honestly I think
>> I think it is bro No, for real. I I do
think it is, bro.
>> No, I don't think anyone's jealous. I
just think uh they tried to like, you know, really
>> Don't forget, bro, you're younger than
these people and that.
>> No, you were, Pete. You were, but now
you're getting old. It's been what?
>> Yeah, but I'm about 20. Yeah.
>> Yeah. But what I'm saying is like it's
not doing you any good.
>> Let go of all the Let go of the hate.
let go of all that [ __ ] Just
[ __ ] try and bet yourself and
>> No, we can't let these [ __ ] women win. >> Yeah,
>> that's what that's what one of these
accounts said to me, isn't it, Greasy?
There's an account. Yeah, that we we
thought it was you at first, isn't it?
Like, don't let these [ __ ] women win.
It's true, isn't it?
>> Yeah, but forget the women, forget the trolls.
>> No, but that's what that's what the
account said. Do you remember? We was
having a normal conversation and Yeah.
can't change how [ __ ] [ __ ]
You got like too many enemies right now.
Your women, trolls, like
just focus on yourself.
>> I sent I sent I sent WhatsApp I sent
these women to my dick on WhatsApp, bro.
>> Yeah, you can't be Listen, the whim the
women that [ __ ] It's not the
problem. I remember speaking to you ages
ago. You're doing all right. You're
jumping much better.
Don't let all this [ __ ] get to you.
>> They don't get to me.
>> But you're reacted on it.
>> Yeah, but they're reacting to me.
>> Okay. But you're letting it affect your life. >> Yeah.
I went out yesterday.
>> You know, I'm not saying you don't go
out that, but what I'm saying is it's
affecting your life. All this like
[ __ ] like unnecessary crap.
You do you remember Anman?
>> Yeah, I remember him.
>> Did you like him?
>> Yeah, I didn't mind him. But listen, he
left like he knew this [ __ ] was toxic.
Toxic as [ __ ]
>> Yeah, he he live in Thailand now. He
moved to Thailand cuz of the women were
known to well, fair play, but he knew
this [ __ ] was toxic. But with you, PJ,
you love this YouTube. You're proper
addicted to this YouTube [ __ ] But I
like Jimmy Eldridge.
No, you you love it. Like you're
probably worse cuz you [ __ ] got more
sense than that. [ __ ] [laughter]
>> Yeah, but I like to be out.
>> Yeah, listen. But you're probably worse
cuz you got more.
>> He said he got a [ __ ] He said that
he got [clears throat] [ __ ] and his
dick is still hurting. [laughter]
>> Yeah, but PJ, get the [ __ ] off this site
and your life will be much better.
>> I need I need revenge on women. I need
to get revenge and then come off this
site. Yeah, but you don't need to get
revenge on nothing or no one. You don't
need to like hurt anyone. Like you just
>> Yeah, I [ __ ] do it. But
>> why? You're just trying to prove a point
to everyone here to pay for what they've done. Bro,
>> no, but you're just trying to prove a
point to people on here. [laughter]
>> Thing is, PJ, you don't need to do that
[ __ ] man. You're [ __ ] nuts. No, seriously.
>> If you were to look after yourself, you
get [snorts] the [ __ ] off this [ __ ]
Just look after yourself. Better your life.
>> I'm leaving England, bro.
>> No, but you said that a million times.
>> Yeah, I'm moving. I moving, bro. I went to Amsterdam.
Antman left. And so I can if he left, I
can. Isn't it?
Do you know what you have to realize
though? Most of the people on here have
actually probably got families and jobs.
>> And that's even worse then, isn't it? Really?
>> No. No, it's not worse. But
>> because they're doing cuz they're doing
it's just like a past time for them.
>> Well, every day all day every day.
>> No, not all of them. Not all of them.
I'm just saying hand few people.
>> So like,
>> you know, Monty lost everything over the
site. know that
>> PJ I remember you from back in the day
like uh [laughter] >> Joker >> Jo,
>> did it.
>> Yeah, but you were like 19 you [ __ ] getting worse.
>> Yeah, but no, but you're not answering my question.
You're not answering my question.
>> Go on.
didn't didn't want to lose everything over YouTube.
>> Look, I don't give a [ __ ] about I
[laughter] don't even know. Yeah,
>> I'm asking you. Is it?
>> Okay. Maybe, but what I'm saying is not you.
>> How do you think he got on here?
>> Yeah, cuz he's [ __ ] like
>> Do you know how he found this community?
>> Through you. Yeah, you know
he was he was arguing with Timmy Aldridge.
>> I remember you finding you through Timmy
Aldridge and like you're bit more normal
than you are now, but like this shit's
making you get [ __ ] like worse.
They're trying to [ __ ] you up. I
remember when you first came on, you
used to go out on dates, but listen,
they used to hate it. Now you're just
losing the pl what the [ __ ] you're
giving into this [ __ ] Get off this
crap. Get back on your gym. Eat well.
PJ, you're good. You'll be fine. You'll
be decent. But
>> no, we can't let them cut. We can't let
them win jokes. We can't let them win.
>> You're too addict to this YouTube crap
and like trying to get revenge where
it's focused on your own life. That's
not a You don't need to do that, bro.
You don't need to get no revenge on no one.
>> The women are keeping us sexist, though.
>> No, it's not women. It's like you're
getting trolled to [ __ ]
>> I'm saying it's women, bro.
>> Bro, it's not women. You're getting
trolled to [ __ ] on here.
>> Yeah, women have trolled me as well.
>> But you they're not trolling you.
Sometimes they just
>> they lead you on.
Yeah, but PJ, I think you're just
letting all these people affect you.
Well, you don't need to. You know,
you're doing much better back in day.
You're going, you're chilling. Do you
know what I mean? I know what the [ __ ]
Like now you're just like nuts. You're
just angry as [ __ ] Why?
>> You know, cuz he's [ __ ] women, bro.
>> Yeah, but it's not the women, PJ. Forget
the women. Like
>> it is.
>> You're blaming that on everything. It's not.
>> Yeah, cuz they're [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
>> Yeah, but they've got their own
opinions. They can say yes or no, right?
>> Yeah. And I can [ __ ] with them if I want. >> No.
>> Yeah, but they don't say yes or no,
though, do they? Because they lead
people on and play games. So, how is
that an opinion, bro?
>> The people on YouTube are [ __ ] your
head up so much for blaming the women.
This is what you don't understand. You know,
>> you can just chill out, mate. You're
fresh. You go gym. Do whatever you need to do.
Get the [ __ ] off this site. But you're
just letting this [ __ ] take your life
over. I don't understand why you're doing that.
>> Yeah. If if I come off this site, Grezy
will be starved of content. Poor [ __ ]
>> You can message him off mafia like
privately as friends. Poor [ __ ] No.
that you can message him off here
privately as friends. But
>> is it you that's trolling me behind these accounts?
>> No, PJ. I'll never
>> So, who are these accounts that keep
saying don't let these [ __ ] women win?
>> You know, listen,
>> who is it, bro? Who is it? It's got to
be someone, isn't it?
>> It's probably that bomb geese that that
guy was obsessed with you.
>> He keeps saying, "Oh, he keeps saying we
can't change our [ __ ] [ __ ] show.
These women are [ __ ] keeping us single."
>> You know what? It's probably not even
just him. It's probably a lot of people
cuz you react and
>> but it seems like you're saying Greg you
know the account I'm talking about is it
like I told you okay Joker you know
where I had a one night stand in
elephant and castle the account said
Peter Benny's got a lot of history in
elephant and castle see
>> listen if you had good people give you
>> know who it is though who is it bro
seriously zero advice but what I'm
saying if you had good people giving you
good advice without getting you mad
you might be a bit chill killed
>> Joker. The account said that Peter B
can't get attached anymore because he's
already found his mama. So where do they
get that from? How
>> Yeah, but how do they know all of this stuff?
>> Cuz you [ __ ] go on about it daily.
>> Yeah, but so they repeat what you saying here.
>> No, but what [clears throat and snorts]
I'm saying, PJ, you go on about it
[ __ ] daily. Yeah, [laughter] >> obviously.
>> You like it, is it?
>> No, I don't. I'm just That's mental,
bro. Do you like a because he's already
found his mama?
>> PJ, when I first heard your [ __ ] it was
that [ __ ] Isabel. You wrote her a
poem. I was thinking, what the [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> Just chill out on that [ __ ]
attachment [ __ ] man. Cuz they forget
you straight away. It's like
What was that?
>> You were better before, man.
>> Me and you and Timmy need to meet up.
Oh, Timmy, are you joining? >> Yo, >> so
um when when did you last go out drinking?
maybe like a couple of weeks ago. I
don't really like I'm I'm a bit old. I'm
in my 30s now and I don't do that [ __ ] too much.
>> I used to do a lot in your 20s, is it?
>> Yeah. Like early 20s. When I joined this
site, I was really [ __ ] up. But I
realized that ain't normal.
Listen, DJ, I would invite you to my
house and chill [ __ ] B, but
you're just like you you've proven
yourself to do mad [ __ ] All right,
this woman's having double standards on
in uh on Instagram. Can I tell you what
h what happened?
Can I tell you what happened? Uh,
>> do you know what I [clears throat]
think? I think
the trolls that take,
>> she said, well then if you want that,
you can go to places for that and then
you can't moan no girl wants you when
you've admitted you just want sex. So
make that make sense. I said, I don't
only want sex. And there's women out
there that only want sex. No.
>> So is it okay for them to only want sex,
but men are not allowed to only want
sex? How does that work out then? the
>> if there's 10% of people if there's 10%
of people women that only want sex. Yeah.
>> Why are they allow sex then?
>> You're taking No. No. Answer me. Grey
>> PJ, you're taking out on the women the
[ __ ] trolls that are trolling you.
>> I'm in.
>> PJ, can you hear me?
>> Answer me then, Grezy. I can hear you.
>> You're taking out on the women. the
trolls that are trolling you.
>> No, I'm taking out on them cuz they're [ __ ]
>> No, you're taking out on the people.
>> So, what's your opinion on that one, Greasy?
>> That's just mad, huh?
>> Yeah. Jok,
do you know what the mad thing is? You
probably had more women than most of the
people on here, but you're just treating
them right. I hate them, bro. I hate them.
>> Yeah, because of the trolls.
>> They're little fake [ __ ] in this, bro.
>> Yeah, you can't be saying that [ __ ] bro.
>> I just read it out to you, Grezy.
[ __ ] sake. I'll read it again. [ __ ]
No, listen. One second's over.
She said, "Of course there's women." Oh,
no. She said, "Well, then if you want
that, you can go other places for that,
and then you can't moan. No girl wants
you when you've admitted you just want
sex. So make that make sense. And then I
said, I don't only want sex and there's
women out there that only want sex. No, double standards.
That's what I said to her.
That is double standards, bro. Because
10% there will be some 10% of people
that only hook up with people. Maybe
five I don't know the percent. 5% 10% or
whoever the [ __ ] they are
>> with the trolls. So why why can't men
only want sex then
>> with the cold clapping your head and
your behavior that's [ __ ] up. Like
you have to come to a mutual agreement
like you can't just you know [snorts]
>> you have to recognize you have to
recognize your mistakes.
>> You can't always be right BJ.
I'm right when it comes to women.
>> No, but you have to recognize your mistakes. Like,
>> yeah, but she's saying that no one would
want you if you only want sex. That's
what I'm trying to say there. That's
what I'm trying to say, Greasy. She's
saying that if you only want sex, no one
wants to be with you. But then there's
women out there that only want sex.
But that doesn't make sense.
>> Yeah. That's called nympho,
whatever. that she's basically saying
that if you want someone for sex, if you
say that you want someone for sex,
that's not going to make someone want
you. That's But then she But then I'm
saying that there's women out there that want sex.
>> Yeah, but you you I think you're letting YouTube,
>> right? But there's women that only want
sex though, Grezy. But also, Grey, but
Grey, there's women that only want sex.
>> PJ, you might have met a woman that only
wanted sex, but YouTube has taken over
your life so much.
It doesn't matter if it's the majority.
There's women out. Okay. What about USA?
Is he? What about Sig? What about the
other one on my birthday? They wanted
they wanted to hook up. So,
>> yeah. But if you found that person,
would you be happy? Huh?
What did you say?
>> I said if you found that person, would
you be calm? >> No.
>> Exactly. YouTube has [ __ ] your life
up. Like [laughter]
>> it's okay, Joker. I'll just >> wait.
>> I'll just wait.
>> What I'm saying, you could find the dream.
>> Yeah, but Joker, I'll just wait.
>> You You can't wait. Either get off
YouTube. I will wait until it's been made.
>> You have to make
>> That's okay. I'll just wait.
But PJ, you you have to make a compromise. You know,
everyone knows they can [ __ ] with you.
That's the problem. Everyone knows they can.
>> You know
>> that's the problem, PJ. Everyone knows
they can [ __ ] with you.
>> No, they can [ __ ] with you in it.
>> No, no one can [ __ ] with me.
>> No, everyone knows they can, but no one
can [ __ ] with me.
Timmy, are you joining to talk to me and
Jo or what?
PJ, you were like a much healthier,
better person a few years ago than you are now.
>> Yeah, I like YouTube.
>> Yeah, ain't it ain't doing you no good.
>> Yeah, but but this is the same website
the Sideman's on.
Joker, you watch the side, is it?
>> Yeah, but listen.
>> Yeah, but they're on YouTube, so why
can't I be on YouTube?
>> Yeah, you let it affect you too much.
>> Yeah, but they're on they're on the same website now.
>> Yeah, they are. They are. But [laughter]
you're deteriorating. Do you know what I mean?
You take any like help as negative
criticism. It's not.
>> You're a troll.
>> How am I a troll, mate? I [ __ ] spoke
to you from time, PJ. I'm just saying you just
you're taking it as like negative for
some people genuinely would like to see you.
>> This woman said to me on Instagram
briefly that I'll meet someone when I
least expect it. Is that true?
Cuz my mom told me that when I was 14.
14 years ago.
What do you think we did?
This is when I least expect it. >> Really? >> So,
>> you know what I think?
>> So, Joker, do you watch porn? >> No.
>> You used to it
>> back in the day? Yeah.
>> What? Like business porn?
>> Anything? Like
>> I like business porn. No, but that's the
thing. That's that's just like how
people go through that [ __ ] in their
20s. But I was thinking is
>> Well, I never got to it, but
>> it's like in the like born in the ' 70s.
>> Vintage. That's what they call it. >> Yeah.
Well, PJ with you, like you have to realize
you got a lot of people that want to
[ __ ] see you fail cuz all that
[ __ ] you put online. But you have to
be real. You're not a [ __ ] [ __ ]
I mean, this is trolling me.
>> How the [ __ ] am I trolling here?
Well, who follow
them were laughing at us,
>> mate? I've been trolled myself. Like, it
doesn't give like it it doesn't matter.
Like, there's real life.
>> Look, there's real life, there's instant
life, but if you can't differentiate
that, you're [ __ ]
And I know you see Did you see me
shouting at that woman in the park?
>> I seen you do all mad [ __ ] you know. [laughter] >> What's
the worst the worst thing I done then,
>> bro? I saw you [ __ ] wanking outside
like that [ __ ] motorbike.
>> Did you see the video of me arguing with
that woman on the train? >> No.
>> You You didn't see it?
>> No. I just know there's a little bit of
hope for you. [laughter]
>> Stop it.
>> Okay, stop it.
>> What is that hurt for you? >> No.
>> What the [ __ ]
>> You remember when you and LG had beef?
>> Yeah. But listen, I had m
>> You're boy. You're boys now, is it?
>> No, we're not boys. But what I'm saying
it was bollocks. It was nothing. But he
actually genuinely tried to give the advice and
>> he got Yeah, but he got involved.
Remember when he got involved in the USA thing?
>> Yeah, I didn't agree with that. I didn't
agree with that. I said,
>> "No, but he said Yeah. Do you know the
reason why he got involved?" He said,
"Cuz I kept messaging him about her
every day and I was threatening her and
he wanted to warn her about me." That's funny.
>> It was just clout. PJ's clout cuz you
used to get mad as clout.
>> I remember you from
>> Yeah, but who who the who was the root
cause for that USA thing?
>> Probably her.
>> No, but yeah, but who's Yeah, but how
did the whole LT that get involved in that?
>> Cuz he started messaging uh [ __ ]
trying to get sloppy seconds and that.
Look, the guys have Look, I'm not going
to try and [ __ ] defend him, but what
I'm saying is like
>> back in the day when you first joined
this little [ __ ] show, you're kind of normal.
>> What do you call it? Little [ __ ] show.
>> Yeah, but you were kind of normal. Now
you're [ __ ] losing the plot. [laughter]
>> This joke is a troll.
>> How the [ __ ] am I a troll?
You're saying funny things.
>> Yeah, but I'm not trying to be funny.
I'm just trying to be real.
>> Now you're letting all these [ __ ]
>> Why you you watch nons? >> No,
>> you sound like you sound very posh.
>> Look, I know the [ __ ] stalks you, but I don't watch,
>> you know. Hey, bro. You know he started
saying Chev's attractive to fit in.
Look, the guy's a [ __ ] pedo. [ __ ]
that guy. [laughter]
>> What is he?
>> He's a [ __ ] pedo. Just forget him.
>> Do you remember that trend though? Um,
Joker, when everyone used
>> I remember when I was bang on YouTube.
>> No, but Joker, do you remember that
though? When everyone was saying, "Oh,
>> I remember."
>> Do you remember when everyone was saying
that though, Joker?
>> PJ, when I was bang on YouTube, that
[ __ ] said, "Oh, 15y olds are legal."
He's a kilo [ __ ] Yeah. Anyone who
knows, they know. [ __ ] that [ __ ] Yeah. So,
>> move on from him.
>> You remember when people used to say
that though was attractive to fit in?
>> Well, she's not not attractive, is she?
>> Yeah, but people used to say it to fit
in. Do you remember? Like you like 11
years ago, bro.
>> [ __ ] talking about this little weird
[ __ ] You just
>> Yeah, but you remember they used to say
to copy each other.
>> PJ, do you know what any other person
would have done? They would have smacked him up.
>> Bro, did you see I done posted of him?
>> Yeah. Forget the posters. They would
have done the Bizo.
>> Yeah. No, this is a troll.
>> No, trust me. any other person would
have genuinely done the phys.
>> Well, I tried to beat a [ __ ] bird in
a million times. Like I [ __ ] done a
lot of things. Like you you've done a
lot of things. You could have done that.
You didn't try hard enough.
>> You didn't try hard enough.
>> Yes, I did. I went to the I went to the virgin area.
You never tried enough.
Bro, stop it. I went to his area
>> facts, bro. I'm telling you facts.
>> I went to his area three times.
>> Yes, but
>> I went to the virgin village where
they're all virgins.
>> Dad G was your mate back on day.
>> You're an absolute virgin, man.
>> How can you tell me how how can you tell
me I didn't try you absolute virgin?
100% you didn't try hard enough. [laughter] >> Virgin.
>> How the [ __ ] am I a virgin? Please
>> could you find it funny?
>> It's not funny, mate. Like for me, it's
real talk, mate. I [ __ ] smack someone up.
>> You know what I mean? Joker
>> PJ, are you are you a Scorpio like me?
No, I'm [ __ ] uh what am I? What's October?
>> Yeah, you're you're a Scorpio.
>> Yeah, maybe.
>> Yeah, I'm 27th October. It's my birthday. >> When?
>> [ __ ] is it? >> When?
>> When I get my hands on that [ __ ]
virgin. When I get my hands,
>> PJ, I saw that video that Ger you ain't
doing nothing, brother.
>> Yeah, he caught me off guard.
>> Listen, PJ, some of us are not fight.
Just have to [ __ ] it a bit,
>> bro. The guy caught me off guard two
years ago. Did you see that? Did you see
the video where I put on the bouncer and
he shot himself? Did you see where I
stuck on them two guys?
>> [ __ ] He couldn't do it, PJ. Some of
us are not about that. You have to
[ __ ] admit the truth, brother.
>> You're a joker. Listen, you're not that lie.
>> How do you know?
>> Okay, meet me then.
>> Well, why am I gonna mate? I ain't going to [ __ ]
>> meet me in it,
>> PJ. I'm not talking about me. I'm just
saying you have to.
>> Okay, I'll meet you. But sometimes you
have to admit when you're not about that
life, that [ __ ]
>> I'm definitely about that life. You're
not a PJ PJ.
>> I'm definitely about that life.
>> That Giza put it on you and you [ __ ]
>> Yeah, he caught me off guard.
>> Bollocks PJ.
>> Okay. How many people have you seen me
stick on? Okay. Okay. Whatever. And how
many people have you seen me stick it on?
>> What? You talking about me?
>> Yeah. How many people have you seen me
stick it on? People
>> quite a few people. >> Twice.
>> Who? the uh
bouncer and that guy.
>> Oh, so you saw it then? So you did see it? >> Yeah.
>> Did you like it?
>> Well, both of them [ __ ] made you melt. [laughter]
>> This guy is on cheap.
>> Just admit you're not
>> This joke is on cheap bus. He's on
>> Listen, PJ, just admit you're not about
that. It's not even a big deal.
>> I agree. Who do you think would win now?
Yeah. Me or Prime? me 100% in it. 100%.
I'm bigger than I was 2 years ago. Yeah.
Yeah. Definitely me, bro.
>> PJ, it's not a shame to admit you're not
bad at life. Like,
>> who do you Who do you think I reckon I
could I would win now? 100%.
>> 100% out of a game.
>> 100%, bro. Yeah.
>> Yeah. That When was that? Was that two
years? Two two and a half years. Where
was it? Wait, hold on. One year I was in
the old. Yeah, that's like two and a half years.
>> Last year I wasn't even living it. Yeah.
Yeah, that was
>> PJ the North. >> Huh?
>> It's not even a big deal. That is
>> He wouldn't beat me now though. No way
would he beat me now, bro. No way.
>> It's 100%. If you're not It's not a big deal. Yeah,
>> you acting like it's a bad thing. It's
nothing. Who cares?
>> You want me to meet that prime again,
Greasy, and [ __ ] him up?
>> Do you want me to do that? If I knew
that, would it make you happy, Joker?
>> No, PJ. Cuz you're not like,
>> bro, he's not about that life. All he
done was set up that he could win
against. Anyone can do that, bro. Anyone
can do that.
>> He might be about that life, but a
little bit more. No, he's not about that life, bro.
>> Do you want me to meet him? Gre, do you
>> Why the [ __ ] do you have to take
everything so defensive?
>> No, I'm saying do you want me to meet him now?
>> Sometimes you have to admit your fools like
>> I'm not playing.
That's it. Who cares?
>> What do you mean? H
>> I'm not playing nice, bro. Do you So, do
you want me to meet him then?
>> No. PJ,
[ __ ] sake, man. People have seen me
meet a few people. It's just who gives a
[ __ ] man. Why are you letting affect you? >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? Like, what's the
point? Just leave it. But
>> I would win now. 100% I would win against him.
I'm powerful now. Um, Joker,
>> it doesn't even matter. Like, that's
what I mean. You're making it matter.
>> So, if I if I if I met him and beat him,
would that mean I win then? Guy,
>> would that mean I would win?
You know what?
>> He said he said that he's trying to He
said that he's going to catch me again.
He It's not going to happen, bro.
>> Listen, you would never meet that guy and win. >> What?
>> You won't.
>> Why not? >> Like,
>> you just won't. Trust me.
>> Cuz you can just tell. Like, you can
But you might win against other guys,
but not that guy.
>> No, I would win against him now.
Because think about it, that was two and
a half years ago. I'm bigger now, you know.
>> Yeah. PJ, I think you win like maybe
against a [ __ ] someone like Pat
Master L, but not against Ag.
>> He's not But he's not even big.
>> Yeah, but
>> but that wasn't his city and I didn't
run off. I didn't, bro. But listen, he
had m multiple chances to hit me and he
never and we all know here's the
biasness on here. Yeah. You know, if LT
grabbed me and done that, do you know
what everyone would be saying to LT?
They'd be like, "Oh, you didn't hit him.
You didn't hit him." Prime, you know how
long he set me up for? A year. A year,
bro. A year.
>> He set me up for a year.
>> It doesn't mean you're weak. You will
never win against Prime or LT.
>> You know what I'm saying? And he was
bigger than me as well. That's not a
win, bro. Tell him to beat me now then.
>> You might win against other people, but
you just have to write down. That guy is
not going to beat me, bro.
>> Look, he did. He Listen, PJ, he he could
have hurt you, but he let you off. So,
>> yeah, but he wouldn't he wouldn't win
now. No way.
>> This is what I mean. That's delusional
stuff, PJ. That's [ __ ] mad.
>> No, he wouldn't beat me now, though. He
wouldn't beat me.
>> He did not hurt you. He let you off.
That's a win on its own. No.
>> Do you not think there's like something
wrong with that?
Huh? Well, I I would win against him now. >> How?
>> No, I didn't. Yeah, bro. He Okay, bro.
Anyone can do that. Listen. Listen,
Joker. I could set someone up right now.
Yeah, that's Okay, let me let me give
you an example, right? I could find
someone that's smaller than me and
humiliate them. That doesn't mean you're
winning, bro. Anyone could do that to
anyone, bro, that's smaller than them.
Do you realize that?
>> Yeah, but he didn't humiliate you. No,
but any what I'm saying is anybody can
do that, bro. Anybody can do that. You
know what I'm saying? Anyone can anybody
can do it.
>> Okay. So, you're saying you're smaller than him?
>> Yeah. Well, I don't know now. Not now,
maybe. But back then, of course, I
[ __ ] was, bro. Are you mad?
If he prepared me, if I was prepared and
I was like, "Okay, this is what this guy
looks like." I would have been prepared,
bro. You know what I'm saying? I'm
thinking I'm going on a night out. I'm
wearing shoes. The guy's bigger than me,
bro. There was no way I was going to win.
>> No, you're going out with a mate that
you thought was a friend that
>> Yeah. Not a friend, but yeah.
>> Nothing to do with size, but you didn't want it.
>> Admit it. Like,
>> yeah, but okay. I want it. You know
what? Yeah. If you people keep bringing
it up, I'm just going to stop madness
with him and I'm going to No, no, I'm
just saying I'm just saying if it gets
brought up again, I'm more than happy
meeting this guy.
But I'm just saying I'll be more than
happy to meet him.
>> DJ, your [ __ ] levels is Shauny.
>> I didn't run away at all, mate. My phone
dropped. I didn't run away. But like I
said, if you want to keep bringing it
up, I'll just start it all over again
and he's not going to win.
>> So it's up to you, bro.
>> Listen, no one shook like you said. No
one should what I'm saying. You
forfeited. Yeah. Bounce. Done your own thing.
That's it. Done. the guy had his edge
over him. That's it. You know,
>> sometimes that's the way it works
>> with uh Lord J. It weren't like that.
The guy mate, that would have been a
fair fight cuz that he's a [ __ ] as
well. So, that's it. Done. But that's
>> I'm going to I'm going to call out that
prime again, Grezy. I think
>> you don't have to call N.
>> I'm calling him out again, bro. I'm
calling him out again, bro. I'm 100%
calling him out again since this guy
wants to level, bro. I'm calling this
guy out again. Delayed.
>> Listen, you don't The guy was your He
was all right, mate. He let you off, bro. Like,
>> and he's not going to win. And he's not
going to put anyone in hospital. Believe
you me, he's not going to put anyone in hospital.
He didn't humiliate me. He didn't even
touch me, bro. Someone's caught you off guard. >> Yeah,
>> PJ. He didn't,
>> bro. Someone bigger and older. Yeah.
going for someone they know they're
going to win against. That's not
winning. That's like That's like The
Rock here going for one of these people
and saying humiliated. You wouldn't do
nothing. You wouldn't be able to do
anything yourselves. So why are you
acting like this is what I don't
understand with these people when they do?
>> Yeah, but he didn't.
>> They're acting like they would have done
something. They wouldn't do nothing,
bro. Listen to me a second, bro. Yeah,
these people would wouldn't do anything.
They I don't know what they would say. I
don't know what they would say, but they
would not do anything, bro. Mark my
words. They would not do anything.
>> Yeah, but do you not think like that was
let off lightly?
>> Listen, it doesn't matter. It doesn't
matter what I said, but I'm saying these
people would wouldn't have done nothing.
Dusty wouldn't have done nothing. They
would not have done nothing, bro.
Believe you me.
They like, think about it, Jo. I'm not
telling anyone anyone to go to my door,
call and [ __ ] I'm not talking [ __ ]
Think about it, bro. Yeah. How many of
these people knew where I lived when I
lived by myself? How many of these came?
No one as a as an example. I don't want
anyone to come. How many of them come? None.
>> Half these people probably couldn't
touch you, but
the other half [snorts]
they can. You have to admit to it. Just
>> listen. Triple H. I went to Newcastle
three times and you didn't even come
out. That's not even a joke joker.
Listen. Triple triple triple triple
triple. I came to Newcastle three times
and you did not come out. So, do you
really think anyone's going to believe
that you're going to do this and that?
you're going to do this and that. You
did not come out. Tell everybody the
excuses that you made. 280 miles there,
Joker. 280 miles back.
>> Listen, think about it, bro. If
someone's so anxietyridden that they
can't even [ __ ] come and meet you in
Newcastle, what are they really going to do?
>> PJ, you could probably bash up 50% of
the people on here, but the other 50%,
you can't. And you have to admit to it. So,
>> I don't [ __ ] know who these people.
I'm just saying that they won't do anything.
>> The other 50% have to admit that we
can't. I mean, you can't break. Why
don't you tell everyone why didn't you
didn't show up when I went to Newcastle free?
>> He didn't mean because he thought you
going to dox him.
>> No, he told me that he would meet me if
I went to Newcastle. That's what he said.
>> Listen, he's
>> That's what he said. Joker, I didn't
make it up.
>> Yeah, but Dusty, you would never do
anything, Dusty. Like, and this is what
I mean. Yeah. This is what I mean,
Dusty. If someone grabbed you up, you
wouldn't do anything. And this is what
makes me think that I will prove it,
bro. I will prove it if you want me to.
But any of these people want to meet me.
I will grab them up and see what they can say.
>> No, no, no. But I'm being real though.
I'm being real.
>> Yeah. Okay. So, if you see like LT or
bit scared of him, whatever, but half of
these guys are the same. You know, you
can't put everyone.
>> You wouldn't fight Dusty. You 100% would
not fight you. So, you're telling me,
okay, you're telling me if The Rock
grabbed you, you're fighting? Yeah.
Let's use as an analogy. Yeah. Because I
don't know how big you are. You're
telling me if Mike Tyson grabs you,
you're fighting, big man. Yeah. Yeah.
Big man. Are you really really doing
that, big man?
>> PJ, are you doing that? Scared of You're
not doing that. You're not about that life.
>> Stop it. So, you're telling me if Mike
Tyson grab his hands on you, you're
fighting? [laughter] Yeah, bro. Really?
Okay, bro. Well, do you know what,
Dusty? How about me and you meet up
then? If you're so sure about this, bro.
Yeah. How if you're so sure about this,
why don't you meet me? We'll arrange it. Yeah.
Why don't me and you meet up then? And
and and let's I want to put I want to
test your theory. I really want to test
your theory. Come on. Come on. No. So
now you're saying me or not me? I'm
telling you I will put my hands on you.
I will put my greasy I will put right
[snorts] my greasy dirty hands on you
and you won't do nothing. So are you
going to meet me or not? So you're not
meeting me then? So you're not even
about it then? So but you're you're
yapping on yapping on yapping on yapping
on yapping on yapping on yapping on but
you're not actually trying to meet
anyone. So it's it's ridiculous.
It doesn't you know what I'm saying? So
yeah, what I'm about Well, guess what?
I've I've been to PE. See, this is what
I'm saying, bro. Listen. Yeah, I have
been all over the country trying to meet
people. I've stuck it on a bouncer. I've
stuck it on two people. I've tried
meeting Mark Samson twice. It doesn't
matter. I No, I stood in front of my
mom. Again, I'll repeat myself. I stood
in front of my mom, watch a video
properly, and I told him to [ __ ] off.
Stop making excuses. Yeah, bro. I was in
front of my mom. Get your eyes tested.
You have just said that no one's going
to meet you and put their hands on you.
I will happily put my hands all over you
and you won't do a damn thing. Yeah. I
stood in front of my mom telling them to
[ __ ] off. No one stood behind their mom,
[ __ ] Yeah. Secondly, the door was
not even closed properly. So, he could
have easily kicked that door in my face.
And also, I tried to meet him again and
he didn't come out. Dusty, you're not
about that life. Stop it.
Yeah. Yeah. And guess what, Dusty? It's
recorded that you're not meeting me.
Yeah. 3 years later, you're not meeting me. Simple.
Do you really think? Okay, think about
it like this, right? There could be
there could be a boxer that loses and
loses and loses and now he suddenly
starts getting better now. Now he's
winning. No. So that's what where was I?
I opened the door and told him to [ __ ]
off. Think about it, bro. Listen,
listen, listen. I was in the window. I
opened the door and I told him to [ __ ]
off. I went outside and I mocked him. I
didn't need to open that door. I didn't
need to open that door. I knew it was
him straight away. I did not need to
open that door.
I didn't need to open that door at all.
>> You still there, Joker? I went through
the window and I went and I went
downstairs and I said, "Yeah, what you
going to do? [ __ ] off." Do you think any
of you people
>> Bro, listen. I'm going jail. No, you're
not, bro. I'll come on your door.
Listen. Listen, Billy. Billy. Billy.
Billy. Right. Listen, bro. Listen. You
get You email me your address and I will
come on your door. I'll come in your
mom's door. No, no, no. Because this is
what pisses me off, bro. Yeah. These
people are here trying to act about it.
I will come in your mom's door. I will
see. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Listen, listen, listen.
>> Little dance guy.
>> One second. One second, bro. Email me.
>> Email me. I'm not going to dox you. I
don't want to dox you. I don't want to
do I will come in your mom's door.
>> I will come in your mom's door.
>> I ain't got No. No. No. You made a
statement. You made a statement. One
second. One second, bro. It doesn't
matter if you live with your mom. I'm
going to go on her door and I'm going to
and I'm going to go live at your mom's door.
>> I wouldn't even want to hurt you. That's the fact.
>> Come on, bro. What you scared of? What
are you scared of?
>> I'm not scared.
>> You don't Doesn't matter if you don't
live with your mom. I will go on her
door and I'll do her windows in. >> Listen.
>> And I want to see you go jail. Come on,
big man. Come on. Come on.
>> Cuz it'll be serious damage. >> Yeah.
>> So, you're not doing it, bro. You're not
doing it. You're not doing this at your
>> This is what I mean. You're idiots, bro.
>> About you're going to go to jail. You're
not going to go to jail, bro. You would
probably watch your mom get slapped up.
>> You would watch your mom get slapped up,
bro. I'm telling you. Yeah. Right now,
Joker, if if L J went on these people's
doors, they wouldn't have even opened
the door, bro.
>> [ __ ] melt,
>> bro. I'm telling you, if you, me, or
anyone went on these people's doors,
they wouldn't even open their door, bro.
They wouldn't even open their door.
Think about it, bro. How long have they
had people's addresses? Multiple
people's addresses, mine, bellies, and
they ain't they ain't come on no one's
door, bro. They They ain't come on
anyone's door. Yeah. Problem is
>> anyone's door.
>> Yeah. Uh my email is it pjx@yahoo.com. I
don't want I want your mom's bro. I want
your mom's door.
>> You said that you're going to go jail.
You said you're going to go to jail, big
man. Come on. Yeah. Izzpjxyoo.com.
Listen, if anybody went on these
people's doors on this community, they
would not even open the door, bro. They
would look through that spy hole and
[ __ ] it. They wouldn't even open the
door, bro. That is that's that that is
one you definitely definitely can say
about these people.
>> We don't
>> I don't know about Prime, but I know
definitely definitely these people would
have not they would not open their door, bro.
>> I don't think they would. I think LT
might maybe, but I don't think you know
these people would. Yeah,
>> trust me. There's a lot of people trying
to help you and
>> you wouldn't do anyone. You wouldn't do
anything if someone knocked on your
door. You would not come out that door,
bro. You would not come out that door,
>> You would not come out that door.
>> I hid behind my mom again. I hid in
front of my mom. You might want to watch
the video again properly. I was in front
of my mom again. You might want to
rewatch it. You're getting angles
confused, lad. And guess what, Joker?
You told me to come to Newcastle and you hid.
>> I've never told you to come to Newcastle.
>> No, Triple H told me to come to
Newcastle and he hid.
>> PJ, I'm not your
>> You hid, bro. So, what how does anyone
believe that you're going to do anything?
>> You've told people to come to Newcastle.
>> People come to Newcastle. You didn't
come out. So, why would anyone believe
anything you've got to say,
>> mate? I'm [snorts] not your enemy.
>> Telling me to come to Newcastle, bro.
You told me to come to Newcastle and you
didn't come out. >> Never.
>> [ __ ] what a clown, bro. And you
expect You think someone's [snorts]
you think someone like you is really
going to do anything?
>> Mate, I never said I was going to do it.
But I've never if I wanted to do anything.
>> Listen, PJ, if I wanted to do something,
I could do it right now. I [ __ ]
>> Joker. Do you know Timmy's channel?
No, but you're [ __ ] going on a mad one.
>> No, but what's Timy's channel?
>> [ __ ] no.
>> You don't know his channel?
>> I would literally [ __ ] help you, but
you're [ __ ] just acting crazy.
>> What's his channel, bro?
>> I don't know what the [ __ ] wrong with
you, mate. Like,
>> what's Timmy's channel?
>> Fruit Mad World, ain't it?
>> How do you know?
>> Everyone knows Fruit Mad World. Yeah,
you would never meet me, bro, because
you're a coward. Yeah, you would never
meet me because you're a coward.
>> I would [ __ ] meet you today.
>> Yeah, if you're pray, you would never
meet me cuz you're a coward, bro. Three
times I locked up to your city. You
didn't even come out, bro. G.
And you know it as well.
Yeah, you know as well.
You know, bro. You know, [ __ ] [ __ ]
You people wouldn't even open your
doors, bro. If someone come on your
door, you wouldn't even open your door,
bro. That's a fact.
You wouldn't even open that front door,
bro. You're not about that life.
You're not about that life, bro.
You're really not about that life.
Well, I know what someone's about when
I've rocked up to their city a few times
and they've not come out. I think I have
a pretty good idea of what that person's about. You know,
yeah, we've seen me confront a bouncer.
We've seen me try to meet Arsenal Mark.
We've seen me stick it on two guys. But
you seem to forget all of them things as
well. But you are biased. So yeah, but
you are biased. And you've also seen me
stick it on more people in this
community than any of you ever have and will. So yeah. Yeah.
You'd never meet a disabled man. Why?
You're disabled yourself.
It's fair. I mean, that's pretty fair to
be fair. But that is pretty honest, lad.
Like, you're you're disabled yourself.
So, you could easily meet someone,
you know. No, but I'm saying you. I'm
saying you're disabled.
You're not saying me, but I'm saying you're disabled.
No, but I'm saying you're disabled. So
if you met a disabled person, it would be fair.
They were saying,
"Yeah, sorry, LJ." Yeah, but guess what,
bro? You're not going to meet me, so it
doesn't matter. I also stuck on a
bouncer. I stuck on two people last
month. No one cares. You know what I'm saying?
So anyways, I'm more than happy, bro.
Listen, disabled. The only people on
here disabled are you people. That's why
you come on here every day repeating the
same [ __ ] cuz you are disabled. So
before trying to talk about other people,
right? Right. Have you gave me your
mom's postcode yet, Billy? Have you gave
me your mom's postcode yet?
You can't even beat Gas, bro. You've
never even beat a Gas. You're still a
virgin. I've been with more women than
you. You're virgin. This is what I'm
saying about how I don't understand why
you was defending them.
Bro, I beat more gas than you. You're
virgin. Everyone see my YouTube channel
liping up people, kissing people. You
little white knight virgin. And I'll
beat you up. Come and meet me. Why don't
one of you people meet me then? Why
don't one of you people come on my door
right now, bro? Why don't you know where
I live? So why don't you come right now?
I'll wait for you.
No, we don't want to be watch. We want
to watch you little clowns. We want to
watch you little clowns back down for
me. That's what we want to watch. You
little clowns. We're not interested,
bro, in in repeating [ __ ]
because you said that if if someone you
said if someone gives your you said that
if bro Oh, don't use my mom as an
excuse. I lived by myself for a year.
You still didn't come. Yeah. Stop using
my mom as an excuse. This is another
thing you little [ __ ] used to do. Oh,
you live with your mom and then I lived
with by myself and none of you came.
Bro, you you're full of excuses. You
done the same when I lived by myself
for over a year and one time three years
or two years. Sorry. You You're full of
excuses. Just shut up, man. It's embarrassing now.
That that thing is so boring. Oh, you
live with your mom. Oh my god. I used to
hear that all the time in the old house.
Mommy went, no one came.
So that's another weak excuse. That's
another weak excuse. Will you live with
your mom? Yeah, we used to hear that all
the time. We can't go cuz you live with your
>> like [ __ ] bring that up.
>> [ __ ] off, bro.
>> Hey, if I [ __ ] met you, I do some
serious damage. Like, I wouldn't want
>> Well, then stop making stupid statements.
>> I'm not making stupid I'm trying to be your friend.
>> I'm going to knock him out.
>> I joke. I'm going to knock him out. Do
you remember that one?
>> Yeah, but why say that?
>> Yeah, but Timmy Timmy said it. Yeah, you
could [ __ ] do it against Timmy, but
>> No, but Timmy said I'm going to knock him out.
>> Yeah, but UK asylum, man, it's okay for
you to hit disabled people. You're disabled yourself.
>> You're disabled yourself. So,
>> you knock half these [ __ ] out regardless.
>> You know what? Watch when I get one of
these people's addresses. Joker, you
watch what I'm going to do, bro. Yeah,
you watch what I'm going to do. >> Huh?
>> You're mad against them. like [ __ ]
>> watch when I get one of these people's
addresses. It's they're going to get
docked, bro. And I'm going to go on
their [ __ ] door, bro.
>> I'm saying Peter, you don't need to do that. Like,
>> forget them all. Like, just treat them.
>> Yeah, I am bringing trouble. I'm
bringing my I'm bringing trouble to my
mom's door now. Yeah, I am bringing
trouble. Yeah, now I am bringing
trouble. Yeah, now I am. Yeah. So, you
you you better bring trouble then, might you? Yeah.
No, I don't need to bet myself. Why
don't you bet yourself? Why don't you
get off of YouTube?
Why don't you [ __ ] get off of YouTube?
That's what you need to do. Why don't
you mind your own business and get off
of YouTube? Stop repeating every day. [ __ ] clown
to go to the Armor Road. We're not
talking about Banger. We're talking
about you little clowns.
[ __ ] idiots, man.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> Don't worry about me better than myself.
Don't you worry about me, bro. Is that right, Joker?
Or a Joker?
Yeah. They hate me. I hate them. I'm
getting revenge on them. So, you're not
going to be hearing it soon.
Yeah, they are all the same. So what?
Yep, all women are the same. So what?
Anyways, I'm coming off this in a bit.
I'm going to go on Reddit, I think. Yeah,
might be on tomorrow. Might not. Well,
I'm not going to cinema tomorrow, so
I'll probably be on tomorrow to be fair.
It's [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, they all the same. So what?
Yeah, you're on YouTube. Oh, incel. Oh,
I'd rather be an incel than be a white
knight like you, mate.
knight like you.
Yeah. than a white knight like you
defending women for the sake of defending women.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm an incel. Yeah.
Anyone that don't lick women's asses is
an insult, aren't they? Yeah. Yeah.
So, do you get rejected? You don't even
have a girlfriend, which makes me laugh
that you defend women when they don't
even like you.
Yeah. Same same to you. You don't even
have a girlfriend yourself.
Yeah, you don't even have a girlfriend
yourself. You also get rejected. You sad bastard. [snorts] >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, I'll do what I want.
Is Timmy live? PJ. >> Yeah.
>> Stop letting him get to you, brother.
>> I want to see if Timmy's live.
What the [ __ ]
I just went on Timmy's live. Yeah. And I
got a picture.
This is pathetic now. No.
>> Look, this is what I found on Timmy's channel.
Yeah, I think that guy.
>> He needs to get off YouTube. Just Timmy, man.
>> Yeah, so do you.
>> He needs to get off the YouTube.
Why don't he just get off YouTube? Just leave it.
>> PJ, when I first met you on YouTube, you
were now. What the [ __ ] No,
>> you need to get off of YouTube, bro.
I [snorts] can't believe this Monty and
Rice thing is still going.
>> Yeah, but they're [ __ ] both like
[ __ ] degenerate [ __ ]
[laughter] How do you put yourself on them levels?
>> It's funny, isn't it?
>> It's not funny, PJ. Like unless you put
yourself on them levels,
>> well, I'm going I'm going on Reddit and
then going to bed.
>> Yeah, you're [ __ ] going really these
little trolls following you. You need to
[ __ ] sort your [ __ ] up, [ __ ] If you
want me to help you, I'll genuinely help
you, but you have to help.
>> No, I'm I'm on Reddit.
>> Yeah, you're massive trolls following
me. No, but I don't post anything, so
they can't find me.
>> Everyone finds you, man.
>> They don't find me because I PM people.
I private message people. I don't post anything. Look,
>> if you want real help, you got a few
people that can gender, but you just
need to sort [ __ ] out, man.