Just checking just to see who's still on YouTube.
That's what I'm doing.
Checking to see who's on YouTube still.
You know this little routine.
If you're going to write something at
least let someone reply back, you know.
disrespectful just like you. You
ignoring is disrespectful.
>> You reply to negative things straight
away though, don't you? Notice that
uh you reply to negative things straight
away at 7:39 in the morning.
No, not really. Same old, same old.
Unfortunately, I woke up today. I was
hoping I died in my sleep, but
unfortunately I woke up. I know. It's
sad, isn't it?
I wish I just went to sleep and not woke
up, bro. Oh, someone replied, by the
way. Of course they would. They reply to
anything negative. Whether it's
insulting, whether it's someone winging,
whether it's a dick picture, they're
always so fast enough to reply to
negativity and then block you so you
can't even reply back to them. The little rats.
I said I had to message them through
SMS. I said, "Yeah, it's disrespectful."
Just like you ignoring people is disrespectful, [ __ ]
Yeah. And that's what it cost me now cuz
they were from a different country.
Yeah. Bit like you keep ignoring people, [ __ ] [ __ ]
That's also disrespectful, but you don't
see me crying about it. [ __ ] off, you know.
So, no, I went to bed at like I think 7
in the morning. I'm staying in bed all day today.
I was going to go cinema, but couldn't be [ __ ] Nope.
I'm not getting out of bed today.
Someone reply back Grezy. Oh, that's disrespectful.
Yeah, just like you ignoring is disrespectful
and disgusting. Yeah, just like you
ignoring I had to I had to SMS them but
they cuz they block they block me on
WhatsApp so I had to SMS them. I said
just like you ignoring is disgusting and disrespectful.
They didn't they didn't say anything
back to it. Yeah,
they didn't say anything back to it.
I'm just not going I'm just not I'm just
not getting out of bed today, bro. I'm
just doing nothing. Just like tomorrow.
Just like the next day.
It's a depressing life here, isn't it?
Every day is exactly the same. I don't
know how people on Reddit tell you that
it will change. Nothing ever changes in
this life. Maybe for the worst, but
that's about it.
It's like what Adman says yesterday,
it's like you got every right to be pissed off
after what they've done. You have every
right to speak your mind. He's he's right though.
Does talk a lot of sense. Bro,
I'll probably go back to sleep soon to
be honest. This is depressing, bro. I
don't even know what the point I woke up
for. Don't need to eat yet.
Yeah, I'll probably be going back to
sleep in a minute. To be fair, just
going to drink this tea.
I'm just going to drink this tea and go sleep. Yeah.
Wish you could just sleep your life
away. That'd be good, isn't it? If you
could just sleep, sleep, wake up, food,
sleep. It would be It'd be lovely, in
it, bro. Lovely.
You know, this is depressing, bro. I
don't even know why I woke up. I was all
right sleeping. Why have I woke up for
this again? About more bad experiences
with women. [ __ ] that.
I'll be going back to bed in about 15 minutes
and then going back to sleep again and
going back to sleep again and going back
to sleep again and then going back to
sleep again and then going back to sleep
again and then going back to sleep again again.
Simple. That's what I'm doing, bro. [ __ ] this.
I'm saying absolutely [ __ ] this.
[ __ ] this for a game of [ __ ]
[ __ ] this for a game of soldiers.
Good for them.
Yeah, good for them.
And I shouldn't be sat here without a
sex life with bad experiences with
women. So, good for them.
At least they could actually change
their life. At least they these people
could actually change their life if they
wanted to. It might take a while, but
they I'm pretty sure they could change their life.
Well, I might as well have been I might
well I might as well be a disabled person.
I might as well be in a wheelchair. So,
you know, you can't take a day off of
YouTube. So, don't try don't try and
tell me about quitting YouTube. You
can't even You can't even take a day off
for YouTube, lad. So, worry about
yourself. Don't worry about what I do.
But yeah, I might as well been in I
might as well been with I might as well
been like Timmy. I might as well been
born like Timmy.
Then I can be like, "Oh, I can I can see
now. Yeah, I can see. Yeah, I'm I'm a
[ __ ] I'm like Timmy." Rubbing the
[ __ ] back of my head. I might as well
been born Timmy Eldridge.
basically might as well been born like
Timmy just cuz then I could I could be
like, "Oh, okay. That's why I I know now
I'm a [ __ ] like Timmy."
You know what I'm saying?
Nah, he's not dead. Just doesn't come on YouTube.
And they're not even trolls. They're just spastics.
I don't know why why we're normalizing
this. They're not trolls. These people
are spastics. Just like the people that
go for me, they're spastics. They're not
trolls. They're just disabled repeating people.
But yeah, anyways,
but I might as well been born like I
might as well been born like Timmy Eldridge.
I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't give a [ __ ] if there's people
worse off than me. Worse off, better
than me. I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't give a [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
I've basically been homeless. I don't
give a [ __ ] you know.
Good for them.
Good for them. Well, no. Why should I
have empathy for them? They don't have
empathy for me. No one has empathy for
me after all of the [ __ ] I've been
dealing with these [ __ ] women for
[ __ ] years and years and [ __ ]
years. So why the [ __ ] am I going to
have empathy for them, lad?
And not really.
Again, we're not getting into that
again. That's repeating
and that's not something that needs to
be brought up. That's repeating that.
Yeah, that's repeating. That was last
month. We're in a different month now. So yeah,
why are we still talking about that? I
was really thinking of calling out that
prime yesterday, bro. really really
thinking of starting some madness up cuz
it wouldn't be right for me to pick on
women if I can't come and go and knock
this [ __ ] out. You know what I'm saying?
Griez, I really was thinking of doing a
video, you know, bro.
Really, really thinking of like starting
madness again. Really, really, really
thinking of starting madness, bro.
Talking about [ __ ] LJ's kids up
again. I was thinking of starting
madness again, bro. Seriously. Yeah.
When I say that was then I retract the
sorry and I'm starting to talk about
kids again. So you need to you need to
you need to you need to teach me a
lesson. I need to be taught a good old
I was going to say prime. I'll be your
I'll be your kid's new daddy. Yeah. I'll
be your kid's new daddy. That's that's
even that's even worse, bro. Yeah.
[ __ ] little [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, I'll be his kid new daddy. I'll be
Father Christmas. I'll be I'll be his
kid's new [ __ ] daddy, bro. >> Yeah.
Finish his tea. Go back to sleep. Yay.
What a fun life, eh? Yay.
Not answering your stupid question.
I've took weeks off of YouTube. I've
took days off of YouTube.
And I've already fighted people on
YouTube. But again, you people are
biased. So, we're not going to get into
that conversation again. So yeah,
bomb. We're not going to get into that
conversation again. Bomb, get a life.
[ __ ] sake. You've been doing this for
[ __ ] years now. Get a [ __ ] life.
>> Yeah, they make you miserable really.
The bad experiences make you miserable.
They make you miserable. They make you
think about it all day miserable. It
really, really, really does make you miserable.
And so it should. And so it should.
That American uh blocked me yesterday on Snapchat
getting another struggle dismisser.
Dismissing people struggles.
Dismissing people's struggles.
And Adman's right. You should be mad at
people that hating on you. It's the truth.
Yeah, that's doing you dirty. It's the
truth. It is the truth.
It really, really is the truth. You
should be hate. You should be angry at
people that are doing that, you know. Yeah.
But yeah, we've seen you people. You're
biased anyways. Why do Why do you want
Why do you want people to fight anyways? You're biased.
Even when you're shown wrong, you still
talk [ __ ] The bouncer, the two people
sitting down. You talk [ __ ] every time.
Why do Why does it bother you if if I'm
fighting? You're just going to make up
stuff anyways like you always do.
You're always going to make up stuff.
You're going to keep making up stuff,
making up stuff, making up stuff. So,
right, like you've done the past three
or four times. So, why does that bother
you? What I say?
You're going to make up stories anyways
like you always do. They can't hit you
there at work. Someone stuck it on me
when they clearly didn't even stand up
once. You would always make up dumb excuses.
That's what you sados do on here. So why
do you want to why do you why do you
even want to see people fighting?
Just like the Mark Samson thing never
gets brought up. You're biased, jealous people.
But Prime I would make an exception for
cuz I know that that's that in it.
Look at this ghost. And this guy didn't
get called out for what he done. We
yesterday when he come on the chat, no
one said anything. They're all biased on
here. Biased. Autistic
idiots. That's what they are. Morons.
They will ne That's why I don't I will
never meet anyone. That's why I will
never meet. Prime I will. Prime I will
cuz I that's that's an exception. But
these other people I will never meet
them. I won't show money. I won't meet.
I avoid any kind of conflict with these
people because because
well I didn't lose because he doesn't
even live there.
But he doesn't even live there. So,
but it doesn't matter anyways. 1-1 1
nil. No one said anything about it.
Just like they don't say anything when
you show them thousands. They're just
they're just all biased jealous people.
They're always going to be like this on here.
Just like the [ __ ] the Ferrar the
same the same with that [ __ ] It's
just normal on here now what they do, you know.
They seem forced enough to reply when
when you when neg negativity.
They're forced enough to be there when
negativity is sent. Is it Grezy?
Concerning, eh? Uh, same old same old.
Depressed. I'm going back to sleep in a minute.
But yeah, it's like the bouncer. You you
fight the bouncer and apparently you're
uh apparently Oh, he's at work. He's at
work. He's at work.
They always make excuses, bro.
They always make excuses.
I don't agree with Joker and I don't
agree with Joe. They don't do it for a reaction.
But then you realize when you're
explaining this stuff, you're explaining
it to autistic people, which is why you
have to repeat yourself over and over
again because it's like you repeat
yourself and then you repeat yourself
again and it still doesn't register in their brain.
Like I've had to say a million times to
about three different people that it's
not about a reaction because even if you
do not react to them, they will still do
it. It's not about a reaction and no
matter how many times you explain it,
they it doesn't see the process in their
brain. So that's what makes me think a
lot of people on here have got some kind
of mental illness where you have to keep
explaining stuff that doesn't sink in their brain, you know.
So that's how you end up with a headache
because you're trying to you're you're
surrounding yourself with autistic
people that that don't have a brain.
So what what's going to happen after 2 3 days? Huh?
Be like that.
Oh, look at this [ __ ] response. Um, Reezy.
Yeah, I'll reply to this message. I I
would just reply to this message because
it's not worth it. Even if I was
ignoring you because I was doesn't mean
that you can send photos of your dick to
me. That's just childish behavior. I
think even a child is more maturing than
you. I don't think what you would expect
to happen by sending photos. I honestly
don't care. I'll do what I want. And you
honestly do care by replying.
You care by replying.
You want to talk about I quote second maturity
when you're sat there ignoring someone.
Make it make sense there.
So the irony of an ignorer telling
someone they're more immature than a
child. Someone that ignores
an ignorer is is talking about maturity.
Oh dear, dewy me.
And it does mean that because I'll do
exactly what I want cuz I just did. So
lucky these people can't get the police
involved greasy cuz different countries
and that in it. [laughter] Yeah.
[ __ ] off, mate. I'll send you what the
[ __ ] I want when I want. You're not
talking about maturity when you're the
one that's sat there ignoring people,
[ __ ] [ __ ] off. You know what I'm saying?
You obviously do care. You obviously do
care when you're the one that's replying
and and and blocking.
So, you obviously do care, you know, by
by responding. You obviously do care. If
you didn't care, you wouldn't have
responded just like you hadn't been the
past six months
over a period of time. It's so funny,
bro. This person as well,
this [ __ ] person is like
I don't know what they are, bro. They're
like slightly below average and they're
kind of overweight. And you got these
[ __ ] thinking they're better than you.
It does mean I do what I want. So, it
does mean that I would do exactly what I
want. You don't tell me. You're not my
[ __ ] mother. You're not my [ __ ]
father. You don't tell me what to do.
Don't tell me about maturity when you're
sat there ignoring someone, you [ __ ]
You know what I mean?
And I didn't expect anything to happen.
I just sent it because Yeah. I wanted
you to wake up to something gross. Yeah.
A lot of people blocked me when I sent
it though, Greavves. Yeah, a lot of
people did. I just find it so mad how
they're so fast to react to any kind of negativity,
[ __ ] talking them, dick pitches, or
moaning or anything drastic. They're
they're there. They're literally there. You know,
[ __ ] off you [ __ ]
You know, they're literally there before
you could say Jack Robinson.
They are literally there before you can
say Jack Robinson.
They're there straight away. 7:39 in the
morning. They're there straight away.
But don't forget, Grezy, not all women
are the same.
Not all women are the same. Remember,
not all women are the same.
No, not all of them. They just do act
do the same thing. But they're not all
the same. Did you not know that by now?
You don't say one word to someone and
they pretend they've got a boyfriend.
You don't get people's numbers and they
lead you on and play victim. No,
they're not all the same. What would
make you think they're all the same?
No. So many similarities, but not all
the same. No, no, no.
To that I always say there's no one in
the world like me cuz no one's the same
as me. There is not one person in the
world that does act and say the things
that I do.
So that's the definition of being
different. And I always say this to
them, Grezy, if they're not all the
same, why do they act, do, and have the
same mannerisms? And they can never answer it
cuz they're all the [ __ ] same. If you
went out right now,
no, no, no. They are definitely
definitely definitely definitely all the same.
Just because they might look different,
they are all the same. Just cuz they
might look different, they them as a
person is all the same.
Just like if somebody looked different
than me and they were the same as me,
they would be the same as me. But no
one's the same as me cuz I'm different.
These women are not different.
I don't know how people can sit there
and say women aren't all the same and
they do act. They've all got Tik Tok brains.
They've all got them Tik Tok batteries
and maybe if you take the Tik Tok
batteries out there, you know, like a
dolly where they've got batteries like
Chucky, they've got Tik Tok batteries.
Yeah. Once you take the Tik Tok back
batteries out the back
then they might be different. It's like
they've got B. It's like they've got Tik
Tok batteries. They are literally all
the same. If you watch any of these
approaching videos, you will see they
are literally all the same.
I will just reply to this messages this
message because it's not worth it. Yeah,
she's talking about childish behavior
when she's ignoring people. How does
that make sense?
You get a job. You get a job.
You get a [ __ ] job. How can you talk
about childish behavior when you're sat
there ignoring like a [ __ ]
Just just throw that out there. Grezy,
I thought I was mature. I thought I was immature.
I really thought I was immature. you
know, agrees. I always thought I was
really immature, but to the these women
are more immature than anyone. And I'm very immature.
I laugh at anything, but not like they
not the these [ __ ] are really immature.
They've all got the same attitude as
well. But you obviously do care.
You obviously do care to a flyer, you
[ __ ] [ __ ] You know,
I think I got food poisoning, Grezy. I
was on the toilet 10 times yesterday. I
don't think that chicken was cooked properly.
Oh, there's even maturity to me. Yeah,
coming from the person that ignores.
[ __ ] off, you stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] You
don't even know what I'm going to say next, bro.
Look at this [ __ ] via text.
If a child's more mature than me, then a
[ __ ] baby's more mature than you, then.
That's what I'm going to write. If a
baby's If a baby's more mature than you,
one second. I'm going to roast this. One
Then a toddler. No. No. One second, bro. Easy.
Repeat on here. But yeah,
it's got roasted.
They're all very very good.
Very, very good until they meet their
match. These [ __ ] it's because they're
so used to dealing with like white
knights and simps, so people never give
it back to them. But they don't know
about Peter Belly. Grezy, they don't
know about Peter Belly.
You could just You just know they're
[ __ ] Just the what? Just the way
they're writing, Grezy. The way they're
writing, you can just tell that they're [ __ ]
I think even a child is more mature than
you. I said, "Bro, if a child's more
mature than me, then a [ __ ] toddler
is more [ __ ] mature than you then,
isn't it?" sat there [ __ ] ignoring
someone. [ __ ] annoying. How How are
you telling someone about a child
when you're the one ignoring? That's the
most immature thing someone can do. [ __ ] off.
You can tell she's a [ __ ] as well by um
by the way they're writing. They're all
[ __ ] They've all got the same attitude.
Who do they think they are? And this
[ __ ] is [ __ ] fat and like a four out
of 10. Who the [ __ ] do they think they are?
Even if I was ignoring you because I
was. I told her to go get you know
[ __ ] what? Drop the attitude. I said
go get [ __ ] you know what and drop
the [ __ ] attitude.
I'll be the one to put your ego into place again.
Don't know where your egos come from,
but I'll be the one to put your I'll be
I'll be the one to put it back to where
it's supposed to be again. Cuz that's
what it is with a lot of these um these
little [ __ ] [ __ ] Greasy. Yeah.
They need to put them back in their
place. Not below their place, but back
in their place where they should be
cuz it seems like they're they think
they're four or five stars above what
the [ __ ] they are. So, you know, they
they actually need putting in their
their ego needs putting back into place.
Are you talking about childish behavior
when you're sat there ignoring you
[ __ ] stupid little rape victims?
[ __ ] off, mate. You know, [ __ ] off.
Talking about a child.
I don't actually I don't to finish Izzy
as well. Um
I don't to finish Izzy.
Yeah. My dick
because I can. I do it cuz I can. Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
won't be live long by the way.
Got banned off Reddit earlier. It's such
a power hungry site, isn't it?
This is um this is part of the mods have
got absolutely no life outside Reddit.
It flags up and then they just ban you.
They're [ __ ] losers, bro.
Only power hungry site I know is Reddit.
They're so power hungry.
Like you should see how many people get
banned. You can you can see right people
commenting deleted, deleted, deleted,
deleted, deleted, deleted, deleted.
They're so [ __ ] power hungry. I've
never known anything like it in my life.
They probably masturbate every time they
[ __ ] every time they ban you. It's [ __ ] pathetic.
Sad bastards. Sad, sad, sad bastards.
Sat there looking at a screen all day.
It hurts your eyes, you know. I've done
it for two days.
Reddit mods are the saddest people ever.
Yeah, I'm [ __ ] as well. Not financially
because I post about women and stuff. Yeah.
me. Every time I make a new account now,
they ban me. It's like, oops, a certain
action can't be performed. So, they ban
you even if you don't post. They they IP
ban you and then when it flags up, they
just click ban. It makes them feel powerful.
I'm [ __ ] as well, but not financially
Just womenly [ __ ] basically.
Sad times, is it? Sad times. It will
never change. Never change.
I got a really bad stomach, man. I'm
sure it was that chicken.
I don't know if it was cooked properly or not.
I was an ignorer trying to call someone childish.
How's a [ __ ] ignorer trying to call someone childish?
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] about Christmas.
Months, months. There were being months
and months and months.
They were doing it for months, bro. They
only replied once saying, "Oh, I don't
think I'll be able to make it." Even
though they were still in London and
then they were just ignoring. I wasn't
messaging him all the time.
I won't message him. I don't like them.
I just don't like ignoras.
They need to drop the attitude.
They really need to drop the attitude. These people,
I'm going to deprive you of content,
greasy poor [ __ ] Yeah.
Oh, and there's this tenant, Grezy, that
I used to be friends with, not the one
that you know about, years ago, and was
messaging. I was like, "Oh, you're back
in London. This is how snaky they are."
I said, "Oh, we should meet up." And
they are, you know what I mean? They're
rats. They're snakes. And they don't
even reply. I was I was thinking to dash
them, and they weren't replying.
They wasn't replying. Um, Grezy, they're
all rats. They're all snakes.
They're all snakes, bro. Greasy. They're all rats.
Yeah, and they just weren't responding
all of a sudden. So, yeah, I blocked
them. I don't like ignores on my Instagram.
And they know me as well. It's not like
they didn't know me and they weren't
talking to me before. So, it's like,
what the [ __ ] You know, it's not like
you just message a random person and
then when they're caught being in London
and then when they're caught being in
London, they're trying to [ __ ] just
It just annoys me, bro. It really really
does annoy me. So, I just block them.
cuz I would have ended up just saying madness.
I hate all women, bro. I hate all women.
I don't miss any of them. I hate all of
I hate all of the [ __ ]
So I just block them in the end.
because these women are in different
countries. I'm smart, bro. You think I'm
going to do that to someone that lives
in England? I'm smart. Of course, they
they would call the police, but
obviously they it's got to be a lot
harder for them to do that in a different country.
Like I'm not stupid, bro. I know that's
the first thing they do. Do you really
think I'm going to say that stuff to
someone that lives in England?
Well, like via a message. Like
seriously, I know what these rat women
are about grassing and trying to play
victim and [ __ ]
You really think someone's going to do
that, bro? This person lives in Spain.
One in Spain, one in Finland. I mean,
they can call the police, but I mean,
the chances are that it's going to be a
lot harder, isn't it? And take a lot
longer. So, I was very smart. There was
one in Ireland, though, to be fair. So, yeah. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah. Who the [ __ ] does this [ __ ] think
they are with attitude, bro?
These women need definitely definitely
putting in their place.
Definitely definitely need putting in
their place. These [ __ ] women. They
definitely need putting in their place.
Look at them. Who the [ __ ] do they think
they are? I'm looking at these messages
and who the [ __ ] do they think they are?
That's like That's like a common That's
like a common saying, bro. You know what I mean?
Yeah. And that finish one, I sent her my
dick for being a [ __ ] and leading me on.
So you want to play games and be
immature. Why can't I be immature?
Why can't I be immature? Greavves. If
they want to be immature, why can't I be immature?
Maybe I want to. Maybe I want to fit in.
Maybe I want to be immature as well. You know,
this woman definitely needed putting in
her place. Where did that ego come from?
Where does this their ego come from?
what I was just looking at, bro. You
didn't see what, bro? Where did that
come from, bro? That ego for someone
that looks like you. You got a [ __ ]
big ego, mate.
Who the [ __ ] did they think they are, bro? Jesus Christ.
They are literally all the [ __ ] same.
I don't know how people can sit there
and try and tell you that these women
are not all the [ __ ] same. Must be
having a laugh. They must be They must
literally be having a laugh.
They are literally all the [ __ ] same, bro.
You don't tell me anything, mate. I know
more than you would ever know about this country.
How is someone like that How is someone
that's fat and ugly having an ego like that? Really, bro? So, yeah. Madness.
A child is more immature than me when
you're the one that's mature than me
when you're the one that's ignoring.
Really, I I think sending a dick picture
is a lot less immature than someone sat
there ignoring someone, you know, [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] idiot, man. [ __ ] off. Come
Women on Reddit say that women aren't
all the same. Indigo,
what do you think about that?
Bro, even below average ones have ego.
Even below average ones have have egos.
Even below average.
This one that was on the text was about
a three, four out of 10 overweight.
How long have you been waiting? Not
long. Just a week or so.
I'll be live. Still waiting. I'll be
I'll be live. Yeah. I'll still be live.
You You'll be I'll be alive. I I'll be
I'll be live seven days, Greasy. You'll
come back and I'll be like You'll be
like, "Are you still waiting?" I'll be
like, "Not long. Just a week or so.
I'll stay alive for a week.
Just like this. Look.
And they'll be like, "You still there?"
I said, "You'll be like, "Are you still waiting?"
Not long. Just a week or so. Yeah.
Stay live. just waiting. Yeah.
Did you see the wild simp appear
yesterday when I said about sending uh
women dick pictures unsolicited? I said
I'm absolutely sending them unsolicited
dick pictures. I absolutely am and I'm
proud of it. He said, "Oh, you're doing
that." I said, "Yep, and I'm proud of
it." Loud and proud.
You ever heard that saying, Grezy? Loud
and proud. Yes, I bloody well am. And
you're not doing anything. They're not
doing anything. And the police aren't
doing anything cuz they live in another
country. Peter Benny smart, mate.
Because you have to, you need to
understand with these little victims, Grevy, is
they they try to get rude
to people because they assume that
you're going to react like these white
knights and these simps and [ __ ] And
then when they realize that you put them
in their place, what's the next thing they do?
When all else fails, what's the what's
the what do they do? It's the boys in
blue, mate. It's the boys in blue.
We've seen it a million times before.
When all else fails, it's the boys in
blue, mate. But obviously, they can't do that when
they're in a different country. [laughter]
Oh, yeah. You know, so
I don't think that the police should get
involved with stuff like that, you know,
like if you send them dick pictures or
you give them [ __ ] I don't think they
should. I think that should be done
through a civil matter because if
they're allowed if they're allowed Grezy
to lead people on and give attitude, why
can't you give it back to them?
I I I I think they need to change the
laws in this country. I need to I think
they need to change the laws in this country, bro.
Grezy, I'm going to contact the MP.
Are you pissed off with the MP? Zippy, I
need we need to There's some laws that
need to change in this country.
I generally think, okay, so I'll tell
you about fair, right? So, you know, all
that [ __ ] I done to USA is I didn't get
nicked. Yeah, that's fair. I think
that's fair. No, if me, if I got nicked,
that would be unfair because they got
away with what they're doing and then I
got nicked. That's the way it should be.
If they want to be [ __ ] or lead people
on or troll people, then they should get
it back. Especially if it's over
texting, there shouldn't be no law
against it. I I I think they need to
change the laws.
I think they need to change the laws. Me personally,
yeah, we need to we need to change the
laws. Like I said, Greg, you're going to
see me on ITV once one time in my little
suit. My little suit and my man bun
saying, you know, speak speaking my
mind. It needs to change.
Definitely. I think some laws need to
change. Definitely. They should not be
able to get police involved via social media stuff,
by you reacting to people. Cuz if I was
in America, I would have got Nick. I
would have got nicked doing that.
[snorts] You know,
you What do you think about it, Greasy?
Do you agree with me?
Maybe we should do some of the Maybe
some of the things that they do should
be illegal. Given their number,
ignoring, leading people on um all I
think all of these things should be illegal.
or if they're not illegal, then anything
that you anything that you say back to
them, it should be fair game
cuz they shouldn't be allowed to do what
they do, you know? They should not be
allowed to do what they do and then get them involved.
Why is it Why is it illegal to send a dick picture?
Yeah, but it shouldn't. But it
shouldn't. If you want to send a dick
picture to a woman ignoring you, that
should be allowed. Why is it okay for
them to do what they do? Ignoring,
leading people on, you know?
You know what I'm saying? That shouldn't
that shouldn't that shouldn't be
allowed? Why should that be allowed?
You don't agree with what, lad?
The dick pitches. I think it should be allowed.
Why not? They're allowed to lead people
on and ignore people and be [ __ ] Why
not? It's only a dick. It's not like
they don't suck a dick. It's not like
they don't [ __ ] people.
It's not like you're sending them child porn.
If they really felt dick pictures was
disgusting, they wouldn't go anywhere
near a dick, let alone put one in their
mouth. So, I don't really really
understand that. They're just
hypocritical to me.
I know most of society won't agree with
me, but that's just my opinion on it.
I think if you find something gross,
then you wouldn't go anywhere near it.
Married, not married. So, it just
doesn't really make a lot of sense.
That's my opinion, though. Even though I
know most people would disagree and
they're entitled to, but that's that's
how I feel.
Yeah, but you Yeah, but you get nicked
for mouthing off to people.
You can get nicked for mouthing off to people.
But even if you mouth off, you can you
can get, you know,
you can get in [ __ ] I was I I went to
the police station uh I think it was in
February or March and the police was
like, "Oh, well yeah, you you we need to
call you about something." They never
did in the end uh about something on
Instagram me arguing with someone. And
I'm thinking, "What? You just said that
you don't get involved with [ __ ]
social media and whatever and now you're
telling me and they never did call me in
the end." So it's like, "What the fuck?"
So, and that would have just been mouthing off.
So, even even if you even if you mouth
off, you're still going to get [ __ ] Two days.
Two days. twice.
I was waiting.
I was waiting for the decision, DJ. I
was waiting in the cell.
Not long. Just a week or so.
Well, I'm not sure it's been made, so
you're not going to be able to watch it.
It's okay. I'll just wait.
You'll wait. Yes. until it's been made.
How about this? I'll I'll I'll let you
know the ve the the the the very
I'll let you know the very moment it
comes in. Yes, the very moment. Please.
I'm a busy man.
As they always are and always will be.
Same old, same old, depressed. Had an
argument with a woman earlier.
Same old, depressed. Was it supposed to
be any different?
I mean, was it supposed to be different?
Was I supposed to wake up and it was
supposed to be different? I had this
argument with this woman, uh, UK silent.
I sent her my dick picture. Yeah. And
then she wrote uh I said, "Hi, I tried
to reply to your message but didn't let
me. It's disrespectful just like you
ignoring it's disrespectful."
Uh she said that uh it was disrespectful
selling my dick and that.
Yeah. No one cares about yourself
reflecting. We've heard it all before. Anyways, um
she said she said this UK asylum. I will
just reply to this message because it's
not worth it. Even if I was ignoring you
because I was, doesn't mean that you can
send photos of your dick to me. That's
just childish baby. And I think even a
child is more mature than you. I don't
know what you expect. It would happen by
sending photos like that. And I honestly
don't care. I said, "I'll do what I
want." And you honestly do care by
replying. You want to talk about
maturity when you're sat there ignoring
someone. Make it make it make sense. If
a child is more mature than me, then a
toddler is more mature than you. [ __ ]
off and get raped and drop the attitude.
Uh, anyways, on to you. Uh, yeah,
Wister, that's self projection. No one
cares about that.
No one cares about your self-reflecting comments. Yeah.
Would you believe this [ __ ] is [ __ ]
overweight and ugly as well?
Jesus Christ. The attitude. Where the
attitude comes from. from these women. I
shall never know. I shall never never know. But
don't write to me being a [ __ ] I
don't think I'm going to say anything
back. Don't even try to be a [ __ ] on
my phone cuz I'll put you straight in
your place again, bro. Back down to
where you're supposed to be.
I already put them where they're
supposed to be.
These simple white knights seem to build
their ego up. Build it. Build it. Build
it. Build it. Build it. Build it. build
it. And then they come across Peter Belly.
Yeah, that's again, Bister, that's self projection.
That's self projection. We don't care
about your self-p projecting comments.
And then they come across Peter Belly
and then Peter Belly puts them in their place.
You're still using that M word. It's
almost 2026, bro.
still telling people to get a job and
you ain't got one yourself. Bro, it's almost 2026
and you're still saying the same stuff
from seven years.
Bro, it's almost 2026
in less than 1 month's time. Now, I
believe you when you say that you don't
show your face because you've got high
IQ. So, if you've got high IQ and you're
intelligent, stop repeating yourself
cuz you're intelligent and I don't want
to put you down, but when you keep
repeating the same [ __ ] for seven years,
it's showing that you're very, very low IQ.
So, again, it's almost 2026. So, think
of some more
projecting words, some new ones.
Entertain us with some new ones cuz
these ones are boring.
very very very very very boring now.
You just repeat the same [ __ ] for years. It's madness.
You must do not get bored of doing it.
Seven years. Seven [ __ ] years you've
been doing this.
Do what you want, bro. Do what you want.
I don't care. [snorts] Yeah.
A child is more mature than me. A
toddler is more mature than you then, isn't it?
I said do what you want.
I just don't understand, bro. That they
say that they don't show their face because
because they've got high IQ, but all
they do is sit repeat the same [ __ ] for
seven, eight years.
I'm a bit confused to be honest.
They said that they're they said that
they're smart people.
We're intelligent. We're not stupid. So
why do you keep repeating the same [ __ ]
for seven years?
The same old [ __ ] has been said for
seven years now daily.
Skin. You go on Timmy's an account just says skin.
Skin skin. Skid skin. What the [ __ ] bro?
Yeah, I've had women and I hate women.
I'm unbiased. See, I'm completely
and they're [ __ ] evil and I hate
them. And I've probably had more women
than anyone on here. Well, a lot of
people on here. I don't know everyone, but yeah,
they seem to think because you say this
stuff about women, you hate women. Uh,
sorry. You you've never been with a woman.
So, you basically have to be a virgin in
order to have a different opinion.
That's basically what they're saying.
Uh, Greaves is that you have to
basically be a virgin.
They believe anyone that doesn't lick
women's asses is a is a virgin basically
or something along that lines. Like then
there's no way you could be with women,
have had women, and sick of them.
There's no way. you. There's absolutely
no way. You have to be a virgin.
You have to have never been. I'm not
talking about uh YouTube. I'm talking
about Reddit. I'm talking about general.
They think that if you they think that
if you moan about women and you complain
about women, you've never been with a
woman or you're a virgin.
You can't just be unbiased and be sick
of them. to them that that's that's not possible. You know,
do you know what I'm saying?
Do you know what I'm saying? So, yeah.
Why do they think that there's not a
third option, Grezy?
A fourth option. You're either white
knight simp on incel. Why not just be
someone that's just sick of women and
not be any of them things?
Why? Why is that not possible for
somebody just to be sick of them?
I just don't understand why there's not
that option there.
You're even m Well, you're even
misogynist on incel. Why can't you just
be someone that has valid reasons for
what they're saying? Why is that not an
option? Because in my case, it should be
an option looking on what they've done,
the bad experiences, but it doesn't seem to be.
This American was saying about my
attitude and I explain multiple times
that these women have got attitude
problems themselves. It gets dismissed
time and time and time and time again.
It's like you're not an actual candidate
in the argument. If you're moaning about
women, you're basically not a candidate.
You're not a candidate in that in in the debate. Basically,
you're talking, but no one can actually hear you.
Yeah. Okay. We've just been I've already
been with women multiple times. We're
not going into that again. But yeah.
Okay. Yeah. That I'm sick of them
because they don't want me. And this is
exactly what I'm saying to you. This is
exactly what I'm saying. They think that
anyone that's got a different opinion
than them can't get a woman or or is a
virgin. This is what I'm trying to say.
There there's no You're basically not
You're talking but they can't hear you.
They're talking greasy but they can't
hear you. It's like you're behind the glass.
You're you're you're saying what's
happening but they they can't hear you,
bro. Cuz you don't actually exist in the
in the debate.
Because if they if you did, they
wouldn't keep dismissing what you're saying.
So I don't think they can hear what you're saying.
So yeah, they seem to think that
it doesn't matter about my relationship.
Don't worry about me.
And stop going on about this
relationship thing. It's it's boring and
it's not a life experience. I don't know
what it is with people in this community
that's been in a relationship with one
person and they think they know more about women.
I don't understand how you think that's
that's having more experiences with
women. That's not having more
experiences with women, bro, because
you've been in a relationship. I don't
know why you seem to think about a
relationship is some sort of life experience.
I really really don't seem to think why
you know more about women if you've been
in a relationship. I've had multiple
chances of being in relationships.
Multiple chances. That's not a brag.
That's not a brag to be in a
relationship. I don't know why you're
bragging. I've had chances to be in
multiple multiple relationships about
three or four years ago. Not now, years
ago. Why do you keep bragging like it's
some sort of life experience?
Why do you keep say thinking that you
know more about women if you've been in
a relationship? Why do you seem to think
you know more about women than someone
that's traveled all over the country for
years meeting women? I don't know why
you think that's some sort of badge of honor.
I don't know why you're
why you're why you keep doing this. I
don't know you. I don't know if you've
been in a relationship or not. And I I
don't know you. I'm I want to know why
you keep bringing it up.
That's not a life experience.
You know, I've said this to [ __ ] the
virgin multiple multiple times that you
do not have more life experience than me
because you've date that you because
you've dated dowies.
You've dated absolute dowies. That does
not mean you have got more life
experience than me. You said that you've
been in a relationship, right?
Your relationships were like 2 3 weeks.
This is the only long relationship that
you've been in. And you do not know more
women than me. You don't need to know
what my longest relationship was.
You don't need to know that. You do not
You don't need to know when my last
relationship was. You don't need to know that. >> [snorts]
>> But I don't know why you're why you keep
bringing it up.
You seem to think these people seem to
think, right, if they if they're in one
relationship with a woman, they know
more than you. They seem to think
because they've been with one woman,
they know more about women than you.
Even though that woman is an individual.
How does that make sense? And I've said
this as well multiple times. You don't
need to be in a relationship with
someone to know what they're like. They
seem to think that you need to be in a
relationship to know what a woman is
like. You don't need to be in a relationship.
with a woman to know what they're like.
You can know what someone's like within [ __ ] minutes. So yeah,
you don't need to know where my last
relationship was. I'm not answering your questions.
You seem to That is strange, bro. You
don't need to be in a relationship with
people to know what they're like.
You literally don't need to be in a
relationship to know what women are like.
relationship to know what women are
like. Why do you think that? You don't.
You don't need to know what Bro, I met
someone for 4 hours and I knew exactly
what they were like.
I've spoke to people for 10 minutes and
I knew exactly what they were like.
I didn't need to be in a relationship
with them for [ __ ] 10 years to know
what a narcissist is like. You know,
women are evil anyways. Why the [ __ ]
would you want a relationship with pure scum evil?
Why would you want to be in a
relationship with evil people?
cuz that's what they are. Evil scum of
the earth. So why would you want to be
in a relationship with that? And I've
had multiple multiple multiple chances
to be in a relationship.
It's not a brag, bro. It's not a brag.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
So if I wasn't So if I go into them four
relationships, does that automatically
mean I'm better than everyone? I'm
better than everyone. And women are
perfect because I have been in three
relationships. Is that what you think, bro?
I was we was talking about women
yesterday on Instagram. We was [ __ ]
talking about their tits and [ __ ]
Why would you want to be in a
relationship with someone? If you get
with someone, you use them for pleasure.
That's what you do. You're supposed to
use a woman for pleasure and that's it.
If you ever do meet someone, you're not
supposed to be in a relationship with
them evil [ __ ]
you use them and you [ __ ] him over.
Oh, one second, Grezy. Right. I There
was this um woman yesterday saying that
um she uh she met a guy uh on vacation
and he [ __ ] her and left her and then
she was trying to say men have no
limits. I I went straight on that inbox,
mate. And I was like, you're saying
you're saying you're saying you're
saying you're saying about men have no
limits. Men have no limits. Men have no
limits. You're one to [ __ ] talk, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Men have got no limits. Says the [ __ ]
that sit there and string people along.
[ __ ] off, mate. Look at your [ __ ]
selves. Yeah, he got you before you got
him. Good on the [ __ ] man. He got you
before you got him. Do you say this to
women first off so they know what you want?
>> Um, Grezy,
you're not dismissing my struggles
again, are you?
Greasy, what did I tell you about dismissing struggles?
Now, you've just said, "Do you say this
to women first off so they know what you
want?" Now that tells me you're
dismissing struggles, Grezy. Grezy,
come on now. You're better than that. No struggle dismissing.
Well, Grezy, if you watched my
approaches and you saw my messages, you
would know the answer to that question.
You wouldn't need to be asking it,
right? But if you saw the approaches and
you saw the messages, you would know
exactly what the answer to that is.
So why are you asking if you would
already know that? You would know the
you know the answer already.
If you watch the approaches, you would know you know
you see you've seen approaches. You've
seen the messages. You've seen where
I've said hi to someone and they've said
straight away not interested.
Very rudy. I'm I'm sure you've seen her
videos. So why are you asking that question?
Stop dismissing people's struggles.
Stop being a struggle dismisser.
Stop being [snorts] a struggle dismisser.
He does have a point. any part of any
about me saying that I've approached
women and you've seen approaches?
Nope. Completely dismissed.
Guess my voice ain't working today.
Completely dismissed. Same old. And this
is exactly what I'm talking about.
There's no point in getting into any
debates with anyone because they just
dismiss everything you say.
I've literally just said this to you
over and over and over again and you're
not saying anything back to it.
You're asking me when I've shown you approaches.
I've literally shown you approaches. Why
are you asking me? I've shown you when
I've tried speaking to people. They said
you're not interested straight away. So
that answers your question. No.
Surely that just ends the whole thing. No. So yeah.
Well, no, I'm not up front about it
because I didn't want just the sh.
I'm saying nowadays people should use
them for that. I never said that. And
why are we having this conversation?
You've seen the messages. You've seen
the approaches. Dismissing them again.
You know, I literally put up approaches
for you to watch and you obviously keep
dismissing them cuz I know you've watched them.
No, [ __ ] that, bro. No, these comes to
pay. They need to pay for keeping me
single and secless. This is part of when
all the [ __ ] ends up. If a woman's
[ __ ] me over, I will make sure she
never gets with another guy. I still
[ __ ] with USA. Is he? I'm still trying
to find her boyfriend. If anyone [ __ ]
with me, I will make sure that they will
never be happy. Bro, I'm like that just
cuz I don't like them. I will make sure
that they never be happy. I keep [ __ ]
with them. You don't know what I'm like,
bro. You really don't know what I'm
like. If anyone [ __ ] with me,
if anyone [ __ ] with me, I will make
sure I'm I'm a I'm like Chucky. You
can't get rid of me. I like Chucky the
doll. You can't get rid of the [ __ ]
You can't get rid of the [ __ ] lad.
So, anything about the approaches,
Greasy, or did you just dismiss them?
I don't think my voice is working
properly because you're not you're not I
think I need to go to the doctors.
I think I need to go to the doctors cuz
I don't think my voice is working
properly because I've explained
something about five times now and you
still don't see say anything about it.
You just completely dismiss it. Strange.
I literally You're talking about people
saying about having a shag. I have
showed you my approaching videos. Did
you not learn anything from them?
No. Was there any point of me putting
the videos up if you're just going to dismiss them?
>> I've literally showed you where people
have said straight away not interested.
They did that not happen. But now you're
talking about sex. That doesn't make sense.
I've shown you I've shown you
I don't have double standards. I don't
know. You're saying that do I ask people
for sex straight away and I've show and
I'm telling you that I've shown
approaches where they've said straight
away that they're not interested. Does
that not answer your question?
Do I have double standards? I'm
literally telling you a video that I put
out there. You keep dismissing it.
We're having a conversation like I've
not put approaches and messages up.
We're basically having That's what I'm
trying to say. It it seems as if you're
dismissing because we're having a
conversation as if I didn't put a load
of messages and [ __ ] approaches.
You know exactly what happens when you
approach someone. It doesn't matter what
you want. Sex, a relationship, a
friendship. It doesn't matter what the
[ __ ] you want. You go up, you speak to
someone, straight away I have a boyfriend.
They act [ __ ] They're [ __ ] Well,
does it matter what I want?
But worry about what I want when you can
actually get a conversation out of
someone. When you can actually get when
you can actually get a conversation out
of someone then then that's when we
should worry about what we actually want.
So you are dismissing you are dismissing my struggles
[snorts] because if you watched well we
know you've watched the videos. Why are
you asking is something that you already
know the answer to? [sighs]
I could want friendship and I still
wouldn't get friendship.
So what I don't understand what what
what your question is. Even if I wanted
friendship, say I wanted friendship with
a woman, right? And I was asexual. I
wouldn't even be able to get that
because they're [ __ ] If I wanted
sex, I wouldn't be able to get that. If
I wanted a relationship, I wouldn't be
able to get that. What does it really
matter? I don't get it. [snorts] Really don't.
>> [clears throat]
>> This does not make it don't make sense.
I [ __ ] hate them, bro. I really
really hate them.
I [ __ ] hate him, bro. This this part
I really really really hate him, bro. I
don't think it's a good idea that I go
out on Saturday, bro.
God, they're not seriously hurting
someone, bro. I said I was going to go
out this week cuz I have my haircut, but
I will end up seriously seriously
hurting someone, bro.
I don't think it's worth it. I really,
really don't think it's worth it.
We [snorts] shouldn't still be having
this conversation. It's almost 2026,
right? [ __ ] should have changed by now.
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] should have changed by
now, bro. We shouldn't be in the
be having this. I shouldn't still be
having this thing.
Yeah, that self projection. We don't
care about self- projecting comments.
We're actually on here trying to have a conversation.
Yeah, we don't care about self
projectors. I will say the same thing as
I said to the other account. You ain't
got a bird. You ain't got a girlfriend.
Again, a mirror is a very very uh good
investment for these people on here.
You don't have a girlfriend. You don't
have a bird. So, no one cares about your self-reflecting comments.
Just the same old. You're going to love
this, Joe. You're going to love this.
So, I started sending people dick
pictures to see what the reaction would
be, and I got a good I got a good
response, by the way. Right. They didn't
know who they were dealing with. It's so
mad how they're fast enough to reply to negativity. Negativity,
um, hate or any kind of drama. They're
there before you could say Jack Robinson.
Um, it's mad, isn't it? Seven in the
morning. [ __ ] me. I don't think I've
ever had a response at 7:00 in the
morning before. I'll read it out to you,
Joe. I said, uh, I sent my dick and she
like, "Oh, that's that's that's disrespectful." And
what did she say? That's disgusting and
disrespectful. I replied,
then she blocked me. So, I I SMSed her
saying, "Hi, I tried to message I tried
to reply to your message, but it didn't
let me. It is it is didn't let me. It is
disrespectful. just like you ignoring is
Then they wrote, "Uh, I would just reply
to this message because it's not worth
it. Even if I was ignoring you because I
was, doesn't mean that you can send
photos of your dick to me. That's just
childish behavior. And I think even a
child is more mature than you." The
attitude. Jesus. I don't know what you
expected it would happen by sending
photos like that. And honestly, I don't
care. I said, "I'll do what I want." And
honestly, you do care by replying. You
want to talk about I quote majority when
you're sat there ignoring someone. make
it make sense. If a child is more mature
than me, then a toddler is more mature
than you. So, [ __ ] off and get raped and
drop the attitude.
I don't give a [ __ ] I'll do what I
want. But she don't don't call people
immature when you're the one that's sat
there ignoring the attitude on these
women is mental, bro. They are. These
women their attitude are mental. She's
like fat and [ __ ] below average. Who
do they think they are? Who do these
[ __ ] women think they are, bro?
They need a harsh reality check. They
just need putting back. They they you
know people that need putting in their
place, right? You know people that you
know you know the saying, putting in
their place. That's what these women
they seem to be stars above their level,
bro. You will get a five thinking that
they're [ __ ] 18 stars. five stars
thinking they're 18 stars and then they
and then they're so used to men licking
their ass and being a white knight. Then
they and then they think they can go
around being a [ __ ] to you and then you
tell them back, right? And then you tell
them about themselves back and then
they're [ __ ] absolute [ __ ] bro. You know,
I'm really going to end up hurting
someone, Joe. I swear to God, I'm really
going to end up [ __ ] hurting someone, bro.
really really really really really
really badly. It's not even a joke.
Really really really really badly. >> Yeah.
Nah, I'm I'm really I was trying to [ __ ]
with this tenant job. I was trying to
[ __ ] with this tenant from years ago,
Joe, and she wouldn't uh we was talking
to that and then I was like, "Oh, you're
in London. Let's meet up. I was going to
die in Nasha." And then she started
ignoring. I just blocked her. It wasn't
a random person I messaged and I was
like, "You going to sit there and ignore
me?" I just blocked them. I just blocked
them cuz I was going to end up doing
madness, bro. So, I just blocked them.
So, don't [ __ ] sit there and ignore
me. Yeah. You was on the [ __ ] phone
to me for [ __ ] god knows how long.
You know who I am. This isn't a
stranger. Don't [ __ ] ignore me, you know.
But they're lucky in a way cuz what
would have happened, they would be
getting nicked. So I am dying and I am
dying and dashing someone as soon as I
get the chance. Don't worry, I'm getting
revenge. I am definitely definitely
getting revenge on these women 100%. One [ __ ] 100%. you know. Yeah,
I'm definitely ding and dashing.
Definitely definitely ding and dashing.
But that woman trying to say that men
have got no levels. Have you seen your
[ __ ] self? So what? You was on
vacation or someone was on vacation and
they used you for sex and they dumped
you. Yeah. Women do the same thing as
well. You've got no limits. You've got
Yeah. Shut the [ __ ] up about men don't
have no limits. Women have got no limits
just the same as men. So shut the [ __ ]
up. Well, I can tell you a story where
that's happened to me. Shut the [ __ ] up
about men have no limits.
You've got no limits. You have got no limits,
you know, in in other ways. So [ __ ] off
about men have got no limits. What the
[ __ ] you say the people that [ __ ] sit
there and lead people on? [ __ ] off, mate.
Yeah, I'm [ __ ] I'm getting revenge. I
don't give a [ __ ]
I'm getting revenge.
I I could understand if I was in a
wheelchair while I was disabled or I
didn't try, but there's no reason for
this. There is no reason for this. This
is another year now. We're past October.
We're almost in a new year now. We had
this problem last year. We had this
problem the year before when I was back
at this house. Yeah. Why is this still
happening? You know, this should not be still happening.
You know, this should not still be
happening now. Why is this still
happening? I met someone on Saturday.
Yeah. I met someone on Saturday, right?
They didn't reply. You literally told me
to message you and you didn't reply.
I went out Saturday. I went to my local
area with my sister and I got one
number. I done five approaches. It was
giving me a headache at the end of it.
And I'm thinking, "What the [ __ ] bro?
You literally told me to message you.
Why haven't you [ __ ] replied?
What was the [ __ ] even the point of
you giving your number if you weren't
going to reply?" So, Cuz
I know the next time I go out, I'm
pouring drink on someone's face, bro.
I'm pouring drink on someone's [ __ ]
face. I am pouring drink on someone's
[ __ ] face, bro. I swear to God.
Yeah, I'm pouring a Guinness all over someone's face.
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] bro. I don't
Why should I even have to go to
Thailand? Why should I have to go to
Thailand? For what reason? Am I 50 years old?
I won't be doing anything. Yeah. Okay,
bro. We're not We're not getting into
this again. Even when someone does
stuff, you still make excuses. Older
guys at work. Oh, no. No, bro. You're
full of excuses. No one no one cares
what you think. But anyways, uh back to
Thailand. I'm I'm not 50 60 years of age, bro.
Yeah, I'm not 50 60. I'm not in a
wheelchair. I'm not an old man. There's
I don't need to go to Thailand. I
shouldn't have to go to Thailand. You know,
I'm not an old man. I'm not in my 70s.
I'm not in my 80s. I'm not in a wheelchair.
So, I've not got any disfigurements. So,
there's there's no reason for me to go to Thailand.
But we don't really care. Like I was
thinking of calling out that prime
yesterday just for my own satisfaction
so I can knock the [ __ ] out. But he was
the only one I probably would meet on
here I think unless someone come on my
door because we all know how the cookie
crumbles with you people. Even when you
take L's you still pretend it never
happened. So no one really cares about
meeting any of you showing you money cuz
you just you're just biased. But with
that prime I just embarrass him for my own satisfaction
2 and a half years later.
That's different. I would do it for my
own satisfaction. But anyone else,
they're not you're not worth meeting.
Yeah. Change. Yeah. Change. Yeah. Like
you try to speak to someone and they
pretend they've got a boyfriend straight
away. What do you want me to do, bro?
Put a gun to someone's head. Stick my
dick in their mouth. How do you want me
to change stuck up people? How do you
want me to to change evil, stuck up
people? I can't change people. You can't
We we can't change these these
[ __ ] This is another thing, right?
I had this guy on on this Instagram,
right, sat there trying to blame me. Oh,
you need to lower your body fat. Oh, you
need to go to the gym. But you shouldn't
be saying these things to get women. You
should be telling people to do this for
themselves cuz that's not going to get
you women. That's given that's that is
giving false hope. I'd rather someone
sit there and say, "Oh, you should go to
the gym. You should uh do this because
to look better." If they said, "Oh, I
think you can look better by doing
this." I'd be like, "Yeah, but you're
telling people that they need to change
for women that will never change."
That's what my problem was. Then you
could be you could work, you could live
by yourself, you could be you could go
to a gym, you still would get the same
results. You could be homeless, you
could look homeless, you could be broke,
you'd still get the same results. You
need to tell people to better themselves
for themselves. Don't tell them that
they need to become [ __ ] 5% body fat
to try to get a woman cuz that is just
that is just setting someone up for disaster. So,
bro, it was in bars and clubs. Oh,
>> they're in bars and clubs.
No, you won't. Even if you work on
yourself, you still will be in the same position.
Stop giving people false hope.
You definitely definitely won't. You
will still get the same bad experiences.
I've worked. I've lived by myself.
I've been broke. I've had loads of
money. I've had moderate amount of
money. You literally, it will never ever change.
You will change as a person.
you I I've done loads of different
things. Not gambled, not you still get
the same results.
You cannot change these people. You
changing yourself is not going to change these people.
You are not going to change these people
by these things. You're not going to
[ __ ] You're not going to give up for
6 months, go to the gym, get a job, and
and stop hearing, "Oh, I've got a
boyfriend." You're not going to stop
hearing that, bro, as an example,
because you've worked on yourself.
You're never going to unless you become
some sort of billionaire, bro, and
you've got a [ __ ] Ferrari. I don't
see how it's going to change because
even there's Tik Tockers now. Ed
Matthews getting rejected. Oh, I watch
that guy, by the way, and he's even
getting rejected. How's that? How did
that even make sense?
Again, not comparing, but I'm just
saying that I I still don't compare
myself to him. I still I I think it's
mad, but I don't compare myself to him.
I I I see it in a way as these people
are telling you to work on yourself, but
I still don't compare myself to him. I
still think that when I go out, it will
be different unlike him. Even though
he's better than me, you know, let's
face it. But, you know, he's But I still
seem to think, "Oh, okay. Well, you
know, yeah, I'm not attractive." Again, self-p projection.
Yeah, I'm not attractive. Yeah. Again,
the amount of times you keep saying,
"I'm unattractive," is not going to
change the fact that you're projecting.
You can do it 2026, you can do it 2027,
you can do it 2028. You can keep
projecting until the cows come home.
You're not going to make me insecure.
You're wasting your time. So,
no, I never. No, I didn't. And I've
still got money. I don't know why you
seem to think, Joe, you don't know how
much money I have. So, I don't know why
you keep talking about money. You don't
know how much money I have. Um, so I
don't know why you keep bringing that
up. And no, I didn't. I mean, look at
when I become homeless. I still had the
house. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I was
still bad. Even when I got that money, I
was still bad. In the winter time, I
was. Maybe not the summer time. In the
winter time, I was. Yes, I was. Even
when I had the house. Yes, I was. The
only reason I was a little bit better,
the only the only reason I was a little
bit better um is because I was living
with people. So, people calm me down.
No, I wasn't. I was still the same even
when I had money, more money.
So, it doesn't really matter. It was it
was uh if you won money if you won money
then temporarily it would go away. Yeah.
But it was still the same. I was still
depressed. Even two years ago when I was
here I was still depressed.
Yeah. It might be a little bit [ __ ] that
you don't get as much money now but it
No. No. I was still the same. I was still depressed. So
you don't know how much money I have.
Don't you worry about how much money I
have. Worry about you, bro. on how much
you have. You don't need to worry about me.
You say that I'm poverty. That's your
that then you don't need to worry about
how much money I have. You don't know
how much money I have, bro. Just keep
bragging about your pension, showing
your wins, and that's all you need to
worry about. You don't need to worry
about what Peter Betty's got.
So, no, I didn't. No, I didn't. No, I
You must You have You have memory loss,
mate. I was bad two years ago. Even when
I still had the house, you've got memory
loss. I've always been bad.
I've always been bad. Look at that whole
USA thing. Look at that whole USA thing. So, yeah. Yeah,
that went on for ages.
Ages. Even when I was going on dates, ages.
I that was going on for ages and I had
money. It still never made a bell. It
still never made it better.
So I was still bad. You might be worse
now, but you still I was still bad then.
And the only reason I didn't do anything
silly is cuz I realized like how
privileged I was not having to work and
getting that money. You know,
I don't give a [ __ ] bro. Why Why does
it matter anyways?
I've took your advice and your advice
don't work. You're not going to change
women because you go to the gym or you
work. It's not going to You're not going
to change women.
And I've not lived off £1,100 a month
for [ __ ] months,
months, months, and months. So, you
know, I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
I don't really care.
No, it isn't. No, it isn't. I've got money.
No, it isn't. I've got money. It's
women. I hate women, bro. I [ __ ] hate
these [ __ ] women. I shouldn't still
be having this conversation. I still
shouldn't be having this. I still
shouldn't be having this problem
again. Go away white knight. I'm going
to block this white knight in a minute,
bro. If he doesn't stop selfjecting
white knight and white knight. I think
you people on here a lot of you people.
Me and Antman was talking about this
last night. We don't get these people.
They sit there and stick up for women.
They don't get women. Women don't like
them. I think they're lying to
themselves. I generally think they're li
I don't think it's autism. I think
they're scared of having an opinion that
matters. So, they sit there and say,
"Oh, yeah. Yeah, women are perfect.
Women are perfect." Because they don't
want people to jump on them. I don't
even think it's autism why they do it. I
think they're just scared of what people
think. So, they they lie to themselves
thinking that women are not the problem.
It's [ __ ] madness.
become likable, bro. No one cares if you
think I'm likable or not. You're biased.
Your opinion doesn't matter. How much
you think I have doesn't matter. What
you think doesn't matter. No one No one
cares about you. You're biased.
So, we don't really care about what you think.
No one cares about you, biased, Joseph
Ferrar. No one gives a [ __ ] about you.
There's only one person I meet on here
for a fight and that's Prime. No one
else. I don't give a [ __ ] about. Like I
said, unless they come up, unless they
physically came to me, then I wouldn't
that prime. I just get my own
satisfaction out of it, bro. No matter
what people would say,
trust me, I'd eat him alive now, bro.
I'm This is two two and a half years
ago. Yeah. Now, he would not win. Yeah.
Apparently now, you know, even I knew
what I know what I'm getting myself in
for now, bro. I would easily whoop his
ass, bro. I would easily whoop his ass
in less than half an hour, bro.
Yeah. Two and a half years ago. But
Peter Belly wants a rematch.
But half an hour is only about um
minute. So So yeah.
Yeah, bro. I was two two and a half
years ago. I was a little I was little.
I was a [ __ ]
So meet me now, bro. Meet me now. Meet
me now. Meet me now.
We was having this conversation
yesterday, bro, about this and wrong
wrong uh wrong place, wrong time to be fair.
No, but obviously Lo can email him and
stuff, can't he? The thing is, we was
talking about this yesterday, right?
That if anyone came on your doors, you
people wouldn't even answer the door. If
someone grabbed you, you wouldn't do
anything. You're saying that you won't,
but you you're saying that you will, but
you wouldn't. you wouldn't, you know,
just like two and a half years ago, I
was a I was a, you know, I was a [ __ ]
and I weren't expecting it. So, I admit
it. But we all know, bro, that if
someone came on your doors, you would
not answer that door, bro.
Deep down, you know it. So, I don't know
why you're trying to act like, "Oh, if
someone done that to you, you wouldn't
do anything, bro. You really, really
would not do anything."
Trust me, as soon as someone gets
stocked on here, they're running away. So,
but yeah, I mean he can Prime can easily
get emailed by Lord Jay. I'm sure like
they contact each other. I would eat him
alive, bro. Like a dog now. Like, I'm
not even joking. I would eat that [ __ ]
alive. Only in these dreams do you think
he would put me in hospital? He
wouldn't, bro. Trust me, he wouldn't. Yeah,
he wouldn't. He wouldn't beat me now,
bro. Trust me.
And what happens with apologies? They
can be retracted.
You can also retract apologies.
And I even start talking about his kids.
So, you know,
I can even I would even start talking
about his kids, bro. You know what I'm
saying, bro? Yeah. So, yeah.
Yeah, of course you would, bro. We
believe it. Yeah, Wish, we believe it.
We believe it. We believe it. Yeah, we
believe it, bro. We believe it.
We believe it. We totally believe it. We
We totally totally totally believe it.
Yeah, it's it's believable, bro. Very believable. Yeah. I
I thought he was a [ __ ] [ __ ]
That's what I thought. He was a fat
[ __ ] And I still think that.
And Joseph, you need to stop putting
only wins up because no one no one no
one um wins that much on FBI. And I'm
not jealous. I don't give a [ __ ] about
what people have, but you're you're not
winning as much as you're saying you're
winning. Believe you me, you're not,
bro. Believe you me, you're not. You're
losing and you're not telling people
what you're losing. Don't be a stop and
step, bro. Come on. Just show your
losses as well. You need to show your
losses as well. There's no point showing
only wins and not showing you losses.
There's no point only showing your wins
and not your losses, lad.
cuz that is just weak.
You need to show your losses as well.
So yeah, like the house and the money,
it would be more of a case of like, oh
yeah, we can get pissed off, but then
you realize how lucky you are. But it
still affected me. It still affected me.
This women [ __ ] still affected me. It
was it was only like that that was like,
h well, you know, you're kind of more
lucky. And it kind of stopped me from
wanting to do anything. But I still got
these mood swings.
Even when I was getting that money, I
was still getting these nasty mood
swings. You know what? You know, and you
don't know I ended up homeless even when
I still had the house.
So it wasn't that
you don't understand that no matter what
money you get, you adjust to it.
You adjust to any money, not £300 a
month, not 500 a month. Any money you
get, you adjust to any amount of money
you get. You get three grand a month.
Three grand a month is not enough for me.
And some people get £1,300 a month and
that's plenty for them. You know, you
don't you you adjust to any money that you get.
Any money that not not again at a limit.
There's a limit. Obviously, there is a
limit, but you know,
I've done pretty good.
I had £1,700 last month. I had to buy stuff.
Yeah, it was a buzz getting money, but
it is what it is. Yeah.
But it doesn't matter anyways, but does
it? It's only money. So, it's not like I
can't afford to do what I want.
So, you know, I can still do what I
want. I can still go out whenever I Yeah. So, yeah.
And I can make money if I really wanted to.
But Peter B is lazy, man. Peter B is too
lazy. Too [ __ ] lazy, bro.
Too [ __ ] lazy.
I was going to say don't do anything
illegal in the future so it can never
stop, but anything can stop. You can
make money on YouTube and that could stop.
You can get 30 grand a month from
YouTube and then you'd start getting
less money. You can get [ __ ] over
anyway. You can become [ __ ] um
you could you could be made redundant.
What's happened to a friend of mine who
worked at Barclays. So I mean even if
you do think it's a legit way, you can
still you can still get [ __ ] over. So
you could still get [ __ ] over.
You still there, Joseph?
I was on USA Izzy's Instagram um the
other day. Joe, she still got them boobies.
You still got them big boobies.
Yeah, it was a buzz getting the money,
but it's not. It's still I still had
these mood swings.
But Sig always used to say, "Oh, you
should be lucky you have that house and
that." That's why I never really I just
calm down and I would never do anything
that would get me locked up
because why would you want to get locked
up when you've got a house that you
could lose and the money from the house
now it's a different story. I've still
got money but
you know I don't know it's it's
different but no I did still get the
mood swings. I still did get the mood
Shut up. No,
I'm just telling you. Is it?
I'm just telling you. Yeah, I had £1,700
last month, Joseph Farra, but I bought
trainers and jeans.
So, think of how much you spend on
clothes. Those are for Oh,
I don't go out as much now. Not cuz of
money. It might seem like that to you,
Joseph F, but it isn't. It really,
really isn't. I could easily go out,
spend 150, 200 pound. I really can. You
might think that it's money, but it isn't.
Even when I had the house towards the
last six, seven months, I stopped. So,
but if you didn't have the house in your
prime, I don't know how you you would
have been able to afford like the [ __ ] I
done in like in my prime and that. So, I
don't know what I would have done, bro.
Like 24 25. Say you're 23. What? 24 23
So obviously you go out more at that
age, but obviously if you didn't have
the house, how could you do all the
madness? Now we don't want to do as much
madness now cuz we were older, but you'd be [ __ ]
Yeah. At 23, 24, if I didn't have the
house, I would have been [ __ ] There's
no way I would have been able to afford
things. Now, if I have 14,500, it's
enough for what I want. I can go out
when I want. And you know
I I don't know.
Yeah, I get next boxes Joseph Farah.
I like expensive jeans, Joseph Ferrar,
because they I mean it's a good
investment. They last about 3 years. So
would you say it's a waste of money
spending £200 for jeans if they last 3 years?
I need to buy a new phone soon cuz I'm
not getting another contract out. So yeah,
why don't you get a flagship phone,
Joseph Farerra? You win all of this
money, so why don't why don't when your
phone pack up, you get a you get a you
get a flagship.
You should get a flagship. You got all this money.
Bro, I don't even care about the
flagship phones. It's just the fact that
I like the fold.
See, this phone that was £250 I was
going to buy. It's back up to £400.
Absolutely no way am I paying that.
Absolutely no way. It was 250 and I was
and I was going to get it and it was
like £400. I was like, absolutely no way.
I ain't paying that, bro.
I'm not paying that. So,
I'll pay 300 and something. It will go
down to like 330, then I'll pay that.
I'm not paying for £100, bro. [ __ ] that.
No, I wouldn't get a flagship phone. If
it wasn't for the phone being a fold, I
wouldn't get a flagship. I'd get like a
uh not a budget model, Grezy, but um
what what they called? Not budget.
They're not flagships. They're like uh
what are they? They're
they're not budget ones. What's the next
thing called? There's budget something
in flagship. If there was no folds, then
I would just get
the moderate ones. I wouldn't get I
wouldn't I wouldn't I wouldn't get the
budget ones, though. No,
I've got Yeah. mid-range one. I'd get a
mid-range one. So, it's not too slow,
but it's not cheap. I wouldn't get a
budget one if they didn't have a fold. I
only like it because the fold. It's not
because of its flagship. I just like the fold phones.
I can get one out now on contract, but I
don't if I was to get a contract, I'd
get a year contract and pay £200 a month. So,
yeah. So, whatever. Yeah. So,
yeah. Mid-range. Yeah. But you might
have got your phone used, that's why.
But I'm talking brand new. Yeah. So
maybe 300. When it goes down to 330,
I'll pay that. But I'm not paying £400. That's ridiculous. So yeah,
I paid it before when I was doing Uber. Nah. Yeah.
So yeah, Joseph Farra, these women are
[ __ ] What's the point of giving me
your number saying, "Oh yeah, drop me a
message." And it's not like you acted
uninterested and then you didn't reply.
You literally was like, "Oh yeah, drop
me a message." Yeah. And then you didn't
reply. What's the point of that? I can
understand if someone felt obliged to
give you their number, but it wasn't
that. So what's the point of giving your
number being all enthusiastic if you're
not going to [ __ ] reply?
Yeah. Nobody messages me back. Yeah.
What's the [ __ ] point?
What's the [ __ ] point of it? What is
the What is the point?
And I'm never going out with people ever
again, Joseph, for real. And I And I
went out I went out with my sister and
her friend. Absolutely no way.
She was acting all enthusiastic and that
and then she didn't even reply.
Absolutely no way. I'm never going out
with more than one person ever again and
only certain people. It was bad, bro. I
don't like going out with people
cuz I feel like I've got a
responsibility when I go out with
people. I don't like going out with one
friend is good. Yeah, you can go out
with one friend but not more than one. I
don't understand how these people go out in groups.
I don't understand how these people can
go out in groups. I hate it.
It's just like you you've got more of a
responsibility than actually enjoying
yourself. Does that make sense? Do you fra?
I don't know. I can't explain it. It
feels like you've got a responsibility.
I don't like having
I can't explain what I mean, bro. It's
like you if you go out by yourself,
right, you're you're drinking. You're
enjoying yourself. You're doing what you
want to do. You're going to meet new
people. You're going to meet new friends
by yourself. If you go out with other
people, more than one person, then you
feel like you got a chip on your
shoulder. I can't explain it. It's weird.
Basically, if you do things by yourself,
you don't need to wait on anyone. You know,
one person's fine. If it's a good
friend, you can go out with a friend.
That's fine. If it's one person
occasionally, yeah, but not any more
than one person
cuz where where I go is so busy. You're
always talking to people. You're never
going to, you know, you're just going to
blend in. So, I don't see how these
people, especially around Christmas, you
know, I'm not a social person. I I'm not
a social person. Peter Bell is not a
social person. Joseph,
come on, bro. I I approach people sober.
I can speak to anyone.
You You wouldn't understand what I mean,
but you just feel like you've got a chip
on your shoulder.
How am I not a social person? I've been
up and out the [ __ ] country by myself
meeting new people.
Why the [ __ ] am I not a social person?
So, I don't like going out with more.
But it was all right on Saturday. That's
only spent £100. So, so yeah.
Yeah. Maybe I don't want to socialize,
but I'm not scared to socialize. I'm not an introvert. So,
yeah. I was playing some pool. Joseph, I
So yeah. So how can you make money now
Joseph for all without working?
You can't mate. You can't.
I bet you was jealous when I had that
house in it, Joseph Fro. Come on, man.
You was You was a bit jealous, isn't it?
You can be honest now. It's over.
Yeah, of course you was jealous, bro.
You must have been jealous.
You must have been jealous in it. Come
on. Of course you was jealous, man.
You know, I think a lot of people was
jealous to be fair.
And yeah, I did say, oh, like you you
moan and wins and stuff, but look, you
you don't have to work and you get this
money. But like I said, it would still
it was still it was still you you you
you're still getting the mood swings
over women. You're still getting the bad
stuff over over women,
which is why you got you go to gambling
to win to get a buzz.
It's only if you won money it would go
away. Not if you was getting money. Only
if you had won money. It's weird. It
doesn't make sense, I know, but it's it's weird.
Yeah, but you was Yeah, but you had to
work. Joseph Ferrar.
Yeah, but Joseph Ferrar, you had to work.
You had to work, bro. I had more
disposable money than you. Think about it.
Now it doesn't even feel like it's any
different because I've just accostumed.
I've I'm used to the money that I get
now. It took like three [ __ ] months.
Yeah. But like, no, two months maybe.
But now it's I'm like I've made it a way
where I'm just used to what I get now. I
can just get what I get now. And that it's fine.
I told you this conversation even when
you was on here before. Three grand a
month is not enough. Do you remember
when I was telling you about, oh, three
grand a month's not enough? Three grand
a month is not enough.
Yeah, the house was stressful to be
fair. It was stress. Well, when I was
living there, no, it's okay if you're
living there. When I moved back there,
no. When I moved back there, it was
fine. But when you're not living there
Yeah. because you can't see what's going
on and [ __ ] and letters and stuff. Yeah,
it is. It was stressful. Yeah.
Unless you're living there cuz obviously
you can keep tabs. Yeah, it was it was
stressful if you're not living there. Yeah.
That's another thing. When I had that
£,700 last month, I was like, "Oh, look.
I got £1,700 and I've got no responsibilities."
And I've got absolutely no [ __ ] responsibilities.
It felt [ __ ] good.
And no responsibilities.
Yeah, it was. It was. It was. But when
you're when you're living there, it's
all right. When you're living there,
it's all right.
But not when you're not living there.
Unless you live like up the road. Yeah,
it is. Because you don't know what's
going on. They can call you at any time. Yeah.
It's annoying, bro. No, I don't have any
responsibilities. It's lovely.
I miss the barbecues. I missed the
house. The money again, I said to you a
million times, three grand a month is
not enough. Three grand a month is not
But now all of a sudden, the money I get
now seems to be enough.
This is what I'm trying to say. You will
always adjust to no matter what money you get.
I'll find a way. It doesn't. It's just
it's just the way it is.
Don't ask me how.
I done a lot of things last month. A lot
of things. You wouldn't think that
someone who doesn't work, that doesn't
do any ille illegal things would be able
to do it, but you still are able to do it.
I knew what I was doing with the
football bets and the saving and that. I
knew what I was doing. So,
I mean, I could technically gamble now
and if I have £700 left, I can gamble
all my gamble over a,000 now. If I have
700 left, well, I would adjust to having
£700, wouldn't I?
What could I do? Eh,
you know, I don't [ __ ] know, bro. Yeah.
Nah, bro. [ __ ] that. Didn't you hear
what happened yesterday when I gambled?
Didn't you Didn't you hear the story?
I'll tell it again if you want.
Please tell me you didn't so I can
explain it. I love I love the sound of
my own voice. Did Didn't you hear what
happened yesterday? I think I got food poisoning. Joseph Joseph.
No, I can't gamble. You wasn't here. You
wasn't [ __ ] here. Okay, Joseph, for
so I went yesterday to get a roast
dinner and there's a William Hill like
opposite the train station and obviously
William Hill is my favorite bookies.
Haven't gambled for a long time. I said
let me try £50 on roulette. Let me try
£50 on roulette. [ __ ] up down up down £80
back and forth, bro. It was pissing me
the [ __ ] off. In the end, I just took
the £51. I just took £51 and I was still
pissed off. Yeah, people like me
shouldn't gamble. People like me
definitely shouldn't gamble, mate. You
didn't even lose money. And even if you
lost money, it would have been money I
could afford to lose. Yeah, people like
me definitely shouldn't gamble.
Wherever it is, you you shouldn't
gamble. And I And I won a pound and it
was still It's [ __ ] annoying.
Everyone in the [ __ ] shop was
looking. Yeah, people like me shouldn't gamble.
The football isn't as bad, but you Yeah,
you people like me shouldn't be gambling.
Especially if you have all these
problems with women and stuff, you shouldn't.
There was roulette. Yeah. And then I
went to this roast dinner place, Do Ferrar,
and it cost me £44. I thought, what the
[ __ ] And obviously I because I'm I'm so
used to it being like 31 32 pound. They
gave me chicken, lamb, and beef. 44
[ __ ] quid it cost me.
The prices have gone way up. They do
this service charge now. So I won't be
eating roast dinners anymore out. [ __ ]
that, bro. [ __ ] that. That is mad. I
could have bought a leg of lamb of that. Joseph.
Yeah, I could have bought a [ __ ]
I could have bought a [ __ ] I could
have bought a leg of L with that. That's extortionate, bro.
Never did it cost me that much. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, it was just roulette. It was the
bar roulette. I thought I tried £50.
People like me shouldn't gamble.
If that's the way you are, then you
shouldn't gamble. As simple as that.
It's really as simple as that, bro. So,
cuz it's either you get you're depressed
if you lose or you're happy when you
win. There's no in between. So, it's not no point.
Nope. Oh, yeah. I did actually. I played
it Saturday. I put 20 pound on it in the
pub and I didn't even get a bloody bonus
but I was with people so I had to hold
the fact that I was in pissed off. I
remember when I was with that Somali in
Yeah. and I done 600 pound on roulette.
Oh my god, bro. Oh my god. I was in the
toilet and then I come back. She's like,
"Is everything all right?" I said I was
like trying to hold my anger in.
I was really trying to hold my anger in,
bro. And it was hard.
Yeah, I remember I remember that time
when I had to hold my [ __ ] anger in.
I lost [ __ ] 600 pound on [ __ ] online roulette
back when I had a house and that so I
had money coming in. So
yeah, it was very very hard to try to
control my anger. It was online roulette.
Yeah, I played Frankie in the pub. 20 Joseph,
not even a [ __ ] bonus. Jesus Christ.
I said to this person on Reddit, I
should get these women back by trying to
find someone and getting one pregnant,
Joseph. And they said, "That's stupid
because then you'd have a kid." I said,
"Yeah, but you can have a baby in it."
And they said, "You just want to get a
woman pregnant and stuff." I said,
"Yeah, and then you could just leave them."
And they said, "Yeah, but then you're
going to have a kid." I said, "So what?
You just [clears throat] leave the baby in it."
Just the same old.
I've won a couple of football bets.
Joseph Ferrar, did you see that? Both
score no draw.
Generally, I think the only way you can
actually you have a good chance of
winning on on on gambling nowadays is
these um football bets. I've won so many
on him, bro. So many. I'm up so much
over the past three months.
They're very good winners, bro.
Yeah, they're good. I don't know how
anyone wins on their machines anymore.
I don't know how people win.
I might go out Saturday. I might not.
My hair still looks good. No, I don't know.
>> Oh, by the way, Joseph, do you know how
I went out on uh Do you know how I went
out on uh uh last Saturday?
I'll tell you how I went out last
Saturday. My sister's friend had to
literally come round and talk me into
coming out. I was like, I'm not coming
out. I'm not coming out. I'm not coming
out. I'm not coming out. So, you've
already had your haircut. So, when
you've already had your haircut, it's a
case of do you either stay in or do you
go out? I mean, you can go out and spend
£100. You're not going to lose anything.
But if you haven't had your haircut,
that's when you'll go. We won't go out
for like seven weeks cuz that means you
have to get your haircut and then go out.
That's why if you've I literally had to
I got forced to go out on Saturday
otherwise I would have went out.
Now I'm in Now I'm in it too deep again.
No, I don't know what I'm having for tea.
So what do you think about that Joseph
for our £700 disposable for a month?
You reckon you can live off that?
I think I've got like a thousand and something.
Yep. Until I next get money.
Money doesn't come as fast these days, matey.
But that's all right. That's okay.
Ah, that's how much I have. Oh,
well, you can live off £700 a month disposable money. How?
No, you couldn't, Joseph Ferrar. How are
you going to go out drinking?
Don't be a silly goose.
What? £700? How can you live off £700?
What? You could what? £700. Well, how
how are you going to gamble?
Yeah, but you might gamble. You might
get an escort. You might.
Trust me, without the without the house,
it's not that bad. Really, really, it
has its benefits.
Yeah, we're talking after bills, Mike.
We're talking after bills.
Yeah, but we're talking after bills, bro.
We're not talking. We're talking after bills.
See, this is what I'm saying. you you're
talking about 1,200 pound Joe but most
people that work well I don't know most
people but a lot of people they don't
even have that after they've paid everything
well people people can g anyone can gamble man
What? So, you don't think you could go
out drinking every week with £700?
I think you could.
Maybe. Depends how much you spend.
Yeah, but you're not going to buy
clothes every month, are you?
You're not going to buy [ __ ] clothes
every month, are you?
Yeah. Say, well then people should but
people with that work shouldn't gamble then.
I spent like I had £1,700 last month. I
spent like £400 on clothes.
It was just some money I won. So I just
put it away and just bought some
clothes. And I bought jeans and
trainers. I bought coat. So I have like Yeah.
Just depends. Depends, bro. Yeah,
which obviously it would be hard to do
if you don't It'd be hard to do if you
had to just do that for your payment in
it. It'd be It'd be hard to do that.
But obviously, I had money that I'd won
and [ __ ] so I just saved it.
It doesn't matter, bro. I think it's
worse. I think people that work and
gamble is worse.
I could never gamble money I work for.
Never. Of all the times I worked and
never gambled. Never gambled. I could
never gamble money I work for. I don't
know how people can do it.
I I don't know how people can do it, bro.
But they do it. They do it. They do it.
They do it. They do it. They do it. Bro,
why? How much do you have a month, Mike?
Yeah, I don't feel hard done by. I got
my money jeans. I got my Vapor trainers.
I don't feel hard done by.
Obviously, any money you can get, any
money you get could be better, but
don't feel hard done by. So,
how often do you get a haircut?
I got my haircut last week and it should
be all right for this week. I reckon it
should be all right. Yeah,
every two weeks.
Well, how much do you get, Mike?
I haven't lost my jeans yet, by the way.
They were good investment. Good investment. Yes.
Do you remember Mike? Remember Mike?
You're better looking than them. You've
got more money than them and it kills them.
But bro, what? Even if these people had
money, they still wouldn't have a life.
That's funny. And it and it kills them.
That's funny, bro. Good old Ronald Pump.
I love good old Ronald. McDonald.
And it kills them.
You're better looking than them. You've
got a better life than them. And you've
got more money than them. minute kills
But I mean any any money is more money
than these people. What you know what
I'm saying? What what would you say is more money?
How much is more money than these people?
>> You know
Yeah, it's cuz I was showing 50 notes
and stuff. It's cuz I was showing 50 notes.
It was showing I was showing 50 notes
and obviously you're better looking and
you got a better life than them when
these people sit in. I think that's why
he said that. He's He is right though.
He is right.
But I don't think it's just the money
thing. I don't think it's all about money.
I don't think it's all about money, bro.
Cuz you could have £1,500 and be happy
and have more than a life of these
people. So, I don't think having
thousands and thousands and thousands.
It's like you're younger and you're
better looking and you got a you can do
whatever you want in your life where
these people are sat doing nothing.
So it's not I don't think it's just
about buddy, bro. You know,
so how would you go out drinking every
week, Joseph, if you had £700? Huh?
But there's people they get university
loans and they've got loads and loads of
money. I know people that's done it. I'm
not telling you who, but I know people
they've got like £20,000 because they've
just took uni loans out. But I wouldn't
do that. I'd rather just work. I don't
want to do get uni loans and not pay
them. I I'd rather just not do that. I
don't give a [ __ ]
you know? Why wouldn't I'm not doing
that. That's long, bro. [ __ ] that. But
there's people that do it.
There is people that do that.
They say you don't have to pay it back
until all. But yeah,
it's all right if you actually wanted to
do a trade, but I'm not doing that, bro.
I ain't doing that. [ __ ] that.
What do you think of people that do
that, Joseph Farra?
That uni thing. What do you think? I'm
sure you know about it. Joseph Ferrar.
And with the money thing, I we assumed
that they didn't have as much as me
because they wouldn't show anything.
And amount of times they they kept
trying to get my money stopped.
I don't think a lot of people had as
much money as I did, bro.
much money as I did in this community. I
don't think people a lot of people don't
even have as much as I've got now, to be
fair. Maybe you do. Maybe I'm not saying
everyone. I'm just saying I think
there's a lot of people on here
that that probably don't even have
[ __ ] 200 to their name.
Timmy being one of them.
Obviously not everyone, but I'm saying
yeah, I I do think that
cuz what I don't understand, right, is
and you're and I know we're not going to
come out here the best of friends,
Joseph Fra, but why would someone if
they've got money, right? Like me, I'm
moaning about women. I'm saying I'm
giving up with life. So, I'm kind of
acting depressed. But what I don't
understand with these people is that if
they've got all of this money and this
life, why they on here doing what they
do every day? This is what the bit I'm not understanding.
If they're saying that they're not
depressed, right? They're not moaning
about women. They're not skin. Why are
they on here doing what they're doing all day?
Why are they not traveling the world?
Why are they not? It just doesn't add up
to me. It don't add up, bro. Yeah. Some
people can have [ __ ] kids and come on
here after work as a pastime.
I think a lot
>> [clears throat]
>> No. Yeah, I I generally do think that.
Yeah, I generally generally do think
that. It just doesn't make sense. When I
was working, I had no time to be on
here. You know, when I was when I'm
going out approaching, I've got no time
to be on it. And it's what they do. It's
not the fact that they're on here, it's
what they're doing on here every day.
They don't come on here for 2 hours a
day, 3 hours at the end of the day.
They're on here constantly doing what
they're doing. And if people had a good
life, they wouldn't be doing that.
There's no way they would be doing it.
So they'd be living their life. They'd
be living their best life. So yeah.
And another thing is they want it or
not. And and in the summer as well, like
they unless everyone doesn't like the
sun like me, but they do like the sun.
They'll be sat here on a hot summer's
day. On a hot summer's day, they would
be on YouTube
cuz when I'm busy, why do you never see
me on here then? If I'm busy, why do you
never hardly see me on here when I'm
busy? But we will always see you people on here. So,
yeah, it doesn't make sense. initial
saving for core. It's not co anymore. You know, [snorts] man,
don't know why this woman ain't replied.
Yeah, but I'm staying in. I'm not going
out. I'm not the one on here saying that
your [ __ ] skin and my life's better
than yours. I'm I'm not the one saying
it. You are the ones coming on here. I
mean, they calling people skin, but you
can't get off YouTube.
So, I'm actually admitting what I'm
actually what I am and what I'm doing.
You are going on here like you got this
life, you got this money. It just
doesn't add up. Your YouTube activity
don't add up with what you're saying.
Do you think people with a great life
would be coming on YouTube trolling?
Okay. Like like that Jamie Thompson,
right? Sits on YouTube all day stalking
me. Stalking me on Reddit. Do you think
this guy's really got a life?
Come on, bro. Someone that looks like
that. Come on now.
I don't think so.
That's strange why this person was very
un was very enthusiastic.
No. Yeah. Yeah. But you're on my stream
for 6 plus hours. You're on my stream.
Yeah. But you're on here typing,
which means that you ain't got a life. So Yeah.
Yeah, but yet you're on YouTube talking
to me all day. Yeah, you got jobs,
wives, kids, hobbies. Yet you're sat on
YouTube all day talking to me, self
projecting. Okay. Okay, [laughter] bro.
Okay. Okay, bro. Of course.
Of course you do.
Of course you do, bro. Hobbies.
Yeah, of course you do, bro.
Yeah, of course you do.
No, it doesn't add up, bro. It doesn't
It doesn't add up.
And then when I say that you're jealous,
do you think I I think I'm better
looking than you? Do you think that I
think everyone's jealous of me? No.
I think you're jealous because of what
you do on here, not because of what I am
and what I look like. It's just because
I came to that in conclusion from what
you do on here. Jamie Thompson, Red
Star. It just gives the impression that
you're jealous of something in life to
be honest by what you do on here.
It's really quite sad. Well, either way,
none of you have got lives. So, at the
end of the day, bro, at the end of the
day, at the end of the day, even if
you've got like a job, you ain't got a
life. So, it's it's simple as that. Even
if you do have a job, you still ain't
got a [ __ ] life. So, does it really matter?
Yeah. You've never had 200lb jeans.
You've never had 200 pound jeans.
And even if you have a job, bro, you
ain't got a life. So, it doesn't really
matter, does it? So,
I've been off of YouTube for weeks
before. You haven't. But I'm telling you
why I'm live. Yeah. Yeah. But I'm
telling you why I'm live. I'm telling
you why I'm live, though. But I've
already told you why I'm live. And I've
been off of YouTube for weeks before. So
what's I don't get your point.
I've already told you why I'm live. I'm
not the one waking up every day looking
for someone to [ __ ] with. I'm not the
one making videos, screen recording,
[ __ ] people. I'm going live. Yeah.
You people wake up every day and you
think to yourself, hm, who can I [ __ ]
with today? Who can I project my misery
onto today? Oh, we found a channel.
You're fat, your skin, your am
who can we project our our failures on
today? You literally do this every day.
You literally you literally do it every
day. You wake up to [ __ ] with people
every day. I'm live streaming. I'm
telling you why I'm live streaming.
I ain't going out today. I'm not I'm not doing anything.
Spending 1/8 of my money.
What? 1/8 of your money or my money? Are
you talking about? Is it your money or my money?
Uh why did I get him caught? What?
When I get somebody to meet me, I'm
still trying to find someone to meet me.
Are you talking about my money or your money? 18. Oh [ __ ]
Why don't people call RJ what? Sorry,
I'm trying to keep up. Why do they call RJ what?
But I know what you mean, bro. Ski.
this person. Oh, let's go meet for a
steak someone else.
It's weird why they don't respond to
that though, but they respond to negativity.
Strange that, is it? Nowhere to be seen.
A normal nice message, but when you
insult them or you say something
negative, they're there straight away.
1/8 of my money.
You don't know how much money I have.
You don't know how much money I have, bro.
1/8 of my money.
Yeah, you don't have any friends.
Otherwise, you wouldn't be projecting on the internet.
Nah. Sorry, man. Your YouTube activity
gives you away.
Your YouTube activity gives you away. Sorry. St.
I can't believe you get jealous of 200
pound uh jeans. That's pathetic.
All right. And how much money was I
getting in the next week?
How much how much money was I getting in
the next week?
Right. Okay. And how much money was I
getting in the next week since you know so much?
Yeah. So, you spent £200. So what? You
got 1,500 left.
Okay. And your point is is what?
So you have 1,700 and you have 1,500 left.
Okay. And your point is
what? And how much was I getting in the next week?
So you you need to what you people need
to do, right? a lot of you people on
here is you need to worry about your own
life, your own finances. You seem to be
very interested in other people.
Why can't you Why can't you buy £200
jeans if you got £1,700?
What's wrong with that? I don't I don't
I don't understand your point.
Well, can we can we see your £24,000 car?
You got very jealous over them jeans,
isn't it, bro? A lot of people got
jealous over them jeans talking about
colon and that. Jesus Christ.
Is it cuz you thought you stopped Peter
Belly's income and he couldn't afford
such a thing?
Man, what you people do on here is [ __ ] weird.
like you try to get people's money
stopped and all sorts of madness and
this is why we think you're jealous.
This is why we we we come to this
conclusion that it's jealousy with you people.
And I don't like I said, I don't think
it's just money. I don't think it's just
money with these people. It's the money
is is as long as you don't have to
stress about money. I don't think it's
everything. I I don't think it's that.
I don't think it's that, bro. I don't
think it's just just money with these
people. But what they try to do is madness
and they do it every day. Like I wish I
wish I could actually explain to someone
how sad it is what these people do every
day. But they don't understand where
they don't understand things. They don't
understand what I'm saying. These people
wake up every day hating on people that
they don't know.
You know how mad that is like every
single [ __ ] day, bro?
Like waking up hating from the time they
wake up to the time they go to bed and
they don't seem to think that they're
reacting to you.
They're actually idiots. That boy, right?
I'm saying like, you know, these people
have to do this every day. Wake up
hating on someone and they do it all day
from the time they wake up to the time
they go to bed. Red Star, The Virgin.
But then they say they've got a better
life than me.
This is where I'm like confused, you
know? They say they've got a better life
than you, right? And you're this, but
this is real energy, bro.
I'm surprised their brains not exploded
doing this every day.
I know it's not weird. It's cuz I wanted
revenge on these women over what they've
done. They're [ __ ] Women leading
people on is weird. Women being
[ __ ] are weird.
Anyways, we'll go out this week anyways.
And yeah, we'll make our decision from
there. So that's it.
Or what what the [ __ ] ever, you know?
So I don't know how they could they
could do it every day for years.
Do you not see it being mad? I couldn't
do that with USA every day for [ __ ]
years. I got bored in the end.
So, and this is someone I met. These
people have never met me. I just This is
what I was trying to explain to Joker
yesterday that like you're saying that
they do it for reaction, but do you not
know that they're actually reacting to
me and then you explain it again and
then they they don't understand it? So
I was like, "Well, but you're reacting to me." So yeah,
it's not it's not a reaction either.
They don't do it for a reaction. They do
it. And like I said, if you come off of
it and you stopped, yeah, people would
stop going for you, but Red Star and
these other people will never stop.
So that's why we think they're jealous.
Not cuz we think we're better looking
than them. We clearly think that they're
jealous of something to be doing this
every day. Yeah. I went on someone's
Instagram yesterday. Okay. Your point. Yeah.
And if I ever come across their
boyfriend, I'll message them if I can be bothered.
Maybe. Maybe not. But these people
actually live to [ __ ] with people on here.
I don't understand. I just don't Maybe
someone could explain it to me one day.
I just don't understand it to be fair.
Not [snorts] stalking at all.
Bro, please stop misusing that stalking
word. Please stop using that word, bro.
That's a narcissist's favorite word. It
doesn't look good when you're using it.
It's like that one from South America
that I was [ __ ] with. I got called a stalker.
That's a narcissist's favorite word. You know,
Joseph, how are you going to live off
700 pound disposable a month? How are
you? You said that you like to go out drinking though.
What do you call it then? Going on someone's Instagram.
Oh, you're right. Yeah. Will you eat him?
I can't believe that roast dinner
yesterday. That is [ __ ] insane.
That's expensive, bro. >> Yeah.
Yeah. Less. It would have been less
cooking, not more cooking. That's a special. Yeah. >> Yeah.
Yeah. You might as well just get a leg
of lamb and cook it your [ __ ] self.
Well, I went to Hawks. My horse was
nice. But they only do beef. So if you
wanted pork, they don't do pork. >> Yeah.
I would say I would say do
>> Yeah, I was literally going to say that.
Yeah, literally. Yeah,
>> I say beef and gam. Yeah,
cuz you can't do g and and pork because
they're both white meats. I like g. >> Yeah,
but you can't forget them in it.
I'll just wait for it to be cooked in it.
Or you eating today?
What do you fancy?
Yeah, but you're hungry though it
later you will be in it. I like that
savon ships, man. Oh, they're not Oh,
no. They're not the [ __ ]
Yeah. Oh, yeah. So, we're [ __ ] basically.
I like sine chips.
>> So the only other place is Michaels you
can get pork sausage in it.
Yeah, that's the only place in it cuz if
it's allow you can't you could Are you
sure? So you could eat a pork um salad
in it but not a chicken one. That's disgusting
for the hello people, isn't it? When I
have a drink, I can't have anything
greasy because it makes me throw it back up.
I'm sure they do do it with in allow
places. I'm sure they do do it.
Yeah, but why would you want to have sausage?
Because it's supposed to be pork, [laughter] huh?
Yeah, that was expensive. £44.
That was vile, man. I'm surprised it was
so busy. I'm surprised people can afford
it. What was it like Saturday going out?
What was it like? [ __ ] that.
Oh, I hate that cat, man. It copies me,
Mom. Every time I go there, the cat copies me.
Yeah, it won't leave me alone. It kept
following me. It kept it kept following
me out the bloody balcony and stuff.
I don't like cats. That's why I've never
liked Because where does the desire come
from to want to copy another person? H
Yeah, but why would you want to copy
someone? That's why I've always
preferred dogs. I don't like cats.
I was watching I was watching the Little
Britain um shopper yesterday again. I
sometimes go back to that and he's like,
"Oh, I'm looking what he said." He's
like, "I'm looking for a Linda
Williams." And then there was like we've
got a a Linda Williams. Absolutely no
way. And he said, "Hair length?" He
said, "Anywhere from here to here." You
get it? He said, "Because at my time of
age, I can't be picky, you know.
See, you don't get it, do you? Do you get it?
You don't get the sketch, do you? The
the man that goes in the shop and he's
asking for things. What's he doing? How
do you know? Because he was like, "Have
you been Have you been there? Have you
been waiting long? Just a week or so?" [ __ ] Twilight, huh?
Just a week or so.
You never watched it really, did you?
Oh, people put a bet on that. Uh, I'm a
celebrity, didn't they?
>> Did over already.
>> Already? It just started. >> No.
>> Did you actually enjoy watching the
wrestling with me? Well, when you
actually come, you actually enjoy it.
But you would have you watched it if it
wasn't for me.
Yeah. The era died around
2011 then it stopped. You're not
>> I am No, it died after 201 about 11.
Yeah. The games come [ __ ]
I only liked it up until 2010. But do
you know how little I was in 2010?
I have a beard.
I used to like playing the
the wrestling games.
There was so many glitches in that game, is it? One sec. Yeah.
You don't like cats, do you? What about
you, Joseph? Do you like cats?
No. They copy.
Who do you know that's a copycat?
Joseph, who do you know has a copycat?
Sat there waiting for his next copycat statement. Copycat statement.
Who do you copy? [clears throat] [laughter]
Yeah. Three to one. That's only 300
pound off of 100. Oh, is it? No, it's
£400 off 100, isn't it? You get your 100 back.
It is. Yeah, it is. Yeah,
that's decent to be fair.
Yeah, that's not bad odds.
I'm going to get a correct score next
time. Jose Fra with the football. I'm
going to get a correct score next time
on the football lane.
I'm going to get a correct score on the football.
How much you reckon that would return
if you if you guess two games with the correct score? How much?
[ __ ] a lot of money, matey.
A lot of money. If you projected like 2132 Jesus imag
Yeah, that is good though. 100 to 400.
cuz on a both teams to score 100 is like
310. So yeah, bless you in life them. Bless you.
What did we do?
Yeah. Well, it's not cheap in central
London when you go out drinking. It's
about £8 a pint.
Yeah, it's 8 pound a pint weaves you
when you go out.
8 pound a [ __ ] pint, bro. Yeah.
What do you think of that? G8 pound a pint.
So the on drink I would have spent
I spent 100 and it was 60 I spent on
drink was it? Yeah it must have been 60.
Yeah, I spent £60 on drink. Yeah.
Yeah. Well, that's fun.
Bless you then.
30 to50 dose of Fra.
Oh, bless you.
Bless you, Joseph. Bless you. Yep.
[snorts] No, we're enemies.
Joseph's a little copycat.
You little copycat.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
Nah, Joseph just copies.
Where does desire to desire come from to
want to copy someone else?
Nah, Joseph's a copycat.
Isn't that right? It's a little copycat.
Copycat statement. That's why I keep
giving Greavvesy content because he
comes he comes up with some funny sayings.
That's why I give Greavesy content. The poor [ __ ]
He says that I'm find I'm trying to find
someone to latch on some new boobies to
latch on to Grezy.
To latch on to
latch on to it, Grezy
sounds like a copycat statement. Bless you.
I might give you a moderator, Greavvesy,
if you if you be good. Oh gosh, Laney,
we're going to eat something later.
Oh, my bill come out my free bill.
I've got 800 Oh gosh.
No, she didn't get back to me, which was
strange cuz she told me to message her
and she didn't reply.
Good old England. Do you know what? I
might give you some content on Saturday.
Greed, I'm going to go out. No, I'm
going to go out on Friday.
I'm going to go out on Friday.
Friday, Saturday, whatever. Maybe f
Thursday. M. Nah, Friday.
And then next week we'll do Thursday.
I'm going to give you some content, Grezy.
To latch on to some new boobies, Grezy.
So, why does why does Peter Belly need
boobies then, Grezy?
I was telling Antman about this
yesterday. He lo he laughed.
You have to say some funny sayings,
Greaves. I'm providing you content here,
you know. I'm providing you content. Yeah. [snorts]
Do you still watch le? Uh, do you still watch Lex?
Do you still watch Lex? Bro,
I don't know why she didn't reply, bro.
She told me to message her. It's not
like she seemed unenthusiastic. It just
doesn't make sense.
But don't forget they can't find normal
men. Greasy, they can't find normal men. Remember,
they can't remember that they can't find normal men.
My friend said you got some balls on you
for going out and approaching.
Joseph, I don't understand how these
women say they can't find normal men
when when they come across normal
people, they're not interested. Weird, isn't it?
I was watching some vintage porn yesterday, Joseph.
Yeah, I was watching some 70s porn.
I'll never forget what Adman said. He
said, "Do you watch porn from the 70s?
That is weird."
No, they say that they can't find normal
people and that all men are the same,
but then when they have chances, then
they're not interested. So, I don't I
don't I don't really understand them to be honest.
It's like that it feels like they're making excuses
for the men that they're going for.
I feel like it's a cover up for the men
that they're going for. Does that make
sense, Grezy? So they're saying that to
excuse why they actually go for these
people because they don't want to sound
[ __ ] up in their head.
So they just say, "Oh, we can't find
anyone normal." Which me and you both
know that's not true. So I I think they
say it to stop so they don't sound
[ __ ] up in their head. Oh yeah, we
can't find a normal person.
Yeah, that's why they do. That's why
they do it.
I think that's why they do it, mate.
personally cuz that doesn't make any
sense cuz you've had people be genuine
and tell you what you are but then they
would have easy got with you.
So I think it they they do it to to to
cover up the fact that they like [ __ ]
up people basically.
How that person didn't even reply back.
That is rude. Especially when they were
telling me to message them. What the [ __ ]
can understand if you spoke for like 10
seconds and they they seemed
unenthusiastic then I could understand.
[ __ ] me, bro.
Well, maybe Well, maybe Joe Well, maybe
Joseph if they stopped saying they had a
boyfriend every 5 seconds, they might
actually be able to meet someone.
Maybe if they actually gave people a
chance and stopped pretending they had
boyfriends and you know, maybe
they could actually maybe find someone.
But you're not going to find someone
saying that you got a boyfriend every 5
seconds, are you? Or ignoring people's
messages or leading someone on.
I mean, how are you going to find
someone? How are you going to find How
are you going to find someone if you're
constantly saying that you got a
boyfriend and you don't? But how are you
going to find someone that treats you right?
That doesn't make sense.
That doesn't It doesn't make sense, Joseph.
Like I told you with that woman on
Snapchat, oh, thanks for approaching me.
You seem sweet. R But then why are they
not meeting you. Why they not going? And
I don't think it's lies either. I don't
think it's lies. So why are you not
going on a date with someone? I don't
give a [ __ ] I don't care about them. I
don't expect it. I'm I'm trying to put
myself in your position.
I'm trying to put myself in their
position. I I don't give a [ __ ] about if
they meet me or not. I'm just saying.
And surely to God, it's contradicting
everything that they're saying. Really, Joe?
So you're saying women are not all the same?
So you're you're saying that women are
not all the same, Joe?
I mean, they do the same thing. They say
the same thing. They act the same way.
I mean, I'm pretty sure I can torn them
in the same brush.
I'm pretty confident I can torn them in
the same brush.
I went out Saturday, I got one number
and the rest of the people that I
approached, they all said the same thing.
I don't know, bro. I think I can torn
them in the same brush.
I really think I can.
I don't know. I don't care. I don't
compare myself to people in relationships.
I don't compare myself to strangers. I'm
only going by my experiences. If women
aren't all the same, right? Okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay. If women aren't all the
same, why do they do act
the same way? Pretending they got
boyfriends, have the same attitude, lead
people in the same way. If they're not
all the same, then surely they wouldn't
do all the same stuff.
This is what I'm not saying.
No, I don't compare myself to strangers.
I don't compare myself to strangers. If
they're not all the same, why they do
act all the same?
That's me asking you a question and I'm
not comparing. I'm asking.
Yeah, they don't want you either.
So, they are definitely definitely all
the same. One million% they are all the
same. And I'm not a woman that's
generalizing men just to be angry. I'm
legitimately telling you they are all
the same. And I have been with women and
I've had sex. I've been with women and
I've had sex and I'm telling you they're
all the same.
So like I'm I must be one in a million.
I will refuse to to say something I
don't believe. I wouldn't sit here and
say something if I didn't believe it.
They are exactly all the same. Even when
there's other people talking to women,
they're doing and saying the same stuff.
They are literally all the same. And I
have no reason to lie about that.
Why would I say something if I didn't
[ __ ] believe it? You know, that's
doesn't even make any sense.
I thought this person might have been
different uh on Saturday when they told
me to message them, but they didn't
reply. So, yeah, same old [ __ ]
No, they're not the same. They're not
the same. Sorry, they're not Sorry,
they're not different. Sorry, they are
all the same. Definitely are all the same, bro.
But it's not a belief, it's facts. It's
not a belief, it's facts. people that
believe in God. People that believe in
God, right? People that believe in God.
But I don't care about people in
relationships. I'm talking about my own
experiences. That is not a belief. That
is a fact. I went out Saturday and three
people said I had a boyfriend before I
finished my sentence. That's a fact.
It's not a belief. A belief is believing
something that is not proven. Like
people believe in God. God is not a
fact. It's not set set in stone. This is
a fact. Again, it's missing my
struggles, a belief. I'm not believing
it. It's what I've been shown,
you know. So, you might think I'm being
awkward and I'm being difficult, but I'm
not. You might think, "Oh, I think it
really, really, really isn't that."
Don't forget, I've got a lot of
experience with this. You I don't I
think you fail to realize that I have a
lot of experience with this. You know, it's
you know, people in relationships have
got nothing to do with me. People that
are poorer than me has got nothing to
I'm going by my experiences. Why do I
care about anyone else?
You don't compare me to people that are
richer or poorer. So why are you
comparing me to other people when it
comes to women?
You don't compare me to anything else ever.
So why are you comparing me when it
comes to women? That doesn't make sense.
If they're not all the same, why do they
do act and say all the same stuff? I'm
not ugly. I'm not I haven't got social
anxiety. So what is it then? So why do I
keep having these experiences then?
Okay, if if they're okay, there's
people. So why why am I having these experiences then?
And don't make up stuff cuz the
approaches are out there. So don't say,
oh, it's the way you're acting because
Ricky Millington already tried that one.
And so you tell me what it is then cuz
it isn't the way I [ __ ] look and it's
not the way I dress. I don't look like
Timmy [ __ ] Eldridge. So what is it
then? If they're not all the same, what
is it then? Are they stuck up [ __ ]
Have they got unrealistic standards?
What is it?
Cuz I'm I'm not understanding how
me thinking about other people in
relationships is going to help me.
What's that going to do for me?
What is that got to do with my experiences?
I can I can find someone in a relationship. Okay,
maybe these people in relationships just
got lucky. Maybe these people in
relationships just tolerate each other.
Maybe these people that are married are
on the verge of divorce.
Okay, so we answer your question and
then what? We're still back to the same thing again.
So no matter if I answered you or I
don't answer, we're still back to me again. So I mean what? Yeah.
What about you?
So you going to get fish? Okay. But it's
expensive, isn't it?
Unless you get a big one. We just share
it in it.
This should be enough, isn't it? Yeah.
If you get a large one, you just share it. So,
summon a message stage.
I'm a manta self projecting. Anyways,
um that's self projection. And I've
already been with women, more women than
you. And another thing, and that's not
even joking. See, that's and this, you
know, when I'm saying this stuff, it's
it's the truth, though. It is the truth.
Which is why my op why what I'm saying
is so true. Why why I'm saying is so
true because I'm completely unbiased.
And also, they are literally all the same.
So, that's another thing. And yeah, they
do and say and act the same way, Grezy.
They are all the same.
Women are all the same.
They are literally all the same. Women
are definitely all the same.
So now we answer the people in the
relationships. Okay. Then what?
And what's that supposed to And now what?
Okay. And now what? I'm still stuck in
the same position. What? This is why I
said that comparing is
like Saturday. So you're telling me
they're not all going to pretend they
got boyfriends on Friday when I go out
greasy? They're not going to give me
their number and lead me on. Is that is
that really what you're saying? So when
I go out on Saturday, none of that
stuff's going to happen.
I've already explained it and it still
never changed my situation. They are
literally all the same. Every time you
approach a woman, it's always the same
thing. It's one of three things.
It is one of three things that happen.
They are definitely definitely
definitely all the same. And the day I
get shown different is the day I believe
it. I believe different.
The day I'm shown different is the day I
believe different. And I think that's
fair. I generally think that is fair.
And I used to have that same opinion about God. You know,
no, no, no. They are they are for
others. They Here's the thing, Joseph,
right? You're trying to make it seem
like this stuff only happens to me when
it's happening to about 85 90% of
people. I mean, people are moving to
Thailand now. People that are Tik Tok
[ __ ] stars are dealing with the same
[ __ ] You're making it seem like I'm the
only one in the world that's dealing
with this. This is what makes me laugh
when I guarantee you now, yeah, there
were more there were more people dealing
with this than not dealing with this.
Just because you see couples on the
street that have met years ago or met
through a friend or got lucky, that does
not mean, mate, listen, you go on
YouTube right now and you look up people
that are approaching women. It's not a
me problem. It's not a me problem. So, I
just want to throw that out there. As
long as you realize that it's more
people that are dealing with this than
not dealing with this, I think that we
need to set that straight before, you
know, it's not I'm in the 5% or I'm in
the 7%, bro. I'm in the 80 90% that are struggling,
you know. So what's happening for the
10%? Oh well the 10% now they met years
ago. No the 90% is not bollocks. No no
no no no. 90% is not bollocks. It has
been proven multiple multiple times. No
it is not bollocks. No it is definitely
definitely definitely not bollocks. All
of the people that you will see now in
relationships met years ago maybe met at
work maybe got lucky. It's not at all
comparable to you or other people that are struggling.
I'm making it up. Wait, wait, wait. So,
I'm making up that 80 90%. Nope. I'm not
showing you proof cuz any proof that you
you're shown, you dismiss it.
So, why do you want Why do you want Why
do you want to see proof? You're just
going to dismiss it? What do you want?
What do you want proof of? Um, I'm not
making up stuff. I'm going by what I'm
seeing. People moving to Thailand.
good-looking people now moving to
Thailand. Things I've seen with my own
eyes. I'm not making it up.
You know, I can show proof, but I'm not
proving myself to a biased person. I've
shown you women being [ __ ] I've shown
you women leading me on. You still make
excuses for them. So, why what do I get
from showing proof to you? You're biased.
You're literally biased.
So why why am I why am I going to show
proof to you when you're biased,
you know? And that's not even an excuse.
Okay, I'm coming out with complete
rubbish. Why? Because the truth hurts,
you know. Yeah. Okay, I'm coming out,
bro. You've seen You know what makes me
laugh, right? I have shown videos of
women being [ __ ] and you're still
defending them and you're still saying
they're not the same. It's a madness. It
is actually mad.
And yeah, women are definitely
definitely all the same. And people that
are in relationships are not at all
comparable to you. You can't compare for
several different reasons. Comparing is
weak. It's a weak argument. I used to
say the same thing to Pat Bustard.
Comparing yourself is is is not uh it's
not at all comparable
for several several several several
different reasons. And most people I
know are single. The most most people I
with no girlfriend. That's telling you
something. People that are not a part of
this community and whatever. So yeah,
it doesn't matter anyways, does it
really? It doesn't really matter the percentage anyways.
Do you're saying that I'm biased?
Joseph, listen. You want me to explain
how you're biased when I stuck it on the
bouncer and you're trying to say that
the bouncer can't do anything because
he's at at work yet we see bounces beat
people up all the time yet. You know,
you had no problem with a bus driver
giving it to me. Please, let's not talk
about bias now. You know, you know,
so at the end of the day, you don't talk
about people being biased. You've been
shown a man backing down and tried
saying, "Oh, he can't hit you cuz he's
he's at work when the guy's a bouncer."
Bro, stop it. Let's not talk about
biasness now, man. Let's not talk about
biasness. You had no problem with that
bus driver chucking it to me at work.
[ __ ] off, bro. Bro, don't do not talk
about people being biased.
You know what?
I'm not showing proof. Even when you're
shown proof, you deny it. I'm not showing proof.
I'm not. Bro, listen. Even when you're
shown Even when you're shown proof, you
still deny it.
So, I'm not showing you proof. And if
you think I don't have it, okay, I don't
have it. Whatever. You're biased, bro.
with the bouncer thing, the women thing.
You're all bi You're biased, bro. You're
bi I can I can list you so many times
where you've been biased. Why is anyone
going to waste their time?
Why is anybody going to waste their
time, bro? It's stupid.
You Yeah, that that was definitely definitely definitely,
bro, it doesn't matter about the
percentage. It's not accurate. There's
loads and loads of single people out
there. So, and also check the ages of
these people that are in relationships as well.
Comparing. See, this is what I mean,
Grezy. You don't have an argument. It's
all comparing. This is what I'm saying.
You don't have an actual argument
because it's all you're doing is comparing.
It's like Friday. If I go out
approaching Friday, I'm not caring about other people.
I don't care about other people.
Listen. Listen, I've Okay, and I'll
repeat myself again. I'm not showing
anything to you, bro. I I can shut it
down because And I'm explaining to you
why I'm doing it. And Okay. And I'll
explain to you for the fifth time why
I'm doing it. I'm not showing you
anything because you dismiss people's
struggles. It's a valid reason. You're biased.
The fifth time, I will explain it again
why I'm not putting evidence up. You've
You've been shown more than enough
evidence, and we're still having the same argument.
You have been shown black and white
Felix the cat evidence and you still
resort to making [ __ ] up.
So why am I going to put anything on the
channel trying to prove stuff to [ __ ]
biased people? It doesn't make any
sense. You've got your way of thinking
and that's it. Women can't do no wrong.
That's you're always going to think
that. It doesn't matter what you're
shown. So I don't know why you're asking
me to. You know what I mean?
So yeah. Yeah, man. Well, [ __ ] off then.
Yeah. And you're going to keep seeing
the same episode. We're going to keep
repeating the same episode as well. So
if you don't like it, [ __ ] off.
But yeah, comparing is a weak argument.
It's a complete complete complete weak argument. Yeah.
It's a complete and utter weak argument.
And the only thing you say as well and
the only thing you say, right, it
doesn't matter how many people are in
relationships. Women are all the same.
My evidence proves that. I don't care
about madeup statistics. I don't care
about madeup statistics. I care about my
experiences. I don't care about
statistics. Made up statistics.
I care about my experiences. How can
they be? Because I put videos up.
Because I put my videos and my evidence
up. That's how they can be. Because I
put my videos up. Again, repeating
myself. Because you're not
understanding, right? Because I put my
videos up and they do and say the same
thing and act the same way. I'm going by
my evidence. I don't care about
inaccurate [ __ ] statistics. I'm going
by my evidence, my experiences. I don't
give a [ __ ] about other people poorer
than me, richer than me, virgins, people
with women. I care about my evidence on
my phone, what I'm seeing. I don't care
about anyone else. I'm caring about me
going out approaching people and then
pretending they've got boyfriends and
giving attitude and leading people on.
That's what I care about. I don't care
about inaccurate statistics, madeup
statistics with strangers. I don't give
a [ __ ] about that.
So yeah, simple.
it's not going to change the fact that
they are literally all the same. Like if
you went on the vid, if you went on the
WhatsApp messages, you would literally
see. You know what I'm saying? I've
already pulled a bird more birds than
you'll ever pull. You know, again,
biasness. This is why people don't prove
themselves to you people anymore on
here. This is exactly what I'm talking
about. Why do you think people don't
show you money? Because you just make
stuff up. This is why no one proves
themselves to you anymore. This is
exactly what I'm saying to Grezy. I'm
telling you why I'm not doing it. I'm
giving you a reason why I don't show
anything on here anymore. Because you
just make stuff up. You've been shown
money approaches, women. You just make
[ __ ] up. So why is anyone going to
[ __ ] show anything to you? I'm I'm
explaining the reason and you're not on
You don't understand. You know,
you know what I'm trying to say.
You're an idiot, bro. You No one's going
to prove themselves to you people. I I
made that mistake many many times. I
[ __ ] put messages up there. I put
approaches up there, you know. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. But more people more people
are go more people are dealing with this
than not dealing with it, Joe. So surely
it's women that are the problem though.
Again dismissing my See, this is what
I'm trying to say. You're dismissing
struggles because more men are dealing
with it than not dealing with it. Yeah.
Do you want me to get on my whole
WhatsApp me my my whole WhatsApp thing
again and show you these people that are
single? It is definitely definitely the
women. When you go to different
countries, you don't get this problem.
It is definitely definitely definitely
one million% women. Do not make me put
my approaching videos up on my channel
all over again, bro, cuz I will do it.
It is definitely the women. This is why
most people are going most people are
[ __ ] single. More people are going
Thailand. It's definitely definitely the
women. It's a gender thing. You do not
think it is me. You do not think it's
me. Cuz if I was moaning about men,
you'd have no problem. So, you don't
think it's me? You're defending them cuz
they're women. Just like if I went on
Reddit right now moaning about men,
people wouldn't say it's me. It's a
gender thing. It's not a me thing. It's
a gender thing,
you know. It's a gender thing. It is the
women. You have been shown normal
conversations. You have been shown
normal approaches. You're choosing to
dismiss it cuz you're ignorant. You're
choosing. Yeah. Well, you fought wrong.
My evidence shows otherwise. You think,
but my evidence proves it's them. And if
you wasn't so ignorant, if it wasn't you
weren't so ignorant and you weren't so
[ __ ] sexist, you would actually, you
know what I'm trying to say? You're
choosing to dismiss what you're shown
because you're in denial and you're
ignorant. That's the That's the reason. So,
no, I've shown that women are clearly
stuck up [ __ ] and they're the
problem. So, yeah. See, even when you're
shown evidence, you still dismiss it.
How is that even possible to me? Yeah.
How can people be shown black and white
evidence and still think women aren't
the problem? You can You literally see
men going up speaking to women having
the same thing. You'll be shown evidence
and you will still defend women.
It blows my [ __ ] mind. Me and Ant-Man
was talking about the same [ __ ]
yesterday before I went to sleep. And we
don't understand how these people then
keep defending women even when they
shown them doing what they do. It's
autism. I'm telling you these people are
autistic. I'm telling you 100%. It's got
to be autism for people to be shown
black and white evidence in the eyes and
be like, "Nah, nah, never happened. It's
autism. It's 100%
autism. It's got to be, bro. Autism."
And they're lying to themselves. They're
[ __ ] lying to themselves,
you know. You know, you're you're you're
you're an idiot, bro. You're an absolute
idiot. It is definitely definitely
definitely definitely the women. If it
was not women, right? No. No. Okay.
Disagree. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Right.
Right. Let's go one by one then. Right.
So, you're not defending people just
because you disagree. That's that's
that's autism. Okay.
you know. Okay, fine. Let's put it this
way then. Per belly is giving you the
benefit of the doubt again. So, you tell
me what was wrong with these approaching
videos. You tell me what was wrong with
these approaching videos in the bars and
clubs. And you tell me what was wrong
with my messages where people agreed to
meet then suddenly backed out. Okay,
bro. You can't get a date with a woman.
Triple H. Your [ __ ] MS broke up with
you. So there you go. I'm giving you the
benefit of the doubt. Okay. So you don't
dismiss people's struggles. I'm talking
[ __ ] Okay. So you tell me exactly what
was wrong with them approaches. You tell
me exactly what was wrong with their
messages. If you remember any of the
messages, you tell me exactly what was
out of place in their messages one by
one. I'm always You said that you know I
always think I'm right. Now I'm asking
you a question now. So yeah.
So you tell me exactly what is wrong
with them approaching videos. What's
wrong with the
um the ones in the clubs, the ones in
all of these? You tell me exactly what
is wrong with their messages? Cuz I'm
the problem. Okay. Okay. Whatever. So
what's wrong with it then? I'm not
blocking anyone. I'll be here all day
waiting. I don't mind. You know,
so when somebody goes up and speaks to
someone and they say straight away, I
have a boyfriend and they're not
interested. What would you like me to
do? So, we're trying to learn now. We're
trying to learn from ourselves.
So, there's been so many different videos.
There's ones where you haven't finished
your sentence and people said they have
a boyfriend straight away. You've had
people say straight away they're not
interested straight away. Uh you've had
people lead you on. Okay. What did you
want me to do?
I think we're talking calm here now. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You have just said that I'm the problem.
So, you tell me exactly what is wrong, you know.
Yeah, I've never Triple H. I've had more
women than you've had hot dinners, mate.
Please stop it. [ __ ] all of that [ __ ]
Anyway, that's not important. So, you tell me.
You're taking a very long time to
respond to this. I've got all day, bro. All day.
So, do you not see that it's it comes
across that you're making excuses for women now?
Do you not see
that it very much seems like that you're
making excuses for women when I've just
lied it on the I've laid it on the
table. No comparing, straight up videos.
Criticize them one by one. Say what you
want and I'm waiting.
So, I'm still waiting. I'm waiting. No one's blocked.
So, at the end of the day,
it seems to me, right, this is what it
seems like to me. It seems like people
make up excuses for the fact that women
are shallow. This is what it's coming
across to me as. It's like they're
always it's a bit like when they make
excuses why when people leave people on
it's like they're so scared to just say
you know what women have got unrealistic
standards and then they say oh you're
the problem. Okay I'm the problem. Okay
then if I'm the problem then tell me
what is wrong with these approaching
videos. What's wrong with the messages?
So it seems it seems that you're just
making excuses to be honest with you. Um
because you just don't want to admit
women are shallow cuz in people's heads
women can't do anything wrong. I don't
come away. What? So what else do you
want me to do then? So I'm coming across
as desperate for what? Going up and
speaking to someone. Okay. What what
what do you want me to do?
So this is a gender thing. This is a
gender based thing. Um you know
I've shown women being stuck up. I've
shown. Okay, Grezy, can you maybe answer
the question then? So, Joe Joseph Far
can't answer it.
So, you tell me
why when you try to speak to a woman
straight away they say not interested or
they give attitude,
right? Which you clearly just missed,
right? So, what about these women then? You know,
yeah, no one's home. I know what that
feels like. I generally generally feels
like what what I've literally tried
explaining this to you now for the past
two days and it's not getting in your
head. I I know very very much no one
being home at the end of that light.
Trust me, I know because I've been
explaining this right for the past two
days and you're not understanding what
I'm saying. I'm telling I'm telling you,
right? Yeah. I I've literally told you
I'm explaining this and you just keep
dismissing it and dismissing it and
ignoring it, you know. And another
thing, I don't say, "Oh, I see you from
over there." I don't say that. So,
again, you're not even answering it
because you know you're wrong. This is
what I'm trying to say. I've asked you a
question and you're not even answering
it. You know, women are stuck up
[ __ ] You know it. You know that's it,
bro. Triple H, they don't want you
either. Your baby, bro. Another man is
bringing up your kids. So, another man
is bringing up your child right now.
They don't want your ass. Another man's
bringing up your kid. So, don't worry
about me, bro. Another [ __ ] man, your
[ __ ] child is calling another man daddy, bro.
Right, right, right, right, right,
okay, okay. But it's not just cold
approaching though, is it? But it's not
just cold approaching though, is it,
Grezy? But it's not just cold
approaching though, is it? It's not one
thing. I think you know you're miss
right. Should we just leave this now?
Because clearly you're setting your
ways. You can't be shown different and
we're just having the same argument now.
Women are perfect. Women don't do
anything wrong. Yes, they're all
different. Are you going to stop then?
If I agree with you, are you going to
stop? Because it seems like you're not
going to stop until someone agrees with you, bro. You know,
you have been shown multiple multiple
evidence. Yeah. No one wants you either,
bro. Another man is bringing up your
[ __ ] kid, you little [ __ ] So don't
[ __ ] sit there and try and say, "Oh,
oh, oh, you would do this. You would do
that. Yeah, I might have took an L from
Prime, but guess what, bro? I went to
Newcastle three times and you didn't
come up. You didn't even come out."
Yeah. Yeah. So what, bro? Prime might
have gave me a big fat L, but guess
what? I traveled to you three different
times and you didn't come out. So, stop
the [ __ ] cap.
So, stop talking [ __ ] as well. Um,
Grezy, about it just being one thing.
It's not just You know what? I'm just
going to moan now. And I'm I'm not even
going to answer any of your questions.
Since you're so ignorant that you seem
to dismiss everything I say, I'm not
even answering any questions anymore
now. Yeah. I'm just going to keep
moaning and moaning and winging and
everything you do, I'm not even going to
acknowledge it now. I'm not even going
to get into it now. You know, because if
you can't even be shown different,
[ __ ] good luck to you. You know, I'm
just going to keep moaning. I'm not
going to get get into anything.
Why are you talking about cold
approaching? It's not just cold approaching.
It's what they do via text. It's how
they act. It's in bars and clubs. It's
dating apps, you know.
So, it's just you are you're defending
them because they're women. This is this
is another thing we need to know that
you are just defending them because they're women.
You know, you're sat you're sat there
saying they're not all the same when
man's put up about a million videos of
them doing the same thing again. You ignored it.
Yeah. I don't give a [ __ ] Yeah. 90%.
And I can blame it. And I And listen, I
can I can prove the 90%. I can prove the
But I'm not going to.
There's no trying to make you people
understand anymore. You've got your ways
of thinking, you know. You've got your
ways of thinking, bro. You have got your
You know, and that's it. Your way is
your way. You can't be told different
because because you're saying that women
aren't all the same. I have shown
approaches of them doing and acting and
saying the same thing, having the same
attitude, but you're saying that they're
not the same. I don't want people to
agree with me. I've shown videos I have
shown videos that you keep dismissing
over and over and over and over and over
and over and over again. It's not a
debate. You've been shown different. You know,
you're still going on about that 96
square thing, bro. You living in the
past, bro. You're boring, man. You're
boring, kid. Shut up. Yeah. So,
I've explained to you about [ __ ] a
million times about my approaching
videos and you have not said anything about them,
you know, and you expect me to believe
that women aren't all the same because
other people are in relationships. So,
don't go. So, what your logic is, right?
What your logic is, right? What your
logic is, right, is don't think women
are all the same because there's people
in relationships, even though most
people are single and every single woman
you come across will be the same and has
been the same for years. You have to
agree with these people because of other
people, not your own experiences. [ __ ]
off, mate. So, I'm going to think that
all women aren't the same. Yet, most
people are single just because you see
other people in relationships. So all of
your experiences for four years, all of
your experiences for four years don't
count because there's others in
relationships. Not a [ __ ] chance,
right? It's like trying to explain,
"Bro, my videos show that they're the
problem. My videos show that they're the problem." Yeah.
No, it's not made up. No, it is not made
No, it is not made up.
And also, so wait, so you want me to go
by other people's experiences and not by
my own? Most people are single. Most
people are not in relationships.
And I'm not Nothing's telling me that
I'm the I'm the problem. I'm showing you
women are the problem. You're telling,
but I'm showing. I've got my messages.
I've got my approaches. I'm not telling.
I'm showing. You understand? I am
showing. That's the difference. I am showing. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm just Yeah, Mike. Yeah, Mike.
I'm trying to explain to them. Yeah.
That all women are the same and they're
not having any of it.
No, I'm I'm watching my videos. I don't
need to tell myself anything.
I don't need to tell I'm just watching
my videos of my experiences with women.
I'm not going by other people's
experiences. I'm going to go by my own.
I don't care about others. I'm going by
my own experiences.
I don't give a [ __ ] about other [ __ ]
strangers in relationships. It hurts my
brain as well. Like Mike, yeah, I've
literally been explaining for the past
two days that women are the problem.
I've shown them messages. I've shown
them approaches and they still won't
have it. No matter what I show them.
How do you think I feel? I've been
trying to explain the same thing for two
days and they're like, "Nope, nope,
nope." Even though I've literally put
videos up there, I've literally put
messages, videos, they still won't have it.
They literally they literally will not
have any of it.
No matter where I've traveled to,
they're like, "Nope, no, no, no, no,
no." They're like Pluto the dog. No
matter what you show them, they're like,
"Nope, nope, nope, nope." You can't show
these people different. They've got
their ways of thinking. They want to
defend women. They want to lick women's
asses. They want to think women are
going to sleep with them.
and they'll be like they they that's
their that that's their way of thinking.
I'm trying to explain to them, Mike. I
don't care if you agree or disagree. I
don't want people I don't want I don't
want people to disagree. I don't want
people to agree. But I've shown videos
where women have been stuck up and rude.
They keep dismissing it and saying that
I'm the problem. Even though I've shown
them leading me on, and they're still
not having any of it.
They're still not having any of it for Topy.
I've shown them videos where women have
led me on, [ __ ] me over, said they're
not interested straight away. And they
still keep defending women,
right? Because I don't care about other
people's experiences. I care about my
experiences. I don't care about other
people. I know more people struggle than
don't struggle. End of the statistics are irrelevant. >> [laughter]
>> Look at this little white knight. One
second. Ew. A s. He's even trying to
defend them. Even leading me on now. Ew.
A s. Sorry, white knight. Sorry, lady.
Sorry, lady. I had to say that. Sorry.
Ew. A white knight that defends women
for just defend just for them being women.
There you go. That is definitely
definitely a white knight. Definitely
definitely definitely a white knight.
These people think women are angels.
They literally think women, they've got
autism. I'm telling you, these people
are autistic, bro.
You know, you can't get through to
autistic people, bro. That would just
lick women's asses all their life. How
did I harass people? By going up and
speaking to someone.
Definitely confirmed. Definitely.
Definitely confirmed. I'm leaving it up
there now. Yeah, they Yeah, there's
there's no point. You know what, right?
I think this is this is the healthiest thing. Yeah,
you have your opinion. I have my
opinion. And well, I've actually got my
facts. But anyways, and I think we
should just all agree to disagree.
I really, really, really, really, really
think because it's getting unhealthy
now, bro. Like, it's like
if people if people can't be shown
different, there's no hope.
If people can't even be shown
differently, then we're wasting our time here.
It's always [ __ ] other people, isn't
it? Never you. Always the strangers, you know?
I don't care about statistics. I know
more men struggle than don't struggle.
It doesn't matter the statistics,
even though the statistics is 90%.
But even if it was 75 or 80%.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Anyways, we're moving
on from this now anyways cuz we're just
going round and round and round and
round in circles. Listen, Billy Bundles,
remember me when you're an 80year-old
man on your deathbed and realizing that
women don't like you. Defending them
never got you laid and you'll never ever
be with a woman by defending them.
Remember me when you're on your deathbed
that you wasted all of these years
defending people that don't like you and
hate you. Just remember me. I'm not
getting into this anymore now. Anyways,
my fish and chips should be here in a minute. You know,
you know what I find strange about this
Grezy is that no one is saying that
they're wrong ever. Even if I was wrong
90% of the time. That's very, very
concerning to be honest.
No, you'll be laughing at yourself,
mate. still a virgin defending women for
the sake of it. What a loser. Yeah.
I mean, you're the one that's defending
them. You're a [ __ ] loser defending
them just for defending them. You'll be
laughing at yourself. Well, you won't
actually be laughing actually.
90% of the minions. I'm not answering
your questions anymore.
I'm not answering your questions
anymore. Simple. I'm an answer and I'm
not getting into no debate with biased
white knights. So, end off. You know,
listen, I don't give a [ __ ] what the
statistics are. It's not going to change
my experiences. I don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah, I don't. Yeah, bro. Sending dick
pictures, bro. That's just a start, bro.
The dick pictures are just the start.
I'm immature, but yet it's okay for
women to lead people on. Make it make sense.
So, I'm immature.
I'm the one that's immature, but it's
okay for them to do. I'm not, bro,
that's the start of it. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm just going to eat my fish and
chips, by the way. That's just the start
of it. I'm [ __ ] them over royally,
bro. I'm going to ruin one of their
lives. I'm not going to be happy until I
ruin one of their [ __ ] lives. Nope.
because it's not crap.
Anyways, I'll be right back.
So, that's immature sending out, but
it's okay for them to leave people on. Mom,
why do people love defending women for
just having a [ __ ] in between their
legs? I feel like I'm constantly having
the same argument over every day. Huh? >> Hm.
say that for me.
>> But why do they keep defending women? I
just want to know. I've been asking the same question.
I've been asking the same question now
for God knows how long and it just keeps getting ignored.
>> And I've been asking you not to go on YouTube.
>> Right. But I want to know why people
keep defending women.
I'm just wanting to know why people are
doing it. That's what I'm asking.
H why do they think they can't do no
wrong? Why? Why is it? I want to know.
>> Where were these good women then? Where
were these good women? If you can show
me, I would believe it.
>> If you can show me it, I would believe it.
>> You know, it's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
It's so annoying.
I've asked you a question. Oh, there's
good women. Where are these good women?
It's a question. You've said it,
>> you know.
>> You know, I'm sick of hearing the same [ __ ]
>> No. No. Because I'm sick of hearing it
out. I'm sick of [ __ ] hearing it.
I'm sick of hearing.
I'm sick of it.
I'm stupid [ __ ] idiom
people. [ __ ] off. It's annoying, bro.
You know they don't want you. Another
man's bringing up your [ __ ] kid. You
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] They don't want you
either. That's why your [ __ ] your son
don't even see you, bro. Your son's
calling another man daddy.
They don't want you either. You jeweled
[ __ ] with an ugly kid. [ __ ] [ __ ] You know,
stupid [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] your kids calling another man
daddy, bro. Your ugly [ __ ] kid. And
you're trying to [ __ ] talk about me.
[ __ ] off, mate. Yeah.
I don't want you. You [ __ ] Georgie [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] older than me. Still
living with his [ __ ] parents.
with his [ __ ] parents in in [ __ ]
the northeast. [ __ ] off, mate. [ __ ] [ __ ] Mm-
I be 28 and be a 40-year-old loser like
you, you [ __ ] [ __ ] defending
women. You [ __ ] [ __ ] At least I'm
not a virgin like you defending women.
You [ __ ] [ __ ] loser.
in my lane, bro. Yeah,
they're not mature, bro. They're [ __ ]
ignoring little [ __ ] I'd rather be
[ __ ] than a 40-y old virgin like you.
Little white knights.
Little [ __ ] white knights.
They defend women, but women don't even
want them. They're losers. That they're
defending women, but women don't want
them. Look at all of the women that I've
been with. They've never even been with
a woman. Defending women because they're
virgins. Because they're so interested
that they think by defending them
they're going to get laid.
They think by defending them they're
going to get laid. They're losers.
I don't listen to no one. I don't listen
I don't listen to no one. Me,
right? [ __ ] white light.
[ __ ] white knight defending all the
bad things women do. Loser loser.
>> I'm going to go out. I'm going to end up
going out and punching woman in her
face. I just told this to my mom like
I'm going to end up going out and
beating up a woman. I swear to God.
The more you keep doing this, the more
I'm going to want to bang one in their
mouth. And you keep annoying me. I'm
going to end up banging one in her mouth
in front of any man. Bro, just leave me
alone. Stop antagonizing me cuz I will
go and just bang one out of their face.
So just stop aggravating people, bro.
You understand? Just stop aggravating people.
Yeah. So do women leading people on, you little [ __ ]
Yeah. The same as women leading people
on that you keep ignoring. You little s
little white knight. Yeah. So do women
leading people on. But you got no
problem with that. So don't [ __ ] come
with my [ __ ] telling me that I'm going
to buy another [ __ ] child, you little
[ __ ] I'll do what I want. I'll send
dick pictures. I'm going to whine and
dash them. I'm going to do everything
cuz I can. Just like I said that person
on a message. Just like I said that
person a message. I'll do it because I
can and I will keep doing Yes.