These little [ __ ] idiots got my
[ __ ] WhatsApp band.
I'll have to sign up with a [ __ ] new number now. Jesus.
I mean, that's really the only way they
could get me in it. Cuz what are they
going to do? Call the police from
another country? I don't think so. No. [clears throat]
No. I can't use I didn't have [ __ ]
thingies number on that [ __ ] thing.
It said I got banned from spam. It must
have been the [ __ ] dick pictures I was sending.
So, I've appealed it in it. If it I just
have to sign up with a different number
and then just have to start
conversations again, I guess. Isn't it?
It's not a big It's not a big deal. They
don't have to make a new number. Hope I
don't have to. But if I do, I do. [laughter]
They're such cowards. They're fast
enough to report people. They give it,
but they can't take it. These cowardly
women. They can give it, but they can't
take it. I was giving that Finnish one
[ __ ] via SMS.
I was giving her [ __ ] via SMS.
Proper proper [ __ ] bro. Proper [ __ ]
I said, "Haha, you're all well and big
leading someone on and being a being a
[ __ ] Yet when they send you their dick,
you block them. [ __ ] off and go get you
know what, man. Literally, you're only
big at playing games till you meet your
match. All you [ __ ] are victims.
Women are all the same." Done. Yeah.
It's the truth, is it, bro? Just give
them some [ __ ] what they've gave you
over the years. Bit back what they gave you.
If I get if the rocks app gets banned
and I just have to register a new
number. My the number that I got.
Not a big deal. Bit annoying but oh well. Yeah.
It was pictures in it. Definitely. Oh well.
I need to go back on that, bro. Anyways,
no more arguing. No more no more going
back and forth because we're never we're
always going to agree to disagree. So
there's point it's pointless.
I have my experiences. I'll continuously
keep having my experiences and you say
what you say. I think that's the best way, bro.
Yeah, it's completely the best way.
It doesn't matter who's wrong or right.
The fact of the matter is it's never
changing. So I don't I don't know the
point of it the whole thing in the first
place to be honest. So yeah,
I won't be on here tomorrow. Anyways,
I'm I am actually done with this YouTube [ __ ]
after today. 100% I am done with it
after today. I'm just going to use
Reddit and other other forums. Yeah,
that Red Star still stalking me. By the
way, that wasn't uh that wasn't me that
actually posted that. still stalking me.
Yet you got all this money, this life.
Yeah, right. A normal person can only
keep it up for so long, bro. Can only
keep it up for so long. It's obvious
what these people are in here now, bro.
I don't care. I'm off anyways tomorrow.
They're just sad people and got a life.
So yeah, that's that. Oh,
hopefully I get his WhatsApp come back. Yeah. Hopefully if not
doesn't matter anyways really.
Yeah, I'll be in bed again tomorrow. I
haven't left the house today, have I? Nah.
This is almost 2026
and we're still dealing with these
problems. We're still having these
We're still dealing with these problems.
I could have got arrested today if I
carried on shouting.
That's what happens when your struggles
keep getting dismissed. [ __ ]
irritating as [ __ ]
But we need to put it down to now that
everyone's just always going to dismiss
your struggles. So they're always going
to defend women for being women. So just
get out of any kind of argument that
we'll get into that
anything they do will just get
dismissed. So there's no point having an
argument. There's no point talking about
statistics, explaining your experiences.
It's all pointless, you know. It's all
[ __ ] pointless. Because the way I see
it is if we go out on Saturday, we know
exactly what's going to happen. I know
it. I know exactly what's going to
happen. So, it doesn't matter about
anyone else. It doesn't matter about
other people. I know exactly what's
going to happen.
And that's all you need to know,
you know? So, nothing's going to change
these things. Other people better,
worse, same as you. None of these people
going to change this. This is always
going to be the same. So, um,
yeah, it's always
it's always going to be the same with
these women, so it doesn't really matter.
I was giving a lot of women [ __ ] today,
bro. a lot of them [ __ ] I'm not
surprised about the what's happening to be honest. Yeah,
I gave a lot of them.
All the bloody bad experiences they kept
giving me for years. Yeah.
That's what I'm saying. It's still It's
still dismissing it. Look, I don't agree
with how you talk about women are
approaching dating yet dismissed all of
the things that they've done to me. So,
you're always going to have this
problem. Every time you get into a
debate, you're always going to keep
having these problems where they just
dismiss everything that they're doing.
And then you argue and argue and argue
and eventually just lose brain cells.
And that's all that happens.
So you don't agree with how people talk
about women, but you agree with what
they do. Leading people on and giving
attitude, being [ __ ] that all gets
dismissed. That's what I'm saying.
That's the whole point of dismissing struggles.
You know, they really really do dismiss
your struggles. Like it isn't it isn't
even a joke.
It is it is dismissing struggles cuz
everything you show goes back to you again.
It all goes back to you. It's like a
wheel and it spins and spins and spins
and then it goes back to you again. It's
all about you. You, you, you, you, you.
It doesn't matter what they do. They
don't give a [ __ ] about what they've
done. It's you.
One second. I'm going to send a voice
note to this woman. Hold on a minute.
Let me say
that just gets thrown under the bus what they've done.
I just sent her a voice note. So I said,
"Okay, you're saying about how I'm
talking about dating and women, but what
about what the women have done? That all
seems to get thrown under the bus again."
>> Strange, isn't it?
>> Very, very strange. I couldn't even eat
my food today in peace.
So why are you saying about how
right I'll repeat myself again
same conversation again I'm talking
about them because of my experiences
with them same old conversation um I'm
gone tomorrow anyways, bro, cuz I'm sick
of having the same old [ __ ]
conversation. We've been having it now
for weeks and weeks and weeks and weeks
and weeks and weeks and weeks.
I'm speaking about them because of my
experiences with them, you know.
Yeah, it's definitely just missing struggles.
>> Just double standards.
>> I went on that V's channel, by the way.
He's so desperate to get a reaction. He
needs to stop. Bro,
this is boring now. You've said all of
this before. Someone's lost their sub.
It's this the same old boring now, bro.
Think of new [ __ ] It's just the same
people doing the same [ __ ] This is why
people don't rise to it cuz it's the
same people doing the same [ __ ]
[ __ ] that. hate you, reject you, and
leave you sexless and lead you on. Are
you supposed to big them kind of people
up? I don't understand. Constantly
They just they well they do get it.
Look, I'm buying my nails a lot, bro. Look. Ow. Yeah,
they definitely dismiss struggles though. 100%.
You are dismissing struggles. I'm not
saying women are innocent or that your
experiences aren't real. Two things can
be true at the same time. People can
treat you badly and the way you speak
about women and approach state can push
people further away.
Yes, but that's not the problem, is it though?
Yeah, exactly. And it's not even that.
And I'll continue
to get bad experiences
as well. But the past will continue to
have bad experiences. So long as we keep
trying, we'll continuously have bad
experiences. It doesn't matter how many
people are single, how many people are
in a relationship. [ __ ] the whole
world could be in a relationship. the
whole world could be [ __ ] single. It
really doesn't really matter because
every time you go out, you're going to
have the same experiences.
Even if we was to erase the past and
make the future, you are going to have bad experiences.
So, I think that's pretty much all that
matters to be honest. Yeah,
you're going to have bad experiences. If
I go out on Friday, Saturday, I'm going
to have more bad experiences.
I think that's all that matters is
you're going to keep getting bad
experiences with women.
That's that is it.
[ __ ] WhatsApp got banned. [ __ ] sake. Yeah.
and then you have the same argument. You
have the same conversation again.
That mindset is exactly why I said what
I needed to say.
It's a mindset. Okay. Okay. So me saying
if I go out this week I'm going to get
the same [ __ ]
What happens depends on the mind on
mindset behavior and how you treat people. Huh. Okay.
What about what about the dismissing
struggles again? Um
yeah definitely just missing struggles.
They always want to turn this into a you
problem. If you're a man, this is what
I'm saying. There's no point with these
people. I'd [ __ ] give up.
Yeah, they're definitely dismissing struggles.
They're definitely definitely definitely
definitely dismissing struggles. They
Yeah, I I definitely give up now. I do Yeah, definitely.
What happens depends on mindset,
behavior, and how you treat people.
You just said that you don't dismiss my
struggles. So, if you didn't dismiss my struggles,
Well, I care about them.
Yeah, well, I care about him. Well, you
care about women's struggles, so you
should care about my struggles. Don't be sexist now.
Look, lo and behold, she hasn't replied again.
She hasn't replied again. Oh, damn.
>> Yeah. He said, "What happens next week
depends on your mindset behavior and how
you treat people."
I said, "Okay, what about the
experience? What about the approaches
and the messages where I was nice and
they [ __ ] me over or they said they
weren't interested straight away." She
turned around and said, "Not every
experience isn't going to be easy and
not everyone will treat you well. That's
part of dating for everyone, but not
everyone is is the same either. How you
respond and adjust matters. So if I go
out this week, you're telling me it's
not going to be the same as last week,
the time before that, the time before
that, the time before that, the time
before that, the time before that, the
time before that, the time before that,
because you think it's not going to happen,
really. So if I go into this pub on a
Friday, right, thinking, "Yep, I'm
wrong. All women are innocent. Nothing
bad's going to happen. Nothing bad's
going to happen." No, I'm struggling to
believe you going by previous
experiences. I'm I'm I don't believe you.
I really really really really don't believe you.
It's not about mindset. Your mindset is
We're just going around in circles
again. Yeah, we're just going round and
round in circles.
And you're saying you're not dismissing
it, but Well, you kind of are dismissing it.
You are dismissing it
because my my videos are contradicting
everything you're saying. That's part of Yeah.
No, they're definitely definitely
dismissing struggles. They don't really
seem to realize that bad experiences
are making you think the way you're
thinking. And no matter how many times
you explain it, it it's very logical. It
makes perfect sense, but it doesn't it
doesn't quite sink in. They seem to
think that people come off of their they
come out of their um the the they got
snipped out off their biblical cord and
you just started hating men or you just
started hating women. They seem to think
that people are born like this which
don't make sense.
It's not about mindset. They are why you
have got a bad mindset. It is because of
them. Just like when I went out
Saturday, I have a bad mindset because
of them. I didn't even want to go out on
Saturday because of their [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] again. You know, they are
the ones that cause negativity
just like loads of other things in the world.
[ __ ] idiot. They'd still dismiss it,
Autumn. they'd still dismiss it.
No, it's not because I'm a no one to
them. They don't care because you're a
man and not a woman. Let's be real about
this. If you was a woman complaining,
everyone would feel sorry for you. So, that's that.
Yeah, it gave me a [ __ ] headache.
that boyfriend [ __ ] last week. He gave
me a headache, bro. I was about to bounce. Yeah.
Nah, I don't think I am going to go out
this week to be honest with you. I don't
think it's good.
You know, if you give if you don't go
out this week, there's a chance you
could calm down a little bit. If you go
out, you're just having this the same
thing's going to happen again, bro.
No, I don't think it's worth it. It's
not worth it.
Yeah, I do. Yeah.
I think it's a good idea, bro. To be fair,
I get everything done when I go to the
barbers. I get everything. Hair, beard,
face mask, and you still can't find no one.
>> You still get the same old.
This shit's not cheap either.
So, this is why we kind of think that we
got no hope. But, I mean, when you say
that you got no hope, they're telling
you you're negative. Completely
dismissing the fact that you tried for
years, you put up with their [ __ ] for
years, you keep getting [ __ ] over for
years, you're weak, you're negative.
That's that's their that's their that's
their that's the way they think. So
yeah, they just struggles. It's really
sad, bro. It's a really sad world we live in,
you know. It is.
You know, I get everything done.
And how you know you won't find anyone
is because of years. It's been going on
for years as well. I used to get my
haircut every week. You know, you'll
never meet anyone because it's been
going on for years.
My [ __ ] is [ __ ] banned. I can't even
go on my WhatsApp now. Oh well.
Hopefully I'll get it back in it.
Otherwise, I have to register my new
number and start conversations again. Oh no.
Probably a good thing they banned it to be honest.
Yeah, I was [ __ ] with people today
via SMS. They replied straight away.
These women truly truly are evil. I
really think that I shouldn't go out
this week, bro. I I don't think I should
go out. Nah, I don't think so.
You might as well just lie in bed and do
nothing. It'd be the same anyways, you know.
Yeah. You might as well just lie in bed
and do nothing to be honest.
Too frustrating to even do anything bad.
Is it bad? Very bad. Very, very bad.
Really bad that this is still going on.
It's bad it's still going on in it in almost 2026. Yeah.
2020 2026 and this is still going on.
It's super bad, is it? No wonder so many
people killed themselves. I can see why
they do it.
It's bad. It really is bad.
I'm not far behind them to be honest.
Oh, I might not kill myself. I might
just give up in life,
which I already have done. Oh yeah, I
don't think I'll kill myself.
Shouldn't be that way. You should be
living. You should be happy in your
life. You should be with someone.
There's no reason why you're not with
someone. You should be enjoying your
life, bro. Not having to go out and
speak to people to try to find someone
at 20 almost 29 years of age. You
shouldn't have to be doing that.
There's no reason for you to still be in
this position with the amount of effort
that you have tried.
But why are we still in this position? I
don't understand. You've tried more than
anyone in the [ __ ] world. You're not
[ __ ] disabled. [ __ ] sake. Not that
there's anything wrong with being
disabled, but uh that's society judging
you, you know? There's no reason.
There's literally no reason for it.
>> Yeah. I won't be getting into any debates
anymore about this. Yeah.
I did it.
Truly are evil, mate. Truly are evil. I
don't think I'll be doing anything Christmas either.
No, I don't think I'll be doing anything Christmas.
Why not let me send that?
Yeah, I might not be doing anything
Christmas e to be honest. Probably just
lie in bed. Yeah. We uh
they'll be in bed. Come here.
Yes. So they must have reported me for that thing.
They must have reported me for that dick
thing. Ain't it?
You really need to leave this country, bro.
>> Cuz think about it. If Ant-Man If
Ant-Man didn't, he he'd still be in the
same position. Depressed. Probably in
prison. No, he would be definitely be in
Yeah, that's the only way, mate.
I think I generally think it really is, you know,
cuz there's no reason why you're you're
in this position.
There's no re there's no reason.
Yeah. There's no reason why you're in this position.
You need to go to another country. This
is never changing in this country, bro.
Even if we said, you know what, [ __ ] the past.
You're still going to have the same bad
experiences. Even if you don't even if
you don't want to bring up the past,
every woman you come across is going to
[ __ ] you over.
That is literally exactly what is going
to happen. You're going to be dealing
with the same [ __ ] Even if you wanted
to forget all about what happened,
you're still going to have the same problems
and then it will escalate and escalate
and you'll become miserable again and
miserable again and then you have the
same argument again and it will never change. Simple
and that's it. So,
you're not going to meet anyone that's
different. Even if you went out week,
even if you went out every week,
they're all the same. It doesn't matter
what kind of face that they put on.
They're all the same.
They're all the same. Stuck up, entitled
[ __ ] mind [ __ ] They're all the same.
So, the only reason I'd be tempted to go
out this week is so I get the money for
my so I get money's worth for my haircut. Yeah. And then
months. I won't be out for months then.
Months and months and months and months
and months and months and months and
months and months and months and months.
I don't care about no woman on YouTube.
Months and months and months and months
and months. I will I'll just not go out for months.
I mean, the longest I've not been out
for is about 6 to 8 weeks. Long time.
Too many bad experiences.
That's why I don't go out. Too many bad
experiences. Toxic, waste of time. Not
even about the money. It's just a
complete waste of time. Um, that's why I
don't do it.
She didn't tell me that. Yeah,
she didn't tell me that, did she? I
didn't hear that.
I didn't say that.
I didn't even hear that. Oh, let me have
a look in a minute. I didn't even hear
it. What? Go out and get real friends.
I've got real friends. I don't go out.
Oh, not this again. We're not having
this conversation again. And then people
are going to come on here and say that
you got no friends. It's the same old [ __ ]
Yeah. He's a sad bastard, bro. He's a
sad, fat, ugly bastard. He ain't got a life.
We've said what we've had to say about
him. He's a loser. Life's loser. I
already told you about this earlier.
For people to be doing this for years,
still doing this hate every day, mate.
They got something wrong with them.
I would get bored after like a month or
two months. They They never seem to get
bored. It's madness.
And they try telling people they've got a life. Nah. So yeah,
I'll be in this week anyways. So
I feel like if I get one more bad
experience, I'm going to be on the watch list, bro.
I don't want one more bad experience.
And if I go out, I'm going to get more
bad experiences and I will go mad. So
just wait now. You should calm down by
tomorrow. You should be all right
That's it. You should be all right again.
I was fine. I was only pissed off the
other day cuz I knew what I was in for
and I knew I had to go out otherwise Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, I don't want her.
I hate these westernized women. I hate
them, mate. That Finland one, I gave her
[ __ ] as well. Oh, I told her to get you know what.
Yeah, I'm sending like four people a
picture on my dick. Now my WhatsApp's
banned. Hopefully I get back tomorrow.
I don't give a [ __ ]
You're not big now, are you? Why are
they not big when when they meet their
match? Why are they never big when they
meet their match? They're big enough to
lead people on and be a [ __ ] but
they're not big enough when they meet
their match, is it?
I don't want any women. I want revenge
on women. I want revenge on women now
for what they've done to me over the
years. I don't want no women women now.
Why would you want scum that all the same?
I gave someone the benefit of the doubt
last week. Uh yeah, they done the same thing.
Same thing again. Told me them, they
didn't reply. What was the point of you
even giving your [ __ ] number? So you
go around in circles. You go around in
circles. That's all you do. You just go
around in circles. You don't need to go
out and give anyone the benefit of the
doubt. Because I was forced to go out
because I was forced to go out and
obviously I had to approach in order to
get somebody to meet me so I can get
revenge on them. I had to go out. Why
was I out in the first place? Cuz I was
basically forced to go out.
Uh, lead me on. Uh, she led me on.
Uh, she led me on. I don't You might not
remember the um conversation.
Yeah, but I'm not going to. If I'm
forced to go out, then obviously I'm
going to approach, aren't I? What else
am I going to do?
But yeah, anyways, I approached because
I wanted to find one to [ __ ] over. So,
how did she lead me on?
Uh, I'm not even going to explain how
she led me on because in your eyes, a
woman can't lead you on. So, there's no
point of me explaining it.
If you saw the messages, you would see
um what did she do? She was saying, "Oh,
yeah, you should come to Finland." No,
no, no, no. And then all of a sudden I
was sick I was sick. I was sick of this
[ __ ] here. And I was like, "Oh, let me
go to Finland. It might cost £400 or500.
I might come to Finland and see you soon."
Um, then she said, "Oh, I've actually
found someone I I like and I'm going to
try with them. Wish you all the best
though." Didn't even reply. Didn't even
reply. This was months ago. Messaged
them two weeks ago saying I hate women.
They didn't reply and I thought, "Oh,
who can I send my dick to?" Yeah, she
was being a [ __ ] in the end.
So, yeah, I just just done it to her as
well. You did not just find someone that
you've met once that you like. People do
not catch feelings that quick. Yeah.
Yeah. She was being a [ __ ] She might
have been polite over the messages, but
she was still being a [ __ ] A leading on
[ __ ] So, [ __ ] off. Simple.
You wish me all the best. [ __ ] off. You
know, don't [ __ ] type if you're not
going to meet anyone. [ __ ] off. Simple.
I didn't even reply to it. I didn't
reply, you know. So, yeah.
And she is still part of it.
You know, you're you don't people don't
change their mind that quick. We're not
going to get into this conversation
anyways. We're not getting into this
conversation again, bro.
You think what you what think. I know
what I know. No, no, sorry. You think
what you think. I think what I think. I
think we should agree to disagree here.
I'm not going to say I know. I think
what I think. You think what you think. Simple.
People People do not change their mind
that quick. We don't hear these excuses
for men. So, let's not hear about women.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And it's not an
excuse. It's not an excuse. Yeah. People
don't just change their mind that quick.
So stop it. So stop it. Okay. Yeah, but
Okay. But she's saying But she's saying
I wish you all the best.
But what if that guy cheated on her?
What if that guy didn't like her back? Then what?
No, it's not normal because that guy No,
it's not normal because that guy could
have cheated on her.
Anyways, we're not talking about this,
right? You're making excuses for her cuz
she's a woman. Me and you both know
that. We're not having this, right?
Okay. You're making excuses for her cuz
she's a woman.
Um, so all of this is irrelevant what
they're doing, you know? So,
yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That was
in my mind. Yeah. Yeah. Of course.
Anyways, you're defending them because
they're a woman, not cuz you think
they're right. So,
you're bro, we're having this conversation
because she's a woman,
not because you think that she's right.
Uh, she did do something wrong. He did
So, she did do something wrong. Madness.
The guy could have cheated on her. The
might the guy might not feel the same way. Um, so yeah,
end of conversation. This is where it
starts becoming unhealthy. Now, I don't
understand the whole point of this
conversation, bro. What What's the point
of me agreeing with you, me disagreeing
with you? Does Does it really matter,
bro? Does does it really really really
really really matter?
At the end of the day, if I go out this
week, I'm going to have more bad experiences.
I will have experience bad experiences
for the rest of my life. Does it matter
who agrees? Who doesn't agree? I don't
see the whole point of this. Even if
you're right and I'm wrong, I don't understand.
Right, bro? It's all irrelevant. Whether
you think they're the same or not, it's irrelevant.
It's just all irrelevant. If I go out
this week, I'm going to get bad experiences.
That's a fact. So, all of this talk is irrelevant. So,
but yeah, she definitely definitely did
do something wrong. People don't change
their mind that quick. And again, I'm
not I'm not even just, bro, I'm not even
having this conversation no more.
So, it's pointless. If you think they're
all innocent and they whatever, I don't care. Simple.
It's not going to change if you're right
or you're wrong. Does it really matter
what will happen if we go out on
Saturday? Bad experiences with women.
But let's move forward and think this is
going to happen.
Right. End the conversation. [snorts]
So yeah, end the conversation.
We're not getting into this again.
Actually, I don't want you to agree with
me because even if you agree with me,
it's not going to it's not going to change facts.
I'm saying that you're making excuses
because they're a woman.
So, you don't even disagree with me.
You're only disagreeing because they're a woman.
I don't care what you agree on. Disagree
me all you like. I don't care.
You can disagree all you want. I don't
give a [ __ ] if you agree or disagree.
What is you? What if you agree with me
or you disagree with me?
That's not going to change my
experiences whether you you agree or
not. So, do I care? Do I really really really care?
If you agree with me or you don't agree
with me, I don't give a [ __ ] Agree,
disagree, I don't care.
So, anyways, end of story, right?
Well, I don't really care whether you
agree or you don't agree. I've said what
I've had to say. I've proved that people
make excuses just because people are
women and that's it. I don't really give
a [ __ ] I don't care who agrees or who
disagrees cuz at the end of the day,
you're not me. You're not in my shoes.
So, what the [ __ ] would you know about
me and what I've been through? So, what
the [ __ ] would you do?
Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro. Whatever.
Yeah. Okay. Whatever, bro. Anyways,
moving on. We're moving on now
[snorts] cuz I don't really know why
we're still talking about this.
Well, that's interesting. Wait, so really?
So you need to date someone to lead someone on? Really, bro?
Really, bro? You you you you would say
so someone has to date someone in order
to lead them on. Really?
I don't think you're believing what
you're saying now.
Oh, right. Okay. So, if a woman's
flirting with you and then saying
they're going to meet you, then come out
with some [ __ ] excuse. That's not
leading someone on.
That's not leading someone on. No. Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
So, you have to date someone.
Oh, so you have to date someone before
they lead you. Okay. All right.
That's I've never heard that one before,
bro. Thanks. Thanks. You learn something
new every day.
All right. So, all of these women via
text, they weren't leading me on. Oh
wow. You learn something new every day,
don't you? You have to date someone
else it's not leading on. Huh? Come on. Okay.
Oh, you need to know someone. Oh, right. Okay. Oh. H. Interesting.
Okay. So, you need to know someone now.
Define knowing. I mean, how how long
would you need to know them for?
Oh, right. So, a woman texting you
talking about how she's going to meet
you and sending you lover hearts and
stuff. That's not leading someone on.
Oh, well, I guess I was wrong all along
then. Thank you for that, man. You you
learn something new every day.
Oh, and you have to know the person
because if the if you don't know the
person, that's not leading you on. Oh,
right. So, USA didn't lead me on cuz I
didn't know her. The other American in
California didn't lead me on cuz I don't
know her. See, if I knew her, if I knew
her, if I knew her, then that would be
leading on, right? But because you don't
know her, that's not leading on. Oh, right.
Wow. Interesting. And you always say
that. You always say, you know,
Wow. That's not leading someone on. Okay. Oh, okay. That's interesting. Yeah.
Madness. But you'd care if I was a woman
though being led on, wouldn't you?
Too hot. Tough crowd. You'd care if I
was a woman though saying I've been led
on though, wouldn't you?
I'm not showing you anything. I'm not
showing you anything because you're biased.
I'm not showing you anything because you're biased.
You've already seen messages of these
women leading me on. If you if you
wanted to dismiss it, that's your problem.
That's [snorts] Bro, listen. I'm not
having this conversation with you, bro.
You gave me a headache earlier. [ __ ]
off. You have seen women leading me on
and you deny it. That's cuz they're a woman.
I'm not showing you it again, bro. I
done like a [ __ ] 10, 15 minute video
showing all of my messages. [ __ ] off.
I'm not showing you anything more. You
just defend women just because they're
women. I'm not [ __ ] showing you
anything more. [ __ ] Right off. If I was
a woman, you'd all be defending me, so
[ __ ] off. You gave me a [ __ ] headache
early, you bastard.
Oh, don't owe you anything. Oh, yeah.
Another one. When a woman does something
nasty, she doesn't owe you anything.
Woo! Simp line. Simp line. Yeah. A woman
that does shitty things does a shitty
thing cuz she doesn't owe you anything.
Classical simp line. sugar coating all
of the bad things that women do. I'm
putting out there. Yep.
That's exactly what anyone would do to
justify their shitty behavior. You could
go on Reddit and see it everywhere. Yeah. [ __ ] madness.
You've never heard men don't know you
anything though, do you? No, of course
not. Anyways, we're I'm not talking
about this anymore.
Uh, do you do you want to know what the
problem is? Kentucky Fried Pete. Just
like a man doesn't owe a woman anything.
What's the problem? You want me to answer it?
Do you want me to answer it?
Do Do you want me to answer it or you
just saying it? I can answer it if you want.
Can I Can I answer a question?
The problem with that is no one has ever
ever said to a woman, "A man don't owe
you anything." When a man has done wrong
or a man has done something shitty, I
have never in my life seen someone say
that a man don't owe you anything.
That's the problem. It's double
standards. You should know this, man.
You're on the internet all the time.
Sorry to God, you would have seen it.
You know, the problem is is when a man
does something shitty, he's called for
what he is and how he should be called
for. A woman does something shitty,
don't know you anything. Women don't
know you anything. Straight to their
rescue like Superman. I have never seen
it. And I have never ever seen someone
say to a woman, "A man don't owe you
anything." I have never seen that.
Maybe I've never seen it. I have never
ever seen that. And I've been around on
Reddit for years. They're straight to
their rescue like Superman. When a woman
does something shitty, they're
Superman. They don't know you anything.
But then when when a man does something,
they get called for what they are. Bro,
have you not seen double standards experiments
there? There is double standard. You
might get the odd impartial person that
will call out a woman. Yeah, I've got
zero life experience.
Okay, bro. Um,
you you might get the odd unbiased person.
You might get the odd unbiased person,
but most of the people are biased.
Yeah, I've got no life experience.
Traveled all around the country,
traveled abroad, lived by myself, worked,
you know, been almost homeless. Nah, I
ain't got no life experience. Nah, nah,
none. None at all. Teach me the way of
life. Never been with a woman, never met a woman.
Don't have any friends? Nah, I don't
know nothing. A 28-year-old doesn't know anything.
Okay. And your point is what? A
28-year-old doesn't know anything in life.
Yeah. Yeah. I I don't know anything. I
don't I don't got no life experience.
You realize how that sounds? You're
telling someone like me I've got no life
experience. Are you [ __ ] for real?
Are you [ __ ] for real, bro? Like for
real, for real, for real, for real, for
real, for real, for real.
Friendship. I have got friends. We're
not getting into that again anyways.
We're not getting into that projection.
You've got no friends and stuff. That's
projection, bro. So, we're not going
down this conversation route again.
We're not going down this um self-reflection route.
self-reflecting route, lad.
Yeah, we're not going down that. Yeah,
I didn't even I didn't even hear her say that.
Yeah, we're not going down that
self-reflecting route. Yeah, she
probably says that because I'm on here
talking [ __ ] [ __ ] all [ __ ] day.
I've got [ __ ] friends.
I didn't see it.
One second. I'm peeing.
Bro, if people want to give up with
life, that doesn't mean they've not got
friends. If people want to give up with
their life, they're more than happy to.
You know, they can do what they want.
Yes, I can ring a friend now. And I'm
not going to cuz I don't need to prove
anything to you, bomb.
Yes, I can. And I'm not proving anything
to you. Just like you're not seeing no
receipts and you're not seeing no money.
Get the idea out of your head. that
people need to prove themselves to you.
Get the idea out of your head. Like just
just Well, I don't know about other
people. I don't do what you want to do
to other people, bro. I don't care. But
get it out of your head that anyone
needs to prove themselves to you. I'm
not proving nothing to you. So, stop.
Yeah. Okay. I've got no friends. Okay.
Yeah. Okay, bro. I've got no friends.
I've got no money. Yeah. Okay. No one
needs to prove themselves to you. People
been there, done that. Worst mistake of
my [ __ ] life.
Yeah. Okay, bro. I've got no friends.
Okay. I've got no money. I pay off my
things. Okay, bro. Whatever.
Whatever you say, bro. I I don't mind.
It's his word behind the screen. I don't
give a [ __ ] Seriously.
Just like I use colana, right?
I didn't lose 50 yesterday. You might
want to go back on the video and watch
it properly. Didn't lose 50.
Yeah, you might want to you might want
to go back in the video and actually
listen to what actually happens.
>> Yeah, I did lose 50 pounds.
Might want to watch the video again, bro.
You might want to watch the video again.
Yeah, you might want to You might want
to watch the video again.
You might want to watch it again. And I
don't think you watched the whole way
through cuz that's definitely not what happened.
Can I ask you this question though, please? Why
can you show it that I'm not showing you
anything? When you start showing me
stuff, I'll start showing you stuff. You
know, no, I didn't say that I lost it.
No, I did not. Listen, bro. When you
when you show me stuff, I will show you
stuff. When you show me the way you
look, show me your job, show me your
missions, show me your car, come back to
me. Yeah, I made one pound. Yeah. No, I
didn't say that. Anyways, when you start
proving stuff to me, I will start
proving stuff to you. >> Simple.
I hope he's all right.
>> No, I didn't. So, you start proving
stuff to me, I start proving stuff to you.
I think that's fair.
Right. I think that's fair.
You show me £100.
No. Right. Show me £500.
You can get £500 out the bank. You show
me £500. I'll show you £50.
Yeah. You show me £500 and I'll show you
£50. How's that? [ __ ] underbound. Yep. What? Okay.
No. Do you know what? I'm not even
playing these stupid games with you,
man. I'm not showing you nothing.
I'm not even playing these games.
But I don't gain anything. I'm not even
showing you nothing anymore. I'm done
playing these games.
Yep. You're right, bro. I've got
completely no money and I'm starving. Yep.
Yep. Whatever you say. I've got no
friends. I'm starving. Yep. Okay.
You see how I'm not getting frustrated
because I know you're talking [ __ ]
I know you're talking [ __ ] So, you see
how I'm not getting frustrated because
what you're saying is [ __ ]
I'm not showing you anything.
Think what you want. You don't know me.
I don't care. I'm not showing you anything.
>> Okay. Whatever.
>> So, if I've got no friends then we can
talk about this now. Why have you seen
me out with my friends multiple times?
Did you see me out with a friend last
month, the month before that?
I mean, people have seen me out with
friends numerous times. So, if I've got
no friends, why have I been out numerous
times with people the whole night?
Yeah. So, shut the [ __ ] up then.
Yeah. She's probably saying, "Get some
real friends because I'm on here talking
to you [ __ ] rejects."
Yeah. Guys are approaching a club. Okay,
bro. Whatever you say. Yeah, whatever.
My eyesight's getting [ __ ]
Anyways, I'm ignoring your little self
projecting comments now. Anyways, little self-reflectors.
Um, right. What else? H
this is what bomb used to do. Self projection.
Yeah. Anyways, we're ignoring this
little selfector now. Bomb used to do
the same thing.
I ask you a question. Oh dear.
This serious question I'm asking you how
old are you
and I'm asking you how old you are for a
reason cuz you're acting like a an
absolute [ __ ] 12y old now.
You're actually acting like a child.
Yeah, you're 25. Start acting your age.
You might want to start acting your
[ __ ] age, bro. It's [ __ ] really immature now.
It's almost 20 26 and you've been doing
this now for [ __ ] how many years?
And you've been doing this now for how
many years, bro? Really, bro? Come on.
You think you'll get off the internet in 2026, man?
You people are older than me and you're
still doing this [ __ ] on YouTube years
later, bro. What the [ __ ] man?
You're supposed to be a [ __ ] role
model. Just the same people doing the same [ __ ] [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, I'll shut it. You know what I'm
saying? I don't need to prove myself to you. M
I actually had the £51 in cash
yesterday, but I paid for the food with it.
But I wasn't going to show the money
anyways cuz I don't show self reflectors money. So, [snorts]
bro, it's getting boring now, man. Stop
it, please. It's getting really boring.
Yeah, I'm sending dick pictures to women
that are leading me on. So, by your
logic, should they shouldn't they have
to should they be growing up then?
They should be growing up then, shouldn't they?
Sat there leading leading people on.
Well, surely if I'm if I'm a child, then
they're a child then, aren't they?
Leaving people on.
Why you got such a problem with me
sending dickpicks here, bro?
You got no problem with them leading people on. Not fair.
We're not answering your self-reflecting comments, bro.
This is self-reflective.
It's the same as what fantasies does.
We're not interested.
We're not interested in fat, ugly people
that are trying to bring other people
down to their level, bro. We're not interested.
I don't give a [ __ ] if it's weird. You
don't need to know what I have to offer.
You don't need to know anything about me
that I don't want you to know. You don't
need to know that. Worry about your own life.
Worry about yourself.
Yeah. Good for you, bro. Worry about yourself.
Worry about yourself. Don't worry about me.
I'll survive. You don't worry about me.
Anyway, moving on. So,
the GTA 6 has been [ __ ] delayed yet again.
I reckon it's going to be delayed for another year.
I reckon it's going to be delayed. Yeah.
For another year.
Maybe I've got a feeling maybe August. Maybe October.
Maybe October. Yeah.
Yeah. We're not we're not entertaining
self-projecting anymore, bro. We're over it now.
So, anyways, yeah, I'm saying October.
Yeah, maybe October.
Maybe later to be fair.
You're all right.
Do you remember Tommy's sideburns?
You remember Tommy Cyburn's account on YouTube?
Do you not remember that Tommy sideburns
account that asked me why am I always so angry?
This community needs to change in 2026.
I don't really understand the point
anymore. There's no gambling videos.
It's just people that don't have things
that are telling you you don't have
things. There's people self- projecting
their life onto you. I don't really
understand the point of this now. No one
does gambling videos.
>> No one puts content up.
I don't really understand the point of
this community now
because it's just full of like self- affecting people.
Yeah. Fat, ugly, self projecting, depressed people.
So, you need to know someone.
Oh, that doesn't mean they're leading you on.
That doesn't mean that they're leading
you on then, right? If you don't know them,
[ __ ] [ __ ] from what?
Not a problem. I've only got 199 contacts. Done.
Message all the people I need to
message. This is my number. M
the side radio.
I don't care about 99%.
I don't care about 90. But guess what?
99% of men haven't dealt with what I've
dealt with. And I mean trying and I mean
actually trying not because it's what
happened to them. So what the [ __ ] would they know?
If 99% of men dealt with what I dealt
with, they would have ended up killing
someone. They would have ended up going
to jail or giving up. They might have
just gave up. They might they would have
either ended up in prison seriously
hurting someone or they would have just
gave up and left or and or left. If 99%
of people dealt with what I dealt with,
they would be something we would have heard something.
You know, there's only there's only so
much you can take from this [ __ ]
You do realize there's only so much
someone can take. It doesn't matter who
they are. They can be the most laid-back
person, the most aggressive person,
someone that's not aggressive, normal.
It doesn't matter who you are, there's
only so much someone can take. And to be
honest with you, right, I've put up with
that [ __ ] for a very, very, very, very,
very long time. Um, so yeah,
I reckon I'm thinking this is weird like
Ant-Man Ant-Man Ant Ant-Man
hasn't dealt up with hasn't dealt with
10% of what I've dealt with. And he left
and he's more and he's more laidback
than me. And he was like, "Fuck this,
I'm leaving. [ __ ] this, I'm leaving.
[ __ ] this, I'm leaving."
Yeah, Whisker, that's self-p projection.
Um, we're not interested in self-
projecting comments. So, if you don't if
you can't have a normal chat and there's
no point in you being on it, then he
left. And I he hasn't dealt with 5% of
what I've dealt with.
And he's more laidback than me. He's
more mature than me. And even he was
like, "Nah, [ __ ] this." So, the fact
that I put up with this [ __ ] for as long
as I have, I mean, yeah, I I deserve a
medal, mate, for [ __ ] sake. Yeah.
Hopefully I get this WhatsApp back. No. So yeah,
I would love to see any of you go out
and approach a woman and see what would happen. Cuz
I I don't think you people have got the
balls to even speak to a woman.
That's another reason why I think you do
this white knight and sing him because
you don't know what you got no life
experiences with women. If you don't
know how what they're like, they're
[ __ ] evil [ __ ] [ __ ] And because
you're scared and you don't meet women,
you don't know what they're like. That's
what it is. That's what it is. And do
you know why? How I know? Do you want me
to tell you how I know you ain't got a
life? And and what I'm saying is true?
Do you want me to tell you how I know?
Really? Do you want me to tell you how I
know about this?
Because of the way people act towards
autumn because people people
if people had a life, they wouldn't care
about a woman on the internet. I've
said, "Oh yeah, you're my mama." As a
joke, but do you see why I don't care
about any woman that comes on my live
stream? because I know that I could just
go out and meet someone and get a
number. Not that it would go anywhere,
but I mean, I could go out and get a
number and maybe a chat. I don't need to
[ __ ] go and speak to some woman on
[ __ ] YouTube. That separates people
that have got a life and people that
ain't got a life. That's also an easy
way to tell. V's been caught. Trevor
Dawson's been caught. They wouldn't care
about some woman on the internet,
but they do. So
yeah, I would never get with a woman
from YouTube. Never. You wouldn't even
be able to pay me. Never. Because if
people really had a life, they knew that
they could just go and speak to someone
and and get a number whether it goes
anywhere or not. You But the point is
I'm trying to say that you could just
get a number. So why would you [ __ ] with
a woman on the internet and she can't
speak to women? So that's another way to
catch these people out as well.
Yeah. You've had more girlfriends than
me. I believe it, bro. I believe it.
>> Nah, I don't think so.
>> I really, really don't think so. The
fact that you go mad over women on the
internet, it shows you ain't got a life.
It really does. That that definitely
shows you ain't got a life,
you know? Definitely.
Why would you care about some woman on
the internet that's probably using
filters that's probably going to [ __ ]
you over? that's probably not going to
look like you, but you could literally
just go out and [ __ ] and meet someone. You know,
Natalie G, I had my chance to get with
her, wouldn't get with her.
I couldn't even approach back then when
I rejected Natalie. I couldn't even
approach back then. I remember used to
do it back when I was 21.
So, it tells you really about these people
when a woman comes on the chat.
I had my first, bro. You a You ain't
even had your first, Chris. You're
probably still a [ __ ] virgin.
You're so asked about other people's
lives, but you don't you don't think of
your own lives, do you? Because you
ain't got a life. So, I understand why
you obsess and you focus on other
people's lives cuz you ain't got a life
of your own. So, what if I kissed that
21, 24, 28, never kissed? What's that
got to do with you, bro? And it shows
that you ain't got a life
because of what you're doing on here
other people's lives. It just shows, you know,
you ain't really got a life really. [ __ ] madness.
It just shows that you ain't really got
a life. Come on, man. I There's nothing
wrong with dick pictures, bro.
My box's got banned, by the way. UK
asylum. There's nothing wrong with dick pictures.
No, there's nothing wrong with dick pictures.
If women really didn't like dicks, they
wouldn't have sex. That's the way I see it. Well, yeah,
I've appealed it. I don't know if I'll
get it back, but I've got another
number. I'll just sign up with my other
number and message the numbers again. [ __ ] sake.
Yeah, I peeled it. Of
course I've been reported. You know what
these scum women are like.
And I gave that Finnish Izzy [ __ ] as
well. I gave her [ __ ] as well, bro.
I gave a lot of women [ __ ] today, bro. A
Well, hopefully I get it back. Well, I
will get it back. I'll just have to use
my that number I had for years. My
WhatsApp number, my other number was different.
So, I have to use a different number now
for WhatsApp. Yay.
Doesn't matter. Message people, but
they can give it, but they can't take it.
They can give it these women, but they
can't take it. Just remember that.
I'm trying to think if I should go out
on Saturday or not. I could,
but do I need any more bad experiences?
I think it's pretty full at the moment. Yeah.
Um, I'm going to wait for you people to
do the deed.
I'm going to wait for you people to do the honors.
Uh, I'm waiting.
Uh, excuse me. I'm waiting.
Give it some more time. Uh, excuse me.
This guy didn't show up.
You people are not saying anything.
I'm I'm waiting for you to do the honors.
What's going on, bro? And this is why
people don't meet you. This is why
people don't show you money. This is why
people don't show you [ __ ] messages.
What the [ __ ] bro? There's 20 people in
the [ __ ] chat. Why is this Why is
this [ __ ] not getting called out for
being a bottle job? So, this is why
people This is why people don't waste
their time on you.
This is why we don't waste our time.
Yeah. No one cares about the
self-reflecting skin talk, bro. It's
self- projecting now. It's almost 2026.
Come up with new sayings. Remember,
you're supposed to be intelligent.
You're supposed to be intelligent. come
up with different sayings. Stop self
projecting, bro. It's boring now. This
it's been going on for eight years, mate. Yeah.
Stop self projecting. You've been doing
it for 8 years now. And and I knew about
you anyways. I knew you was a [ __ ]
house. What gave you away? Yeah. Is when
you was talking about paying off for
jeans, b people that are saying that
stuff ain't meeting no one, bro. People
that are saying that stuff ain't meeting
me to no one because the chances are
that this is the same person behind
about three or four different accounts.
It was easy. It was easy. When you start
saying these words, it proves that
you're never going to meet anyone. See,
Prime will come in and say, "I don't
care if you think I'm ugly. No, no, no.
I'll meet you." But someone that's doing
what he's doing is never going to meet anyone.
Never ever ever ever going to meet
anyone. And I and I and I clocked it,
Mr. B, right, when I was saying that
these people don't do it for reaction.
And he was like, "If you say so." I
said, "No, I know." So, I don't say so.
I know so. Um, but I didn't say
anything. There was little things there.
I said, "I don't say I know." So, but um
you I knew it. Anyways, you wanted me to
go to Chicha and you don't even live there. Idiot. [ __ ] idiot.
I knew it. I [ __ ] knew it. People
that talk like that, I ain't never
meeting anyone, bro.
Eight years of being skinned.
No, cuz that never happened. No. No, we
don't remember that. But we remember
that you didn't show up the other day.
We remember that. Everyone remembers
Everybody remembers that you're the
keyboard warrior that never showed up.
We remember that though. I remember
that. But we we don't remember that. No.
No. No. We don't remember that.
You didn't show up, you little [ __ ] house. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Eight years of being skimp.
Do you know what's so weird? Yeah. That
you've been doing it for eight years.
Yeah. And it's not changed you being
skint once. All of them months. Yeah.
You've been coming on here talking about
people being skinned, but has it changed
the fact that you're skinn? No. So, are
you going to spend another 8 years
telling other people that they're skinn
when you're the one that's skinned? Bro,
you're supposed to be intelligent. If I
if I told you right now, show your face.
What's your first comeback going to be?
I'm low IQ. My life has been ruined over
because of YouTube.
Bro, we've already explained this. We've
been over this.
We've been over this self-reflecting
[ __ ] It's boring now. Very, very, very
boring. It's a time to grow up. It's
almost It's almost a It's almost a new year now.
All you're doing is just embarrassing yourself now.
yourself now. That's all you're doing. Yeah.
Okay, keyboard warrior. My mom pays for
my haircut. Okay, keep making up stuff. Keep self-rejecting.
I will remain unbothered.
Okay, bro. So, why didn't you show up
the other day?
So, why didn't you show up the other day?
Huh? Why didn't you show up, big man?
What boring bro? Very boring account.
This is boring now, bro.
Yeah, that's where the je bro that's
where the jealousy comes from cuz
obviously I've got a mom. I've got a sister.
Um yeah, you've also seen the clip where
I stuck it on a bouncer and I stuck it
on two lads and I went to Mark Samson's
area two times. Yeah, you've all seen
that as well, but you pretend you don't,
funny enough. Yeah, you've all seen
you've seen recent videos as well. Yeah,
but you you forget about them ones cuz
uh well, you're biased. Yeah, you've
also seen other ones quite recent as well. Yeah.
Yep. Oh, my [ __ ] uh WhatsApp got
banned, bro. I'm sending these women
dick pictures, Ben. I woke up today in a
foul mood, bro. proper proper foul mood.
I started sending like the ones that
[ __ ] me over like dick pictures and [ __ ]
and then they um uh my WhatsApp got
banned. Trying to get it back now.
Yeah, it's true though about the Nly thing.
Yeah, it's true.
Ben, do you know how you know that these
people are here?
can't get women or can't meet women. Do
you want me to explain to you how you
know they can't meet women or they don't
get women or anything? You know,
I can tell you exactly how you know,
but you probably know yourself to be fair.
So basically, you notice this Autumn
Rose or Natalie G or any woman that
comes on this community, soon as she
goes on the live, soon as one of them go
on the live chat, you get all of these
men pouncing on her. Now me, right, I
would never ever care about a woman on
YouTube. They're using filters. It can
go wrong. You you can get [ __ ] over.
So if these people really had a life,
they could easily go to a pub or
anything and get a number. You could
easily meet not you wouldn't get a
relationship. you would get sex, but you
know, you could still try to get
something. But the fact that they can't,
it shows that they ain't got a life
because if they had a life, they would
just go and, you know, I could go to a
mall right now and approach.
I'm using it as an example, but that's
how you know they really really it show
they show them up with these people.
Their YouTube activity really shows them up
like Autumn Rose. You think I would ever
get with that [ __ ] Autumn [ __ ]
rose, bro? You [ __ ] mad. I'd get when
I own. It doesn't matter what they look
like. I don't wouldn't care what they look like.
>> I didn't even do it when before I approached
because I can go out and approach and I
could get a number and a chat and it
would all be off here. All of it would
be off here. No one would know about it.
So why the [ __ ] am I going to try with a
woman on a community where people know
what they look like, they use filters,
and I'm going to get [ __ ] over?
That doesn't that it doesn't make sense.
Unless you can't unless you don't leave
your house or you can't meet a woman. It
doesn't make sense. And by me, I mean
literally. I mean in a literal sense.
Not [ __ ] meet one and have sex. I mean literally. So yeah,
that's how you know they um
and um yeah basically so
you see it on LJ's Ben, but I don't go
on LJs but I have seen it in the past.
I don't go on L JS because of uh
same people doing the same [ __ ] So
yeah. So anyways, Ben, I got my WhatsApp
that banned for sending [ __ ] dick pictures, bro.
I had to tell a few women about themselves.
>> I'm not doing anything New Year's Eve. I
was going to, but I can't be fat. No,
no, the whole WhatsApp. I've had to appeal it.
So, if the bill gets denied, I'm going
to have to sign up with a different number.
I'll just have to message the numbers
that I've got again in it.
Yeah, these women were pissing me off,
Ben. I thought I wanted to give a bit
back for them leaving me sexless and
single for years and leading me on and
[ __ ] me over. Yeah.
So now I can't go and watch that for sake. Yeah.
It's madness, isn't it?
I tried to eat today, but I got put off my food.
This women [ __ ] really pisses me off,
man. Really, really pisses me off, bro.
I was scared I was going to go out
earlier and smash someone's face in, bro.
I calm down in the end. That's why I
ended the live stream. Yeah,
my mom thought I was going to hit her.
What the [ __ ]
I said I'm going to go outside and smack
one of these women in the face, bro.
It's [ __ ] annoying the [ __ ] they do.
[ __ ] hated me.
I didn't even eat properly today, but I
couldn't eat in peace.
You know, I could go out this week, Ben,
but I don't want more bad experiences
with women. I don't want more bad
experiences, you know.
Well, I don't want more bad experiences. Jesus.
[ __ ] [ __ ] Connection's full. Try
again [ __ ] next year, bro.
Yeah, I was arguing with lady cuz I
said, "Stop dismissing my struggles.
It's [ __ ] annoying."
I was going [ __ ] mad. Just [ __ ]
dismissing my struggles.
What the [ __ ]
Yeah, I can't get into these debates
anymore. It's too unhealthy, bro. Yeah,
I've been banned from WhatsApp.
Yeah, I've been banned from WhatsApp.
Yeah, I've been banned on WhatsApp for
sending dick pictures.
I'm appearing trying to get the [ __ ] account back. Weird. I think
I just think they've got unrealistic standards.
I I don't know what it is, bro. I think
they've got unrealistic standards
because, babe, it's no these women sit
there and say that they can't find men,
but then when when people are
approaching them that are normal,
they're not interested. So, how can they
moan about men? This was my whole
argument recently is that when I say all
women are the same. I mean, I've never
show been shown any different. So, I
would and I put and I've met loads of
loads of people. So, they say it based
on three or four men that they've chosen
in the past. Okay, whatever. So, then
someone comes and approaches you, but
you're not interested. So, how can you
say you can't find Yeah, you know,
normal men, you know, it doesn't make
any sense. So, it doesn't make sense, bro.
I don't know what it is.
No, but it's not that though, Ben,
because they lead you on over messages.
No, because it's the same in bars and
clubs and pubs. Ben, I was out on
Saturday. I got a number. She's like,
"Oh, yeah. Drop me a text in a in a in a
club." She didn't reply.
She's like, "Oh, yeah. Yeah, drop me a
message." Seemed very like keen. Didn't even reply.
That was Saturday when I went out
Saturday. These were I done I only done
him in the club yet on Saturday.
This I only went to I only tried it in
the club Saturday.
I don't think they're [ __ ]
I don't think they're [ __ ] bro.
So no, they do it because they are [ __ ]
They are evil [ __ ]
I don't want to see what I said to this
woman today, Ben.
Yeah, I gave that Finnish Izzy some mad
[ __ ] bro. Leading on, [ __ ]
And you know what? The most respect. I
spent a lot of money, you know, that uh
that week weekend.
I spent a lot of money, bro, but um
lucky I won the money back, but I spent
a lot of money. But I remember that when
I made that finish, I
Well, I sent her my dick picture and she
said, "That's disrespectful and disgusting."
Then she blocked me. So, I SMSed her. I
said, "Hi, I tried to reply to your
message but didn't let me. It is
disrespectful." Yes. Just like you
ignoring is disrespectful. And then she
was like, "I will just reply to this
message because it's not worth it. Even
if I was ignoring you because I was,
doesn't mean that you can send photos of
your dick to me. That's just childish
behavior. And I think even a child is
more mature than you. I don't know what
you expect it would it would happen by
sending photos like that. And honestly,
I don't care.
Then obviously I wrote, Ben, I'll do
what I want. And you honestly do care by
replying. You want to talk about
maturity when you're sat there ignoring
someone. Make it make sense. If a child
is more mature than than me, then a
toddler is more mature than you. So,
[ __ ] off and get raped and drop the attitude. Yeah.
Hope you like [snorts] my response.
A child is more mature than me. Are you
for real? You little [ __ ] You're
the one sat there ignoring you [ __ ]
[ __ ] And you're trying to talk about
a child being more mature than me. [ __ ] off.
They're just [ __ ] bro.
I didn't go on a date with them. It's
just someone I approached ages ago. Bro,
they're such [ __ ] You know they're
[ __ ] by the way they text, bro.
Just they're just [ __ ] They're
just [ __ ] with inflated egos.
Yeah, they're just [ __ ] with
inflated egos. That's what they are.
And even if they're not [ __ ] they
just lead you on anyways. Even if they
are nice. So,
oh, Grey, are you still there?
I learned something new today. Yeah.
Yeah. I learned something new today.
I learned that a woman can't lead you on
unless she knows you.
Wow. Yeah. So, unless they know you and
you know them, they can't be leading you
on. So, if you get someone's number and
they're sweet talking you saying that
they're going to meet you, that's not
leading on cuz they don't know you. But
if they knew you, then it's leading on.
I didn't I didn't even know that to be honest. Yeah.
That sounds really silly. Really,
really, really silly, Ben.
Yeah, that's not leading someone on. [ __ ] me.
I can tell you why. Because the
channel's not changing. Triple H. We're
trying to change the channel, but it ain't changing. Yeah.
Yeah, listen. Because we're trying to
change the channel, but it ain't
changing. Triple H. We've been trying to
change the channel for years, bro.
But it ain't changing.
It's constantly repeating because we're
trying to change the channel, but it
ain't changing, bro. Yeah.
So, what's your opinion, Grezy? Do you think someone
Someone has to know you in order to lead you on.
Do you think someone has to know you to
lead you on? Um,
nothing. Just depressed.
How are you?
Yeah, you need a plan. You can't keep
going on like this. You can't keep it.
Well, I told you what the free options
are. Porn star, Thailand, or
prostitutes. There is no other way.
Yep. Same again. I sent them my dick
pictures yesterday. Now my WhatsApp's
banned. I was giving some women [ __ ] today, bro.
But I just think it's mad how you, you know,
cuz of all the [ __ ] they've done to me
over the years, the leading on the
[ __ ] all the things they've done to
me over the years.
Yeah, it's a bit disgusting leading
people on as well.
It's a bit disgusting leading people on
as well, but hey, who's noticing, you know?
Um, so yeah, uh, Ben.
And also, I don't know why they find
Nicks disgusting. It's not like they
don't put it in their mouths. See me? I
find vaginas disgusting, but I'm not
going to put it in my mouth.
I don't know how they can find something
that they they they [ __ ] attract. I
don't know how they can say that. How
can they say it's disgusting when they
put that in that they put that in their mouth?
That doesn't even make sense.
I don't agree with that. They're hypocrites. Not really.
Yeah. They all blocked me, by the way.
Even the Finnish one. And I gave her
some [ __ ] bro. I gave her some proper
cuz you don't understand. It's cost me a
lot of money this, you know.
I I they've gave me a lot of [ __ ] These
women have gave me a lot of [ __ ] bro,
over the years.
Nope, I haven't.
But they go down on men, but then they
say dicks are disgusting, so I can't
really keep up. They seem hypocritical to me.
I'm sure no one will agree with me, but anyways. Yeah.
But Ben, what I'm trying to say is
before I was rudely interrupted is this
shouldn't still be happening, bro.
This is should have ended like a year ago.
But we're still having the same problem again.
What's people going to do, bro, in
[ __ ] 5 years?
I'm not going for slags. They're all the same.
No, I don't want to dick out someone.
I'm not. That's [ __ ] disgusting.
No, I was just saying that it shouldn't
still be happening, Ben.
This shouldn't still be happening at 20
[ __ ] 8 years of age, bro. Yeah,
I don't need to work on myself. Working
on myself ain't going to change women.
It's not going. I mean, if you're
telling me to work on myself to better
myself, then fair play.
No, no, no. Women are definitely
definitely all the same. They definitely
are [ __ ] They are [ __ ] Definitely.
They definitely are all the same.
And I don't need to work on myself.
That's not going to change women. That's
going to change me for the better. I'm
Why am I going to work on myself?
Well, I am [ __ ]
Oh, wow. Bro, did you just realize that?
Did you just realize that I'm [ __ ]
Did you just realize that? Wow, bro. Did
you realize that? I've been [ __ ] for
the past two and a half years. What the [ __ ]
I could go out this week, man. I'm
thinking maybe I might go out, I might
not. But I don't think it's a good idea
to be honest
cuz like I don't want no more bad
experiences with women. Yeah.
I'm going to have to take a leap of
faith and think what I'm going to do. I
don't think so because I've got 199
numbers on my phone. There's no reason
why I'm not with one of them. So probably not. Yeah.
I lost my WhatsApp up today.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah, most of them are women. Not all
them. Most of them are women. Yeah,
most of them are women. Not all of them.
I'm pushing them as well as well. N
Uh, but I have had dates. Stop self
rejecting. People have seen me on dates.
Self rejecting again. This I think this
account is ter by the way. You can tell
with them because it's the same atmosphere.
Nope. That's you making things up now,
peeps. That's you completely making stuff up.
Nope. That's you.
That's you literally making stuff up.
I went on I went out on Saturday. I got one number.
I got one number on Saturday and I
messaged that number. Yeah.
Over the over over the period of a year.
I just they're just approaches from a
year. I've tried Tinder Ben. Yeah.
And I didn't really get any matches and
the matches I did get trolled me.
I also went on Hinge as well. But
no, not really.
I don't care how many% of men are single.
cuz we know if I go out this week, it's
going to be the same old sad song.
So, it doesn't really matter how many
people are [ __ ] single, does it?
Let's forget the past and let's talk
about the future. If I go out this week,
it's going to be the same old. That's
all that matters.
Everything else doesn't matter,
does it? Yeah. Yeah,
that autumn is so fat by the way. That
autumn is a proper fatty.
Proper proper fatty, bro.
Yeah, I've tried Tinder and Hinge.
Why am I talking to her? I don't talk to
her. She comes on my channel.
I don't care about a woman on YouTube.
I'm not like I'm not like these low
lines. If I wanted a conversation with a
woman, I can go out and approach.
I wouldn't need to speak to someone on YouTube.
and then get [ __ ] over. Yeah. But now
it might be. It might be different. It
won't be different. I've done 101 different approaches.
Could it be?
No, I think he does.
I think he does get all these people.
No, Timmy's not lying, bro. You kept all these women.
I've done 101 different approaches. It's
not about the way you approach them.
It's not about game.
It's about these women. This is all all
these years, right? These guys seem to
think they're the problem. Oh, I need to
get a haircut. Oh, I need to say this.
But they don't realize that it's the
women. So, no matter what you do, work
on yourself. You're not going to change
stuck up women. No matter what you do,
you're never going to change stuck up
[ __ ] Whether you work on yourself,
whether you you just doesn't matter what
the [ __ ] you do, you know,
you're never going to change stuck up [ __ ]
So, if you want to change yourself,
change yourself for yourself. Cuz if
you're changing yourself for women,
you're going to be s you're going to be
very disappointed because you're never
going to meet anyone.
So, you're never going to meet anyone ever.
I haven't been to Wales for ages, bro.
But they didn't seem as stuck up as London. Uh, no.
I don't think they were.
Not like London.
The worst is Liverpool. The worst is
Liverpool. I think the worst is
Liverpool, Ben. They are stuck up as [ __ ]
Them dirty [ __ ] scout bathrooms.
No, they're the worst. Them scout clubs
are the worst.
Yeah, Liverpool's the worst, bro. And
I've only been Liverpool once. N there
were they're [ __ ] They're [ __ ] Here in London
that you get people from all over, so
you don't really
I tell you the worst I I tell you the
most stuck up people. Yeah. Cuz you know
these women in London that look Indian. Yeah.
Yeah. You know they they look Indian but
they're but they're but but they're from
London. They're the worst, bro. They are
the worst. But they've got a London
accent. They're the worst. Good luck
with them. You'll find them in Sims.
They're the worst. But yeah, Liverpool.
Liverpool's the worst, bro. Manchester
is pretty stuck up as well. Uh,
it's called Gorilla Powder.
Well, I've only been to Liverpool once,
but I remember them being stuck on. [clears throat]
Why are you asking?
You can't go out with nonslegs. You
You couldn't go out with nlexs, man. You
could not go out approaching with
nonsexs at all. It just wouldn't happen
because all he's going to be like is [laughter]
imagine going out approach with that copycat.
You know, you know, wow.
you little copycat. I'm going to your
events, but I'm going to his events, by
the way, Joe. I'm going to his event and
I'm going to be like,
>> you copycat.
>> And I'm going to point,
you know, I've logged back in and you've
been at this all day. How have you got
the best life and over one people on
here? And how?
Well, because Joe, I mean, I've given up
with life, haven't I? So,
yeah. But yeah, Ben, we really need to
think of something, bro, cuz this ain't
normal, bro. This really, really, really
is not normal. Now,
this really is not normal, bro. This
this this really needs to stop, bro.
I'll do it one more time for you, Ben.
I'll do this approaching one more time
for you. Then I'm signing up to that
porn thing, bro. Because this is not normal.
This is not normal for anyone, bro. It's
not a normal life.
I can do all three, but I can do two of
them because this is not a normal life,
bro. You know?
Yeah. And I'll be like, "Yeah, I'll
dress and I'll be like, you copycat."
>> Yeah. You He got caught being a copycat
then. He got caught. Hey, Joe, did you
see that? He got caught being a copycat.
They were calling each other gay,
you know, because they said, "Oh, uh,
yeah, um, I like I like uh, if you don't
like Chel Cole, you're gay." He got
caught. Did you see it, Joseph? He got
caught being a copycat. Caught red-handed.
Then he tried retracting what he said. Copycat.
Nothing wrong with Nothing wrong with
wanting to follow the crowd. As he would
say, he likes to follow the crowd.
the videos. I'm not really asked. I'm
I've never been one to copy. So, I've
always preferred dogs, you know. But yeah,
no, I'm just I'm just I'm just I I just
want to get revenge on these women. I
want to get uh I want to I want to get
revenge on these women, peeps,
that account. Yeah, my WhatsApp got
banned, by the way, Joseph.
You know. Yeah. Get revenge. Yeah.
You need to You can't Someone can't lead
you on unless they know you.
Does that sound silly to you yet, Grezy?
Does that sound silly to you yet?
I was thinking of messaging that [ __ ]
Damon Joe and Finn's [ __ ] friend again
saying come on you [ __ ] [ __ ] Come on.
No, we're not doing that because they're
just going to [ __ ] themselves.
[ __ ] them fuckingelves.
You know they'll [ __ ] themselves, bro. I
ain't doing that again, bro. [ __ ] that.
I always like it's good if you can start
on people in other countries because it
means they can't get the old bill
involved which is the way it should be.
They shouldn't be able to get police
involved. If they start [ __ ] they used
to be able to do stuff back
without PC plot.
You know, don't you?
I've already got friends. I've already
got friends. I'd prefer to go out by
myself. I've got friends.
I've got friends, matey.
Okay. I don't have friends, bro. Okay,
whatever. I ain't got friends.
Whatever, bro. Okay, I don't have friends.
You're probably smelling your own [ __ ]
Okay, bro. I haven't got friends.
Whatever. Even though you've seen me
with friends, okay? I've not got no
friends. I've got no money. Okay,
whatever. It's the pointless going back
and forth with you people, bro. You
know, that's why I disagree with you.
You know, I have got friends. cuz I can
meet I can go out [ __ ] on Saturday
and meet with someone.
Just cuz you don't have any friends, it
doesn't mean that I don't have any
friends, bro. It's not it's not a big thing.
I've got more than £800. You don't know
how much money I have.
And £800 is more than what you've got.
So, and I've got more than £800.
even if I did only have 800 pound.
Uh because like what why did I bring it
up? Because you tell people that they
skip when they've shown money. You tell
people that they're [ __ ] they ain't
got no friends when they've shown you
money. I'm just using it as an example.
Even when you're shown things, you just talk [ __ ]
£800 is nothing, bro. You ain't even got £800, you know.
And you've also seen me with women. Why
do you never mention the women that
you've seen me with and the friends that
you've seen me with?
You know, I was out on Saturday Triple H
playing pool. What are you talking about?
No way. I'd rather I'd rather sit in bed
for 3 months and leave. Well, it's not
three months, but about a month and a
half. I'd rather literally
sit and leave. I' I'd save and then
leave. I'd leave my 50 a week and I'd
leave. I don't give a [ __ ] I can save
any I can save money. I don't need to do [ __ ]
I I would easy do it, bro. Even if it
took 4 months, I would I wouldn't be asked.
I do things to you all the time. Yeah.
No, I was with I was with I was with two people actually,
>> you know. Oh gosh.
£800, bro. Who's got £800? You don't
even have £800.
You don't even have £800.
Everything's nothing to you people in it. 1,500,600.
It's because you're skintselves.
Yeah, I I could do it.
And how much money would I have in four
months, Joe? Thousands. [laughter]
Okay. I've got no money, bro. Okay.
Okay. I've got no money. Whatever.
Bro, I don't care if 90% of women are
single or not. I don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah. Okay. Anyways, um I don't give a
[ __ ] if 90% of women are are single or not.
No, not her fella. She doesn't She's not
She's not in a relationship. Try again. Listen, bro.
Don't worry about um Yeah,
bro. It it does it really matter how
many people what the percent of people's
that are single are. Is it going to
change my life?
And I never said 90% of people are
single. I said 90% of men are
struggling. I didn't say 90% of people
are single. So you might want to
actually uh look back. But it says I
actually looked up uh this is what
Google says in the UK.
It says this is what you what this is
what it says. I've looked it up, right?
And it says that
40% of people are single.
That's almost half the population that's
single. I rest my case. That's what
Google says. I rest my case. That's almost 50%.
Which is half the population.
So yeah, I can I can I can definitely
explain that one. I can definitely
definitely explain that one. And I said
90% of men struggle. It's probably even
more than 40%. But it says 40%. But it's
Yeah, it's definitely more than that.
It's definitely more than that cuz most
of people that I know are single.
I looked at it myself and it says 40. So
let's just say give or take is half the
population. Okay. So half the
population's [ __ ] single. So could
you imagine could you imagine could you
could you could you imagine half the
population had [ __ ] cancer?
So yeah. Okay. So half the Okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay. So, what So, let's say half
the population single and half the uh
population's in a relationship. That's
basically Yeah. Okay. And Okay. And and
what? Half and half. Okay. So,
Okay. And what is your point?
What what what's your point?
I think it's more than 40% personally,
but we'll call it 40%. I think it's
because the amount of men that struggle
and when I watch videos, they struggle
and struggle and struggle and struggle
and struggle. It's it's it's more than 40%.
It's more than 40%. It has to be 40%.
There's no way. There's no way. There's
no way 60 70% of men are getting women.
No way. In these westernized countries
there's even Antman's friend went to
Thailand and he's good-looking. Even he
went to Thailand. I was like what? I
he's going to Thailand now.
So loads of people are going to Thailand.
No, I'm not looking for those videos.
No, I'm not.
So no. No. Okay, Joseph, like I've told
you, I've shown you videos that weren't
me. I've showed you messages that
weren't me. Like I said, if you're
ignorant to dismiss that, that's your
problem. That's something that you need
to work on. You can say it to me all you
want, bro. You know that you can say it
to me all you want, but my videos show
otherwise. And and the thing is it
doesn't really matter because the way I
see this as Joseph Joseph Ferrat is it
doesn't really matter because if I went
out on Saturday, I'm going to get the
same [ __ ] So I don't really if we let's
just forget the path, right? Say you
want to move on from the past now. Let's
talk about the future. I'm going to get
the same experiences this week.
End of. That's the way I see it. If you
if you really really want to if you
really really really really really want
to, right, I'm going to show you I if
you want to if you want to [ __ ] the past
off Joe, let's forget about the past. I
can tell you this week will be the same
if I go out. I don't know if I'm going
to go out. No, I don't know. But I'm
telling you, if I go out, it will be the
same. Would you Would you agree with
that or would you disagree? I don't If
you disagree, you disagree. I don't
care. Would you agree or would you
disagree that it is going to be the same
old sad song?
Um, why? Because the out
Oh, so I have had success now. So you're
saying, but you just you said I hadn't
been with a woman. Uh the reason I don't show because
and you know the reason why
uh I haven't had a date since April.
So yeah, I don't think there's much
point in showing something that's 5%.
So Okay. Okay. I Okay. I So you want you
want a rundown of successes as well?
Okay. So you want you want the you want
the you want a rundown of of what happened? Yeah.
Okay. I'll give you a rundown. Okay. So,
you want me to mention successes as well?
So I have been at this for okay I'm I'm
going to tell you for about four and a
half years been up and down the country
Scotland Wales approaching I have
approached about I don't know
six 7,000 people and I've been well it
depends what you mean by success and
I'll tell you what what does it what
does it success mean to you?
Well, it depends what you mean by
success and then I can clarify what you
mean by that and then I can tell you
what the success is. You mean meeting,
date, sleeping with someone, kissing
someone? What do you mean by success
before I get into Cuz you could just
mean sleeping with someone or you could
just meet what what would you define as success?
Maybe I think it's about 5 years.
So what do you mean by success? Do you
mean sex, kissing, hold? What do you
mean by success?
Cuz I know how many people I've slept with.
So I I know how many people I've slept with.
So if you want to talk about slept with,
I can tell you exactly how many people
I've slept with that weren't escorts. So
I've been on loads of dates. that's
wasting my time. I've been on loads of
people that uh you know went on a date
with me to pass time. I've had really
bad dates. So again, you need to I
haven't had a date since April.
No. No, it isn't. I The last date I went
on was [ __ ] [ __ ]
So, I mean, I wouldn't say a date is
success. A date is a success, to be
honest. And I haven't had a date since
April. So, you know, yeah,
I haven't had I I've had three dates this year.
I've been on three dates this year, Joseph.
Three dates this year and we're in December.
Yeah, three dates. I've had three dates, Joseph. Three dates.
The game is so rigged against men, it's unbelievable. Uh,
no, I still had it.
Nope, I still had it.
No, I still had it for a couple more months.
I can't remember. But anyways, I had
three dates this year and I have been
out a million times.
So, do you not see the problem with this?
We have not had a date since April. Since April, Joseph.
So, I don't think we're going to meet
someone. And I don't have a date this week either.
Nope. I'm still I've got money right
now. Nope. again. I've got money now.
And I wasn't in a better mind frame. I
was living with people. And that's
that's why. Nope. I wasn't in a better
mind frame. Nope. It's got nothing to do
with money. Try again. You know,
so nothing to do with money, bro. I
think you've got memory loss. Do you not
remember two years ago when I got kicked
out of the house?
When I had the house? Really, bro?
Something to do? I don't know what it is
with you and money, bro. Jesus Christ.
She keep bringing up money. Yeah,
I was depressed even when I had more
money than I have now.
I was still depressed. So, you know,
there's never been an October where I've
not been. So, [clears throat] there you
go. It's not about money. So, I don't
know why you keep bringing up money, bro. Seriously.
And I wasn't in a better mind for him.
But you've definitely got memory loss
because do you do you not remember I had
a house two years ago when I was living
at Laneies? And what happened?
And what happened when I had the house
with money next to me? Do you not remember?
The only bad thing about this uh house
thing is that like if you go out and you
spend loads of money and you get
nothing, it's even more [ __ ] So,
bro, I can still do it now. You don't
know how much money I have. And my mom
didn't pay for my haircut either. I was
chatting [ __ ] bro. I was chatting [ __ ]
My mom didn't pay for my haircut.
So, again, bro, I could get my haircut
every week if I want to still if I
wanted to. I could I could still go out every week.
Yeah, bro. Listen, you've got memory.
You've got memory lo. I stopped going
out every week the past 9 months when
I've still when I still had that house
before I even knew anything. So, mate,
when I was at the old house, I didn't go
out for 3 weeks, four weeks. You've got
memory loss, bro. You really, really,
really, really got memory loss.
Yeah, I could do. If I wanted to go out
every week, I could. But I don't because
I don't want to. Not because I can't
afford it. So why do you think I I'm not
going to go out this week if I don't go
out this week? Because I can't afford it.
I could, but I don't because I know that
you're wasting your time in this
country. And you're always going to get
[ __ ] over by women. You're always
going to get bad experiences by women,
you know? So why what what would be the point?
There you go. I tried my best and
failed. So what what do I need to do it
again? You know what the [ __ ]
My eyes are hurting. So what, bro? I
When if I don't want to go out, it's
because I don't want to go out.
It's not because I can't afford to go out. So yeah.
So yeah, my mom didn't pay for my
haircut. I just said that I was chatting
[ __ ] You not know I lie about stupid
stuff like that. E. So yeah.
So now you're basically asking people to
prove they can afford to go out every
week. I don't need to prove I can go out
every week. I can go out every week if I
want to. I don't want to because why,
bro? I went out three weeks in a row
last month. Did you not see?
I went out three weeks in a row. Got
escorts. Did you see?
I went out three weeks in a row. I got escorts.
What happened, bro? What happened? I
think it No, I can't remember what it
was. I think it might have been I can't
remember. It was a month. It was either
last month or the month before. I went
out three weeks in a row, bro. Didn't
you see what happened? Nothing.
Sorry that started it.
I could definitely go out every week if
I want to. Definitely. That's the That's
the fun part of you not knowing how much
money I have, you know.
Yeah. I used to get my haircut every week. Yeah.
when I still had hope in this country.
Yeah, I did. Okay.
But there's no hope in this country. So what
what do you want me to do, bro? Go out
every week and what? Say I told you so.
You know what the [ __ ] bro? Yeah.
What do you want me to do? Keep going
out every week for the rest of my life?
Joseph, you want me to go out? You want
me to try it for the rest of my life?
So yeah, this Joseph Farra seems to
think I've got no money. He really
doesn't know me, bro.
This Joseph Ferrar really really doesn't
know me, bro. Yeah. No,
I can't because you know why, Joseph?
Because I don't have have anyone now and
I don't have a sex life now. So, there's
no excuse for it. And there's no excuse
for it. So that's all that you need to
know that I don't have anyone now and I
don't have a sex life now. And there's
absolutely no reason for it.
There's absolutely no reason for it.
How's that one, Greasy?
You're not in a wheelchair. You're not
disabled. You're not a 70-year-old man.
It's not like you haven't tried. So,
let's see it now that we do not have
anyone now. We don't have a date this
week. We didn't have a date last week.
We haven't had a date since April. So, yeah. Yeah.
I don't go out drinking much anymore cuz
I don't enjoy it.
You won't you I don't have anyone now. I
don't have a sex life now. I don't have
any options now. I don't have no date.
I have no I don't have no date, Joseph.
And what's the reason for that?
I'm not disabled. I'm not ugly. I have
not tried. So,
they didn't reply and my WhatsApp's
banned now. Yeah, they didn't reply,
which is weird cuz they told me to
message them. So,
same sad song, is it?
Yeah, my WhatsApp's been banned. So,
my WhatsApp I got banned. So, yeah.
Joseph, why haven't I got anyone now then?
Why haven't I had a date since April?
What's the reason? Do you think I've not
been out a lot? I have.
Do you think I've not been out a lot? I have.
Yeah, Joseph. Oh,
I'm I'm debating going out this week.
Yeah, I just read what you wrote there.
Yeah, I've read
No, you can use the same phone, just a
different number. I've got another
number anyways. It doesn't matter.
Listen, I'm debating going out this
week. Yeah, Joe. Why am I debating going
out this week?
Why am I debating going out this week,
bro? I mean, yeah, I am debating going
out this week. Why am I debating going
out this week? Yeah,
I am debating going out this week. Why
do you think that is?
and yeah. Why do you think that is?
You could probably guess.
Because I'm sick of that [ __ ]
Yeah, but you're saying I'm even
debating going out this week.
Yeah. What I mean by that is I had my
haircut last week, so maybe I'll go out.
Okay. So, bro, I've got money. I can do
what I want when I want. just cuz I get
less money now. You don't you don't need
to worry about that. You do not need to
So, okay, I can get my haircut to I can
get my haircut on Saturday if you want
and go out Saturday and your point is
what? It's not going to it's not going
to be different. You're still going to
get the same bad experiences. What?
What? I I'm debating whether to go out
because I don't want any more bad experiences.
You still haven't answered my question.
Why am I single with no sex life?
There's no reason for it.
So, I've been trying for years. I put
approaching videos out there. So, what's
the reason for that?
Oh, what? Bro, okay. I went out last
week cuz I was forced to go out and I
have to approach people because if I
don't approach people, how am I going to
[ __ ] one over? How am I going to [ __ ] a
woman over if I don't approach one?
Why did I go out last week? You really
want to know why I went out last week?
Cuz I was forced to go out last week.
That's why I went out last week. I I
went out last week because I was forced
to go out
because I was forced to go out.
Yeah. And I would have gotten [ __ ] if I
didn't. So yeah, that's why I went out last week. Yeah,
I was going to be like, "Oh, yeah, I got
my haircut." I don't mind. I just have
my haircut. It's fine.
I went out last week
cuz I was forced to go out. That's why
I I didn't want to go out. I woke up in
a foul mood. So,
should I go out this week?
Oh, really? So, when I say to someone,
"Hi, how are you?" and they say they're
not they say they've got a boyfriend,
they sus me out. Okay. Oh, I'm the bad
person. Yet, they're the ones that lead
people on. Oh, really, Joseph? Yet
they're the ones that lead people on.
They're the one that play games. They're
the one that gives attitude. But I'm the bad person. Oh,
but I'm the bad person. Oh yeah. Because
you open your mouth to a woman and then
they're like, "I've got a boyfriend."
Because they know what you're like. Oh. [laughter]
Oh, Joseph. Come on now.
You're just making excuses for women.
Come on. They're bad people. They're
really, really bad people. I'm I'm sure
if they thought I was bad, I would I
would I'd fit in well with them, you know? Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. When you try to speak to a woman,
they say they've got a boyfriend
straight away. Yeah. Yeah. Being
[ __ ] That's because that's because
um they're like MPCs as well. It's like
the same atmosphere. You're talking I
have got a boyfriend. It's the same
[ __ ] They do exactly the same [ __ ]
They literally do exactly the same [ __ ]
I got forced to go out on Saturday, bro.
That's why I went out. But they're not
the same, remember? But they just do and
act the same way. But not all women are the same. Yeah.
And yes, they are all the [ __ ] same.
Yeah. And I know nothing. Yeah. I've
been traveling up and out the country for years.
Yeah. And I don't know anything either.
Yeah. I've been up and down the country
meeting women for years. I don't know anything either.
No, I don't know anything either.
Yeah, I don't know nothing either.
So, you're saying that I'm a bad person
yet they lead people on and play games?
Were they ever wrong? So, Joseph, were
they ever ever wrong?
Yeah, you're just offending them cuz
they're women. They're not a good
person. So if they they're not good people.
They're bullshitters [ __ ] Got
nasty attitudes. [ __ ] them, bro. [ __ ]
them. And that's exactly why when I get
one of them out, I'm [ __ ] them over
and I'm ruining their life. Simple. I am
[ __ ] them over. Good and proper. So yeah,
they all say the same stuff for people
that aren't all the same. Nah, women are
definitely definitely the same.
They are definitely the same. There's no
doubt about it.
They are all the same. Same mannerisms,
same mind game, same [ __ ] same
attitude. Ant-Man said it. He says, "Oh,
well, these people are saying that these
women aren't all the same, but how many
times have you gone out giving them the
benefit of the doubt?
They're not all the same, though, but
how many times have you gone out giving
people the benefit of the doubt?" That's
what he said to me. I said you're right. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. How how many times? That's what Antman said.
He says that they're obviously the same.
They are all the same. You're an idiot
if you do not think they're the same.
decide this sticker today. Yeah. [snorts]
So yeah, I was forced to go out on
Saturday if you wanted to know. Joseph,
I didn't go out on my own will because I wanted to.
Should I go out this week?
Let's think about it statistically.
What's the chances it's going to change?
What is honestly the chances that it's
going to change?
Let's be real.
What is the chances that it's you're
going to go out this week and it's going
to be different?
So women, so when you go over and you
talk to a woman and they say straight
away they're not interested, that's
because they see you as a bad person.
Well, I had a woman say to me, "Joe, oh,
thanks for coming up to me. You look,
you said you're really sweet and you're
down to earth, but they made an excuse
not to go with me. Surely that
contradicts what you're saying now.
Surely to God that contradicts
everything you're saying.
Surely to God that that that does
contradict what you're saying.
So [snorts] what we what we doing, bro? Yeah.
So why am I not normal then? You tell me
what I've done that's not normal. I've
gone out. I've tried starting a
conversation with people. I've spoke to
people via messages and they've led me
on. You tell me what I'm doing that's
not normal in these approaches, in these
messages. You tell me what I'm doing
that's not normal.
50/50 for normal people.
That kind of contradicts everything
you're saying as well, but yeah, 50/50.
So, you tell me exactly what I'm doing wrong.
nothing. You're doing nothing wrong.
It's the women. It's the women that are
the problem. That's what it is.
So, is anyone going is anyone going to
talk about these approaching videos or
you just going to keep dismissing them?
Anyone going to talk about these approaching videos
or are you just going to keep dismissing them?
See, you just dismiss everything, bro.
It's [ __ ] a waste of everyone's time.
You're giving me a headache now. Well, greasy.
The thing is is that Uh, okay.
No, they're not scared. Definitely not
scared because they've led me on via
text. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
They're not scared. They've led me on via text.
That's not me on Reddit. They don't find
my accounts. I don't post on Reddit
anymore. So, that's impossible. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm not likable. Any think about the
women being rude, leading me on? Nah,
just just dismiss that. Usual.
Uh, no, we're not talking about them
being polite. We're talking about them
leading me on. I've put several messages
up where they've led me on. Being polite
is saying thank you. Being polite is not
leading someone on.
So, um, yeah. uh being polite is saying
thank you or hey thanks nice meeting
you. That's polite. They're leading
people on. But again, you're not going
to ever believe it because they're woman
and women can't do no wrong to you. So
should we just stop wasting each other's time?
I've I've said this numerous times.
We've already proved that it's a gender
thing. So why are we even still arguing?
Bro, what the [ __ ]
In your small minds, you don't think
women can do any wrong. Okay, whatever.
They can't do any wrong. Keep thinking
that. I don't care. I know the truth. I
know what they've done.
I know I've looked smacks. I know I've
approached. I know I've been [ __ ]
over. I don't care. I don't even know. Like,
no. No. Anyways, we're going to move on
now because we're just going round and
round in circles and we're not getting
anywhere here. So, I'm going to stop
answering these questions and we're
going to stop going back and forth,
right? We're going to stop going around
in circles now. I think we've all made
good points and we're never going to
agree. I have my experiences. I know
what women have done. That's that's good
enough for me. And I know that when I go
out again, it's going to be the same.
So, I don't really give a [ __ ] what I or
anyone else says to be honest. So, if
you're going to dismiss my struggles,
then I'm going to dismiss what you're saying. Simple. >> So,
yeah, you're just you're just defending
women just cuz they're women. So, it's
just we need to keep thinking that it's
a gender thing. This is not a me thing.
This is a gender thing.
You are defending women just cuz they're women.
Right? That tells you that you're
wasting your time with these people. Simple.
It will be different in different
countries. It will be different in different countries.
And also, these women did lead me on
because they said they were going to
meet me and they never. That's leading
on. Someone doesn't have to say, "Oh,
I'm going to sleep with you to lead you
on." That's not what leading on means.
So, you might want to go back to school
and actually learn the definition of
leading on. Leading on, what's the
definition of leading on? Giving someone
false hope. That doesn't mean sleeping
with them. That's given false hope. So,
yeah, if a woman is messaging you back
that you've approached saying they're
going to meet you, they are leading your
ass on. They are leading your ass on.
Someone does not have to. But, it's just
a waste of time me explaining this to
you anyways because you think women
can't do no wrong. So, you know, you're
lucky I'm even wasting my time time
explaining this to you
because you're just making excuses
because they're women. Like, you're
lucky I'm just making You're lucky I'm
even explaining this.
Someone doesn't need to say that. That's
not leading someone on, you know?
So, stop making excuses for women, bro.
It makes you look pathetic, you know?
They clearly have led me on. You know,
they've led me on. Defending women's
never going to get you anywhere, bro. So
why do it? Why do it? You know they've
led people on. You know what they're like.
So stop making excuses cuz they've got a
[ __ ] in between their legs. I said the
same thing to Laney earlier. She thought
it was quite vulgar me saying it, but
it's the truth.
Rather, I've already explained this to
you. I'm not explaining it to you again.
If you was and if you was ignorant
enough that you couldn't
watch the videos where I've shown the
messages, that's your problem. Yeah, I'm
not explaining it again. I'm not a
robot. I'm not repeating myself again.
If you want to keep defending women
because you think they're innocent and
perfect, that's on you. I'm not
explaining it again. I've explained it.
I've showed it. If you don't believe it,
that's your problem. End of End the
conversation. End the conversation.
Yeah. End the conversation.
Yeah. Okay. Whatever, bro. Yeah. Okay.
Whatever. You wouldn't cuz you're a
white knight. So, yeah.
It's like you're talking to a brick
wall. Like when you're when you're
telling people what women have done,
you're talking to a brick wall cuz
everything you're saying, they're just
going to dismiss it. So, there's no
point. Why are you asking people to
explain [ __ ] bro? People can explain
stuff and show stuff and you will still
say no. So why why are you asking people
to explain stuff?
Why are you asking people to explain
stuff to you, bro?
You've been shown stuff and you still
deny it. You don't think women could do
any wrong. Simple. We get it, bro.
Okay, bro. No one has ever led me on.
Okay then, Greavesy, what do you think?
Yeah, exactly. Tiger. Tiger, you're
wasting your time with these people,
mate. You're wasting your time with
these people, bro. Don't, bro. Don't.
I've been doing this for the past three
days with these people.
You can't You can't reason with these
white knights. Don't. Please, just don't
waste your time with on them, bro. I've
shown them messages, several different
messages, and they won't have it, bro.
They they they they think all women are
angels. Just leave them, bro. You know,
you don't want to give yourself a
headache. I've given myself a headache
today. In their minds, women are
perfect. They can't do no wrong. That's
their mind. That's that's that's the way
they think, lad.
Their way is women can't do anything
right. And and and as I was saying,
Tiger, is that if if we was talking
about men, everybody would be agreeing with me.
You know, I don't mind being wrong. I
don't mind people thinking I'm wrong.
But I know that if I was complaining
about men right now, we would no excuses
would ever be had.
There'd be no excuses to ever be had.
It's like the guy waiting in the shop.
We'd be waiting for an excuse.
There would be no excuse to ever be had
if it was a man doing it. So, do they
really think you're wrong or are they
just offending people because they're a woman?
Which which which one is it? There'd be
no excuses to ever be had about people
changing their mind and people doing
this. People I'm I'm not going to lie,
Tiger. I sent dick pictures today cuz I
was so sick of these women leading me
on, [ __ ] me over. You know, the
thought that, oh, I need to go out and
try again this week. I shouldn't have to
try again. My my problem, Tiger, I went
out on Saturday, Tiger, or last
Saturday. I didn't want to go out, but
my sister forced me out. But I got
forced out, bro. Basically, and it was
the same thing again, you know. I got a
number. They like, "Oh, message me.
Message them." They didn't reply. What
the [ __ ] bro? They Oh, I shouldn't have
to go out again this week. I shouldn't
have to go out again ever again. Like
unless I want to actually go out to
enjoy myself, I shouldn't have to go out
and and and and meet new women,
you know, I should not have to entertain
the thought of trying again
for a very very very very long time. But
here I am having to. Why? You know,
I should have to I met more than enough
people. I've got more than enough [ __ ] numbers.
So why am I why why should I have to go
out again? Huh?
To get numbers and to get led on again?
Like it's [ __ ] bro. It's [ __ ]
And I'm not going to go on I'm not going
to go on tiger that I'm innocent. I'm
I'm I'm willing to [ __ ] a woman over now
at this point. Like I'm not going to sit
and pretend I'm innocent. I'm really
wanting to get revenge on these women.
Bad though. Bad. Bad. like proper dirty, bro.
You know, cuz I've had enough of it,
bro. I've had enough of it, you know?
I've had enough of their [ __ ]
The whole thing is [ __ ] vulgar, bro.
The whole thing is vulgar.
So, yeah, I sent some dick pictures
today over WhatsApp Tiger.
Just I done it yesterday, but I got
banned today. Yeah,
cuz I shouldn't have to. I shouldn't
have to. Yes, they did. Yes, they did.
Tiger would even tell you that because
Tiger went on the messages and he agreed
with me. And this is not Timmy's Tiger.
Yes, they did. Yes, they did. USA is he
did. Uh, another American did. The
Finnish one did. Yes, they did. Yes,
they did. Another one did in Birmingham.
Yes the [ __ ] they did.
Yes the [ __ ] they did, bro.
Yes they [ __ ] well did. So yeah. Yeah. Yep.
So, yeah, they [ __ ] well did.
They were fast enough to [ __ ] Yeah, exactly. Exactly. [laughter]
See, even this guy Tiger and we he he is not biased.
Yeah, exactly. So, shut the [ __ ] up,
bro. Yeah, me and Tiger's had our
arguments and he's he's he's a LA supporter.
He's a L supporter as well, but he goes
on L's. This guy's not associated with
me, but he's he's agreed a couple of times.
You tell them, Tiger. Tiger, you you you
can explain it, bro. Because some for
some reason when I'm explaining it, they
don't get it. They don't get it.
Yeah, they [ __ ] well did, bro. You
can tell them, Tiger. I can't be
bothered anymore, bro. Yep,
there we go. Tigers must be one of the
only people in the world that doesn't
dismiss Peterbelly struggles. Yep.
I'm not going to do that, Dusty. I'm
getting revenge. I'm not leaving them
alone. I'm getting revenge.
So, no. Thank you for the advice, but
that I'm not doing that, bro.
No thank you. I'm going to keep doing it
and I'm not going to move on. So, thanks
for the advice though. You're always
welcome. But I won't be doing that.
When I get this WhatsApp back, I will be starting again.
Uh well, the same thing as what leading
someone on some innocent person on's
going to do. Leading someone on
the leading what what's what does
leading on someone does?
So, yeah, it's going to make me feel better. Obviously
you don't do any you have no problem in
there doing anything cool to me do you? Yeah.
Another struggle dismisser.
How many of them do you reckon led me on? Tiger.
Tiger. Tiger. Some of them. Yeah. Maybe 40%. 50.
They lead you on. It's like they keep
you on a string and then they snip the string.
Yeah. They they keep the string going
and they snip it. That's what it's like, isn't it?
Yeah. Especially that Finnish one.
That's why I sent her my dick and I told
her to get raped. The one in Finn. Yeah.
cuz she was acting all nice and then all
of a sudden, oh, I'm seeing somewhere.
[ __ ] off, so that's when I started getting nasty.
Yeah, I'm a danger to women, bro. Yeah,
good for you, man. Anyways,
what I'm going to do, Tiger, I'm not
going to hurt anyone. I'm just going to
die and dash someone, bro. That's all I'm doing.
Yeah, a lot of them have done it, bro. A
lot of them have done it. Yeah.
I'm really going to [ __ ] one over bad. Bad.
Like I'm just going to die in a dash one
tiger and just leave him with a bill.
That's what I mean by revenge if you
anything worse than that.
[snorts] So yeah.
No, I don't want to hear Triple H's
voice. It's annoying. Simple.
And yeah, like I said, Tiger, I went out
last Saturday as well. I went to drink
and play some pool. Same old [ __ ] again.
Basically, boyfriend, boyfriend,
boyfriend, [ __ ] off. I reckon if someone
says it to me one more time, I'm going
to break their jaw, bro.
I really am going to break someone's
jaw. like the mood I'm in.
Really, really, really, really, really am. Yeah,
I feel like it, bro. I can't stand
anymore. It gives me a headache, bro.
No, I sent them dick pictures, but
they're f And the only thing is with
these women, Tiger Tiger, they're fast
enough. They're fast enough to reply to
negativity or block you when you send a
dick picture. That's what I find.
They're fast enough to do that.
They're fast enough to reply to
negativity or act out to negativity. But
normal nice messages, they're nowhere to
be seen. It tells you all you need to
know about these sickening head individuals.
It tells you what you need to know about
these sickening head individuals.
Yeah, I'm banned from WhatsApp, but I'll
get it back. Don't worry, bro. Tomorrow.
Yeah, they were send Yeah, like that
Finnish one blocked me. I said, "Haha,
you little snake. You're not so big now,
are you? [ __ ] [ __ ]
I'm scared I'm going to do something
crazy, Tiger. Tiger, bro. I'm really,
really scared I'm going to do something crazy, bro."
You know, seriously. Yeah. I sent them
dip pictures to see how quickly they'd
react. They react. They react quite fast. >> Yeah.
If I ever saw that Finnish one, I'd give
her uppercut in her mouth, bro. If I saw
any of them women that led me on, bro,
I'd give them an uppercut in their mouth. Defa
I know, bro. I need to get this revenge
soon, don't I? I need to get this
revenge soon, bro. I need to get this revenge soon.
Now I'm trying to trying to find someone
that will meet. That's the thing.
Once we get revenge, we'll move on, bro.
So, what you think the finish one was
leading me on as well? Tiger. Tiger.
You think the finish one was leading me
on as well? Obviously,
I'm [ __ ] serious, bro. Why am I going
to say if I'm not serious,
bro? There's nothing anyone can say, Tiger.
What can anyone say?
I don't know what anyone can say cuz me
and you both know
if I went out this week, it would be the
same old [ __ ]
Me and you both know that if I went out,
right, if I went out this week, it would
be exactly the same [ __ ] would it not?
You can't give any advice. There's
so you can't Yeah.
Oh, you wish me all the best. [ __ ] off, mate.
Yeah, I've done my sacking, bro. I'm
completely broke. Yeah, I've got nothing.
Yeah, bro. I've got5 to my name. Oh, it
sucks to be mean, don't it? Yeah.
Yeah, man. Yeah. Yeah. Can you send me
another £5? I'm skimp, bro.
Yeah, I'm really skimp, bro. Can you help me?
Yeah, I'm really poor, bro. Can you Can
you give me a fiverr?
Yeah, I've got £5. Can you make Can you
give me five and make it 10?
And make it 10, please. Thank you.
What a stupid question. Stupid question
gets stupid answers.
You absolute virgin.
Yeah, I told you I'm a skin. Can you send me5?
Yeah, I'm skin bro. Can you send me5,
please? Thank you.
Tommy sideburns, I can't believe you
don't remember that count. Trip H. Uh, Tommy Sideburns.
Should I go out this week? Should I not?
Maybe I'll flip a coin. Should I flip a coin?
I could flip a coin.
Is that okay with you, greasy boss? But
just know that if I am going out, an
innocent person's getting it. Greasy. An
Ah, you remember it? He asked me why am
I always so angry. Well, well, the thing is,
but if I'm going out, some innocent
person's going to get it. Greasy,
you like that talk, Greasy.
See, Tiger Tiger is a good man. Look, he
doesn't dismiss my struggles. Shout out to Tiger.
Shout out to Tiger. Tiger. He's the only
one that doesn't dismiss my struggles.
Yeah. Tiger. Tiger doesn't dismiss my struggles. You know,
mate, I've already stuck it on plenty of
women. You see that woman in the park?
She was [ __ ] scared. That's why. Yeah. I
don't care about what you say about me
on the train because that woman in the
park was [ __ ] scared. That's what you
call [ __ ] scared.
She was [ __ ] scared, Dusty. [ __ ] scared.
And I weren't even anywhere near her.
Compare that to me on the train.
Come on, bro. She was [ __ ] scared.
And I thought that was revenge, but
obviously that weren't good enough.
That obviously weren't good enough.
She was [ __ ] I messaged her on
Facebook. I found her on Facebook. I
messaged her. She blocked me. You
remember the one at the park, Grezy?
H Do you remember the one at the park?
I can't believe Tiger Tiger is the only
one that doesn't dismiss my struggles.
That is mad.
I walked away. Huh? Good one, Triple H.
We all saw what happened. Good one.
Yeah, I walked away. Yeah. Okay, bro. Good one.
Thank you. Anyways, so we've got
everyone disagreeing and then me and
Tiger Tiger agree. So, let's just say
it's me and Tiger agreeing and then
seven people's disagreeing
because Tiger Tiger is not a struggle dismisser. Yeah,
the young Isabella.
I messaged her boyfriend on Facebook.
She unblocked me.
I'm going to say to Izzy's boyfriend,
"Do you want to meet or do you want to
do it dirty?"
Yeah, he messaged me back. Well, she her
ex is just not her boyfriend anymore.
I'm going to say to him, "Do you want to
go for a pint or do you want to do it dirty?"
What do you think about that, Grezy?
Do you want to go for a pint or do you
want to do it dirty? Huh?
Yeah, sat at work. That work excuse is
boring, bro. The work excuse is not
going to wash. It doesn't wash in the
Samson washing machine, lad.
Laughing at me at the table, bro. We all
saw what happened. I told him to [ __ ]
off back to Newcastle and I called him a
[ __ ] and [ __ ] off. Yeah, laughing at
me. And I was laughing at him as well
and I was insulting him.
You know, the more you do this, you
know, this is why people don't put up
content anymore. You know, the more you
make up stuff, right? This is you you
see that you say that you want content,
right? But you you see this is why
people don't put, bro, I told a guy to
[ __ ] go and suck his mom and he
weren't having none of it. Well, he
wasn't standing up to me, was he? Well,
he wasn't standing up to me, was he? He
wasn't answering me back, was he, Dusty?
Yeah. And I was laughing at them and I
told them to [ __ ] off back to Newcastle.
And that they were [ __ ] And I told
them to [ __ ] off and they didn't even
stand up. I was stood up. They were sat
down. I was laughing at them. I said,
"Fuck off back to Newcastle where they
come from." Yeah. And I was And I told
them to [ __ ] off back to where they come
from. Yeah. I was laughing at them. I
said, "You silly [ __ ] My trainers will
cost more than your whole outfit. And I
told them to [ __ ] back to where they
come from. Did you not hear what I said?
You might want to open your ears properly.
They were laughing, but they were sat
down. I was insulting them and they sat
down. Any man would have got up and done
something. Any real man would have stood
up and said something, bro. Any man
would have not stayed sat down. Do you
understand? Yeah. If someone's saying
that kind of [ __ ] to someone in a pub,
no man is saying sat down, bro. No one
is sat sat down.
I was laughing at them as well.
Quiet as a mouse. Okay, bro. Yeah. And
this is why people don't post content
because you're all biased and you make
up stuff. So the more you do this,
right, this is why people don't post
content. This is why there's no content
on this channel.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah. I told, bro, again, I told them to
[ __ ] off back to Newcastle and I told
them to [ __ ] off back to where they come
from again. This is why people, bro,
this is why this is why
people don't post content anymore. This
is why people don't post content
anymore. because of you people.
This is why people bro defended. They
would have not defended their women. I
would have told them I would have said
to their women get raped in front of
them. I would have said it straight to
them. Next time I'll tell the women to
get raped in front of them if you want.
I don't mind, bro.
How could they defend? I would have spat
in their women in front of their face. I
kept at at them, at them, at them. At
them, at them, and then I went to the
next place. What did you want me to do,
bro? What did you want me to do? We
never sat down. What did you want me to do?
You know, you you're biased on here.
This is why people don't post content
anymore. You talk [ __ ] You talk [ __ ] shite, bro.
Yeah, she ruined me. Yeah, I And I
called her a I called her a crackhead. I
called her a dirty crackhead. And to
look in the mirror again. Open your
ears. Open your ears. I said that she's
a dirty crackhead about three times.
Yes. And I said she's an ugly crackhead,
bro. I said she's an ugly crackhead three times.
I said that you're an ugly crackhead and
look in the mirror again. Open your
ears. Open them big ears, bro. Open them
big ears. I said look in the mirror. You
look like a crackhead. [laughter]
I said she looked like a crackhead. Bro,
you need to open your ears, bro. You
know, you need to open your ears. Yeah.
One won the argument. You just said that
I didn't say anything back.
You know, I said that you look like a
crackhead and she done nothing. She done
nothing. She sat She was still sat next
to me. Yeah. Well, did you see where I
said that she's a crackhead three times?
Yeah. And if she went in my face, I
would have knocked her out. Simple.
would have knocked her out in front of any man.
I was half asleep that day as well, and
I've still said it. She wanted to carry
on because I was tired and bored again.
I called her a dirty crackhead. I didn't
need to say anything more.
Yeah. She didn't want to carry on
because she stood sat down. Shut up.
You're just mad that people not doing
anything that's getting them nicked.
That's why you make up stuff. What it is
with you people in this community. Yeah.
You continuously make up stuff because
you want somebody to do something where
you can get the police involved. We know
what you're about on here, bro. We know
what you're about on here. All you want
to do is get people nicked and you will
keep making up stuff and making up stuff
and making up stuff over and over and
over again. Bro, it's not going to work.
Anything we do that can get us nicked,
you're not seeing it. You little glasses
are not seeing it. So, you can keep
making up stuff that people ruined me.
Bro, I bullied a woman in a park and I
made her run away. Did anyone make me
run away on the train? Did that bouncer
make me run away? Did them four people
make me run away? I bullied a [ __ ] so
badly that she had to [ __ ] run away.
Yeah. How many people had to [ __ ]
call the police? No. The bouncer kissed
these teeth at me.
Yeah, run away from the bus driver.
Anyways, we're not getting into this again, bro.
I do bully, man. I bullied a bouncer. I
bully two men in front of their girlfriends.
I do bully man. I do bully man. I
bullied a bouncer and I bullied two men
in front of their girlfriends.
Yeah. And I bullied two men in front of
their girlfriends. They were men as
well. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I bullied a man
that's a bouncer and two men in front of their girlfriends.
Actually, if you watch the video
properly and they didn't stand up once, you know.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Whatever. Whatever.
Yeah, whatever you say, bro. [ __ ] off,
I wonder why that thing never got
brought up. The woman in the park.
Yeah, she deserved that, bro. She
deserved that. 100. You make up bare
[ __ ] bro. You make up really, really
bad [ __ ] It's embarrassing, bro.
It's really, really, really embarrassing.
It's really embarrassing. Really
Really embarrassing, bro.
He Yeah, he kissed his teeth at me, bro.
That's why I started on him. He kissed
his teeth at me.
That's why. Don't [ __ ] kiss your
[ __ ] teeth at me.
Anyways, that's all the past, bro. Why
do we don't care about that anymore?
Why are we talking about that? Let's
talk about some new content. [ __ ] hell.
Why are you talking about that?
Yeah, I showed Finnish Izzy my um Pekka. Pekka, bro.
Yeah, no one cares. It's boring now.
You've said all of this before. So I saw
I showed um
I showed Finn Finnish Izzy my um Pekka.
Yeah, no one cares. You've been doing
this for seven years. No one cares. It's boring now.
Yeah, no one cares. You've been saying
this for eight years and it wasn't it
wasn't affected. It wasn't effective the
first time you said it and it's not
effective now you're saying it, you know.
wasn't effective then and it's not effective now.
So yeah, Steven Howard, you saw my Pekka.
I'll show them my Pekka. Yeah. One.
>> Yeah. Everybody knows you're a crazy [ __ ] Yeah,
everybody knows you're a crazy [ __ ]
>> You remember that one?
>> You need to chill the [ __ ] out.
>> You are right.
>> Yeah, everybody knows that you're a crazy [ __ ]
>> Remember that one thing?
>> Everybody knows that you're a crazy [ __ ]
personality, nothing else. Boring. We've
heard all of this before,
brother. We've heard all of this repeating before,
right? We've heard all of this self projection before.
Switch it up a little bit. It's boring now. Anyways, yeah,
everybody knows. Yeah, it's the truth
about yourself. Yeah. self-projected.
Your looks, you're probably a fat, ugly
bastard. Personality, you're [ __ ]
Yeah, it is the truth about yourself.
Stop self-p projecting. So, anyways,
Grezy, that's that. Everybody knows that
you're a crazy [ __ ]
Yes, we've heard it before. We've heard
this self-p projection before.
Your looks, you're fat and ugly. We've
seen what you people look like. It's
always been projection. Every single
person that has come on here and talked
about people's looks have been fat and ugly.
Everything is about yourselves. You've
been proven to be self project. I don't
understand how you're still doing this.
8 years. Yeah. You're on here 8 years,
right? And you're still self-
projecting. And you say that you've got
a life. And you say that you people have
got a life on here.
You know your fat ugly virgins that have
been on the internet now for [ __ ]
eight years. You know what I'm saying?
People like you, right, Joseph? You fat
ugly virgins have been on here for 8
years on the internet without a life for
8 years ejecting now. You not think it's
time to change it up a little bit.
Change the record.
Yeah, bro. Deep down you're right. No,
deep down you're talking about yourself.
That's why you people won't come on
camera because you know deep down that
you're ugly. How many times? Right.
Okay, I'm going to entertain you one
more time. How many times have you
people that have come on here and spoke
about people's looks won't come on and
show your face?
How many of you people won't come on and
show your faces? And then when you're
asked why you won't show your face, oh,
I'm smart. Oh, I'm smart. But you're not
smart cuz you repeat yourselves every
day. So deep down, bro, you won't show
yourselves cuz you're ugly. You're ugly
people that spend all your years on the
internet self- projecting because deep
down you're ugly. You know what I'm
saying? Ugly fat virgins. 28, bro.
You're 48 and you've never had a
girlfriend. Everything that you're
saying is projection. And no matter how
many times I'm trying to say this to
you, you're not understanding it. You
are talking about yourselves.
48, a virgin, never had a girlfriend. It's you.
You don't have a girlfriend. How many
times does someone have to get it
through that you are these things but older,
bro? No, no, no, no, no, no. You people
don't show your facees cuz you're
[ __ ] ugly. If I went on a community,
right, and I was talking about people's
looks, I would show my face. The only
reason people don't do it is because they're ugly.
Yeah. No. The reason people don't show
their faces is because they're ugly.
Nope. You're talking about yourself. And
it's not And it isn't And it is
unfortunate. Yep. It is unfortunate that
you're talking about yourself, having no
girlfriend, being middle-aged. Yep.
Talking about yourself. And another
thing is all of these people, right,
that have made excuses for not showing
their faces. Oh, I can, Dusty, because
everything that I said about Bomb was
the truth. Everything I said about Pat
was the truth. So unfortunately, I
absolutely can and I absolutely will
because I just can and you can't prove
me wrong. I'm calling you ugly and you
can't prove that you're not ugly. So
until you prove to me that you're not
ugly, shut your mouth. Simple. Shut your
[ __ ] mouth. You have never been in a
relationship, you're a virgin, you never
had a girlfriend, stop talking about
other people. You coming on here every
day, Yeah. Self-p projecting is not
going to change the fact that you've
never had a girlfriend in your 40s. You
could talk about a 28-year-old, but
you're in your 40s and you've never had
a girlfriend. It reverses back onto you.
No, no, no. Okay. No, I'm not
spectating. I'm I'm not speculating. I'm
telling you that all of you people that
have done this have been fat and ugly.
Bomb hat. That's why you do what you do.
And I'm not going to keep repeating
myself over and over again. Right. You
people talk about people's intelligent
people. You people are not intelligent.
If you was intelligent, you wouldn't be
repeating yourselves every day. You fat
ugly [ __ ] are far from intelligent. You
are ugly. It's not because you're
intelligent. It's cuz you're ugly. Do
not even put you and intelligent in the
same bracket. You're not intelligent.
You're ugly. Intelligent people don't
repeat themselves for seven years like
you people do. You people have been on
here for [ __ ] seven years repeating
the same [ __ ] Your skin. Your skin.
That's cuz you're ugly. Not because
you're intelligent. It's cuz you're
[ __ ] ugly and you can't show
otherwise. You are the one in your 40s.
You're the one that don't have a
girlfriend. So fix your own life before
you talk about other people. You're
intelligent. You repeat the same [ __ ]
every day. Every single time people go
on LS or whatever, it's the same
atmosphere, the same repeating people.
Am I lying, Steven Howard? Am I lying,
Dusty? Tell me right now. Right. If you
if you go on Timmy's Okay, if you go on
Timmy's and you go on L J's, is it the same repeating?
Is it the same repeating? Okay,
whatever. I repeat myself every day.
Okay, but I show my face and I'm not
claiming to be intelligent. When you go
on LJ's, when you go on Timmy's, is it
the same repeating people every day?
Right. I'm asking you a question. Is it
the same repeating people every day? Timmy's loss, um,
Monty's. Is it Is it the same people?
But you said you're intelligent.
Intelligent people don't come on the
internet for seven years repeating themselves.
So, stop trying to say that you're intelligent
because you're ugly and you're too ugly
to show your face. That's not being
intelligent. That's being careful cuz
you know you're ugly. Like bro, like you
need to use a different excuse that that
excuse don't work. Cuz if you was truly
intelligent, you wouldn't repeat every day.
You're skin, you're this, you're that,
you're this, you're that. You're
intelligent, but you repeat the same
[ __ ] for seven years. You're not
intelligent, bro. Anyways, I'm banning
you now cuz you're boring. Bye.
So yeah. So you're intelligent, but you
repeat the same [ __ ] every day. Okay, whatever. Yeah,
you're not intelligent. If you was
intelligent, you wouldn't be repeating
yourselves every day using the same
comebacks that we've heard for seven years.
[ __ ] intelligent. You're not [ __ ]
The [ __ ] You're [ __ ] thick as [ __ ]
Mad. No links, Dusty. No links.
They're saying that you're 28 and you've
never had a bro. They're 48 and never
had a girlfriend. They're 48 and never
been with a woman. Everything is
self-reflecting to these people. Like
it's to the point, yeah, where nothing
they say even bothers anyone because
we've heard it a million times before.
You're this, you're that, you're this,
you're that. But they're intelligent
people. Do people that are people that
are intelligent self-reflect every day
for seven years?
Yeah. Intelligent people that repeat the
same [ __ ] every day for seven years. Oh,
but they're so intelligent because they
don't show their face. [ __ ] off, man.
They're fat and ugly. Fat ugly downies
that create the same atmosphere every
day because they've got nothing better
to do. Sados
uh press ups.
No, I haven't for a long time.
I could probably do some though. [clears throat]
Yeah, they're just sad bastards.
They're just sad sad sad sad sad bastards.
Yeah, good one. Triple H. Good one.
Triple H. No wonder I can't get a woman.
Yeah, good one. Thank you. Struggle
dismisser. Thank you.
I can't stop laughing at that account.
We can't deprive Greavves of content.
The poor [ __ ]
Poor [ __ ] And you know what's even
funny about that is
Yeah, I'm skinny. Can you give me some money?
Poor [ __ ] [laughter]
And And the funny thing about that, that
could be anyone, is it, Greavvesy? It
could be an old man, isn't it?
There's lots and lots of history for
Peter Belly in Elephant and Castle.
There's lots and lots of history,
isn't it, Grezy?
So, what do I latch on to then, Grezy?
I like Grezy's little sayings. I don't
care that he I don't care that Greavvesy
trolls me. I like I like the little sayings.
What do I What do I latch on to, Grezy?
What do I latch on to?
No. Come on to me.
Poor [ __ ] Is that your favorite
comment, Greavvesy? Poor [ __ ]
What do I latch on to, Grezy?
What do I latch on to? Reeves.
Nah, not me. That's Tony.
That's Tony, bro.
I want you to fill him in. Yeah, Timmy,
I want you to fill that [ __ ] virgin in.
Can you join Timmy? Come on, man. We
need to talk about how you're going to
fill that virgin in
the virgin fight.
No, you're not coming in trip. We want Timmy time.
I'm only letting Timmy in. That's what
the rules are, Greavvesy. That's what
the rules are.
What? So, you're going to feel nons.
Oh, he's an absolute virgin. That one,
Timmy. He's an absolute virgin that one.
He's an absolute virgin. He needs to get light.
Two absolute virgins, mate.
Right. Should we do this heads or tails?
Should we do this heads or tails if I go out?
Should we do it now? Um, we Okay. [snorts]
Okay. [clears throat]
What do you want it? A pound coin or do
you want a 2p? Yep. Okay.
Should we do it? Should we do best of three? Yeah.
I'm not looking. Right. Tails.
Oh, Tails. Looks like we're going in.
There we go. Yep, we're staying in.
Yeah, we're staying in, son.
[snorts] Sorry, Greasy. You're going to
be deprived of content now. You poor [ __ ] Poor [ __ ]
Do it. Nah, there's there's no doing it again. Sorry, lads.
The rules are the rules.
Yeah. Sorry, boss.
That's what the rules are.
Where's the skin?
Where's the skin version?
Where is that [ __ ] skin version? Yep.
Better than getting told I have a
boyfriend, is it?
Better than hearing that I have a
boyfriend. [ __ ] is it? >> Yeah. [snorts]
Do you want my opinion, Zippy? Aha.
Yeah, but Dusty.
Okay. Okay. Okay. What if I go out on
Saturday, but I get my haircut?
What if I go out and get my haircut
on Saturday? Then then I could get a
date, isn't it, Dusty?
You know, you're not giving us much hope
here. People on Reddit said that we'll meet someone.
Why are you being so negative, Dusty?
Why are you so negative?
You know, well, you go to the barbers. I
can go to the barbers and get my hair
done and stuff. Do a little football
bet. What? What's What's wrong with that?
Why don't you think I will?
You're just being negative.
Why don't you think I will? Yeah, true.
Yeah, you're right, bro. Yeah, I'm I'm
I'm depress Yeah.
Yeah. I'm skin.
How did you know, man? Who told you?
Who the [ __ ] told you, bro?
Who told you, man? You just know me. Yeah.
Yeah. Damn skin, bro. Can you give me £5?
So what? You don't think I should go out
this week? Dusty
and man said that they say they've got
boyfriends because they're [ __ ] I
said, why they're [ __ ] And he said,
because they say they've got a
boyfriend. When nine times out of 10
they don't. Is he right? Is he right, Dusty?
Yeah, he is right.
She says that they're cuntsy because
they say they've got a boyfriend nine
times out of 10 when they don't. He said
they say it when nine times out of 10 they don't. Yeah.
So, if a woman ignores me grievy, and I
messages her abuse, how long would it
take her to to reply?
Like, if I say I hate women, how long is
it going to take for them to reply? Did
you say Grezy?
like two days or three days or huh?
Yeah, but then they ignore normal nice
messages, greasy, don't Yeah. Oh Yeah. Yep.
Yeah. I'd rather be forever alone than
be with a [ __ ] disabled girl that
don't [ __ ] me with a disabled the wolf.
I'd rather be alone than be with a
[ __ ] disabled the wolf that can't
even string a sentence together.
I'd rather be alone than me without >> [snorts]
>> So yeah, he's right.
Yeah, I'd rather be alone and be with a
disabled that don't even [ __ ] me.
Yeah. Yeah. We've heard it all before.
I'm going to [ __ ] with some women all
night. I think I got some numbers. I'm
just going to [ __ ] with them all day. Yeah. N that [ __ ]
Autumn Rose is a fatty.
Nope. I'm bad you. See you later. Yeah. Oh, like
[ __ ] with my back, man.
I shall go.
sound like when I say that? Grezy.
Grezy, say it. Say it for the fans. What
do I sound like when I say that? What? [laughter]
Am I copying Grezy? Did you catch me out? [laughter]
Sounds like a copycat statement.
Oh, you're [ __ ] baby. You're [ __ ]
It sounds like a copycat statement. >> [laughter] [crying]
>> You don't be one sec. [laughter]
I'm going in a minute, lad.
Maybe I want to, Dusty. I do what I want. Gosh.
Yes. So, no going out this week, Grezy.
Sorry. You poor [ __ ] Poor [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm going to keep scaring them.
I'm going to keep bullying them as well,
Dusty. I'm going to keep doing it.
Yeah, I'm going to keep scaring them.
Yeah, and I'm going to bully them as well.
Folder of bad experiences. I need to add
some more stuff on there.
Yeah, I've got a folder called bad experiences.
No, I don't want to back it in. I want to continue.
Do you use um Reddit? Dusty,
it's a top site. It's a top site. Ready?
I don't see them commenting.
Yeah, you know, don't you, Grezy? I'm on
it right now. I'm finding some women to pick on.
Okay with you, Greavvesy boss.
Quite a lot.
I'm finding some women to pick on. Yep.
Well, it's okay for me. It's okay with me, boss. Yep.
You know, Dusty, you know.
Yeah, but you didn't mind me messaging
USA's family, did you, Grezy?
So, why you liked me messaging her family?
That was lovely.
Yep. You didn't Why didn't you mind? [laughter]
You thought it was funny, didn't you?
Grieves of messaging the family.
Yeah, that was lush.
That was [ __ ] lush.
Yeah, Greavvesy supported me on that one.
Yeah, Grezy liked it. [laughter]
Grey liked it.
He likes it.
Yeah. Damn right.
I mean, I messaged the South African's
family as well. The South American,
sorry. Because what she was doing and
she got people to message me even though
she had blocked me. But to be honest, I
would just message people's family now.
Even even I would just message their
family either way.
If I met someone and they I would just
go for the family me
I think it's lush.
Oh, do you remember the five great guys watching um
watching Monty and Timmy? They're like,
"Put the camera on, lad. Monty, put the
camera on, Monty. Lad,
put the camera on, lad. Monty, lad, put
the camera on. Put the camera on, lad. Remember
Imagine that, Greasy. We both got We
both get sent down.
This woman's saying she's 18 and she
says she can't she can't find a bra her
size cuz her boobs are that big.
Grezy, that's weird, isn't it? Cuz
women women aren't innocent.
Uh cuz she wasn't innocent and women are not innocent.
Do you mean why did I or why would I? You know,
because of all the bad things they've
done to me. So I give them [ __ ] back.
I gave them a I gave them chances to
apologize, Greavesy. I said, "Can you just apologize?"
I said, "Can you apologize?
Can you apologize? Can you apologize?
Can you apologize?" And she just kept
ignoring and ignoring and ignoring and
ignoring. I was like, "Fuck this."
Uh, no. Cuz women lead me on. No, cuz
women lead me on and troll me.
So, yeah. work on my appearance. Sadly,
that's not going to change women being
stuck up. I could go out on Saturday,
get my haircut all over again, wear the
best clothes, and you're still going to
have the same bad experiences. It's not
a me problem. It's them, it's the women.
Um, so changing your appearance is not
going to change anything when they're the problem. So,
so you could change your appearance. The
cows come home. You're still going to
get bad experiences.
Why am I going to change my appearance,
bro? What the [ __ ]
You're a [ __ ] idiot. You're still
going to get bad experiences.
There was one in Birmingham. I was going
to say to her, "Can we go out?" She is
one that actually led me on. By the way,
I could try to get her to go out.
Maybe I could [ __ ] her over, but
it's going to be hard trying to find
someone to meet. No, I don't have anyone. Yeah,
I'll try. I'll try. I'll try. Still got
a number. I mean, I'll travel to
Birmingham. I don't mind traveling to Birmingham. Grezy
and I'll call that [ __ ] prime out
whilst I'm at it. Okay with you, boss.
I'll call that prime out when I'm at
whilst I'm at it, lad. If she says yeah. Nope.
So, I'll get a double win.
Well, that make up for some content, Grezy.
Nah. Do you remember that time, Grezy?
I really wanted to smash that USA Izzy.
What would have you done if I smashed
that USA? Ian, Grezy, if I smashed that
USA, what would have you done? >> [snorts]
>> What would have you done?
You would have enjoyed it in it. I'd
smack her [ __ ] face and I'd bang her
face so hard, bro. Yeah,
I'd smack her face so [ __ ] hard
you'll never forget it.
Do you remember when the dad was
messaging me Greavvesy
all talking about Peter Belly Thanksgiving?
All talking about So do do you get a
message from that person? Yeah, we got a message too.
That's not nice talking about yourself
like that. It's not nice to call
yourself a [ __ ] Yeah. [laughter]
Yeah. Tom and Joey. Yeah.
Yep. It's not nice to call yourself a
[ __ ] Don't talk about yourself like
that. It's not nice.
[snorts] Yeah. I I wear small Yeah, I
wear small t-shirts. was plastic.
Probably I'm staying in bed.
I'll probably be staying in bed to be
honest. Uh yeah, the the the coat was uh small. Yeah.
Yeah. I do feel sorry for Laney though.
I can't wait to get revenge on a woman, bro.
Yeah, she can have a she can have a good
Christmas, Grezy, but I won't be there.
You can if you like, but I won't be there.
I got I got that uh quote of the inbetweeners.
Let's organize a nice you know what was it?
What why don't we get a little a little
uh party? What was it? A little um a
meeting. We can all have a meeting
together. You can if you like, but I
won't be there. Greasy, but I won't be
Oh, the in between is class. You
remember the in between is greasy.
Oh, I love that in between as bro. It's
funny. Do you remember Greasy?
I love it. I love it, bro.
Yeah. These women turn you into horrible people.
Now, do you remember when the teacher
was like, he said, "Oh, you can just pop
all of your thoughts." And he said,
"Just pop it in my pigeon. Just pop just
all of your thoughts into my uh what was it?
Into my my pigeon hole or something."
And he said, "Where's that, sir? Any bin, [laughter]
Grimsy. Any bin you see in or out of the
school, just pop all your thoughts there
and they'll get to me.
Grezy, do you remember that one? Any pin? [laughter]
Yeah. Was it? Yeah. Was it? What was it?
It was something. Yeah. I liked I liked this.
Yeah, I did like the inbetweeners. I can't lie.
I'm just on Reddit, lads. So, I'm having to multitask. Yeah.
Why did you think of me and that woman
in the park, Frank, when I was shouting
at her? She was a scared little [ __ ] Is it?
Peter Belly picked up the wind that day,
didn't he? Peter belly picked up the wind. Grezy,
there's an old school saying. Yeah.
Women are evil. Women are [ __ ]
Manta boring. We've heard it all before. Stop repeating. [snorts]
Oh, second one.
Yeah, that's repeating. Stop repeating pre.
Yes, we know you're a manta. Stop repeating.
Oh, there's a woman from England. 34.
Oh, she can be my next victim.
Soon as I saw a woman in England, I'm in.
I [ __ ] with her.
What woman can I [ __ ] with today? Nope. No, [snorts]
she's going to be one of my victims.
No, because of my experiences with
women. That's why I pick on them.
Because of my experiences
with them and they deserve it. Just like
they lead people on because they're life
[ __ ] then is it? Just like when they
lead people on, right? They do it
because they're life [ __ ]
Don't they? Yeah. Because their life [ __ ]
Yeah. Just like when their life [ __ ] whatever
they they lead people on. Yeah.
My life ain't [ __ ] I can go out. I can
do what I want. I've got the money to go
out and do what I want.
It's not the best, but certainly not
[ __ ] I've got freedom. Could be a lot
worse. Could be better. Could be a lot
I'm picking on them because all the
experiences that they've given me
over the years. Yeah.
Yeah, that's self projection. Zero
prospects. Yeah, that's self projection.
You do realize everything that you're
trying to say about me is just about
yourself, but you're just older. You do realize that
everything you're saying is just
basically about yourself. You do realize that?
I don't know how many years I've seen
different accounts, right, say the same
thing. No matter what like situation,
like what situation I'm in, I generally
think it's a bunch of 40year-olds that
failed at everything. the people that
come on here and self-reflect.
>> I generally think it's the same
the same like couple people that's been
doing this for seven years. What do you think?
Have you seen these accounts as well?
I'm just uh on Reddit. Yeah. One sec. My eyes
little eyes hurt greasy from staring at
the screen all day. When I stare at the
screen all day, my little eyes hurt.
My little eyes hurt.
Oh Come on.
[ __ ] off about large age. You little
Doggy the [ __ ]
Yeah. So, we won't be going out this week.
Sorry about that, Greasy.
Yeah, this dog is a [ __ ]
He goes on large.
I'm never out again.
We are never out again. Yeah.
Okay with you, boss.
Okay, ragging. Can you tell our [ __ ]
AVs to move their ragging?
I'll be on
reggae. reggae, can you tell their
[ __ ] abs to move their whacking?
I'll be I'll be here bullying women on Reddit.
Laney thought I was going to hit her
today. I was like, I'm not going to hit
you, Laney. You silly goose.
She actually thought I was going to hit
her. She shut the door and I thought,
what the [ __ ] I said, just stop
dismissing my [ __ ] struggles.
Stop dismissing my struggles.
So all I was saying is stop dismissing
my [ __ ] struggles. Grezy.
Yeah. I thought someone was going to
call the old bail.
I told [snorts] you I'm not going to hit
you. Could you just stop dismissing my
struggles? It's annoying. [ __ ] sake.
I have free sugars. Yeah.
Would I hit Laney Greavves? Nah.
Would I hit Laney? Nah.
This feels like [ __ ] two years all over again.
Reddit told me it get better.
I thought, bro, I thought they told me
on Reddit life was going to get better. Grievy,
they told me life was going to get better.
I'm like I like to hang around with
people greasy that think the whole world
is against them. Those are the kinds of
people that I like to hang around with.
People that think the whole world is against them.
I like them kind of people
that think the whole world is against them.
I just do. I just like them kind of people.
You like them people that think the
whole world's against them greeny? I
[ __ ] do. I think it's [ __ ] l
I wake up at about 1:00.
1:00 1:00 p.m.
How's this fat [ __ ] pulled her?
That's what you call some interracial [ __ ] Oh, Ukraine.
Oh, you crying. That's right.
No, I don't need attention.
Uh, remember the approaching videos, Greavvesy.
Good heart. Do you remember the
approaching videos where they said they
weren't interested straight away?
Sorry, I had to bring that back up to you.
You just seem to forgot.
It's all right occasionally, bro.
I sure like now then.
>> Sorry I had to bring it up to you
because you seem to forget sometimes.
Yeah. Didn't this woman on Snapchat say
that? Thanks for approaching me and I'm
sweet and all of that, but she said she
weren't interested or was I seeing things. Okay. Yeah,
it's all right. No. Am
I getting this WhatsApp back or what? I
think I bit my nails a lot today. It's
all red now. Greasy.
All red. My um fingers are all red.
Yep. It is true.
See, believe it or not, my life's not
[ __ ] It's not [ __ ] now. It wasn't [ __ ]
last year. My life has never been [ __ ]
where I've had like no money. Well, I
have obviously years ago and that, but
my life isn't like it's like 75% good.
It's not about our life being [ __ ] It's
not about that. Since we want revenge on
what these women have done to us, you
know, how they've treated us over the
years. I really want revenge.
My fingers are really hurting from biting them.
My fingers are hurting.
All that biting in it.
I don't even know why I bite my nails.
It's just habit.
I've always done it.
You could be Steven Howard. He was
talking about success. I said, "Well,
why have I got nowhere now?
Why have I got no sex life now?"
And he couldn't answer me. I said, "Why
haven't I had a date since April?" He
couldn't answer me.
He couldn't answer me at all, could he?
Yeah, I see that.
I like show.
I like some of I call
LT was saying it. Does that mean he's a
copycat as well?
LT, he said he used to like her.
He said that she was the one back in the
day. Was he copying then? They're [snorts]
doing mad. No, I'm not doing anything
tomorrow. I'm staying in my I'm staying
in my nesticles. Nope.
I'm not doing nothing tomorrow.
I'll be in my little bed. Is that all
right with you, Grezy?
There's no point me gambling, bro.
There's no point me doing nothing.
I don't see the point in doing anything,
Grez. I've tried my best in life.
Joseph [snorts] couldn't answer me why I
I'm still in the same position I'm in
this year. He couldn't answer me.
You couldn't answer me at all.
No, you couldn't answer me, lad. Yeah.
How much money you got, Grezy?
How much longer do you have?
Oh, bless you then. Yeah.
I can't afford to go out apparently. [snorts]
I can't believe Greasy. I can't believe
they actually think it's about money. [gasps]
It's not about money at all.
Nothing to do with money.
I said to this woman I'd slap her in
front of her boyfriend.
I said I'd slap her in front of her
boyfriend. Yeah. She said, "Come on
then. I'm in London." And then she
blocked me. I was going to slap her in
front of her boyfriend, bro.
Stop being a funny boyfriend.
>> I might make some eggs. greasy.
Is that all right if I might make some eggs now?
Triple H. It's another man. Your your
kid is calling another man daddy.
Praise is your child new dada.
Praises your child the new dada.
is your Yeah.
Praise is your child's new dada. Triple,
how does that make you feel? phrase. Yeah. Oh [ __ ]
Have you ever watched Have you ever watched Pluto? Unless you
wonder what happened to LT Grezy.
Yeah, I am in a minute. That's even if
there is eggs. You
Yeah, I'll be I'll go to bed at about
7:00 in the morning. Grezy,
how do you feel about that? Grezy.
She don't want to know you. She don't
want to know you. She don't want to know
Britney don't want to know you. She
don't want to know you. She don't want
So when when January hits, when are you
not drinking again? March.
When are you drinking again? March.
I assume you'll be drinking in March. No.
If anyone drinks, I'm guessing it will
be March. No.
Late Feb. March.
[ __ ] that. Why would you drink in
January, though? It's dead. No one goes out.
No one goes out in January. You can't
meet people in January. People don't go
out in January. They won't be out until [ __ ] midFeb.
People don't go out January here.
Not really. No,
you'll be dead. Try going out the first
week or the second week, third week of
January. No one will be out.
You know, you know that ain't it, Grezy?
I remember I went to a club before in January. Yeah.
[ __ ] No one went.
No one went. No one was out.
No one was going out. So I had to wait
until like [ __ ] midFebruary.
I remember it was like two years ago.
I was going to watch it.
Bro, no one goes out in January.
It's like [snorts] midFebruary the late
the the earliest.
How old do you think Laney will live until?
till? There was these porn stars and
they all died. There was this pornog.
They all died at 66.
Yeah. 66 66 65.
Laney still going strong. No.
Greavvesy watches porn. Everyone
person on Reddit says, "Why do you think
I'm dismissing your struggles?"
And I said, "Because I showed you where
women are ignoring me, rejecting me.
usually watches people. [laughter]
Oh, do you remember when bomb said Mark
said to bomb that he sniffs his
daughter's knickers? [laughter]
Do you like that? Greasy.
Did you like that?
You sniff your daughter's nick.
You know what is [laughter]
it? Oh, I've got one egg. I'm going to
make one egg.
I got some digestive biscuits, though.
I'm going to [ __ ] make one [ __ ]
egg. Am I
waste of time?
See if you do
what's wrong with
what's wrong with digestive biscuits?
What's wrong with digestive biscuits?
What does that mean? the little meow thing. Well,
right. So, who's nonsense copying when
he keeps talking about several clone?
And who's he copying? H
And who's he copying then? Ruby.
his friend back then. He knows he got
caught though. Is it? Hey bro, Grezy, he
know he he knows he got caught now. Is
it being a copycat?
That's why he keeps dismissing it when I
bring it up. Did you notice Grezy? Cuz
he knows he's copying
problem with that.
I'm not greasy. I'm a little copycat.
I'm not groovy.
I'm a little copycat.
I'm not greasy. I'm just a little copycat.
Copy the Um,
This guy said to me, "Do I suffer from
depression and anxiety?" No,
I don't suffer from anything.
I don't think I suffer from anything, bro.
Used to maybe, but I don't think I do, bro. No.
I think so. Yeah.
I don't think I've got anxiety. No.
But do you think I've got anxiety,
grievy? I don't think I do. I don't
think I've got anxiety.
No, I'm only [ __ ] up because of my
experiences with women. That's why I'm
[ __ ] up because of my experiences.
Yeah, but I don't have anxiety though,
do I? Greasy.
Someone said to me the other day, I've got uh
they think I've got ADHD.
Someone else said that.
Yeah, but I don't have anxiety though.
I don't have anxiety with it. No.
You think you think I got anxiety? You
think I've got agrophobia? Greasy.
These digestive biscuits are nice.
Don't let these punting women win. Grizzly,
you know the account I'm talking about, ain't it?
Nothing Peter B can do to change his hunting sit.
rather stay in bed depressed.
I think I'd rather stay in bed depressed
this week, Greezy.
At least I know my place and I'm with myself.
You know what I mean?
out the Streamyards.
Oh, that Simon Wilson's done a new
channel. I need to watch him.
Something to do with it.
Yeah, I haven't watched it yet. I will do.
Yeah, I watched it the cruise one
and that person was winning in on the casino.
Yeah, I see it. I don't I'm not keen on
the idea of going on a cruise though
after watching [ __ ] Titanic.
I don't know, man.
It's the worst way to die, you know,
drowning. Which is weird cuz I can swim,
but it doesn't matter if I can swim
because the water's you're going to die.
So, it doesn't matter if you can swim or
not, you're going to die of [ __ ]
hypothermia. What's it where the water's too cold?
Because it doesn't matter if you can
swim. You'll die. You'll drown either way.
Can you swim, Grezy? Yeah.
Yeah. I I just want to hang around with
people, Dusty, where I just watch these
incel channels. I like hanging around
with them kind of people
even though they've not had sex and I
have. I like hanging around them kind of
people, you know? People that think the
world's against them.
I get on with people better like that.
People that think the world's against them.
I can swim quite easy.
I don't know. I just like them people
that just think the world's against them.
I like them kind of people.
Hey, this person on Reddit telling me to
keep approaching girls.
What do you think, Dusty? They they said
I showed them my approaches on my other channel.
I've got another channel that obviously had uh
I was saying that B they're saying that
basically you need to approach more
girls and stuff.
What's your opinion on that Dusty?
You need to approach more on that.
No, but Reddit says you got to keep at it, Dusty. Yep.
It's good job you back, Joseph. That's
what I should have said. [ __ ] Yeah.
Do you reckon I could afford to go out
drinking next week? Grezy. Sorry, not
greasy. Dusty. Yep.
I could afford a haircut every week and
go out drinking if I wanted. Yep.
I've done this. Even when I used to get
3K a month, I used to just stay in
depressed, save money. Even when I used
to get I used to get 3K a month. Yeah. I
used three months a year. Three months a
year sat in depressed. Nothing. Doing nothing, bro.
Yeah, cuz my mom was ordering fish, so I
said, "Oh, just get a big one. There's
no point getting two separate ones.
She's not going to eat a whole fish." So
I said, "Just get Yeah.
Yeah. You don't, bro. But and they don't either.
I used to do this even when I had the
house, bro. I used to just stay in and
not do nothing. I did, bro. Trust me. If
you have a good memory, you would know
that I did.
No, no. Right. Time to make a new
account on Reddit.
I don't post anymore, so these [ __ ]
can't find me. I just private message people.
Right. Time to make a new account.
This is better than TV.
just read it.
She don't want to know you. She don't
want to know you. She don't want to know
Remember that account that used to
repeat that when I used to say it, we
got a flagship phone.
Joseph can't afford a flagship.
Oh gosh. that
I feel really ill, you know.
Yeah, Laney dismisses my struggles. It's annoying.
He dismisses my struggles, bro.
What woman can I bully on Reddit? Let me
have a look.
24 mom of three.
Three kids at 24. [ __ ] in hell.
What woman can I bully today?
Three kids at 24.
She must like the black dick.
What woman can I bully today? Greavves.
Oh, banned me.
Reddit's obsessed with banning people in it.
Don't worry, I'll screenshot them
profiles. They probably live in America.
They love banning people on Reddit, bro. Don't they
dusty? Why did you say they banned people again?
Yeah. Three kids at 24.
Each to their own.
Why do they ban people on Reddit? You say, Dusty.
No, I'm not having a laugh.
Seems a very power hungry site, doesn't it? Yep.
I think it flags up and they manually do
it, don't they, Grezy?
Yeah. So that must mean the mods are on
it all day then we cuz if I'm keep
making account share and they keep manually banning
then they must be on it all day.
So yeah, that must mean they're on it
all day then.
These are these Reddit mods. Yeah, these
Reddit mods are like this. Look, they're
sat here like this. Yeah,
until early hours in the morning
just drinking Coke. They're sat here.
Look, they got their Coke there, their
tea there, the fridge there like this. Ban ban ban ban
ban. They do that all day in it.
I shall go.
Women are evil. I hate all women.
They're all [ __ ] evil.
Evil [ __ ] I'm getting revenge.
How does that make you feel? Yeah.
All of these numbers [ __ ] block me
when I set my dick. Stephen,
I'll teach him for being ignored. Isn't it?
That's what nonslegs done.
The next day he was like, "I like Co. I
like Sh." I can't be gay. I like Shevil
Co. You're gay. You're gay. If you don't
like Sh. You're gay.
Yeah. I told that I told Finnish Izzy to
get raped and she didn't even reply.
She didn't reply. Greasy.
Peter barely owned a [ __ ]
That was lovely.
I'm not paying that [ __ ]
I'm feeling ill. I think it's my diet.
Uh, where is it?
I've given up life and stuff. My diet is [ __ ] bro.
And that's how we go.
Are you a little copy? I'm a little copycat. Yeah. Yeah.
Uh, Greg, I have a question for you, boss.
I was saying to my friend, it's worse um
for me because I've tried more than
anyone in the world. And he said, it
doesn't matter who's tried more. If
anyone's tried, they've tried. At the
end of the day, women have the final
they make the final decision.
Yeah, I see what he means. But
I don't know. I don't know, bro. Yeah. And no,
cuz obviously the more you try, the more
likely you think you'd be to meet someone. No.
I don't know. It's a hard one. It's like 50/50
cuz obviously if you made it your life
like me, you should you should you
should be with someone. That's what I'm
trying to say. You shouldn't be in this
position. You shouldn't have to be compl
um contra comp contemplating
going out on Saturday or Friday. You
shouldn't even have to be thinking about that.
What what do you need to go out for?
You're 28. You you know why are you what
you going out for? So yeah,
what do you think? Triple
Sorry. Am I going out? No, I'm staying
in bed depressed.
Are you going out?
No, I won't be out now for very very long time.
I'm not probably not even going to go
out on New Year's Eve. I'll just be depressed.
There I'll be staying in bed depressed.
Yeah. Hopefully I go to sleep, Bob, and
not wake up.
life ain't it?
Still dealing with this [ __ ] at [ __ ]
28 years of age.
still dealing with this.
I hope I die in my sleep. I hope I have
like a heart attack in my sleep. This is depressing, bro.
Yeah, hopefully I do.
It's depressing, isn't it, bro? I
thought life would have changed by now.
People on Reddit say it gets better.
This ain't getting better.
I can't approach more. It's too depressing.
The more I approach, the more depressed I get.
I'm depressed from just going out Saturday.
I have a boyfriend. I have a boyfriend.
I wanted to leave early, bro.
No, I don't want to approach more. Then
I get more depressed.
So staying in bed, it is. I think
staying in bed and feeling sorry for
yourself. It is.
Seems that's a better option.
You can't, bro.
You can if you want. Yeah,
it's [ __ ] depressing, bro.
It is [ __ ] depressing, bro. No box.
Nope. I'm staying in bed tomorrow. Depressed.
I'm going nowhere.
Nope. I ain't going out. I'm standing in bed depressed.
Ain't going nowhere.
I ain't going nowhere.
I am not going nowhere at them.
It is not happening.
I'm staying in bed depressed. SP.
No, you won't. This has been going on
for years and it's still the same old
[ __ ] I want out of this life, bro. I
really want out of this life.
No, I really want.
Nope. I'm staying in bed depressed.
Yeah, I'm skin. Yeah. Yeah, that's what
it is, bro. Yeah. And [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm skinn. I got5 on my name. Yeah, duh.
Can you got 5, bro?
I just type this [ __ ] person's name
wrong now. [ __ ] sake.
Yeah, I'm not going out cuz I got £5 in my name.
Yeah. Do you want to donate me a f
I should have to be going out at the weekend. Uh, Dusty,
I should have to be going out. I've
tried enough. I should have to be going
out. I've got enough numbers. I should
have to be going out.
Me again. Oh, [ __ ] this. Uh,
I think she's a [ __ ] that deserves to get raped.
That's what I think. I think she's a
[ __ ] that deserves to get raped. Yeah,
that's what I think.
That's what I think anyways.
Don't know about you.
But no, all jokes aside, I'm not going
out because I shouldn't have to be going
out, Bob. I went out last week.
I shouldn't have to be going out. I've
tried for the past [ __ ] 5 years. I
shouldn't have to be going out again to meet anyone.
If I would have met someone, I wouldn't
have met someone by now.
I would have met someone by now. If I
was going to meet someone, I would have
met someone by now.
I shouldn't have the I shouldn't have to
entertain the thought of even going out
trying again. I've tried enough.
I should have to try again. I've got
enough numbers. I got a number last
week. I shouldn't have to go out again and try.
I should have to I tried more than more
than more than enough.
I shouldn't have to try again. So,
so that's where we're at.
Yeah. Okay, bro. I'm skinn.
Yeah. Okay, bro. I'm skin. I've told you
like multiple multiple multiple times. I
don't gamble. I've told you this
multiple multiple multiple multiple
times that. Yesterday I didn't even lose
£50 and you're still telling me I'm
gambling. I've literally told you
multiple times I do not gamble. Like by
not gamble I mean like Timmy and and you
still are telling me I've done my balls in.
Like do you have a brain or something
bro? Like seriously do you have a brain?
I told you this. This was the first time
in three months yesterday and I didn't
even lose any money. And then have you
played FBI? No. Have you played FOB's?
No. Have you played FOB's? No. Have you
played FBE? No. And you're still saying
that I'm gambling.
That's why that's why I'm agreeing with you, bro.
Because you don't listen to anything anyone says.
Do you remember the approaching videos
by Bills? Do you remember the messages on WhatsApp?
Did you dismiss them? Do you remember
last week when I went out? Well, last Saturday.
Did you Did you forget that?
Oh, you remember? Okay, good. Good.
Yeah, there's no roast. I've actually
got a video of the roast.
I've actually got a video of the ghost.
of the roast.
I've actually got video of the roast.
Well, I'm not showing you. [laughter] I
don't need to prove myself to you
people. I don't need to prove myself to
you people. I've got the video.
But I'm not proving myself to you. It's
simple. I'm not uploading it. No, cuz I
don't need to prove myself to you. It's simple.
Yeah, I know, Timmy, but I'm not
interested. I'll be in bed, bro. I've
given up with life. I don't really care.
Yeah, there's a couple of coming.
There's one coming out New Year's Eve or Christmas Eve.
Yeah, I know. It's called The Bride or
the Maid or something. I won't be
watching it. I'll be in bed depressed.
I think that's the one you're talking about.
Yeah. Okay, bro. I lost my I lost my
money on the FOB. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I gambled yesterday and I didn't
even lose any money.
Yeah, that's the one. Rides made. Yeah.
Yeah. I want I was looking forward to
it. Yeah, but I'll be depressed in bed,
so I won't be out. I won't be watching it.
>> I used to love horrors, but I don't like going cinemas.
I don't like seeing um I don't like
seeing couples and I don't even like
leaving the house nowadays. It's too depressing. So,
I'm just lying in bed waiting to die. Yeah.
Nope. I'm not uploading it. I don't need
to prove myself to you.
I'm desperate to die.
Yeah, I went Valentine's Day before.
Last Valentine's Day, I went to the
cinema. It was lovely. I was the only
one there. It was [ __ ] lovely.
Yeah, that clown don't bully me. But try again.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Whatever.
Yeah. That count doesn't believe me.
Keep thinking that though. Yeah.
Yeah. You keep telling yourself that.
Yeah. That's what I used to do. Timmy Aldridge.
Uh I don't gamble.
Doesn't matter, bro. 28 and your life's
not going to get better. You're going to
keep getting more bad experiences with
women. It should Your life should have
got better by now, bro. Your life should
have really got better by now. But we're
still dealing with this. We're still
dealing with shitty women time and time
and time and time and time again. You
should have been Yeah.
Yeah. I gambled in the bookies and I
took my 50 back.
Yeah. Well, I took £51, but yeah. Yeah.
I put £50 in cuz I was bored and I took
the £50 back.
Okay. Which was the first time in 3 months.
Okay. What's your point?
Yeah. So, what?
Because that was the first time in 3
months and I took the £51.
Well, no, I don't gamble. That was the
first time in 3 months. That doesn't
even count as gambling. If someone says,
"Oh, do you gamble?" And they say every
3 months, they're not a gambler. That
doesn't even count as gambling.
So, that doesn't even count as gambling,
bro. I don't even do the football anymore. So, yeah.
So, yeah, that's that.
Yeah, I'll be depressed anyways.
It's only down from now.
That's what Scales Phil used to say.
What was the point? Because it kept
going up, down, up, down, up, down.
Yep. Lonely and depressed. Just like you.
Just like you. Lonely and depressed.
Yeah. Just like you.
Me and you can be lonely together, lad.
Yeah. I don't care. I don't want to
gamble. I don't want to drink. I don't
want to do anything.
Yeah. I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
I can't believe that, bro.
It was actually 30 profit, but yeah, it
was 30, not 40. Should
have, would have, could have, never. So,
nope. I'll be staying in bed tomorrow, depressed,
just like I did today. I was supposed to
go to the cinema today to watch the
Freddy uh thing. Nope.
Oh, Scream's coming out February as well. So,
I can't believe he's going to be 31 in
February. [ __ ] hell. I met that [ __ ]
when he was 21. Was he 31? Never comfort
never come for eating in my life. That
self projection from you people. Never
ever self never ever ever in my life
have I done that. [clears throat]
Yeah, that's definitely self projection.
Uh what was I saying? Yeah. So, he's
going to be 31.
Yeah, he's going to be 31.
[ __ ] He's going to be 31.
He's still a virgin. [ __ ] hell. 31
and still a virgin. [ __ ] hell.
I reckon he'll probably lose it next
year. Hopefully, he'll lose his Valentine's card.
Hopefully, he loses his Valentine's card. Never know. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't comfort eat. I go out and
I eat once a day. Yeah. That's not comfort eating.
Yes, I am. Yeah.
What number do you prefer? 20 or 21?
Yeah. He's going to lose you. Valentine's card.
No. Bad experiences with women.
Bad experiences with women's enough to
make anyone depressed. Timmy Eldridge.
Yeah, I eat [ __ ] food. Yeah.
Yeah, I eat [ __ ] food. Yeah. Well, by
[ __ ] food, I mean food that's not good
for me. Yeah.
Yeah. You're definitely a virgin.
He's an absolute virgin. What number do
you prefer? 20 or 21?
That cunt's born on the 21st of February?
20. I think I think I prefer 20. Yeah.
Well, do you like that one? Triple H.
When are you going to lose your
Valentine's card? Yeah, because VC card Valentine's card. Yeah.
Do you not get it? B card. Valentine's More stuff. Nope.
I could look better now if I wanted to.
If I wanted to go gym, if I wanted to
drink water, I could look better now. I
could still look better now.
After a while, I could look healthy, but
I'm just not interested.
If I wanted to, yeah, I could go gym. I
could eat vegetables, but I'm not asked.
Bro, don't tell me about gaining weight
when you're heavier than me.
Don't tell me about gaining weight, bro,
when you're heavier than me. It doesn't
even make sense. Yeah. Valentine's card.
Yeah, but you're heavier than me, bro.
So, that's kind of self projection.
Yeah. Bad. Well, yeah. Depression
because of bad experiences with women.
It gets you like that. Once I get
revenge on a woman, I'll be fine, bro.
Once I get revenge on a woman, I'll be fine.
But I could look good again if I wanted to.
Easy, bro. I could easily look good. But
no, I'd rather get revenge on women for
all the [ __ ] that they've done to me
over the years. Yeah. Yeah,
but I don't know why you're talking
about my weight when you're heavier than
me. That doesn't make sense. >> Strange.
I'm not interested.
Uh, Timmy, I'm not interested. I don't
have a terrorist beard at the moment. My beard's short.
I'm not interested, bro. I give up with
life. I don't give a [ __ ]
I'm not interested.
My eyes are [ __ ] hurting me, bro.
I need to stay off the screen.
I don't I don't I don't need advice, bro.
I'm not interested. My beard is groomed.
Look, I went to the barbers the other day.
I went barbers last week.
Yeah, I went to the barbers last week.
Yeah, I need to go piss anyways.
Yeah, look, another terrorist beard. I
went to the barbers.
Look, see, I went the other day.
H what's what's even weirder is being in
your 40s on YouTube self projecting
every day but you still do it so we can't judge. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm not interested, bro.
I went to the house back in the I went
to you back in the old house.
I'm good, bro.
Bro, you're fatter than me, Jimmy Eldridge.
You're [ __ ] fatter than me. I don't
need my next benefit payment. I've got money.
I've got money. I don't need I don't
need a I don't need a benefit payment.
I've got money, mate. That's that's
that's the irony of that's the um that's
the that's the good of not knowing about
people people that you don't know. I
don't need to know who you are. I know
you're probably fatter than me.
It's just self projection with you
people in this community. Bro, you need
to grow up, lad.
I don't need an X benefit payment. I've got money.
There we go. The self-reflecting
comments again. Skin.
Maybe in 2026 you'll think of new words. Repeating. repeating yourself.
>> Yeah, bro. I don't look anywhere near
40. And you know how I know I don't look
anywhere near 40? Because whenever I
meet people, I ask them, "How old do you
think I am?" And they always say my age.
So that's a bit weird how you're saying
that I look 40. I'll be like, "How old
are you?" They say, "How old are you?"
No one ever says 40, bro.
I think you wish I was 40 because you're
in your 40s. No one ever says it. No one
ever says it. They say like 22, 27, 28,
29. No one has ever told me I look 40
ever. People that didn't know me. So
that's just self projection. Definitely.
Cuz no one has ever said it. Of all of
the people I've ever met that's guess my age,
no one has ever said it over 30.
So that's self-reflecting. That is
definitely definitely self projecting.
Cuz I know because I've asked people if
they didn't know when they didn't know
my age, I said, "Well, guess how old I
am." No one has ever said in the 40s. So
you're saying I look 40. How the [ __ ]
can I look 40? Doesn't even make sense.
40, bro. 40? I look 40. Really? No. So yeah,
that is [ __ ] stupid. I look 40.
You're mad. But yeah, it doesn't matter. Anyways,
I'm ill, bro, cuz my diet is [ __ ] What
do you expect it to be? My diet is
[ __ ] [ __ ] I've given up with life. I
don't give a [ __ ]
How do I look 40, though? That is
definitely projecting, bro. That is definitely self-reflecting.
Never in my life has anyone ever told me.
That's another self- projecting. Triple
chin. Yeah, that's self projecting.
Yeah. Don't have a triple chin. That is definitely projecting. Oh, yeah.
Oh, one sec. One sec.
One second, please.
up again, bro. But I need to use another
number now because I don't have that
number anymore. See, I don't even have
that same f I don't even have that
[ __ ] number anymore, bro.
[ __ ] [ __ ] man.
change. Yeah, cuz I can't verify cuz I
don't have it anymore.
[ __ ] madness, bro. One second.
Don't have that number anymore, so I
can't do it. [ __ ] sake.
Yeah, I need to delete it and reinstall it. Hunts, man.
Number. This is my number. [ __ ] sake.
That's going to cover up all the people that's blocked