I'm a little copycat. No.
Whole new whole new number
on WhatsApp. [ __ ] mad.
Had that number for ages, but I don't
really talk to that many people anyways
to be fair.
Yeah, I got my WhatsApp back, but I had
to do a whole another number because I
don't have that number anymore to verify.
You know, the one where they block the
phone. How can they send a code to it?
They can't send a um code to it because
of obviously my WhatsApp got banned
earlier. They reinstalled it, but I
couldn't use the other number because
how can how can I verify it when I don't
have the number anymore? I had to make a
whole I had to use my other number
of headache, bro. But I had to and I had
to delete some people. People that
blocked me, I delete all of them cuz I
don't want people that's blocked me
previously to come up.
I don't know why. A lot of people
blocked me, bro.
So, I've messaged people saying PJ new
number, but I can't use the other number
because it's um but to be fair, people
had ages to contact me. They had [ __ ]
over a year. So, the real ones message
you, they real, the other ones don't. So,
I go back. Yeah.
Couldn't use that number though cuz the
it's the they block the phone, didn't
they? So, if I don't have it, how can I
how can they send me how can they send
me a code?
Was a little bit annoying to be fair.
We got there in the end, didn't it?
Is there anyone else I need to contact?
I kind of don't want this guy to have my number.
I don't want any of the tenants to have
this WhatsApp number, bro.
Is there anyone else?
Yeah, I got to watch that back anyway. [ __ ] Yeah. That's annoying.
Yeah, I had to [ __ ] sort this
WhatsApp thing out. They said you can
use WhatsApp, but I couldn't use my
other number because of um
I can't verify it anymore cuz I don't
have that number. So, they can't send me
a code cuz I don't have it. So, I had to
use the other number. So,
not to worry though.
It's not a big problem. It is slightly annoying.
It would have been annoying if if I just
had the number and I didn't have any
contacts saved and people wouldn't be
able to contact me on that number. That
just goes to show you should never get a
contract phone, bro. Never get a
contract phone. Never.
But it doesn't matter anyways. It's a number.
Yeah. I had to a lot of women blocked
me, bro. I went on it and so many women blocked me.
So many. I had to delete it. It was
[ __ ] depressing, bro. Cuz you see all
the people that's blocked you when you
reinstall with a new number. It's madness.
And people on Reddit still thinks I'm
going to meet someone. Madness. Madness.
Yeah. Someone reported me. Yeah.
I can give all these other women [ __ ]
but I can't be asked. I just deleted the number.
Yeah, I just deleted the number, bro.
I mean though in Triple H I could I
couldn't use the other number because
how can they how can they how can they
email me a code when I don't have it
cuz where they blocked that number
I I took the SIM out so that I wouldn't get a
So, I had to use the second SIM number.
[ __ ] mad, ain't it, bro?
But I only talked to a couple of people anyways. So,
I would have gave that USA easy [ __ ]
but she changed her number as well. Oh man,
I only talked to about on WhatsApp maybe like
I had had that number for ages though.
bounces had my numbers in and
everything, but no one ever reached out.
When I got my phone nicked, right, I
lost a lot of contacts,
which was a year ago, over a year now, December. So,
they had my number, but no one really
reached out except like two people, but
no one really reached out. So, they had
over a year. So, [ __ ] them. I only speak
to Aunt Man, my mom, three other people on WhatsApp.
Oh, my sister and that. I don't give a [ __ ] bro. So, yeah.
I like that number though, 59, but
obviously I don't have it anymore cuz
Yeah, I can't. So, oh well, it doesn't
matter anyways. It's only what's up in it.
Yeah, he's doing all right.
Yeah. So many women block me, bro. So many women.
The escorts have got my I'm trying to
see if there's anyone else that needs my number.
It's not a big deal, is it? The number
thing, triple. Nah.
Yeah. I gave that guy in the new number
cuz he's calling it. Anyone else?
Let me give this bounc my number. Who's call?
She don't want you. She don't want you.
She don't want to know you. She don't
know you. She don't want to know you. Uh,
I might send this woman a voice note.
Obviously, I won't tell her I got
banned. I said, "Oh, yeah, my phone got
stolen, so this is my new number. Should
it come out next week or not?" Basically,
she don't want to know. She don't want
to know. She don't want to know you.
I messed that 19year-old as well.
No, one that the other one was an old one, bro.
I messed a 19year-old. But cuz I have
heard of it, but it's one tick. So maybe
her phone's dead.
>> She don't want to know you in life.
Yeah, that tenant blocked me. He asked
me money. He said, "Oh, have you got any
money, bro? Cuz uh I don't get paid. My
salary is late." And I didn't respond
back and he blocked me.
See how people can switch, bro? I just
didn't reply and he blocked me. What the [ __ ]
So, people can switch at any time, bro.
You know, even your family can switch.
So, why wouldn't anyone switch? I just
didn't reply to the message and he
blocked me cuz I'm not being funny, bro.
Like, how many people do you know?
How many people do you know?
You know what I'm saying? How many
people do you know? I'm sure you you
have someone that could lend you £100.
So, I think it was a bit OT to block.
Yeah, that's a bit wild.
Use WhatsApp triple
me this guy as well.
I couldn't imagine not having WhatsApp
to be fair cuz I I wouldn't use I
wouldn't I wouldn't I wouldn't get
someone's Instagram. I wouldn't do that.
So I couldn't imagine I didn't mind like
not having it for a bit anyway but I
don't know how mess with people
you don't want to know your
Yeah. He asked me oh can you lend me £10?
Sorry. And obviously I I didn't want to
lend it. And it's not like he didn't
know people, you know. Pakistani people
know people. They do know people, bro.
So, it's not like he didn't know people,
bro. And he was going to [ __ ] starve. No.
It's not even like he said 20 or30, you
know? He's asking me to lend him £100.
What the [ __ ] Why
am I some sort of [ __ ]
Yeah, I think he was trying to [ __ ] me
over. I don't trust him.
It makes sense because one of the
tenants wanted £250 out of me in it.
Yeah, bro. Something dodgy.
I don't trust that [ __ ] bro. I don't trust them.
Not £100, bro. Not £100.
In the position that they're in, you
know, and and they're poor. Like, you're
probably not going to get that money
back, you know.
I don't think they would have either. myself.
Nah, 20. I would have obviously if they
said, "Oh, can you name me 2030 pound?"
Maybe. Yeah. But [ __ ]
Yeah, if it was 2030 I would have. So I
reckon he's trying to [ __ ] me over
because they wanted that money back.
Oh [ __ ] No, I did want I did lose one
of the numbers.
Oh, no. But I got um
No, no, no. Cuz I got the other tenants
number that will give me his number.
I lost that sign number. Yeah.
Yeah. I'll get his number from this guy.
But yeah, what do you reckon? He was
trying to [ __ ] me over in it. Yeah.
Yeah. He was trying to [ __ ] me over
in it, bro.
Cuz he's friends with them, man. I don't
know. It was just dodgy cuz why has he
blocked me? You wouldn't block someone,
bro, for not lending you £100. You know
what I'm saying?
Nah, it's dodgy. What do you think?
Cuz to them like £100 is a lot of money
in it. So if they got 100 pound bro you
might see that as stupid but if someone
gets 100 pound out of you they can buy
pizza chicken you know you don't
understand bro like to them the people
from third world countries you know £100
is a lot of money
so they would have had a last laugh.
Well they would have had a laugh in it
basically. So cuz you don't just block someone
you don't just block someone for not
giving you £100. See, I thought that his
number was dead. Now, obviously, I'm on
WhatsApp again. I've had to use a new number.
I've had to use a new WhatsApp number,
Dusty, because I didn't have the SIM to
the other one. Do you know the phone
they blocked? So, obviously, they
couldn't send me a code. Little bit
annoying. Little bit of trouble. Little
bit of trouble, but we got there in the
end. Yeah. He's asked me, "Can I
lend£100? I don't know my salary."
And I've realized he's blocked me.
That doesn't make sense, bro.
This was a tenant.
Yeah, not that makes sense, man.
I don't even want to give the others my
number to be fair.
See, if you lose this phone, this is the
scary part about this WhatsApp.
Uh, I don't care if he block me. I just
thought it was weird. I don't give a
[ __ ] that he blocked me. I just think
it's weird for some a friend to block
someone just because someone didn't give
them £100. I don't really care.
Uh what was I saying? You made me lose
what I was going to [ __ ] say now. Um
about this number.
Oh yeah. If you lost your phone, you'd be [ __ ]
See, this is what I'm trying to say to
you. This is what I mean. Yeah. If you
got if you got a phone Yeah. Especially
Samsung and you've got contacts, you're
[ __ ] If you if you don't have them on
Snapchat, Instagram, you're [ __ ]
Like, you know, Ant-Man, if I if I got
this phone stolen, I'd be [ __ ]
or someone because if they don't have
Instagram or Snap, then there's no uh
Yeah, you're [ __ ] Basically, you're
you're really really [ __ ]
I mean, you can back up stuff, but I
mean, how accurate is it on a Samson?
You really are [ __ ] if you don't have
someone on any other. So, I've got a
friend called Fred. Yeah. From Italy and
I only have him on on WhatsApp.
Don't know his full name. He doesn't
have any other social media. He only has
WhatsApp. I need to start writing
people's numbers down, bro. In case this
day ever happens when my phone gets
snatched again. Instagram's right cuz
you can just log on back. You can just
log back on Instagram with numbers. You can't You know,
I remember Yeah, bro. When I when I got
this phone in November,
I backed up [ __ ] and I got this guy from
New York. Yeah. Who I used to speak to
when I was 15 and I got his I got his
number from the backups. If I didn't
back up, I never would have ever heard
from him again. But yeah, that you need
to be careful, bro. That is when
Instagram is good. If you have if you
have everyone on Instagram, you just log
on Instagram on a different device. but
a phone, you are [ __ ] The only way
you wouldn't be [ __ ] is if you can log
on WhatsApp, the same number, and have
these people reach out to you. That's
what I had. I had to have these people
reach out to me cuz where I was still
under the same number, people obviously
text me and I got their number again. I
couldn't contact them cuz I lost I lost their numbers
cuz I lost their numbers. They still had
my number, but I lost theirs.
You know what I mean? Triple. So,
make sure you you you know. Yeah.
Yeah. Cuz that is scary, bro. It is
scary. It's like that 19year-old like I
was only able to get her number because
I had it somewhere else.
I know where she lives as well.
Yeah, you need to be careful with these
Samsung phones. No, you really do. Cuz
obviously heat, but cuz when I was when
I got my phone last year, I was under
the same number. Even though I lost all
the contacts, I had people reach out to
me. The bounces never did, which was strange.
There was people that didn't reach out
which was strange because I spoke to
them a lot and but people did reach out
and obviously the ones that did reach
reach out are the real ones.
I don't know how accurate this something is.
I know about iCloud and stuff but I
don't know on assumption. You just need
to be careful. That's it cuz you can
lose your phone at any time. You can get
your phone snatched at any time and it
ain't nice cuz it's happened to me. So,
no, just a whine and dash.
I could have gave these women [ __ ] again
on WhatsApp, but no, I can't be
bothered. I've said what I'm about to say,
so I don't want to get my [ __ ] thing banned again.
Anyone else? No. Elliot Roger. No thanks.
No thank. I would have gave USA easy
[ __ ] if she was still under the same number. No thanks.
My is going to be [ __ ] these women
over when I get half the chance, [ __ ]
See that one? I I I I I I I I I I I I I
Yeah. Anyone that doesn't lick women's
asses is Elliot Rogers.
Yeah. Anyone anyone that doesn't lick
women's asses is Elliot Rogers.
I feel ill, bro.
Oh yeah, that Pakistani is still under
the same number, Dusty. So she was
lying. Thought you was changing your number.
I need to give this government. I
thought she said she was changing her number.
See what I mean? These This was a
friend, by the way.
A friend, but full of [ __ ]
Yeah. This was um someone that was a
friend. Apparently they were changing
the number. They seem to be on the same
That's part of their narcissistic
personality disorder, but they can't
admit what they do. Uh any wrongs that
they do? Uh one sec.
Anyone else need to be contacted?
Well, they said they were changing their number.
I was going to message a couple of
numbers saying, "You still leading people on,
Dusty? You still leading people on?"
I mean, they told me that they were
changing their number.
I mean, they lied.
I mean, they lied to me. So, yeah, I
would have been like, "Oh, how you still
leading people on? Got any more victims? Yeah.
Yeah. This is the number from Saturday.
I'll just voice note her some at some
point saying my phone got stolen.
Tiger Tiger said they they are leading me on.
They definitely definitely are.
Mind games and leading on. They're the
two main things.
They definitely definitely did.
Oh, I did say to one, "Oh, you still
full of shit." I did actually message
one, by the way.
Yeah, I did actually say you still full of [ __ ]
I don't need to drive.
She don't want to know
because I don't want to drive. I don't need to.
How old do you think that prime is? Here we go. 43.
Do you know what though? At least
fantasy story says that large A is
scared of LT. He [ __ ] is. He is
[ __ ] scared of LT.
That is true. He [ __ ] is scared of LT.
I don't know why he says he's not. He is
scared of him, bro. It's okay to be scared.
He goes on like he's not scared. He is
scared. He is definitely scared of LT,
bro. Definitely scared of LT.
That used to be annoying, bro. seen that
[ __ ] go around in circles.
>> Yeah, he ain't about it, bro. Trust.
No, he defino ain't about that life,
bro. He picks and chooses these targets,
which is what a lot of people do. Even
people that defend women,
they do it. They pick their targets.
No, I haven't.
Yeah, they definitely pick their targets.
People that defend women do as well.
People that defend women do, too.
Definitely do, mate. Definitely do.
You know how there's a there's Have you
seen this Tik Tok, right? There's this
buff guy. Yeah.
Where he's uh picking people's foods.
Where he's picking people's food. Yeah.
No. All women are definitely bad.
Definitely. They are all bad.
No, they're definitely definitely bad.
all of them. Uh
what are you saying?
But yeah. Yeah. Anyways, there's there's
this Tik Tok of this buff guy
basically um picking women's food,
picking people's food, and they don't do anything.
like picking their food in a restaurant.
That tells you all you need to know.
These people pick their targets.
They definitely pick their targets, bro.
I'm sure you've seen that. They
definitely pick their targets, mate.
There was one time I approached this
person and just like, "Oh, is this guy
giving you grief?" I said, "Yes, I am
giving her grief, you little white
knight, and you're not going to do
nothing about it. I'm being the biggest
weirdo going. [ __ ] hate white knights.
It makes me angry, bro. Them them them
kind of people, bro. I don't like
talking about women and dating, bro.
It's [ __ ] depressing. It's negative.
I don't like talking about it, bro. It's [ __ ] depressing. So depressing.
[ __ ] gets me.
I don't know about you. One sec.
Yeah, it's depressing, bro. It
they're putting me on a power trip again, bro.
These Reddit moderators are putting me
on a power trip.
Well, I put a lot [ __ ] hell.
I put a lot of effort into life and I
haven't got anything out of it. Echo one sec.
Oh my god. Echo again.
You hear me?
Can you hear me?
Can you hear me? No.
Oh, you found you.
Yeah. Well, I put a lot of effort into
life. No changes.
Nah, you might as well give up in life,
bro. And throw in the towel.
>> Wave your white flag. I'm waving my
white flag. I surrender.
I like I like it when you know the walls against you.
I like I like that you know
boy. What did what did Timmy say? He
wants to fight Nles legs. Triple H.
The two virgins.
The two virgins, mate.
The Orington virgin versus the Birmingham virgin.
Both intons in it. Yeah.
He needs to lose his Valentine's card, isn't it?
You're going to die a virgin. You're
Don't die a virgin.
No, he's definitely a virgin.
He's definitely a virgin, lad.
He's definitely a virgin.
[ __ ] sake, man. I'm trying to use my
VPN to go back on Reddit.
Yeah, I'm trying to use a VPN to go VPN
to go on Reddit.
Reddit's addicting, bro.
What does Monty say about these
people doing the same [ __ ] No.
Uh, triple. It's the same people doing
the same [ __ ] in it.
It's the same uh Reddit Cheers, Captain.
Thank you, Captain.
Thank you, C.
He said it's the same atmosphere.
Monty said on here it's the same atmosphere.
It's just what did he say? It's the same atmosphere different yeah remember Fraser
always wanted you phrase
even if it was only up the punang Poor [ __ ]
All right, I put I put the cat Yeah. as
my picture and someone said that looks
like the virgin [ __ ]
The greeneyed virgin [ __ ] J
No. Looks like the virgin [ __ ]
You know who they're talking about.
Triple H. It looks like the virgin [ __ ]
The greeneyed monster.
The all greeneyed monster. [ __ ] virgin. Virgin come
Yeah. Did you like it?
Poor [ __ ] Ain't it? Poor [ __ ]
Yeah. [ __ ] poor [ __ ]
You see that kind of [ __ ] for [ __ ] Poor [ __ ]
Can't deprive him of content. Poor [ __ ]
Have you seen that Jamie Thompson account?
No. You You try to get my money stopped,
I [ __ ] with you. You try to You try to
get my money stopped, mate. I'll [ __ ]
get you killed. I get you killed, you
virgin. You want to stop the color of my
[ __ ] money and my lifestyle? You
[ __ ] skinned virgin.
You [ __ ] skin open virgin [ __ ] I'll
[ __ ] ruin your [ __ ] life, mate.
Yeah, you went to the old bill. His ass
got a good whooping.
Good old whooping.
I went to that virgin's area [ __ ]
multiple times before [ __ ] doing the
posters. He wouldn't come out the virgin
house. He wouldn't get [ __ ] out the
virgin [ __ ] hole.
I said, "Come on. Come on, you virgin
[ __ ] Come on." I said, "If I've got to
go back here, mate.
It ain't going to be [ __ ] nice. [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's hard to do Reddit and YouTube at
the same time.
imagine I was a virgin, Dusty.
Imagine how much worse that would would be.
I didn't speak I all I said was all I
said was phase is the new stepdaddy you know.
No I said yeah I said I said phrases his
kid stepdaddy. So what
you [ __ ] would you have a pipe with Ricky Millington?
Dripple. Would you have a pint with Ricky Millington?
Dusty, would you have a pint with Ricky Millington? Would
>> Yeah, but that could be anyone that
Ricky Millington, bro. It could be
anyone. It could be a fat old man.
Pint a [ __ ]
You nasty virgin.
You nasty virgin. One second.
I've got a lost BPN. The moderators
can't detect it. The nerdy mods.
It's a Ferrar. No thanks. You're You
live near him. I think he lives in Newcastle.
I need to watch this Simon Wilson video
in a minute. He's [ __ ] bagging. Box box. [ __ ] burden. [ __ ] burger.
I'm not doing
>> you right virgin [ __ ]
>> Yeah, PJ, I [ __ ] you up with some
woman. Um, she she's uh she's interested
in you. I've told her a lot about you,
but the only problem is she weighs about
[ __ ] um 18 stone if you're all right with that.
>> You're not interested.
>> Well, she said that uh she's viewed you
viewed your channel and she said to me
that uh you seem like a challenge and
she thinks that she can break you in slowly.
>> Nope. I'm with Kaye. Tell her >> what?
>> I'm dating Kaye. I don't cheat. No, it's
not cheating. It's basically
experimenting. She said that she could
break. She reckons she
>> reckon she could break you in slowly.
Um, this woman. >> Hello.
>> Hey, Kaye. Did you miss me?
>> Hello. I don't miss anyone.
>> Oh, you love peer belly, deep down.
>> Why do you belly?
>> Oh, you love me really, K. Don't be
silly. You do. You wanted to my little beard.
>> It's Peter.
>> Is it?
>> My name is Peter Belly.
>> Oh, PJ, can I ask you a question?
>> Can I ask you a question? I've seen your
Willie. Yeah. Why have you got a hell of
a bush in front of it?
>> Stop asking stupid questions.
>> Well, it wasn't a stupid question. You
got more [ __ ] bushes. You got more
bushes. Do you reckon if me and you do
you reckon if me you done a video
together, Monty would see it straight away?
Can you say that again?
>> I said, say me and you done a video on
YouTube. Yeah. Like say we went to a
restaurant. Do you think Monty would see
it straight away?
>> No [ __ ] Charlotte. But guess what?
You'll be getting the headache, not me.
>> Yeah, but he would see Would you reckon
he would like see it, but he might not
know about my channel in it?
>> Oh, he'd be fuming.
>> Yeah, but do you reckon he would see it
like straight away?
>> Well, obviously he don't miss much, does
he? But you're the one who' be getting
it in the next
But guess what, PJ? That fantasy you got
on in your head Yeah. will never happen.
>> It will. It will. Cuz Kaye prefers me than you.
>> Wow. You're so full of yourself.
>> Not even. >> What?
>> I know you're trolling me behind fake accounts, Bryce.
>> So, wait a minute. Wait a minute. So
you're sitt So you're sitting there
saying Kaye likes you after you sending
prostitutes through a house and having a
kids [ __ ] strip searched. Don't think so, bro.
>> Well, it was an accident.
>> Oh, yeah. An accident. >> Yeah.
>> Really? An accident is when you put, you
know, different socks on by mistake. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But why have you got a bush and
you ain't shaved it?
Because I don't need to.
>> Why are you asking stupid questions?
>> No wonder people No wonder women, right,
don't entertain you.
>> I mean, do they see my dick? No.
>> Well, no, cuz you can't [ __ ] see it.
>> Yeah, very funny. Just worry about yourself. Yeah,
>> I'm fine.
>> Cuz Kay is your mommy. Can I be your daddy?
Huh? Because Kayleie is your mommy. Can
I be your daddy? No.
>> Why we coming?
>> I need to go back. I need to go watch
some stuff in a minute.
>> Oh, don't tell me you're going back to your porn.
>> Watch porn? >> Oh,
>> I don't watch porn.
>> Are you actually part of like the sex industry now?
>> No, I don't watch porn. Why would you say that?
>> No. Wait a minute. Are you part of the
sex industry now?
No. Kaye, did you used to watch porn? >> Wow.
>> Wow. What a conversation.
Why would you ask?
>> You did it. You You did it.
>> Well, how could she watch porn when she
was in a relationship for 10 years?
>> To be honest,
>> you could still watch it.
>> Yeah, but to be honest with you, porn
doesn't do much to me.
>> I like you like porn, isn't it?
>> No, I don't eat porn. I got Kaye.
Yeah, but before before Katie when you
were single, you did?
>> No, I didn't watch porn, mate. >> Remember,
>> do you think do you do you think porn
should be illegal?
>> Do you think porn should be I don't
think that anybody in the world should
watch porn? No, I don't think that's right.
>> What don't you What don't you like about it then?
>> Because I think you should be about 18
years old. So any person in the world
should view it. My mom. My mom. Yeah.
She said My mom said she she doesn't she
doesn't watch it because it's weird
watching two people have sex. Is that
true? Like strangers have sex. >> Really? >> Yeah.
>> Well, kind of. She's right now. Why
would you want to watch another man and
a woman having sex while you could get it yourself?
>> Yeah, but people watch it though. Is it?
Yeah, they watch it because they they
I'll tell you PJ because obviously you
don't get this in a relationship.
Sometimes partners actually watch porn
to you know sprite up their relationship
if it's not working for them cuz you
would know that cuz you're not in a
relationship clearly. But unfortunately
that's what they do. That's why they put
porn out for it. And also they make
money out of it too the people doing it.
So it's not they just put their self
online because they're good in bed. They
want to earn a profit from it. Does that
make sense to you? Obviously. Yeah.
>> You could get a girlfriend now, go on
chart debate, and people will pay you to
do things to your girlfriend. And if you
do, they pay you money. >> M,
why don't you and Katie do it then?
>> Because we're not into that kind of
stuff. Uh, PJ,
you know, if we went on [ __ ]
chatterbait, I think everybody would be broke. >> True.
>> Yeah, it is true. because they donated.
>> Yeah. Right. Yeah. You lost your V card at 31.
>> Yeah. Can I ask you a question, PJ? Do
you think if me and Do you think PJ real
question if me and Kaye was part of
Chatterbait or any sex industry on the
internet, would you actually subscribe to her? >> No.
>> Yeah, you would. You would spend all
your benefits on her, wouldn't you? >> No.
>> Do you reckon? Okay.
>> But seriously, seriously, Rice, was you
talking [ __ ] when you said you was
living you was living off £50 a month or
was you actually being serious?
>> I was being serious.
>> That just sounds bad. You know that.
>> Well, well, it does work if you're
single and on your own, PJ.
>> Yeah. About£50 a month.
>> Well, what's so funny about that? That's
actually quite clever really because I
was earning a profit while not going out
and spending it on [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> So, you're telling me you couldn't live
off £50 a month? >> No.
>> Think about it. You have Could you Could
you live off 50 a month? Your bra? Obviously not.
>> Well, really, you have one meal a day.
Yeah. Have, you know, a cup of tea and
biscuits in the morning, you know, and
come into the night, have food before
you go to bed. That's what I used to do it.
>> 50 a month.
>> That's mad.
>> 50 a week maybe.
>> How How is it mad? Some people don't You
know what about these people in the
third country like Africa and they just
go in miles of water.
>> Could you do it, Kayie? Could you do it, Kaye? No,
>> I'm not even in this discussion. I'm
trying to do something.
>> Oh, bless.
She's been trying to do something.
But yeah, £50 a month is Yeah.
>> Do you know how long you've been live?
repeating yourself? You've been you've
been alive for a week repeating yourself
every broadcast, every stream about the
same subject. Is there no other subject
and you read that you can actually bring
to the table? Cuz you said that the
channel ain't going anywhere. Have you
ever sat back and realized why your
channel is not lifting off and people is
noticing? He breaks her that you're a
liar. You vape and the vapes cost more
than £50 a month and that you talk [ __ ]
>> No, not really because I go on the
internet and I buy a 500 m whatever it
is millimeter. Well, I buy a big vape
thing anyway and basically that'll last
me for like 6 months something like that. >> Yeah.
>> So, back to my question. And you made a
statement earlier on saying that your
channel is not lifting off. Can you
explain to me why your channel is not lifting off?
>> Cuz they're all that's why.
>> Right. Ask me. Ask me why I think your
channel is not lifting off. Go on. Ask
me as a viewer.
>> Why isn't it lifting off?
>> It's because you're too opinionated. You
think the problem is is with other
people. You ain't bringing no other new
subjects to the table. only the same
subjects every day. Money, women, money,
women, and broke. And basically, people
are in the wrong, but you're in the
right. You're not different. And uh
[ __ ] you can't see the trees through
the woods. But you could change the
channel around if you think positive,
not negative, about people around you.
>> Yeah, but you didn't have your first
kiss until 23.
>> But PJ,
>> it's not all about me. It's all about
you. I've got what I got in life. What
have you got? I've got a woman right by
the side of me can say hello to you. Can
you do the same?
>> Yeah, but Katie's mine.
>> Okay, I'll repeat myself. I've got a
woman in my life that I can have sex
with every day. Can you do that? Have
you got a woman like this now?
>> Katie Kay's mine now.
>> It's 1 It's 100 Well, nearly 2:00 in the
morning and he's still live speaking
bollocks. You're so proud.
>> I'm not speaking bollocks. Right. I've
been watching you for you're talking
[ __ ] about living off £50 a month cuz
you used to say you told me that you
lived off £1,000 a month alcohol.
>> No, I didn't.
>> Yes, you did.
>> I look PJ whatever I
>> You said you used to live you you used
to live off £1,000 a month for alcohol.
>> PJ, whatever I did with my life when I
was single, right? It's really no
concern about anybody on this internet,
is it? Come on, be fair.
Yeah. So why are you saying you live off
£50 a month then?
>> So what happens if I lived off £50 a
month, £1,000 a month? Are you really
concerned about that? Because I can afford it.
>> I'm just I just want to know why you're lying.
>> Do you think I'm broke?
>> No, I just want to know why you're lying.
>> Well, I'm not lying. I'm actually
speaking to you, January. But you're
already criticizing me through
everything I'm saying because you told
me you told me before that you you lived
off £1,000 a month alcohol.
No, I said I spent £1,000 on alcohol
near in 13 weeks.
>> But you actually lived up£50 a month. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> 50 a month.
>> You can't get there, can I?
>> No. That's [ __ ] mad.
>> That's almost £10 a week.
>> I know people right uh PJ right to Scott
money. Yeah. and they don't spend the
money. They just go to the basically
food bank to get their food. So
technically when you think about it, if
they give get given food for a week or a
month for basically to survive and they
not spend any benefit money, do you not
think they are smarter than people that
spend their money?
>> Yeah, they can save Yeah. If they they
can save for like six months, they're
laughing in it
>> and they still having food from a food bank.
>> It's a way to [ __ ] the system. Yeah, it
is. cuz there's a way to [ __ ] the system.
>> Yeah, of course. Yeah,
>> that's what people do. That's what
people I know have done.
So when you say, "Do you believe I can
pay off 50 quid a month?" No, I can live
off nothing a month. I just go to the food bank
if I needed to.
>> Oh, you could shoplift.
>> Well, why do I want to shoplift, bro?
It's a bit bizarre that >> Why?
>> Because if you shoplift, you got a good
chance of being in jail. Actually, I'd
be quite good actually when you think
about it. No, actually you won't because
if you're going to jail, your benefits
would stop. So, no, I couldn't stop this.
>> That'd be good though. If say for
example, yeah, your benefits never
stopped. Yeah, that would be good. I'
I'd try to rob a bank. And if I failed,
listen, listen. If I failed and I come
out in a year and a half, 2 months, then
I'm I've got all that money. Say I know
it stops, but say it didn't stop.
>> Then it would be smart.
>> Well, years ago it didn't stop.
It was constantly.
>> Yeah. Now it does. Now it does. I would
just do something and then they get me
like a year and if I get caught, okay,
I'll do a year in prison. Come out with
all that money.
>> Yeah, you are correct.
>> Yeah, it is smart. There's ways and
means out to live PJ without spending
money. You know that, don't you know? I
can give you I can help you.
>> You can pre-drink before going into
clubs and stuff.
>> Well, yeah. You can smuggle in your own
drinks, can't you? like Vular and stick
it in your own cup and you don't have to
go up all the time. You know, there's
ways to do it.
>> Bless you then, Rice. Bless you.
>> So, how many men how many men? So, how
many women have you uh you know, in 2025
have you basically slept with? And how
many have turned their backs on you?
>> Not. I'm a virgin.
>> You remind me that of that person
offenders. What's his name, Kaye? That
that boy, what's his name? That doesn't like women. >> Joe.
>> Joe. Yeah. Have you ever watched
Stenders? Uh, people.
>> Yeah, obviously.
>> Yeah. There's a boy in it. Yeah. There's
a boy in it called Joe and he's against
women and he thinks that women are, you
know, he's a bit like you.
>> You know who it is. >> Yeah. >> This.
>> Yeah. You need to watch that because you
aream. He is an example of you
>> well he thinks women are
you're in the same categories cuz he
thinks that women are basically thinking
that they're bigger than they are and
basically better than men and stuff
similar what you were doing but he
decided to attack a woman and tried to
basically you know what's the word touch
a woman and think that he was correct in
doing it and then he attacked his mother
and I think it's his mother-in-law. I'm
sure of it. And uh tried to kill her cuz
he was listening to some guy on the
internet that he well he was saying to
him, "Oh, women are this, women are
that." You remind me of him.
>> That's funny.
>> Well, it's not really because when you
think about it, people like that is
dangerous because he's willing to kill a
woman because he's got his own views
like you have. Would you kill a woman, PJ? Maybe. >> Wow.
>> So, yesterday you said to me that you
wouldn't rape a rape a woman cuz you
said that was wrong and he wouldn't do
it. But tonight you're saying that you
would maybe kill a woman. So, why would
you kill a woman?
>> For all the [ __ ] they've g me over the years.
>> So, you're telling me you would kill a
woman because all the [ __ ] that they put
you through all the years? >> Maybe.
>> Wow. Are you being serious? Would you
would you do it
>> to be honest? You I know I joke about
and say I like serial killers, but tell
me something, PJ. That's not normal
behavior to say that you would actually
think about killing a woman. So, if you
had a woman in front of you and he had
one better of you and they smacked you
around and hit you and bullied you and
you knew you could have overpower them
and kill him, what would you do in that
situation? Would you stab them, smack
them in the face, whack their face off
the wall? What would you do? Stamping
their head? What would you do?
>> I don't know.
>> And you've killed them. They're on the
floor dead. What would you do in that situation?
>> I don't know.
>> Would you leave him?
>> I don't [ __ ] know.
>> So, just say he was with Kaye now. Yeah.
Kayie mouthed you off. She was in your
face pushing you, punching you, and you
punched her in the face. So, she hit
that head and she died. Would you leave
her there or would you basically go and
get help for her?
>> Yeah. You would leave her there. >> Wow.
>> Yeah, I would. >> Wow.
>> Do you know what, PJ? I I need to go to bed.
>> Well, I need to go to bed. Yeah, I'll