[Laughter]
Oh yeah, it was a [ __ ] good day.
[ __ ] the football bet lost.
Yeah, but you win some, you lose some.
Eh, win some, lose
some. So they say, they
say, don't put too much on it. I had a
[ __ ] lovely meal as well. I'm [ __ ]
knackered. I was having some chicken
balls. I was thinking a lot whilst I was
eating the chicken balls, thinking that
we can share it,
man. And some you lose some. So
this man's like, "Oh, well, when you bet
on the football, yeah, you shouldn't
expect to win." Well, with my bets, you
you would expect to win. because it's
only a double both teams to score. Think
about it. They're not like three, four,
both score, no draw. Cuz obviously you
don't expect them to win. They don't really
win. That's [ __ ] [ __ ] Good.
Anyways, jaming kills a vibe. I noticed
that any sort of vibe that you got going on [ __ ]
it repeating it as
well. Sick of it,
man. I'm sleepy after that meal, mate.
What did that
Yeah. Yeah. Be on here as well. Stop self
projecting. Stop self projecting.
Yeah, that's why you're you're on my
live talking to me, bro. This is Bro, honestly,
man, this really is just such a downy
community. It is such a downy community,
bro. I'm gone tomorrow 100%, man. Leave
these little losers to it. I'm not
reacting to these clowns no more. I
swear down, bro. I'm not reacting to
these little clowns. I let them do
whatever they want to do,
man. I'm not reacting to these clowns. yourself projecting
clowns. Basement dwellers. What I call
them little basement
dwellers. Basement dwellers.
Eye after that meal.
We had a Chinese. It was good. Yeah. Good. Very
good. Bye-bye. You just hold on a
minute. You just said I even got a
carpet. Oh my [ __ ] god.
These people are such
dies. No, hold on. You just said No, I
didn't tell her. It was a good date, by
the way. We had a
Chinese. Um, she said, uh, we mean
again, we had a Chinese and a wine. I
only had one wine, come back, had a
shower, and I'm [ __ ] tired, bro. Oh,
yeah. My football bet lost, by the way,
£40. I just needed Fleetwood to score
and they never I'm done with this
gambling [ __ ] bro. I was just saying to
Antman, I'm sick of having the same
conversation every time. And he's like,
"Oh, like with your football bets, you
don't expect them to win." Well, I
expect mine to win. She's here for 3
months. I expect mine to win because
it's a double both teams to score. So, I
actually expect mine to win. He does
three double. He does three. He does
four teams, both score, no draw. Of
course, that's hardly going to win. But
my one should be winning. I'm done with
it anyways. I'm buying
an I'm going to buy an electric bike as
well, man. I'm going to take up a new
hobby. This is boring as [ __ ] this
gambling, bro. It's so boring. Like, I
won't get I won't get mad. Yeah. Or
nothing, but it's just boring. And it's
boring having the same conversation
about it every time as well. It's so
boring. I'm [ __ ] booking a holiday
next week. [ __ ] it.
Yeah. 40. But £40 is nothing to me. You
are mug. You are a loser. Go
self-reflect on another
channel. Yeah. Well, it is longterm
because I'll go to
America. Oh, I'll go to where she is in
America when she goes back. She's She's
here. She's here for
work. Yeah, bro. I'm actually done with
it now. Anyways, the gambling
lad. I'm done with it.
It honestly is so boring
now. It honestly is
so It honestly is so boring. Is
it And it is boring. It is boring. I'm
going to buy an electric bike. It's
boring. It's boring. I'm going to buy an
electric bike and pic next next
week. It's [ __ ] boring, bro.
Yeah, I need to start the
gym. Yeah. Well, at least I found
somebody that's going to do it.
E, she lives in California. She's from California,
so yeah, it's a lot longer than [ __ ]
Boston, mate. But be it, is
it? Yeah. Not for a few months when she
goes back. So, we'll keep meeting and
when she goes back, I'll just go over and see
her. Mate, you've just said, Hold on a
minute. You just said that I come on
YouTube cuz I got no one else to talk
to. You've just been blocked on four
different accounts. You see how these
people do nothing but
self-reflect, Gary? You see how these
people do nothing but self-reflect? You
just said, "I come on YouTube cuz I got
no one else to talk to." You're You just
got blocked on four different accounts.
You [ __ ] loser. Do you know what?
Yeah, Gary. I might actually post some
content videos. Like, that's the only
thing, bro. I'm not going live anymore.
Yeah. Yeah. For a long time, bro. I'm
just going to post content videos, I reckon.
Maybe my new electric bikes or
something. Leave these little losers to
themselves, to be honest with you.
Yeah. Yep. Leave these little losers to
themselves. I know. He's such a virgin,
isn't it? Well, if he wasn't autistic
and he wasn't ugly, he might he might be
able to lose his virginity. You know
what I mean, Gary? You know what I mean,
Gary? Buddy, he's such a virgin. I call
him the YouTube virgin. The biggest
going. He's such a virgin. You need to go get
laid and go off for YouTube. That's what
you need to do. [ __ ]
virgin. You don't know what to do.
Why? But yeah, I'm done with the gambling
anyways. Yeah, you're right. I can't handle
it. Why does he obsess over Why does he
me? Um, do you want me to tell you the truth?
He obsesses over me because I'm better
looking than him. I've got more money
than him. I've got more family than him.
And I've had more women than him. And
because he can't accept it, he'd rather
just sit on YouTube all day and hate. I
know it's weird, bro. But anyways, I'm
done with the live stream today after
today, bro. I'm putting some content
[ __ ] on my
channel. That's why he does it. He's a little loser.
I'm younger than him and and I've done
better than than
him. Wouldn't it be crazy if you fell in
love and ended up going to America for
for a new
life? Two. Imagine bumping into each
other after three, four or four
years. Who will I who will I be bumping
into after three or four
years? What what are you talking about?
The person lives in England. They're
from California. I met her earlier. We
had a nice Chinese meal. Now I'm
stuffed. Oh, [ __ ] me. Do you know what,
Gary? I'm actually starting to pre
prefer Chinese than Indian, you know,
cuz with Chinese, they do that succulent
beef. With the Indian, they don't do
beef. They only do lamb and chicken. I
like lamb and chicken, but my favorite is
beef. So that's what's good about the
Chinese, but they're [ __ ] tight
bastards. They're tight bastards. I'll
tell you that for nothing, mate. I had
chicken balls. I had chicken
balls. Benefit waster. Stop talking
about yourself. It's not good for your mental health,
man. It's not good for your mental health.
I'm I'm I'm going to train to be a
psychologist. These people really are
sad, man. These little basement
dwellers, they have nothing but calling
people for a living. Yeah. I had chicken
I had chicken balls and uh a beef
curry. But they're so I remember Yeah.
the other uh a few it was like two weeks
ago. Yeah. I went to the Chinese and
they only accept cash. Yeah. Bear in
mind I've been to this place a h 100
times. Yeah. I don't live too far from
it and they only accept cash, right? And
I said, "Oh, none of the cash machines
are working." And I said, "Oh, I'll come
tomorrow and give you the money cuz I'm
going to order again tomorrow." She
wasn't having none of it. I was like,
"What the fuck?" Like, I've been going
to these places, this place for years.
Yeah. I was like, "What am I going to
do? Run away with
£7 and we'll never come back to your
shop. Like, what the fuck?" So, I had to
walk like [ __ ] 25 minutes to a
[ __ ] cash point. It was a madness,
bro. Who's really going to run away with
£7 worth of [ __ ] and never come back? That's [ __ ]
mad. They're [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. They
must think people are going to rob them
or something. It was over £7 as well.
So, um I think it was a beef chain. It's
either beef made or it was like literally seven
quid and I literally had to go and find another cash
point. It's madness, bro. Like, what the
[ __ ] Why would I run away with £7 and
never come back when this is my favorite Chinese?
Crazy. Yeah. Well, I would be good at I
would be a good uh psychologist because
it's like I know what these like I know
why these people do what they do on here
every day. They're fat. They're
unattractive. They got nothing going for
themselves. They got no money. So, they
they uh No, we went for Chinese and had
a wine. We had a little kiss. She might
have not seen me before. She has seen me
before. I've been going to that Chinese.
I've been going to that Chinese for
ages. I used to travel to go to that
Chinese. She has seen me before. It's
the same woman every time. So what? You
think I'm going to run away with
£7. It's She has seen me before because
it's been with the same It's the It's
been the same person for years. I even
know what her name is, you know, like.
And what? So, so you've been coming to
this place for all this time, right? And
literally all the ATMs were out of
service. So, what am I going to do? Run
away with £7 [ __ ] 50 and never come
back to the shop?
What? No, this was another time, you
idiot. And you know what? Yeah, it's a
shame because that's the best Chinese.
Like, after that, like I didn't ever
want to give them my money ever again. I
didn't want to give them my money ever
again, but I feel like that is literally
the best Chinese. There's no other good
Chinese around the
area. So, but no, we're talking about a
different time. Yeah, we
kissed. We're seeing each other again,
LJ. Ah, I'm going to make a baby. A baby from California,
LJ, what a lovely night.
That's going to be a lovely sight. Lord
Jay, I'm buying an electric bike, by the
way. Plus, I have a
wank. No, I'm going to be seeing this
19year-old again soon as
well. 19year-old again
soon. Yeah. I'm going to buy electric
bike, by the way. I'm buying an electric
bike to get around quicker. RJ.
Yeah. To get
quicker. You're not getting no woman
around. Stop these football bets,
bro. It's coming around tonight. Maybe
tonight. Maybe tomorrow.
Well, yeah. Grievy, do you not? No.
Greavvesy, do you not understand how this
works? You, me. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. Listen, Grezy, do
you not know how this [ __ ] works, buddy?
Right. You have different options. Yeah.
So you take it slow with one person and
before you're official, you go with
another woman and have sex with another
woman. That's the way it works. You have
one slag and one person that you take it
slow with. That's what happens. Then
when you become official with that
person, then obviously you stay with
them. That's the way it works. Listen,
say you've got two different women. Say
you go out on a Saturday and you get two
different women, right? Yeah. and you
get two different women, right? Listen,
as an example, and then they both meet
you. You go slow with one of them and
then the other one you go fast with and
you see which one works better. You
know, like, well, you you know, how else
are you how else are you going to get
sex? That's what I'm going to be using
this 19year-old for as my
[ __ ] until I find someone else until I
find someone else that's going to give
me sex. Like hopefully when I meet this American
again, you know, we we'll [ __ ] But it
might take three, four dates. So that's
the way it goes, bro. Or or you can use
escorts. One of the two. One you go fast
with, one you go slow
with. That's the way it
works. But to be fair, I don't really
get a big sex drive anymore like I used
to, man. I don't really care about it. I just want
to Bro, like I said, I'm booking. I'm
booking a holiday next week anyways.
So, got the old passport back and I can
afford an electric
bike. They're not out there. I might buy
my friends one to be
honest cuz this gambling greasy is no good,
lad. It's annoying as [ __ ] It's
annoying as [ __ ] man. You might as well
just get a different
hobby. I I was saying this to Ant-Man as well, man.
Like, it's no good,
man. Is it Greasy? It's no
good. They always come back in the
end, don't they? Mhm. Yeah. Yeah,
man. So, what do you want me to do anyways, Greasy? You
know, you seem to know all of these
things, Greasy, but in reality, you
don't really know anything, do you?
Because who's the one that's actually
been with women
myself? Oh, it's almost April, so it's
about time you got these dating apps, is it, Grezy? Oh my
god, this guy has a date today as
well. Um, no. But sometimes I think of
like, right, he's going to be really
jealous cuz I've met this woman. Like
whenever I meet a new woman, sometimes I
think, "Oh, like if this virgin found
out about it, like he'd get jealous and
and ruin it because he's such a
virgin." Sometimes I think of that though,
Gary, you know, cuz of Morgan, cuz of
Izzy, cuz of uh that one from
Manchester because he's jealous that
he's too ugly and autistic to get
anything himself, which is why he's still a
virgin. You understand, lad? Yeah. You understand? That's it. [ __ ]
virgin. I still got that video, by the
way. Me getting a
[ __ ] Still got that
video. Still got that video, lads.
Bye-bye. Crying. What was I crying
about? Yeah, [ __ ] off. You're boring, mate. You're
boring. Stop boring
me. It's all It's the same spastics every day.
Like I've actually noticed that like Tim
Slots I've just gone on John West's um
thing, right? And it's the same
people from even like years ago, bro.
I'm on it here. Look, it's literally the
same spastics every
day. They got to be old, in it, these
people. It's going good. I went on a
date. I'm back now. I'm [ __ ]
knacking. I'm [ __ ] exhausted.
Yeah, I am tired, man. That [ __ ]
Chinese KO'ed me, lad.
Yeah. Oh, I'm so sleepy.
They're all freaks, bro. They're all
obsessed with me, man. They're all
freaks. Virgin, Virgin Legs, Jamie.
They're all [ __ ] They're all weirdos,
man. They're all obsessed with me, bro.
That's the norm, man. You know, that's
what they're like,
lad. I got KO'ed by that [ __ ]
Chinese, bro. I feel like I've took
about a million [ __ ] colonos.
They're all just, bro. They're all obsessed with
me. Spoke to my sister earlier. Spoke to
her yesterday as
well. Oh, it's right, bro.
It want to get an ebike. I want to go to
the gym and I want to get an ebike. Yeah.
Cuz he's a
coward. Because he's a Cuz he's a
coward, lad. He's a keyboard
warrior. He's a coward. He's a keyboard
warrior. He will never meet anyone. Yeah. Mhm.
Hey, wild super. I don't like that copy
sauce, bro. I had a bad experience when I was
um when I was um young with it, lad.
Uh, mate, you've made How many accounts
have you made? You [ __ ] [ __ ] Get
alive. Get alive, you little [ __ ]
Get off of
YouTube. [ __ ] basement
dweller. Did you see how jealous they
was the other day? Um, Gabby, when I was
in the pub having a Guinness, they were
trying to get me kicked out of the pub. How
sad do you have to be to try and get
somebody kicked out of a [ __ ]
pub? That's mad, isn't
it? Like, how sad do you actually have
to be, bro, to actually do that? It's crazy, isn't
it? Yeah. I just commented on this
thing. A wild s
appears. A wild s appears. Wild
simp. Yeah, they've been doing it for
years. Yeah, it's the same free force
bastics. They've been doing it for
years. Your skin, your this, your even
though it's they are all of these
things. Yeah, it's the same. They've
been doing it for years.
There's an account, I don't know if it's
still on it, called Now Then
Cheese. Well, well, tough [ __ ] I'm
going to go near many women because I
can get women unlike you. You [ __ ]
ugly bastard. Anyways, [ __ ] off you
little nons. You little weirdo. [ __ ] off
you virgin. Anyways,
um yeah, what was I saying?
Um yeah, it is the same people, bro.
There there's an account called uh now
cheese and he used to troll
um he used to troll uh
uh Ant-Man about six years ago and if
you look around it you'll still see that
[ __ ] on YouTube.
Think about it, bro. Look at in all of
them six years, right? Ant-Man, as an
example, right? He was eating cold
beans. He had not a pot to piss in. Six
years down the line, he's going Thailand
three times a year. He's moving to
Thailand. He's got money. He's living
the life. And now then, Cheese is still
on YouTube trolling. Think about it,
bro. These people have got nothing in
their lives. I'm sure you've seen that
account now then. Cheese. 6 years later,
six, seven years later, and he's still
on there. Back before I even had facial
um before I even had facial hair, you
know, they're just losers, bro. That's
all they are.