Right. This is the last I'm [ __ ]
saying about this. Yeah. Right. I've
just gone live to [ __ ] um talk about this.
Right. Let let a few people join, bro.
These comments, the the the self the
self-projecting comments again and again
and again and again and again. I won't
be live long, but that's it. Yeah.
Stop talking about people that you don't
[ __ ] know. You've done this time and
time and again and you always get proven
wrong. Bro, you do not know what people
have. You don't know what money people
have. Stop self-reflecting your poverty
pension life onto other people. Like,
it's it's it's it's madness. You're
going on about a pension and you're
coming on here every day telling people
that they're living in [ __ ] poverty.
And then when someone asks you how much
money they have, you can't even tell
them. Self-reflecting skin people. Come
on, it's almost 2026. Dozer Fra, stop
doing this now. It's boring. Famous
Smokeoky Both Skint. They are both
skint. Why do you think, right, these
two need to gamble to try and win money?
Because they ain't got no money. Why do
you think they always go on about these
community post community post? Because
they have no money. They've got no
[ __ ] money. Yeah. This is why they
keep talking about people because
they've got no money. And to and and
that's why we always see the same [ __ ]
over and over and over and over again.
Yeah. How the [ __ ] are you going to come
on here talking about poverty when
you're showing a pension? We don't care
about a pension. We want to see
disposable money, bro. [ __ ] a pension
that you can't touch until you probably
you'll probably be dead before you can
even jo you can you can touch the
pension. I've got money coming in. I've
got more buddy than you. If you do not
understand English language, bro, then
you need to get your [ __ ] head
tested. Yeah, cuz it seems that people
explain the same thing over and over
again and you're the one living in
poverty because all you're doing is
talking about a pension that you can't
touch. All we hear is a pension that
you're not allowed to touch. That's all
you can show at in your lifetime at 3
[ __ ] 8 years of age. All you can show
is a pension that you can't touch. And
then you're talking about other people
living in poverty. It doesn't even make
sense. You and Smokey B are the
definition of poverty. You're the
definition of [ __ ] poverty for [ __ ]
sake. Then we have my man last week
[ __ ] show6,000 pounds in a [ __ ]
bank account that he's age when he's
older than me. And these two want to
talk about poverty. Poverty, bro.
Really? These two [ __ ] mugs want to
talk about poverty, bro. Really, really,
really, really, really, really. What is
it with you people, right? you, two,
three people on here coming on here
talking about people that you don't
[ __ ] know and every single time you
get embarrassed again, you come back for
more. Yeah. Worry about your own poverty
life. Don't worry about writing
community post and that you are the one
living in poverty, Joseph. You are the
poverty ridden one. Yeah. Just because
someone says they don't want to go out,
they don't need to prove themselves to
you fat ugly people. Stop [ __ ] you
know, um, for one moment. Yeah. Stop
[ __ ] uh creating the same atmosphere
and get it in your head. We don't come
on here to prove ourselves to fat ugly
self projectors. I'll repeat as many
times as as as you need me to repeat it.
Yeah. You're going on about a pension
and you're talking about poverty, bro.
Come on. If you if you're really going
to try and tell someone else here that they're [ __ ]
they're living poverty, right? Then you
need to show money that's yours. We want
to actual see act not a [ __ ] a bit of
money that you can't even touch.
Who the [ __ ] Like it's just it's just
it's just mad. Like I've always had this
in my head. Yeah. That once if I if you
died at 50. Yeah. That's it. you know,
50, you're [ __ ] old and wrinkly. Do
you really think anyone cares about
money that you won't even be able to
touch until you're in your [ __ ] 50s,
[ __ ] 60s? Come the [ __ ] on now, man.
It's not like you could touch it in your
30s or your mid-30s. [ __ ] Jesus
[ __ ] Christ. Think about people that
go to prison, they come out when they're
50, [ __ ] 50 years of [ __ ] age,
bro. You need to sort your financial
circumstances out before trying to talk
about other people. You don't know what
money people have and what money people
don't have. Yeah. Open your ears, fix
your brain, and stop self-projecting. I
don't know how many more clearer I can I
can be about this. You and Smokey be are
the definition of poverty. Is the
definition of poverty. That's why you go
on about poverty. I can go out right now
and do whatever I want. We don't need to
prove ourselves to you fat, ugly people.
This is all I'm coming on here saying.
Yeah. Come on here and type.
You know, you're not going to be so
[ __ ] big now, are you? Stop
self-reflecting your insecure finances
onto Peterbelly. Yeah. [ __ ]
projecting every time. That's why, do
you know why I only stayed live today
for like 40 minutes? Cuz I can't be
bothered with the self-p projecting the
self-p projecting fat ugly people. It's
why no one comes on here anymore.
Yeah. [ __ ] absolute madness.
Yeah, [ __ ] [ __ ] You and Smokey be
are the definition of [ __ ] skint. The
only time you have a bit of money is
when you [ __ ] win. I don't need to
win money to have money. Self [ __ ]
projecting. You just talk you talk
nonsense. And you know what the thing
is? You really don't know about anyone's
life. You really really really do not
know about anyone's life, bro. Just
Dusty and Smokey Beast self-reflecting
their poverty life onto me again. Stop
self-reflecting. You've got your bro.
You do not know how much money I have.
Yeah. You've got a pension that you
can't touch. Yeah. Don't worry about
what I've got. I've got more than you.
Don't you worry about what I've got.
Yeah. Didn't you last month? Right. Wait
a second. Was it last month or was it
the month before? Right. Another case of
you being proven wrong again cuz I
thought, "Fuck it. I can prove you
wrong." and and get what I want at the
same time. You remember when I when I
bought these jeans and you was like,
"Oh, your skin, you can't afford the
trainers." I said, "Should I buy the
trainers? Should I not?" And then you
was like, "Oh, you can't. You can't. You
can't." And I went and bought the
trainers. You got proven wrong again.
Time and time. You get proven wrong
again. Guess what, Jojo Farra? We don't
see you in restaurants. We don't see you
on expensive holidays. All we see is you
gambling 80 to 150 [ __ ] pound. So you
might want to focus on your poverty
ridden life before trying to accuse
other people of living [ __ ] living
under [ __ ] poverty. You are living
poverty. Poverty is your [ __ ] life. Yeah. Refucking [ __ ]
dumbo. If I wanted to gamble now, I
could gamble now. If I wanted to [ __ ]
go out today, I could go out today. You
do not know what I have. Yeah. re [ __ ] [ __ ]
Oh my god, bro. This guy keeps
self-reflecting his poverty ridden life
onto me again, bro. Him and this smoky
bee, two skint [ __ ] in a pod that
ain't got no money trying to talk about
me, bro. Think about it, bro. You're the
one with a 200lb phone. You're the one
that don't go to fancy restaurants.
You're the one that doesn't go to
expensive holidays. Who's the one
really, really, really, really living in
poverty? You are. You are the one that's
living in poverty.
Yeah, you are the one that's living in
poverty, dick [ __ ] head.
And guess what? You want to talk about
my phone being blocked, but guess what?
My blocked phone is still worth more
than your phone. Believe it or not, my
this blocked phone right here and the
only reason I have a new phone is cuz I
couldn't be I can't be bothered at the
moment to buy a new phone. Yeah. Let's
talk about your life, bro. Yeah. Let's
talk about your life right here, right
now. You are the one. You are the one
that's living in poverty. I can gamble
whenever I want to. I can [ __ ] drink
whenever I want to. I can [ __ ] a
prostitute whenever I want to. Just
because someone decides they don't want
to do anything doesn't mean their skin [ __ ] [ __ ]
Just the same self projecting. Oh, you
can't gamble because you sublet. I can
gamble whenever I want. I can gamble
right now. I can gamble in every book in
the area if I want. Bro, you don't know
how much money I money I have. And I
guess the thing is, even when you're
proven wrong, you still talk [ __ ]
Yeah, I've got more disposable money
than you've got right now. What are you
on about, you idiot?
Self [ __ ] projecting.
I understand, bro. You're a bit butth
hurt that there's no gambling videos
anymore, but that's because I don't want
to put any gambling videos up anymore. I
don't want to gamble. Simple.
You don't know people's finances. You're
not people's personal bank account, bro.
You ain't You don't know what people have got.
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ]
self-reflecting little skint [ __ ]
They ain't know [ __ ] nothing about
anyone's life, bro. Give it a [ __ ] break.
Self projecting. Oh, [ __ ] me.
I'm a time again.
Yeah, I'm a skin. Yeah, whatever. Okay.
Self-reflector. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. Okay. Whatever. No one cares about
you, Kevin Murphy. Another
self-reflector. Like I said, when you
come to London, we'll talk about it.
Yeah. I can't buy a phone. Yeah. Yeah.
Just like you said that people can't buy
the other things and you continuously
get proven wrong. Yeah. Self-reflecting.
Like I said, I'm not going to be on here long.
They do. But don't they talk like they
know people's lives though? They
generally think that they know what
people have. But they don't know
anything about anyone's life.
>> It is. It's so It's so pathetic. It's
projecting. I was just talking to my mom
about this as well. They think that
everyone's got their life. They seem to
think everyone is skint like them.
My mom just come up as well and we're
talking everyone. They think everyone's
skin like them. This is what I'm trying
to say, bro. They they do. Anyways,
anyways, Joseph, come on here. Anyways,
yeah, whatever, Kevin. Like I said, come
back to me when you come to London.
You people need to grow the [ __ ] up.
Aren't you in your 30s, 40s, bro?
They don't know anything about anybody.
Okay. No, no, no. I stream all day.
Okay. Okay. So, how much money do I have
right now then? Since apparently you
know other people's life, right? How
much money do I have right this second?
So, you should be able to know cuz you
know everything about me then. So, how
much money do I have right this second?
What am I wearing right now? What color
boxes am I wear? Because you clearly
seem to know so much about other
people's lives, but you re What? What?
What? What? What? What do you know, bro? Come on. You know,
is this all to try to take the heat off
the fact that you people have got nothing?
Come on. Is it Is it Is it to do with
the fact that you people have got
nothing in your lives? Is this what it is, bro?
Right. How much money have I got right
now? Kevin, listen. Are you coming to
London or not? Are you just being a keyboard warrior?
You've got the
Yeah, but that's cuz Well, no. What
color boxes am I wearing? Kevin, are you
coming to London or you just being a keyboard warrior?
Another Terry. Another [ __ ] house. This
is what I mean. There's no point with
these people in this community. I've
only gone live again. Yeah. So, Joseph
comes on here and starts [ __ ] explaining, you know,
[ __ ] self projecting. Oh my [ __ ]
god. Come on here, bro. Please,
bro. Come to Listen, Kevin. I went to
your city. You're never going to come to
my city. I've got one up on you. You
ain't got one up on me. Shut the [ __ ]
up. Yeah. I went to your city and you
shut your mouth. So, shut up. You're not
even worth talking to, bro. [ __ ] off.
Come back when you come back. Yeah. When
you're in London, idiot. Uh,
you're not going to know that because
I'm coming off here. So, is Joseph
joining or what? Because I'm not being
on here all day.
Yeah. M, that's repeating. No one cares
about yourself. Reflecting comments.
Joseph, are you coming on here or not? Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, Kevin. Whatever you say. I
can go out right now if I want to. You
don't know how much money I have. You
don't know how much money I have. Didn't
Didn't you not say that people couldn't
afford traders and they proved you wrong
again? You don't know how much money I
have. So, I'm not even I'm just going to
let you keep writing yourself projecting
comments. You keep self-reflecting your
skinlessness. I don't need to block it
because I know what I've got more money
than you. So, anything that you write,
it doesn't affect me.
I can not l win bets and I can go out
every day if I want to, bro. I can go
out every day if I want to. You don't
know how much money I have. So, keep
thinking that you do. And I'm just going
to let you keep commenting, bro. I'm not
going to block it because all you're
doing is when you're talking, all you're
doing is projecting your own life.
You're only self-reflecting. You're only
hurting yourself. So, I'm just going to
let you keep Yep. I'm skin. I need I
need to win a bet. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Yep. Keep lying to yourself, bro. You
don't You don't need to be blocked, you know.
So, I'm not on here for long. Anyways,
is this is this Joseph going to join or
what? Since you want to really talk
about poverty, bro, you're living under poverty.
Yeah, you're living under poverty.
You You are living under [ __ ] poverty.
Shut the [ __ ] up. Yeah.
Why do what I find very interesting is
you seem to think that people need to
constantly keep proving themselves to
you. Can you explain why people that
have been snippet
attached from their mother needs to come
and prove to you fat ugly people
something every day? Can you tell us why
you seem to why you why you think that?
Why you seem to think that people need
to prove themselves to you fat ugly low
lives every day? Can you answer that
question? I'm very very interested.
Timmy Eldridge, listen, I've got more
than £1,200 right now and I don't have
any bills. I paid all my bills. So
again, it's best off talk not to talk
about people that you don't know, right?
Yeah. It's best to talk about people
that stop talking about people that you
don't know because it can cause a lot of
embarrassment and a lot of
embarrassment. I've got more than 1,200
right now and and I've paid all my
bills. You don't know how much money
people have. You do not know how much
money people have. I don't know how many
times people have to keep repeating this
over and over and over again. Yes, I
would. Even if I didn't. Yes, I would.
Yes, I [ __ ] would. I'm a single
person. I don't have any kids. Yeah. So,
if I didn't live with Laney, then I'd
have my own [ __ ] house.
Yeah. I'm a single person. Yeah. I I
don't I don't I have one bill to pay.
So again, do you want to stop talking
about people that you don't know
or stop comparing cuz Timmy Aldridge,
right? I assume that you're working when
you're saying this, right? So this is
what I'm trying to say to you, right?
Okay. It's nothing. Whatever. Okay.
£1,500 is nothing. Okay. Why are you so
obsessed with what other people have got?
Okay. £1,500 is nothing. Whatever. Why
are you so obsessed with what other
people have got? I'm asking you this question.
Why are you so obsessed with other
people's lives? I'm ask this is a
legitimate question. No one is getting
banned. No one is getting banned. Right?
Why are you so obsessed with other
people's lives? Forget, bro. You You've
got all of this money, right? You're
good-looking. You're this. You're
whatever. Okay? Why are you so obsessed
with other people's lives? You tell
people that they that they block you.
They block you. They block you. They
block you. They block you. You're not
blocked. Why are you so obsessed with
other people's lives? This is a this is
a legitimate question. This is what I'm
asking. But by life, I mean finances. I
mean that kind of stuff, not what people
are talking about. Shouldn't you be
worried about your life?
I'm just saying, bro. No, no, no, no. I
do not talk about my financial
circumstances once cuz it's no one's
business. And you keep bringing up you
keep bringing up money every single
[ __ ] time. And no matter how many
times you get embarrassed, you still
come back for more. Like I don't
understand it, bro. Like you'll get
embarrassed and you'll still come back for more.
Madness, bro. [ __ ] madness, bro.
This is why you're not worth it on this
community. Just not even worth going on.
Anyways, is this guy coming or not?
Is this guy coming or not? You know,
is this guy coming or what, bro?
Cuz we see this [ __ ] every day, bro. We
see this [ __ ] every day on your
community post. This person's living with poverty.
Yeah. And you don't even know how much
money people have.
Yeah. I stopped my Xbox subscription.
I'm just going to buy Franklin when it
runs out. Unnecessary cost. And even if
I didn't have Laney, I would still have
money. It's none of your business as
well. I don't know why you keep [ __ ]
talking about [ __ ] money every time,
bro. What other people got, what other
people don't have.
[ __ ] weird, bro. It is so weird.
You don't know how much money I have and
you don't know how much money I get.
Worry about your own life. Yeah, bro.
You don't even have £1,200. So, stop
talking about what other people get and
what other people don't get. Yeah. You
don't know what I get. You don't know
what I have. And I'm not going to keep
talking about money, what I've got. Let
Joseph Ferrar come on here. Right. The
only reason you are obsessing over
people's money is because you ain't got
none. That's why you people come on here
every day talking about money because
you ain't got no money. That's where the
obsession comes from, bro. Yeah. It's
cuz you ain't got no money. That's why
you sit on here every day bouncing on
other people's lives time and time
again. It's cuz you ain't got no money. Every time
you come on here, people come on here,
money this, money that. It's cuz you
ain't got no money. That's the only
reason you people talk about money cuz
you ain't got none. Cuz you ain't got
none. Do I want to play the money game?
I've told you I am never showing you
anything ever again. I am not showing
you nothing. Not even a pen. So you're
wasting your time. Played these games
before. Made you all run away. Not
playing it again. End the story. Let I
want Joseph to come on here with this
smoky bee and I'm leaving. Simple. Yeah. Done. Simple, bro.
You've been beaten at the money game
multiple multiple times, mate. You have
been shown money multiple times and
you've ran away. Your self-p projecting
games are not going to work anymore.
Your little self-p projecting games are
not going to work anymore. I'm not
showing You know what? You want to You
want to see money? Yeah. You want to see
money, Timmy? Timmy Elders, do you want
to see money? You want to see money?
Yeah. How about you earn your own money?
Stop being skinned and then you'll have
your own money. Then you can see your
own money when you go to work. Yeah.
When you actually work and you get money
yourself, you'll actually see some
money. Yeah. But it's your own money. Yeah. Simple.
Yeah. You keep telling yourself that,
Timmy. You don't know how much money I have. Self-projected.
When you go to work and you get your own
money, you can see your own money and
look at your own money. And stop asking
strangers on the internet to embarrass
you again. Stop coming on here asking
strangers on the internet to completely
embarrass you again. It's happened
multiple multiple times, bro.
How many times does a stranger have to
come on here and embarrass you? Like it
doesn't a stranger an absolute stranger.
Go to work, get your own money, and you
can look at your own money added up. Not
a stranger that will ruin you for the
hundth time again.
Projection. [ __ ] me.
[ __ ] idiots, man.
Yeah, I've been gambling today. Yeah,
yeah, yeah. Of course I have. Self
projecting again. Anyways, right, we're
going to stay live until this guy comes.
Yeah. And then I'm off here. I don't
want to be live long, but I'll wait. Yeah,
I'm gambling. Why? Cuz you just got told
about yourself. [ __ ] so many self-p
projectors in this community.
So many self-p projectors in this
community, bro. It's [ __ ] mental. Absolutely mental.
absolutely mental. The self projection,
you might as well just [ __ ] go on
Reddit. Seriously, you you might as well
just go on [ __ ] Reddit. To be fair,
that's what I'm doing after here. I'm
not I'm not staying on this long. I just
want this country to to come in and join.
Just self-reflecting every day with
these people. They're boring, bro.
Boring. Boring. Boring.
They got a life and they had money. They
wouldn't [ __ ] be doing this [ __ ] you know?
Yeah. I've already come to Liverpool,
autistic boy, and you ran away repeating
again. Yeah. Come on, bro. Come on.
Hurry up, Joseph. I don't want to get
brain damage again.
I don't want to I don't want to get
brain damage again. Come on.
I've already come to Liverpool,
[ __ ] and you didn't show up.
I've already I already went to Liverpool
and you didn't show up. But this is what
I'm saying. And then and then you're
wondering why. Yeah. This is what I'm
saying. Yeah. And then you wonder why
people would never meet anyone on it.
Look at what you're doing right now.
Uh uh uh. You don't need to. Bro,
you don't need to show them. Just show them yourself.
Bro, don't show them me. Show them
yourself. Show them the big ugly [ __ ]
It will save you literally about 3040
every month. You don't need to show them
me. Show them yourself. Self projector.
Anyways, is this guy going to come on
here or not? Yeah, Kevin. You keep
telling yourself that. If it makes you
feel better about you being skinned,
yes, I need to win a bet and determine
whether I go out. You keep telling
yourself that. If that makes you happy,
you keep telling yourself that. Yeah.
Keep telling yourself that. Yeah. You
keep telling yourself that, self-reflector. Anyways,
you don't need to know if I've done a
bet or not. You don't need to know that.
Maybe I have, maybe I haven't. You don't
need to know that.
You don't need to know that.
Maybe I have. Maybe I haven't.
Yeah. Go have a pot noodle. Yeah. Yeah.
No one's really saying about uh when I
went to Liverpool and Kevin Murphy
didn't show up, did they? Now, do you
see Grezy? Why people don't waste their
time on these people now? I know you
like I know you like the lost content
and stuff and you like the fights and
whatever, but do you see now why people
don't waste their time?
Do you see now why people don't waste
their time since you wanted a reason?
This [ __ ] has been on this live stream
for about 20 minutes and no one has
called out this [ __ ] for not showing up
when I went to Liverpool. So, do you
know now why people don't waste their time?
Do you know why now people do not waste
their time? I think it's a valid reason.
It's not even an excuse. You see why
people don't waste their time now on
these little mugs, on these little
jealous projectors? Do you see why
people don't waste their time? You know,
hopefully you know now why, bro? Yeah.
Do you see waste their time, waste their
money, whatever, whatever it is, because
they're not worth it. These are fat,
ugly people on here.
Yeah. Yeah. Whatever, bro. And I just
told you about yourself.
Yeah. Good for you. And I just told you about yourself.
Yeah. And I just told you about yourself
straight up. So, good for you. Stop
self- projecting. Stop repeating.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Whatever. We've heard
all of this before. Anyways, let's have
a new episode now. So, is this guy
coming on here or not?
Is this guy coming on here or not?
Yeah, Kentucky. They're just sad people.
They don't know about anyone's life.
That's why I'm not blocking them because
they go on like they know people, but
these people don't know anyone's life.
Do I just let them type? Because they
don't know any anything about anyone's life.
They they don't know anything about
anyone. That's what makes it like
comical. They don't know what people
have, what people don't have. They
literally don't know anything about anyone.
They only go off their own life.
They only go off by their own lives.
That's why it doesn't bother me. That's
why I don't block them because they're
talking about themselves,
you know. And yes, I did put my camera
on in Liverpool and I was live at the
hotel. Yes, I did. So again, more
excuses. Anyways, Joseph, are you coming
on here before I developed [ __ ] brain
damage or what? [ __ ] spastics on
here, bro. Proper spastics on here.
Yeah. Okay. It's poverty. Whatever.
You've said this. It's boring now. Is
this guy going to come on here and we
can talk about this or what? because I
don't particularly want to keep engaging
with these retards on here. They're
giving me brain damage now. These [ __ ] retards. Yeah. So, yeah.
Bro, shut the [ __ ] up. You didn't come
to London. Bro, don't come on here.
Yeah, take an L and then start making up
stuff. My mom didn't pay for my haircut.
I was taking a piss. Tell us about why
you didn't show up in London, you little
[ __ ] Tell us why you didn't [ __ ]
come to London, you little [ __ ] This
is what they do. This is exactly what
they do on here. Yeah, they take L's,
Greavvesy, and then they deflect. These
little faglord [ __ ] virgins project.
This is what they do. that these little [ __ ]
they self they they they this is what
they do, bro. These little [ __ ] run
away from people and then come back like
nothing's happened. Now, do you know why
we don't waste our time with these
people now? Because they're little
[ __ ] that run away, lose, and come
back for more. They're [ __ ] They're
disabled. They're so disabled, bro.
They're so disabled that even when they
get beat, they come back for more.
You know these little [ __ ] even when
they're shown up, they come back for
more. Kevin Ghosten, this is why people
don't waste their time.
This is why people don't waste their
time on them, bro. This is why people do
not waste their time on these fat, ugly virgins.
These fat, ugly, self projecting
virgins. This is why no one waste their
time on them anymore, bro. He was
nowhere to be seen, bro. The [ __ ] was
nowhere to be seen. The self-p
projecting [ __ ] was nowhere to be
seen. Receding hairline, that's you.
Skin is you. Everything is yourself.
Self-reflector. You did not show up,
bro. Well, you would have seen my
receding hairline if you showed up on
[ __ ] Saturday, wouldn't you? Yeah. So, yeah.
Yeah. I didn't have the money again.
Self-reflecting bomb. Yep.
Self-reflecting. I'm going to leave you
to keep self-reflecting, talking about
yourself. I'm going to allow you to keep
talking about yourself now. I'm not I'm
not going to ban you. I'm not going to
block you. I'm not going to respond to
you. You can keep talking about
yourself, you little [ __ ] You was
nowhere to be seen on Saturday, you
[ __ ] Kevin was nowhere to be seen in
Liverpool cuz he's a [ __ ] And then
the story, simple, simple, simple. The
two [ __ ] were nowhere to be seen and
they're coming back typing [ __ ] bro.
They're coming back typing [ __ ] Uh,
women hate you as well. You're still a
virgin. Women hate you. Your mom hates
you. You're a [ __ ] Life hates you.
You didn't You didn't even have the
balls to come on Saturday. You little
[ __ ] You little undercover [ __ ]
Don't [ __ ] come back here typing
[ __ ] Women hate you. You're still a
virgin. At least I've kissed women. At
least I've slept with women. Unlike you.
You're hated by all women. You're still
a virgin, Mr. Lonely. Coming on here
pretending that you've got a girlfriend.
You've never had a girlfriend, Mr. Ugly.
You've never even kissed a woman, Mr.
Ugly. Look at your own Mr. Ugly life.
trying to tell people that you live in
Chichester. You [ __ ] [ __ ] But you,
you know, you showed yourself up. You
showed yourself up, you little [ __ ]
When you come on here saying about how
people can't do this and people, it it
shows that you're a [ __ ] and you would
never meet anyone. You made yourself
look like a [ __ ] When you started
talking about people jeans, people's
jeans, and people being a ma, you showed
yourself to be the [ __ ] that would
never meet anyone. You're so much of a
[ __ ] that you showed yourself. You
showed yourself up. You showed yourself
to be a [ __ ] [ __ ] You're never
meeting anyone. You've been on here now
for a very, very long time. And do you
remember what I told you? It's not if I
say so, I [ __ ] know so. And I was
going to say that to your [ __ ] ugly face.
Remember, if you say so, I [ __ ] know
so. I [ __ ] know so. [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] that don't meet no one.
Anyways, is this coming on here or not?
because I don't want to keep
entertaining these spastics.
I don't want to entertain these [ __ ]
self-reflecting fat ugly people that
never made it. So, if this guy's not
going to come on here and talk, then
what's the [ __ ] point?
Okay, bomb self. Keep self-reflecting
your life. No one cares. Anyways, is
this guy going to come on or what?
Cuz I'm talking to a bunch of fat, ugly
losers that never made it. And I don't
really want to be associated with these
sad people, you know? I don't want to be
associated with these sad middle-aged
losers. So, if this guy's if someone's
going to actually [ __ ] you know,
come on, then that's fair enough because
I don't want to be associated with a
load of bully victims that ain't got a
life. Sad little losers. Yeah.
Yeah. You keep telling yourself that.
You keep telling yourself that. You keep
telling yourself that. You've never
ruined my life, mate. I'm still on here.
I'm back for more. Anyways, are you
coming on or not, man? Is someone going
to come on or what?
Anyways, we're done with these two [ __ ] [ __ ]
How can I tell? Because you middle-aged
ugly people are losers. You middle-aged
ugly people coming here from the time
you wake up to the time you go to bed,
you're absolute losers. You're alltime
losers. You're the [ __ ] losers because
I'm calling you middle-aged 40year-old
people losers. I'd rather live with my
mom and be 28, better looking than you,
more money than you, than be in my 40s,
a fat bunter that can't even leave the
house than a fat bunter that can't even
leave the house. So, you're trying to
skit someone, bro. But the thing is,
when someone is saying, Timmy, I could
be like you in my 40s, no money, ugly.
I'd rather be living with my mom at 28
than you fat ugly losers with nothing in
life. I'd rather live with an old woman
than be like you bum boy ugly virgins.
I' I've admitted it. I have literally
admitted it though. I could be you
people in your 40s, no money, ugly as
[ __ ] Look at you ugly people. How can
you talk about Right. You actually think
Yeah. people with your lives can talk
about other people to a 28-year-old when
you're in your 40s and you're [ __ ]
fat and ugly and you're trying to talk
about me crying. Does it sound like I'm
crying, bro? I'm just ripping you into
shreds and you can't say nothing other
than I'm crying. I'd rather be a
28-year-old living with my mom than a
[ __ ] 48-year-old [ __ ] too ugly to
even get anything in life. Can't even
show my [ __ ] ugly face. And that's
why you people come on here every day
cuz you're fat and ugly. You're losers.
You're bully victims. You don't even
leave the house, bro. It's just like my
man said. You don't leave your house.
Every time you try to leave your house,
you get bullied for being so ugly and
then you self-reflect on someone that's
28 and better looking than you, bro.
Come on, bro. Seriously. Come on now. We
all know that you are going to be lonely
Christmas. Lonely this Christmas. So,
you're talking about a 28-year-old
living with their mom. You are going to
be lonely this Christmas. The self-p
projection. Yeah, women despise you.
You're still a virgin. At least I've
been with women. Stero relationships. I
have been in a relationship and I have
had a girlfriend and I have had sex
unlike you. Don't make me start putting
the videos back up again. Bro, you
people in your 40s and you're going to
be lonely this Christmas. You're going
to be lonely this Christmas. Should we
put the song up, bro? Should we I have I
have been in a relationship and I have
had sex. You people are going to be
lonely this Christmas. This is why I'm
not blocking you, bro. Cuz you people
are going to be all alone Christmas day.
Lonely. No women, no family. That's why
I'm letting you self-reflect because I
feel bad for you. I feel bad. You people
are going to be lonely Christmas fat,
ugly, lonely people. No wonder you
you've got a problem with someone living
with their mom because someone's got a
mom. Your mom hates you. Not only does
women hate you, your [ __ ] whole
family hates you. So, you're going to be
on Christmas YouTube. Yeah. You're going
to be on YouTube on Christmas. This is
where this self-reflection is coming
from. You're the Christmas
self-reflectors because you're going to
be lonely this Christmas. You're going
to be lonely lonely people. You're going
to be lonely. That's why I'm not banning
you, bro. You're going to be lonely this
Christmas. So, you can keep
self-reflecting all you want. I'd rather
live with my mom at 28 than be a sad,
fat, ugly, 40-year-old virgin going to
be lonely Christmas. I'd rather This is
Look, look, look, Breezy. Have you not
noticed yet that the community right,
it's gotten live again? Was it live last
month? No, bro. Do you not see how mad
it's got? These people are going to be
lonely this Christmas. It's like what my
mom said. You're the only one that's
actually got a loving family. These
people have got no family. It's almost
Christmas. Think about it, bro. When's
Christmas? In less than 20 days. Think
about it, bro.
They're going to be lonely this
Christmas. It's the truth and that's and
that's why they're doing this. Yeah. So,
ghost know you going to come in the
hangouts or what?
You can't even come out, bro. You can't
even come in the hangouts, bro. You're
You're so disabled. You people can't
even talk. You're so disabled and ugly.
You can't even talk. I don't even know
why I'm wasting my time on these people,
bro. On fat, ugly, disabled virgins. Why
the [ __ ] am I even wasting my time on
these people, bro? No one's even
joining. Bro, you don't need to see my
hairline. Look in the mirror and look at
your bald, ugly head. Look at your bald
head. Look at your already bald head.
You don't need to see my hairline. All
you need to do is look at your own baldy
bastard head. You don't need to see
anyone's [ __ ] You don't need to see
um hairline. Just look at your own own
baldy head and give it a polish. You little self-reflector.
Shut. Bro, you don't need to see my
hairline. Look at your own hairline. You
got no hair, fatty. Fatty boy. You got
no hair. Look at your own. Look at your
own. You've made me, bro.
You've made me, bro. You can't show your
face cuz you're ugly. You can't show
your face cuz you're ugly. The only one
that's insecure was you ugly people.
Mate, I owned you on Saturday. You was
nowhere to be seen. Go away, you ugly
little bunter. Go away, you ugly little
bun. You was nowhere to be seen on
Saturday, you ugly little bun. So
anything that you say is just
ridiculous. Now go away you ugly little
bunter that never showed up on Saturday.
You ugly little fat buner. You never
showed up on Saturday. That's the only
thing I'm going to say to you now, bro.
You know, look at all of this hate
because someone's got family, bro. This
is a madness, bro. This is a madness.
All because someone's got family, bro.
It's a madness.
That is mad.
Hopefully this isn't someone trying to put [ __ ] >> lonely.
>> Lonely Pete. Absolutely [ __ ] skint.
>> You are lon You are skinned. You are
lonely. Yep. Self-reflector. No
self-reflectors on my channel.
>> Here we go. The Christmas projectors
going to be lonely this Christmas.
I'm I'm You know what? I'm actually
going to say about this.
Yeah, I'm I'm going to Yeah, actually. Yeah. Yeah.
Do you know what? Yeah. I think you're
you was right what you said the other
day, you know, about these people having
no family. I have you not noticed how
many people have been on here in
December doing this as opposed to last.
Have you not noticed the amount of
projection that they have that they have
come on here doing this? I think you are
one 100% right. They've got no family.
They're going to be lonely Christmas. If
you notice last month, you never got you
got an odd person. You Yeah, they're
very very very
They're very jealous, lonely people.
I've noticed that as well. Very jealous, lonely people.
Of course, they would bait. These people
are ugly, faulty, no family, no
girlfriend. They got nothing in their
life. That it is the truth. It really,
really, really is the truth.
They're going to be sat there on
Christmas lonely. And if you say that to
them as well, they try and say not.
They're going to be sat on YouTube alone on Christmas.
They're trying to convince themselves
that they're that you're everything that
they are. It's [ __ ] madness. And if
you see on January, you won't get any of
this. February, you will not get any of
this. These people are going to be sat
alone on Christmas Day. That is sad as
[ __ ] Self-reflected, isn't it?
No Christmas presents, no nothing. How
many Christmas presents have I got?
About four or five.
I've already got about four or five.
Yeah, these people are proper proper self-reflectors.
Even an old woman knows it. You're the
You're the Christmas self-p projectors.
You know how the grits come down
Christmas. Yeah. It's the truth.
It is the truth, lad. It is the truth.
Yeah. Bully. You people don't bully no
one. You bully yourselves. Bro, listen.
Look at your lives on here, man. Fat,
ugly, and alone. You've always been
bullied. Any bullying that you think
that you do on the internet, bro. You've
been bullied your whole life. So, you
can keep convincing yourself that you
bully people. But you've been bullied
your whole fat, ugly lives. So, keep
convincing yourselves, bro. No one gives
a [ __ ] what any of you Hey, why is that?
Oh, there you go. Yeah.
You're going to be lonely Christmas.
Lonely. Ghost him. No family, no
girlfriend. Women hate him. Can't show
up to London. He's going to be lonely
this Christmas. I might do a song doing this.
It's a [ __ ] madness. Yeah, it's
actually a madness, bro.
It's actually madness. Ghosting. Why
didn't you show up on Saturday? You fat ugly blob.
You fat bro. You're talking about my
speech, but you're the one that can't
come on the hangouts because you're too
disabled. So, I don't know how you're
trying to take a piss out of me, bro.
Lonely. Yeah, women hate you as well.
You're still a virgin. You've never had
a girlfriend. You've never had a
girlfriend. They hate you as well,
self-reflector. You've never had a
girlfriend. You've never even kissed a
woman. At least I've had sex and I've
been with women. You've never even had a
girlfriend. You can't even show up to
London. You silly fat sausage baldy
bastard. There you go. You got owned
again. How many times do you fat, ugly,
disabled, little self-reflecting single
people need to keep coming back for
more? Bro, you get owned every time.
I've been with I've had sex. I've had
more women than you. Bro, you've never
had a woman. You've never had a
girlfriend. Worry about women hating
you. You little self-reflectors.
You know, little self-reflected fat,
ugly 40-year-old virgins. Where's your
girlfriend? Stop self-projected, bro.
You know, the thing is, yeah, I can't
help the way things are, you know. I
can't help that you've got no family
over Christmas. It's not my fault, bro.
It's not my fault that you are lonely
single people with no It's It's not,
bro. It's not my fault that your family
hate you and you got no girlfriend.
Don't keep taking it out on me.
Stop taking it out on me.
Stop. It's not my fault that you got no
family and you're going to be lonely
this Christmas. Don't [ __ ] take out
of me. Lonely. Lonely. I don't give a
[ __ ] about last Christmas. I'm talking
about this Christmas. You're going to be all alone.
[ __ ] hell. You're going to be all
alone on Christmas. This is where this
self-reflecting come from. Anyways, I'm
banning you people now. You're boring
me. You little self-reflecting ugly
people. You're boring me now.
So anyways, is this guy going to come in or not?
This is just the same self-reflecting
over and over and over and over and over again.
fat ugly people, fat ugly losers.
And your band as well. You don't win
anything. You're just boring repeating.
It's just the same repeating by the same [ __ ]
the Christmas self projectors. But
anyways, lad. Yeah. Uh, Greasy, this is
why people don't need people anymore.
Right. This is why you're deprived of
content, you poor [ __ ] We've just had
two people, one of them that's actually
common hangs that did not get [ __ ] for
not turning up when I went to Liverpool.
We don't need to waste our time on these
fat ugly people that ain't got nothing
to their lives anymore. You understand? Yeah,
right. Anyway, this guy going to come on or what?
Is this guy going to come in or what?
[ __ ] Christmas self-reflectors.
Christmas self projectors.
That's what they are. I ain't got no
family. Ain't got no life. Ain't got no
nothing. [ __ ] sad bastards. I'm
coming off here anyways, bro. When this
guy doesn't join, I'm coming off here.
I'm going to give him 15 minutes. I'm
going to put the link out and then I am
done. D done. I didn't even want to come
back live today, bro.
Entertaining little [ __ ] mongos that
ain't got a life.
[ __ ] disabled bully victims,
you know? Disabled bully victims that
ain't got a life.
You people, let me ask you that. How How
old are you people? By the way, I'm
asking you because you don't act your
age, do you?
You don't act your age. And LJ is another self-reflector.
And he's not coming in. The Christmas self-reflectors,
you'll notice this around December time.
They all get mad at anyone that's got a
family because these people ain't got no
family. That's why they do this.
They go for people that's got family cuz
they ain't got no family. So yeah.
So is this guy coming on or what, bro?
I'm going to message him.
And I won't be going on no channels from
today from tomorrow. I won't be going on
no channels. So you'll have yourselves
to talk to. Yeah.
[ __ ] fat ugly self-res. And do you
know the thing is bro? Yeah. You don't
bully people. You bully yourselves. All
you do is people that bully yourselves.
Yeah. Think about this, right? I'm 28.
I'm better looking than you. I've got
more of a life than you. I'm not
disabled like you. Look at you people.
That's why you don't come on camera. You
don't come on camera cuz you're [ __ ]
ugly. Anyone can write [ __ ] behind the
keyboard. You're boring. You're boring
now. You're this bitter, insecure,
jealous, ugly, lowife people. morons
like Laney called you. That's what you
are. Morons. Ugly little self-reflecting
people that's got no family over
Christmas. And you know it's true as
well. And you know it's true. [ __ ]
ugly people ain't got no [ __ ] life.
Anyways, is this guy coming on? Cuz I
don't want to keep talking to these self-reflecting people.
Reflecting disabled people.
So, is this guy coming on or what, bro? Yeah.
Is this guy coming or what? [ __ ] self-reflectors.
I hate this community, bro. I hate this
community. I was only live for like 40 [ __ ] minutes.
says, "You're not [ __ ] coming on, you
[ __ ] skid murdered. You need to go get laid.
You need to lose your [ __ ]
Valentine's card, you ugly bastard. Then
you might be able to come on, mate.
Trying to put news up as well." Yeah.
Self projecting your ugliness onto me
again. Guess what? You need to lose your
Valentine's card. You know, you're still
a [ __ ] virgin cuz you're an ugly
[ __ ] I've had more women than you.
I wish though. Did you show your Did you
show your [ __ ] nieces yourself on
what to not be liked? You should show
them to not be like you, bro. You know,
a [ __ ] fat bongo that can't get off
of YouTube. Did you show them you? It
saves the internet bill. You need to
show them you, your ugly face. Show them
not to grow up to be ugly like you.
Yeah, but he's trying to put nudes up.
He He's trying to put nudes up.
He's trying to put nudes up, bro.
No, no, no, no, no. I haven't.
Yeah, the [ __ ] trying to put nudes up.
He needs to lose his Valentine's card.
need to lose that B card, not be so much
of a virgin.
Anyways, I'm coming off him in a minute.
Anyways, cuz this Joseph Ferrar is not coming on.
Got my little evidence pack here. Got my
little evidence pack. I want to ask him
why he said that Chev was attractive to
fit in, but he he's trying to put nudes
up and it doesn't let me exit the home screen anymore
and I can't like hide it. I want to I
want to know why he felt the need to
copy Grezy. He doesn't make you look
big. He just makes you look like a copycat.
Just trying to put moves up.
[ __ ] lose up.
It doesn't let me exit the home screen.
I want to let the [ __ ] in and ask him
why why he's obsessed with Shel. Why is
your little cop?
That's that's that's the first way I'm
going to say when he joins.
>> I can do better than you, Goozy. Meow. Ch.
It's true though. Is it?
What are you eating today, Greg? I don't
think I'll be eating anything. I' I've
lost my appetite.
I don't even think I'll be eating, bro.
I lost my appetite.
Yeah, he's trying to put nudes up and
he's muted his mic
and I can't exit the home screen. I
don't know how how you do it.
Okay, maybe it's that way.
I don't know.
Maybe. One second. It could be.
Maybe it's that way.
I don't know.
Oh, here we go. You're in. Meow. She's attractive.
Yeah. Can't deny she's attractive, can you? Meow meow meow.
Yeah. Why you not saying anything, you little copycat?
You said Shell Cole was attractive to
fit in. You're He's He's on the He's on
the panel, by the way, lads.
You got caught red-handed
being a copycat, wasn't he, Grezy?
Caught red-handed, willing to follow the
crowd. All because you got bullied at
school by the Scottish lad. Yeah, Jackaryi.
You [ __ ] bullied the [ __ ] out of you.
The next day you went to college.
Are you saying anything or what? Little copycat.
You little copycat.
>> You wanted to fit in with the crowd,
didn't you? Z to feel left out. The [ __ ] ain't talking.
[ __ ] off, you [ __ ] virgin. I just
kicked him now cuz you're not talking.
[ __ ] off, you virgin. You're not talking. [ __ ] off.
I don't think I'll eat today, Greasy. I
can't be asked.
I'm too frustrated to eat.
You know, thinking about my bad
experiences and stuff. I'll go on Reddit for help.
Yeah. I I didn't leave the house for two
days, bro. Pointless.
Yeah, it's five. I don't even have an appetite.
Nope. I'm not eating nothing.
Too depressed, bro.
No, I'm too depressed. Too many bad
experiences. Not interested. I was
supposed to be going back to sleep, but
[ __ ] this [ __ ] I had to go live for Oh yeah.
Oh, I won't be eating anything today.
No, I'll be depressed, bro.
I'll be depressed in bed. Yeah.
Nope. Not interested in eating.
I'm not interested in eating. And having
a cup of tea on a [ __ ] empty stomach is stinking.
No, I'm not interested, bro.
So now when you talk [ __ ] in future,
Joseph Ferrar, you're not going to be mentioned.
Yeah, I probably won't even eat today.
It's too bad, bro. I woke up thinking
about my bad experiences again and how
there's absolutely no reason why I'm in this position.
I woke up dusty and I'm thinking there's
no reason why I'm in this position.
Literally no reason.
Not disabled, not from lack of trying.
There's literally no reason for it. So
yeah, I won't be eating today. That's depressing, bro.
Yeah, I'll be in bed. Depressed, bro.
Well, I had a Fredo actually. Greavves.
I had a Fredo.
Yeah, I had a Fredo.
It's best for people like me to give up
with life doing this, save loads of
money. So then there's opportunities,
you know, when you finally want to get
back on your feet and, you know, leaving
and stuff. It just makes more sense for
people like me that's tried everything
in life. You know, you you that's the best solution.
I know you wanted to see some content on
Saturday, Grezy, but nah,
I wouldn't mind if I could blame myself.
If I could blame myself, then I'd blame
myself and be like, "Oh, okay. Well, we
can blame myself." But you can't even
blame yourself at this point. You can't
even blame yourself for all the bad
experiences you've had.
So, you just give up with life.
That's what I done. Yeah.
Put my camera on.
Oh, I look better today.
Yeah. She wanted to see my hairline.
Yeah. My big nose. I'm better looking
than you. Come up with some different
insults. It's boring now.
So, is this guy come? Oh, we've almost
gave him 15 minutes and he's still not on here.
The state of that it's boring now. Stop
it. It's boring. Now, you're say, okay,
listen, right, that just hurt. You're
saying that you've made people insecure
about their looks. I'm not insecure
about the way I look. I'm showing my
face. You people can't show your face.
That's strange, isn't it? Do you not
understand that you are older than me,
right? And what you're doing is actually
more pathetic than what I'm doing.
You're in your [ __ ] 30s, 40s. Yeah.
Hating on strangers every day on YouTube
that you don't know.
Yeah, bro. No one cares what you think
about my face. I can show my face. You
can't show your face. I don't give a
[ __ ] what you say. I can show my face.
You can't show your face. So, you're the
one that's insecure. Imple. No one cares
about you ugly people, bro.
Self-reflecting. You're always going to
do this. [ __ ] seven years. You've
been doing this.
You've been doing this now for seven years. self-reflectors
coming on here every day hating on
[ __ ] people that you don't [ __ ]
know. How old are you people? How old
are you people again?
How old are these people in here?
How old are you people in here? Can you
tell me how old you are? Cuz you act
like an 11 year old, 12y old. You
actually are. This is what people used
to do when they were 11, 12. That's what
they used to do. Yeah. when they're that
age and you're like what in your 30s,
40s. You're coming on here every day
hating on people that you don't know.
Get a [ __ ] get a grip, man.
You don't make anyone insecure. You
don't make anyone stop showing their
face. Why are you still doing it?
Every time you people get doxed, we see
what you look like. We see exactly what
you people look like when you get doxed.
So, do you think anyone would care what
any of you people say about anyone?
I can show my face. You can't show your
face. That's something I'll always have on you. Yeah.
Uh, being gay is not a choice.
So, again, immature comments. Being gay
is not a choice.
So yeah. Oh damn.
I'm on more of a diet than you now,
Grezy. I'm not even eating.
[ __ ] that. I don't even have Coke and
I'm not going to get Coke. I'm not doing
that. See, it's bad it, bro. Really, really bad.
Really, really, really, really, really, really bad.
There's no reason for me to go out on
Saturday, Friday. There's no reason. I
don't even have Coke. I'm not going
shop. Don't give a [ __ ] So,
I don't understand why this is still happening, Grezy.
You know, you get my point though, ain't
it, Grezy? You understand what I'm
saying? You get what I'm saying? There's
no reason for this. There's no reason
for this. There is no reason for this whatsoever. So,
and the therapy, the thing we was
talking about with the therapy, Reevesy,
is because if we're talking about
therapy, we're taking the blame off of
women. That's what my point was earlier
is that if you if someone's saying their
struggles, right, and then they're
telling people to get therapy, that's
basically trying to take the the problem
off the women.
You You need to stop self-reflecting
your poverty life onto me, Joe. You
don't know how much money I have. You
and Smokey be do not know how much money
I have, what I can do, what I can't do,
whatever. You know, you do not know. You
do not know, right, what people have and
what people don't have.
So, [ __ ] off, bro. Yeah, you're
self-reflecting, bro. Just worry about
your pension that you can't touch. Just
worry about your pension that you can't touch.
Yep. I am. Women hate me and I hate
women. We hate each other.
So yeah, but why as I was saying uh
Grezy is that when you're saying to
someone get therapy, it's like it's
taking the the blame off of women
because I don't live in poverty. I can
do whatever I want. If I want to go get
a haircut now, I can go get a haircut.
If I want to go to a restaurant, I'll go
to a restaurant. If I want to go out
drinking right now, I'll go out drink.
You don't know my life. Yet you're
saying that I'm living in poverty, bro.
No. No. living in poverty. I'm not
explaining this to you again.
No, you can't, you stupid [ __ ]
bastard. No, you can't. You [ __ ]
stupid [ __ ] bastard. No, you can't
cash it out when you want, you stupid [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm stinking. Yeah, okay,
whatever. No one cares about your self-reflecting comments.
It's boring now.
Okay, I can leave the country tomorrow
if I want to. Is that better?
Okay. I can leave the country tomorrow
if I want to. I can go to an expensive
restaurant tomorrow if I want to. I can
buy designer clothes tomorrow if I want
to. Is that Is that good enough for you?
Is that good enough for you? Oh, the
virgin wants to come on.
>> I remember.
Mute the mic again. What?
Where are you little copycat?
You're on there, but you muted your mic.
What? Come on, you little copycat.
Too many bad experiences with him. And
I'm not getting into it
cuz you don't listen. No one listens.
And I'm not here to repeat myself all
day again. So, we'll be on it for a
little bit longer, then I'm gone. Simple.
Too many bad experiences.
Yeah, I can't get one. We've seen me
with plenty of women. Yeah, we've seen
me with plenty of women. Plenty. More
than you have ever had. Again, this is
why I don't want to come on here no more
with these people. And this is why I
can't stand these self-reflecting people
that create the same atmosphere every
day. This is why I don't want to part of
this community anymore.
self-reflecting ugly people that are
jealous of you. I don't want no part of
this [ __ ] anymore, bro. I don't want no
part of these ugly self-reflecting
people that create the same atmosphere
every [ __ ] day. Yeah. Why do you
think I was only live for like 40 minutes today? Yeah.
You know, two people have took L's that
come on the chat earlier. No one called
them out on it. Right or wrong, Grezy?
Right or wrong, Grezy? No one call him
out on it. Yeah. So what is what is the
point of this? Like what is the what is
this community for?
Oh, you are definitely definitely
jealous of my life. You definitely
definitely are jealous because if you
wouldn't if you weren't jealous, you
wouldn't be doing what you're doing. And
I can promise you, you're absolutely
jealous. The fact that you have got
these middle-aged people that are
obsessed with you every day. I can
promise you, pinky promise, that you are
jealous. Cuz if he wasn't jealous, you
wouldn't be doing what you're doing. I
can promise you, that's my promise to
you, that you are jealous because if you
weren't jealous, you wouldn't be at
people every day. You wouldn't be
wasting your life on people every day.
Jeal people that are not jealous don't
do that. Again, I know your brain
doesn't work properly. Bully me, bro.
Bully me. You can't even meet me, bro.
You bully yourselves. Your ugly
40-year-old ugly people. The only people
that get bullied is yourselves. You are
fat, ugly 40 year olds. Again, keep
repeating it until it goes in your
brain. The only people that get bullied
is you lowife ugly rejects that nobody
wants in society. It might sound harsh,
but it's the truth. If I need to say
this stuff to you, bro, I I will. I
will. Yeah. You know, the only people
that get bullied is you ugly
40year-olds. And it's the truth. And you
know it, bro. And you know it's the
truth. You're ugly skinned, jealous
people. Old as [ __ ] Okay. Why don't you
Okay. Okay. Okay. Right. Oh, you're
saying that you're not jealous. Yeah.
Join my hangouts and show and put your camera on.
Join the hangouts and put your camera on
and show us what you look like. All
right. [ __ ] this. I'm going to do this
one more time. Right. One second.
I'm going to put the link out right now
and I want you to join and show us what
you look like. Okay. Yeah. There you go.
You got the link. No excuse. You come on
here right now and show your faces. Show
your fat, ugly faces and I can show you
what you're jealous of. Come on. The
link's there. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Because you're fat and [ __ ] ugly.
This is what I mean. This is where
you'll always have one over on these
little bully victims. These little bully
victims. This is where you'll always
have one on these generous people. They
will never show their face. And all the
people in the past that never shown
their faces before have proven to be fat
and ugly. Isn't that a thing, Joe? Pat
Mustard, Gray Cat, Bomb, uh, Savvy Guy,
Savvy Boy, Savvy Boy. Isn't it so funny
that they're all fat and ugly? You're
not, you're not not you're not fine,
Joe, that all of the people that's come
on here before doing this that's been
docked. I've always been fat and ugly.
But they would have never ever told you
that. They would have never have said
that. Oh, we look like this, we look
like that, we look like this, we look
like that. They would have come up with
some excuse. But have you noticed that
every single one of that's been docked
have all been fat and ugly?
Have you not noticed that? I find that
very, very, very funny to be honest.
But you people are jealous on here, bro.
You people are jealous on here. You are
jealous, bro. People don't sit on
YouTube doing this every day cuz you're
not jealous. Sorry, Joseph Ferrar. It
doesn't add up. People don't sit on here
doing what they do every day because
they're not jealous. They don't stalk
people on different subreddits because
they're not jealous. Sorry, bro. It
doesn't add up. But again, I'm wasting
my time trying to explain to a disabled
person. So, yeah. No,
no. I'm talking about you keep
self-reflecting your poverty with a life onto me.
It's none of your business. I'm not
having this conversation no more. So, is
anyone going to join the hangouts or
not? Because I want to be out of this community.
I want to be out of this self-projecting community. You know,
I want to be out of here, bro. So, what
So, what are you doing, bro? M
[ __ ] same same atmosphere on here.
Imagine that. Seven years and they still
can't create a different atmosphere.
[ __ ] bongos fat ugly people.
No, no, no. You're telling me that I'm
living under poverty. You don't know how
much money I have. I can literally do
whatever I want now.
Like I literally can do whatever I want
now. Right now.
Yeah. No, Kevin can come on. He's not
even trying to come on. Joseph, uh, what
about Kevin not showing up in Liverpool?
And this is exactly why I want nothing
to do with this community. The biasness,
the jealousy. I don't want no part of it
anymore. I don't want no part of this.
You know, you defending the Virgin, you
know, you not saying about Kevin not
showing up. I don't want nothing to do
with people that are jealous of me. I'd
rather get off here here and live my
life. Yeah. And if what you're saying is
not true, that's the end of it. Yeah.
Because I don't like these people. I
don't like these people. And I've had to
go live again talking to these people. Yeah.
Because I I hate these people. I don't
like them. Do you not understand? I do
not like these people. Right. And I've
had to go live again calling this [ __ ]
out again. Do you not understand? Yeah,
if I had 5 seconds with Joseph Ferrar,
I'd smack his face off because the thing
is this keyboard Yeah. has let people
right be brave. We all know that if I
was on Joseph Far's front door, bro, the
fat [ __ ] wouldn't do anything. How have
I even come on a community like this? You know,
I don't like these people. And if I ever
catch one of them, I'll break the
[ __ ] face. I don't like these people
and I've had to go live again. You know,
because this little [ __ ] was winding me
up. Simple. [ __ ] off, man. [ __ ] it. [ __ ]
it. [ __ ] off.
You know what I mean, bro? Mad.
Yeah, I'll do nothing. But why don't you
give me give me your address then? Give
me your address and I'll come and smack
your face down your front. Okay. Okay.
Give me your email me your address.
Email me your address and I'll box your
[ __ ] face in for defending a nons not
calling Kevin for being a [ __ ] I'll
box your [ __ ] face in. Give me your
address right now then, bro. And I will
come tomorrow. You email me your address
and I will come tomorrow. Yeah. And I
will come tomorrow. I will come and I'll
box your [ __ ] face out. You fat ugly
[ __ ] with a pension that can't you can't
touch. You little nonslubber. Yeah. I'll
[ __ ] smack you up and I'll smack your
fat ugly misses up. Yeah. You [ __ ]
northern [ __ ] Come on then. Give me
your address. Email me your address,
right? And I will come and I'll do
something at your front door. Yeah. Give
me your [ __ ] address. YEAH. EMAIL ME
YOUR ADDRESS, you [ __ ] little
northern Jordy pensioning [ __ ] ugly
nonsloving [ __ ] And I will come
tomorrow. Yeah. Come on. Come on. Let's
do it then. Let's really see who's not
going to do nothing. Yeah. Yeah. You
[ __ ] fat ugly nonslover. [ __ ]
pension pension [ __ ] skin [ __ ] with
ugly [ __ ] fingers on a 200lb [ __ ]
phone. Yeah, you're [ __ ] fat, ugly,
ugly with your ugly misses. And I'm
talking about your MS being ugly. Yeah,
you are ugly. She's ugly. You're a nons
lover. And I want to come to your
address and I'm slagging off your fat
ugly misses and you're listening to your
200lb phone. Come on then, bro. Come on.
Give me your address. What you waiting
for, bro? You're doing these community
posts time and time and again. Give me
your address. Give me your [ __ ]
[ __ ] idiot. Yeah, I'll [ __ ] slap
your flat ugly misses up and piss in her
face. I'll piss in her face, bro. Just
for Just for the biasness. Just for the
biasness. Yeah, I'll slap your ugly
misses up and piss in her face or
sucking lunch's dick. Sucking Kevin's
dick. I'll piss in her face and I'll be
like, "Oh, that's what I'll say to her.
I just piss all over her face. Bro, I'll
do nothing. Well, THEN GIVE ME YOUR
ADDRESS THEN, BRO. BRO, give me your
address then. Give me your address. I
will piss in her face for being a dirty
little nlover coming on here creating
the same atmosphere every day. I will
piss in her face. You fat non-slobing
200B phone boy. Yeah, listen, bro. You
want you want to sit there, right? You
you you actually want to sit here and
talk about poverty. Who's the one that's
wearing next jeans, Joseph? Who's the
one on 200 pound? Who's the one that's
got a 200 pound phone? Joseph, let's
talk about poverty. Who's the one that's
got that that's got a 200 pound phone?
You do. Who's the one that's wearing
next jeans? You are. Let's talk about
poverty. Who's the one that has to go to
Malta in the winter? You are. So, let's
talk about poverty, bro. Come on. Let's
really really talk about poverty, cuz
poverty is your favorite word. Come on,
bro. Let's Let's talk about poverty.
Let's talk about poverty. Come on. your
phone, your jeans, your holiday choices.
Let's talk about Let's talk about living
poverty because that's my my favorite
word. Come on. Come on. Come on, Joseph.
Let's Let's talk about it here. Let's
talk about poverty. Come on. I like the
word poverty. It's your favorite word.
Let's talk about poverty. Come on.
You know that's poverty. Yeah. Yeah.
That's poverty. That's poverty, bro.
Yeah. That is poverty. I don't live in
poverty. Yeah. Yeah. You wear next
jeans. Poverty. 200 pound phone.
Poverty. Malta. Malta for Christmas.
Poverty. Who the [ __ ] Who the [ __ ] goes
to a a summer place in the winter? What
the [ __ ] Who the [ __ ] goes to a winter
a summer destination in the winter? Do
not maybe think that you're the one
that's living with under poverty. Do not
seem to think that you're the one that's
living under poverty. You're the one
that's poverty ridden, bro. Not me. I've
got clothes that's worth more than your whole life.
I've my my jeans and my trainers cost
your whole wardrobe, bro. But them just
them two things that was bought recently
cost more than your whole wardrobe.
Wardrobe. [ __ ] off. You know, simple.
You are a self projector.
You are a [ __ ] self projector. You've
never even been to a nice restaurant. I
would actually put money on saying that.
You've never even been to a nice restaurant. You know
you I bet you've never even been to a
nice restaurant. You are the definition
of poverty, bro. You are the definition
of poverty. You are the definition of poverty, lad. You know,
you are the definition of poverty, bro. Yeah. You know,
bro, you are living.
You are living with under poverty, bro.
Yeah. Incel. Boring. We've heard all
this before. Boring.
Boring, boring, boring, boring, boring. H,
you get you call you get called an incel
now for not licking women's asses.
Would you agree with that one, Grezy?
They don't even use the word properly
now, bro. It's mad. They they use they
call people an insult if you don't lick
women's asses. If you don't suck up to
them, they call you an insult. Mad,
isn't it? But when women complain about
men, they get felt sorry for. Madness,
isn't it? Just one of them things, isn't
But they want equality. Don't forget,
they want equality. Everyone wants to be
equal, Grezy. But how can they be equal?
It doesn't matter where I'm going
abroad. You don't need to know that.
You don't need to know where I'm going
where I'm going, what I'm doing, you
don't need to know that, [ __ ] idiot.
Self-reflector. So, the next time you
self-relect your poverty onto me, bro,
you're not even going to get a response.
You know, you are a proper proper
self-reflector. You really are a
How is someone, bro, that's living in
poverty, rolling around in designer
clothes that you can't afford, can do
anything they want, but you're saying
that they live they live under poverty?
Does that that doesn't make sense? That
does literally not make any sense at all.
I can do what I want when I want.
No, I'm not entertaining that self
projector. I don't go on that channel,
bro. I definitely get brain damage. No,
I don't go on that channel. That's repeating
repeating self-projecting people. No, I
don't go on that channel. That self-reflector,
bro. It's almost 2026.
Let's stop this now. Yeah, it's almost 2026.
Stop it and grow up. It's a time to grow
up now. It's almost 2026. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, Joseph, whatever. I'm going
nowhere, mate. You can't even talk on a
panel. Stop it. You can't even come on a
panel and talk. [ __ ] sake. It's
embarrassing. It's [ __ ] embarrassing. Yeah.
No, I don't. I can spend whatever I
want. You don't know how much money I
have. I can literally And my mom My mom
didn't pay for my haircut. I was taking
a piss. Joseph, you do realize I was
taking a piss when I was saying that.
Uh I was taking a piss.
Uh bro, I was taking a piss when I was saying that.
Uh, I don't need to wind back my
spending. I've got more money than you.
So, I don't need to wind back anything.
I don't need to wind back anything. I've
got more money than you. So, I don't
need to wind back in anything. I can
wind it back up. I can spend what I
want. You don't know how much money I
have. That's the good thing about you
not knowing about other people's lives.
I don't I can spend what I want. I got
more money than you. You don't know what
I have. You don't know what I have. Yes,
I did say that. I said Laney cut my
hair. Yeah, I did say that. I was taking the piss.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I was I was
taking the piss.
I was taking the piss, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
You You can't tell. Sarcasm. Yeah. My
mom paid for my haircut. I was taking
the piss. You don't know how much money
I have. So, you can keep saying to me
that, "Oh, you need to wind back your
spending. I've got more money than you.
I'm not the one that shops in next. I'm
not the one with a£300 phone, Joseph.
I've got more money than you. You don't
know how much money I have. I can go out
tomorrow if I want to. You don't know
what I have. I can go to a restaurant
right now if I want to. The joys of
living in London. You don't know how
much money I have.
You don't know.
[ __ ] Why did I say it? Cuz it was
funny. Yep. Skin self projecting again.
Nope. Try again. You don't know how much
money I have.
Try again. You don't know how much money
I have. Again. You don't know me. You
don't know how much money I have.
You do not know how much money I have.
So, stop telling people that they need
to wind back something when you don't
know how much money they have. Joseph,
do you know what makes me laugh about
you clowns on here? Yeah. You come on
here and you self-reflect, right? I've
already got a new jacket. I got one uh
two weeks ago. Yep, I can. I got one two
weeks ago. It's right next to me,
actually. Try again. So, this is what
I'm trying to say, bro. You know, you
know, you people don't know what money
people have. Like, bro, you have been
proven multiple multiple multiple
multiple times that they've got more
money than you. And you keep coming back
for more. You keep coming back for more
even when you're shown wrong. Why do you
keep doing this? You know, I don't get a
300 pound loan. I don't need a 300 pound
loan. You know,
bro, same to you then. If you had money,
you would be out then. Same same thing
to you then. If you had money, you would
be coming on here self-projected, typing
away then. Same to you then. Same to
you. Same to you then. If you people
weren't skinned, you wouldn't be on here
every day hating, would you? Same to you
then. Same thing back to you then. You
know, you people call people skint
because you are skinned. You've been
doing it for eight years and it's not
changed once. It's not changed once.
You people are skinned. That's why you
go on about money every day cuz you
ain't got no money. You go on about
money because you ain't got none. This
is what it is with you people.
Self-reflecting money every day because
you ain't got no money. You can't like
and a normal person right that's got
money wouldn't be asking people to show
their money you know you know bro at
least lany's not like your fat ugly
[ __ ] Mrs. Bro, listen. I have been with
some women in my time, mate. But your MS
takes the [ __ ] biscuit. Yeah, mate.
At least Laney ain't [ __ ] fat and
ugly. Like, your [ __ ] like your fat,
ugly [ __ ] that probably can't even have
kids. You know what I mean? Yeah, bro.
At least we have the I'd rather have
dementia than be some fat ugly sausage
fingered [ __ ] like your MS. Do you tell
your Do you tell your um misses that you
suck nons dicks?
You know what I'm saying, bro? Listen,
Joe, you're another one that's going to
be no family Christmas. You're just
going to be sat next to a fat ugly
[ __ ] Yeah. Yeah. A fat ugly [ __ ]
[ __ ] and you ain't got nothing.
Self-reflecting again. Self-reflecting
with you people, mate. You look at your
fat, ugly [ __ ] before trying to tell
other people that they've got [ __ ]
dementia. Self-reflecting, fat [ __ ]
Bro, you little clowns don't live in the
real world, though. Do you? You little
clowns don't live in the real world.
Yeah, bro. None of you people win. None
of you fat, ugly people win at anything
in life. Yeah, look at this. Eight years
you single virgins have been doing this.
Yeah, you virgin low-life skinned people
have been doing this for 8 years. Eight
years you have been doing this. Yeah,
bro. I laugh at you, Joe. Your fat ugly
misses. You're laughing at someone
that's younger and better looking than
you, bro. You're laughing at yourself.
Joe, you're laughing at yourself. I'm
not the one with a 300 pound phone. I'm
not the one wearing next, right? I'm
laughing at you and your fat ugly misses
on a 300 pound phone. That's you,
Poverty Joe. I laugh at you and L J. You
are skid to the eyeballs. All of the
things that I've done in my life here,
Joe, you have not done 10% of it. You're
the one with a 300 pound phone. You're
the one shopping at Next. You'd know all
about poverty. You would know all about
poverty living in it yourself. Yeah, we
laugh at you, you fat ugly ding [ __ ]
with your fat ugly misses. With your fat
ugly misses and then when and when
someone tells you that they will say it
to your face, you won't do anything,
bro. You won't even do anything. You
laugh at yourself. You and L J, you pair
of skint gay boys. You laugh at
yourself. Yeah. Do you want me to go at
one of you people one by one, bro? One by one.
You know, we laugh at you, Joe. We laugh
at you. You fat ugly northern [ __ ] on a
300lb phone. Poverty Joseph. Poverty
Joseph. I've got more money than you. I
can do what I want. I'm not tied down
with some fat ugly mun that you're with.
Yeah. Some fat ugly mun.
You little skinned people online every
day self-reflected cuz you got nothing.
This is why you're on here. Cuz you
people have got nothing in your lives.
Skin ugly failures that have got
nothing. Did I hit a nerve, Joseph? Did
I hit a nerve? You're laughing at your [ __ ] selves,
bro. Bro, and I'm laughing at you, Joe.
I can't believe someone that shops at
Next is trying to call someone else
poverty. Trying to say someone lives in
poverty. Bro, come on now. You're
putting £80 in [ __ ] machines.
Poverty. Joe, I've already had a
girlfriend and I will call your MS as
much as I want. Your MS is fat and ugly.
Yeah, I'm calling Right. I am calling
you or Mrs. fat and ugly and I've had a
girlfriend. Well, you gonna do anything
about it? No, you're [ __ ] not. No,
you're [ __ ] not. And I'm pretty sure
a single person can talk about your
misses just like single people can talk
about nonslegs as misses and they can
say that she's a fat [ __ ] I mean,
I'm pretty sure a single person can say
this woman's ugly. I would never get
with her. You you you you can you can be
single and say that, you know.
You know, you you could be single and
say that you you you can you you can you
know you really can.
Yeah. You're talking about yourself,
Charlotte. All Okay. If I've got
nothing, then why have you people been
on here for 8 years repeating? Okay,
let's let's stop the shouting then.
Let's stop the shouting then. Let's just
[ __ ] all of this, man. This is getting
hectic. If I've got nothing, why have
you people been repeating yourselves for
8 years? Can I ask Can I ask you the
question? I'm I'm I'm trying to explain
it to you cuz you said this thing has
been here recently. So if I've got
nothing, why have you middle-aged people
been on here for 8 years? You think
maybe you are the ones that have got
nothing? You are the ones that are skin.
You are the ones that are ugly. You
think that maybe it's yourselves that
you're talking about? Just maybe like
we're not shouting. We're not getting
high rate. Do you think maybe you're
talking about yourselves? Ugly skin. Do
you think maybe? Just maybe you're
talking about yourselves just a little
bit. No, not at all.
You've been writing the same comment
since I've actually been on here. Since
I first come on here, you're actually
writing the same comments. You think
maybe that you are the ones with nothing
in life? Just I'm not even trying to
hate. I'm just asking you that you come
on here every day writing the same
comments. There's no videos on your
channel. There's no content on your
channel. I go on your channel. There's
no videos. There's no community post.
There's no nothing. There's literally
nothing on your channel.
Yeah, he's got a best he's got the best
life. What? Sat on YouTube talking to
people every day that he don't know that
will never meet him,
you know. Really? Really? Really? You know?
Yeah. Charlotte, you didn't answer my
question. Do you think maybe it's
because of you 40 year olds have got
nothing in life? I know I might have I
might I know I might have hit a nerve,
right? Do you think maybe it's cuz you
40y old skin? I know it's a bit of a
tough crowd, but bro, you've been on
here for eight years, right? How old are
you people? Tell us how old you are. Come on.
Tell us how old you are, bro. I don't
even know why I'm wasting my [ __ ]
time on you [ __ ] idiots. You know,
you know why are you bongos sat on here
every day repeating
sat on here repeating your lives away?
If you've got all of this money and
you've got a perfect life, answer it.
Answer it. Answer it. Answer it, bro. Come on.
It's because you fat, ugly people have
got nothing. And I can hit a nerve worse
than [ __ ] Monty will ever be able to
because I know what you people do. I
know exactly what you people do and why
you come on here. You know,
you know. Shouldn't you? You But no, but
you don't laugh. Okay, you laugh at me,
bro. Listen. Right. Listen. You laugh at
yourselves. I'm younger than you. I'm
better looking than you. How can someone
like you laugh at me? I've already
explained to you. All of the people that
have done this in the past have been
doxed. And we've seen what these people
have looked like. Bro, you're fat, ugly
people. You can't laugh at no one. And
I'm trying to say that in the in the in
the most clearest way. Fat, ugly losers
don't laugh at anyone but themselves.
You're convincing yourself that you're
laughing at me and this that and the
other. I'm younger and I'm better
looking and that is the truth. And until
you come on here and you show your face
right, then I'm right. Simple. You know,
you know what I'm trying to say. And and
at the end of the day, you do this because
bro, low IQ. Again, you spastics have
been repeating yourselves for years. You
are low IQ. You [ __ ] spastics on here
have been repeating yourself for years.
You are low IQ. You spastics are low IQ.
How many times do you see you people on
Lord J's repeating, bro? People that
ain't got low IQ don't repeat themselves
every day for eight years. You're thick
as [ __ ] You people are dummies. You
can't even think of different comebacks.
You can't even think of different
things, right? You fat, ugly 40 year
olds are so dumbo. Dumbo the elephant
and you can't even think of new
comebacks. So smart. But you come on
here repeating every day. [ __ ] dumb
asses. You know you self-reflectives are
not even worth the time a day.
And you don't even answer my question.
You don't even answer my question.
I'll be rude to her as much as I want.
[ __ ] off. Hunt. [ __ ] off.
You know, you people need to get a life.
It's almost 2026 now.
You know, you're almost 2026. It's
almost 2026. And you're what? How old
are you people?
Like I said, how old are you people again?
At people every day that you're jealous
of at people every day. What lives have
you actually got coming on here every
day being jealous of people for 8 years?
What life have you got?
What life have you fat jealous people
that got no money got? Bro, what lives
have you actually got? Come on. Come on.
We've spoke about me now. Yeah. What
about you people on YouTube? Fat, alone,
lonely people. I'm going to hit a no
again. What lives have you actually got?
Yeah. While you come on here 8 years
repeating the same [ __ ] What What life
and IQ have you got? Answer me that
question. Right. You can't answer it
because you know it's the truth. Because
you know what I'm saying is the truth of
you fat ugly mongos on here. Because you
know it's the truth. What IQ do you have
if you're on here repeating every day?
You ficko. You dumbass [ __ ] [ __ ]
You know that's what they are when
they're [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Absolute
jealous [ __ ] They can't come on
camera. They can't show their face cuz
they're butt ugly. They're the [ __ ]
ugliest people in the world. These
people on here, bro. You do not even see
You will not even see people like that.
Yeah, you will not even see people like
that. 28, bro. You're talking about
yourself, bro. You people are 48, no
money, no friends. Bro, you're talking
about yourself. You ain't got a
girlfriend. You keep convincing yourself
that these this is me. It's not going to
change the fact that that's you. You're
48, no girlfriend, no friends. Self-
projecting, bro. Yeah. What life and IQ
do you have when you come on here
repeating yourself every day? You are in
your 40s. No relationship, no friends,
no girlfriend. The only thing you're
pitying is yourself. Christmas
projector. These things are you. Your
own life. Everything that you're trying
to say about me, it's your own life. No
girlfriend, no friends. That is you.
When you keep looking in the mirror,
it's you. the [ __ ] that have been
repeating on here for eight years. No
IQ, no intelligence, no girlfriend. That
is you people.
That is you people. Yeah.
[ __ ] projecting [ __ ] [ __ ] Bye-bye.
Yeah, I won't be on here tomorrow.
Anyways, uh Steven Howard, bro, I'm
going to come off in a bit. I wasn't on
here as long today, bro. I'm I'm
quitting this community, bro. It's [ __ ] [ __ ]
just self projecting people that ain't
got a life. I'm done with it, lad.
Let me see.
Sorry, Grezy, but you're going to be um
definitely starved of content. Sorry, lad.
I'm sick of these self-reflectors. I
don't want to entertain them anymore.
They're just self-reflectors.
Self-reflecting ugly people.
I can't even find a Five Great Guys channel.
I can't believe there's a channel called
the Five Great Guys.
Oh, here we go. Yeah.
This is all repeating. We've seen all of this before.
M credit score. Yeah, we've seen all of this before.
It's just the same people doing the same [ __ ]
Yeah, we've seen all of this before.
This is repeating.
We've seen all of this. We've seen all
of this before, bro.
Yeah, we've seen all of this before.
You know, we've seen all of this before.
We've seen all of this before. Am I
lying, Steven Howard?
We've literally seen all of this before.
We've seen all of this before. Am I lying?
We have seen all of this before. Yeah,
we have seen all of this repeating before. Right.
Right. We have seen all of this before.
We've had the same conversation before.
You know, and that Joseph trying to say
I would I wouldn't do anything, bro. Are
you [ __ ] mad? I would I would
literally go to this Joseph Ferrar's
house and box his face in. I told him to
give me his address. He wouldn't do it.
He wouldn't do it, bro. He wouldn't do
it, bro. That's not my credit score. You
don't know my credit score. Stop repeating.
Stop repeating. This is repeating now.
And this is why I'm coming off of this
because it's just full of repeating
people doing the same [ __ ] every day. Yeah. Simple.
Doing the same [ __ ] every [ __ ] day.
Joseph, you don't need to worry about my
hygiene. You fat ugly [ __ ] You fat
sausage fingered fat [ __ ] You need to
worry about your weight. Before talking
about people's hygiene, you little nons
lover, dick sucking fat [ __ ] You need
to you need to worry about your fat ugly misses
and your fat body. You don't need to
worry about my hygiene, bro. I would
rather be a dirty, stinky [ __ ] in shape
than a fat [ __ ] like you. Yeah. Yeah. Simple. [ __ ] off,
[ __ ] self-projecting, jealous people. [ __ ] off.
Disowned by my family, bro. This is
self-p projecting. I speak to all of my
family. Yeah, you're lonely with your
fat, ugly misses. Poverty boy. Next
jeans. Next jeans. Poverty. [ __ ]
definition of poverty. Bro, listen. Right. Yeah.
I told him I'd piss in the he [ __ ]
miss his face for all of the not loving
and the biasness from this fat ugly
[ __ ] This fat ugly northern [ __ ]
right? Keep creating the same atmosphere
every day. This fat ugly [ __ ] keep
creating the same atmosphere every day.
Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Oh my god. Disabled same people every
day. Jealous people. [ __ ] off. mad. This same self-reflectors,
bro. You're going to be lonely this
Christmas. You're going to be lonely.
What does that tell you? You're lonely this Christmas.
What does that tell you that you're
going to be single and lonely this? See,
it's the same self-reflecting with these
people every day. This is why I don't
come on here. It's the same atmosphere.
Why do you think I don't come on here,
bro? Creepy. Why do you think you do not
see me on here for two or 3 weeks? Yeah.
For two or three weeks. Because it's the
same ugly, jealous people creating the
same atmosphere. That's why I don't [ __ ]
with this. I don't want nothing to do
with it. Yeah. Out of all of the times
before, bro. All of the times [ __ ] before. Yeah.
Bro, I'm going to go and I'm gonna tell
that Lord J to put the link up, bro. I'm
gonna I'm gonna own this [ __ ] Yeah,
I'm going to own this skint [ __ ] Yeah,
I'm going to own this skint [ __ ] bro.
And I'm going to bully him, bro. Yeah,
I'm going to bully him. Yeah, this fat
[ __ ] skint [ __ ] Yeah, go tell him to
put the link up, bro. I'm coming on. I'm
coming on, bro. I'm coming on.
Yeah, it's the same [ __ ] with these
[ __ ] jealous ugly people. Ugly people
that ain't got no life.
Ugly jealous of a 28-year-old. They're
all jealous of me, a 28-year-old. All
cuz I'm younger and better looking than
them. It shows you all of what they do.
They're jealous. Yeah. Tell this [ __ ] to
put the link up. Charlotte, you Hey, one
second. You said that you got IQ. So why
are you repeating? You are the ma. See,
look. Low. You're talking about IQ, but
you're repeating again. You're repeating
again. You are the ma. You're ugly. Look
at that. I just got going to go to all
of you people, bro. [ __ ] this one. One sec.
Sorry about that, bro.
Yeah, they're boring as [ __ ] Him and
his little [ __ ] gay little virgin
followers are boring as [ __ ] bro. He
couldn't even try and talk over me cuz
he knew. He [ __ ] knew. When is him
and his little gaylord moronic followers
going to get a life? It's almost 2026.
You say you got an IQ. What? You said M
about five times. But they've got an IQ.
These people, they've got an IQ, but
they repeat the same [ __ ] every day.
Yeah. Same [ __ ] projection every day
where Bro, it's just they're [ __ ]
boring, bro. [ __ ] them. Yeah. Simple.
Just wait until one of them get doxed,
bro. Just leave it, bro. Just let them
get doxed. Simple.
[ __ ] sad bastards, bro. [ __ ] ugly.
Why are these people not coming in and
showing their faces, bro? Tell them to
come in and show their faces. Tell them
to come in and show their faces, bro.
Come on. They should join LJ J's panel
and show their faces.
I'm sending you£10. Just drop the skip.
Ma mud ma ma. Remember, these people
have got an IQ.
Don't forget, these people don't show
their faces because they're smart, by
the way, Steven Howard. Yet, they repeat
the same [ __ ] every day. But they're smart people.
But they're smart people. Remember, they
just repeat themselves for eight years.
Uh, you never had a girlfriend. I have
had a girlfriend, Joe, and she's never
been fat like your girlfriend. You're
fat, stinking, Mrs.
fat, ugly, [ __ ] stinking Mrs. And
we've all seen my [ __ ] all the women
I've been with hands. [ __ ] off you self projecting
just like that Flash account. Another
40year-old self projector. They're
they're all the same on here, bro.
They're all little 40year-old single
little muners brain dead ugly that ain't
got nothing. That's what they are. Even
Laney owns them, bro. I don't even need
to go on there, bro. I can just get
Laney on there. I can just get Laney on
there, bro. and she'll tell you about
all of them. They're fat, ugly ma
virgins. So that's probably why they're
so, you know, bro, I have had a Mrs.
Joe. And yes, your MS is fat, fat, and
ugly. And you're living in poverty.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Your MS is [ __ ] fat
and ugly, just like you. And guess what?
I'd rather have poor hygiene than be in
[ __ ] shape than be in shape than be a
fat [ __ ] like you. How are you telling
someone about their personal hygiene
when you're overweight? How is an
overweight person trying to tell someone
else about their hygiene? Does that make
sense, bro? Does that make sense? Smokey
beat. Joey's never going to have any.
I've already had more women than you,
Smokey B. You don't have a woman. You
ain't got no money. Another self
projector. Same self-protecting
comments. You've never been with a
woman. These people on here, bro,
they're virgins. I'm telling you, bro.
These people on here are virgins. They
are virgins. I'm telling you, bro.
They're fat, ugly, single virgins that
are going to be alone for Christmas. I
was already on there trips. I already I
already went on there. These fat, ugly
virgins are going to be lonely
Christmas. And it kills them. Kills
them. That's what it does, bro. It kills
them. These ugly little virgins that's
never had a girlfriend is going to be
lonely this Christmas. Yeah. Obsessed
with me, bro. These fat ugly people like
Joseph and these fat ugly misses. Two
fat ugly people obsessed with me. Him
and his misses. Yeah,
your MS is [ __ ] fat, stinking, and
ugly. Yeah, don't [ __ ] talk about me,
[ __ ] You know,
and I was on there. I was just on there
a minute ago. Triple H. Rewind it back.
Sad people. Sad people, bro. Sad [ __ ]
single little virgins. Smokey be [ __ ]
all of these people. You know, these
these little accounts are sad little moronic virgins.
Sad little virgins that ain't got a
life. Ain't got [ __ ] all just ugly looks
that sit on the internet 8 years rotting
rotten for eight years, bro. Yeah.
Do you know what I'm saying?
[ __ ] eight years rotting their ugly
lives away, bro. Eight [ __ ] years.
Imagine that. Yeah. I'm about to cry,
bro. I'm about to cry. I'm about to cry. Yeah. Yeah.
Sad, ugly people, bro. Monty came on
here earlier, by the way.
[ __ ] you get owned by a [ __ ] old woman.
[ __ ] madness, bro. [ __ ] Mongos.
>> You ain't Smokeoky Bee's never had him,
Mrs. He. He's a [ __ ] virgin. I've
been with more women than you would ever
have. You [ __ ] virgin. Don't [ __ ]
talk about, bro. You people own
yourselves. You're old. You're fat.
You're ugly. You own yourselves. I don't
need to do anything, bro. I don't need
to do anything. I don't need to do
anything. You fat, ugly virgins own
yourselves. Your life's losers. You're
the biggest life losers. And you know
what? Prove me wrong by getting off of
YouTube and not coming back on here ever
again. You people are the biggest life's
losers, lad. Yeah. Yeah. No one cares
about your self-projecting comment. See you later.
No one cares. Self-reflector.
No one cares, Virgin. No one cares.
40-year-old. No one cares about you fat ugly people.
Yeah. No one cares. You keep
self-reflecting is not going to change
the fact that you're the bully victim.
You people on here, right, are the
biggest [ __ ] Yeah. bully victims
going. 28, I have had a girlfriend. You
people are 48 and you've never had a
girlfriend. Look at yourselves,
bro. You're talking about your tragic
selves. You're talking about your own
tragic lives. You've never had a
girlfriend. That's you. You've never
even had sex. You're talking about your
tragic lives. And I agree, it is tragic.
I think it's very tragic for people in
their 40s. No woman, no life, no money,
no girlfriend. I think it's very tragic.
Your lives are tragic. And And that is
honestly the perfect word to describe
your lives. Fat, lonely, singletons on
the internet for eight years. Eight
years. And you washed up people have
been on here for eight years, right? No
girlfriend coming on here talking about
other people. But guess what, bro? Yeah.
You won't ever come and show your face
cuz you're ugly. You're you're you're
actual victims. You people are bully
victims. Not online in real life. You're
the you're the well and truly bully
victims. You've come on here for eight
years. Yeah. Self-reflecting your life
away. And you still don't have money.
You still don't have a girlfriend.
You're still lonely. Your family still
hate you. Bro, what are you doing with
your lives? You, bro, I will tell you.
Yes. When you show us your girlfriend
and you show us your face, I will tell
you about my life. Yeah, when you show
us your girlfriend and you show us your
ugly, funny looks, you can ask me about
my life. Until then, see you later. Self-reflector.
You know, I've had more girls than you
again. Self-reflector. You people don't
have a girlfriend. Why are you
40year-old ugly people talking about
women when you've never been with a
woman? Why are you ugly people that
don't have a girlfriend keep telling a
28-year-old they don't have a
girlfriend? Bro, bro, bro, why are you
people in your 40s that don't have a
girlfriend, don't have a woman, keep
talking about other people never having a woman?
You know, bro, you don't have a
girlfriend. Why does it keep going back
on to me? It's not Listen, bro. Listen.
No matter what you try to say about me,
it's not going to change that you are
single, ugly, 40 year olds. You can call
me this. You can call me that. You can
call me this. It's not going to change
the fact that you are fat, stinking,
ugly people. You can say it until the
cows come home. It's not going to change
the fact that I'm younger and better
looking than you. Your words are not
going to change the fact that your lives
are over. 40year-old hopeless people.
That and it's you can say whatever you
want. It's not going to change that. You
know, fat ugly losers in their 40s with
no girlfriend trying to talk about a
28-year-old. No job, no money, no
future, trying to talk about a 28year-old
whilst you're in your 40s, an absolute
loser. What? So, am I supposed to look
up to you people? Okay. Okay. Okay.
Let's Let's just say that a 28-year-old
Yeah. has hope. How am I going to get
hope from a bunch of 40year-old skint
ugly people that can't get off the
internet? Ugly self-reflected single
people. How are you going to give me
[ __ ] hope, bro? How you're supposed
to be something to look up to,
[ __ ] little [ __ ]
That's what I mean, bro. [ __ ]
retards. See you later, [ __ ] Go
[ __ ] go and [ __ ] self-reflect on
another channel, [ __ ] loser. self-reflecting people
and they're not Triple H. I I tell you
why they're doing it. Cuz it's Christmas soon, bro.
It's Christmas soon.
It's Christmas soon. So, they'll calm
down in January, bro. They'll calm down
in January. But it's Christmas soon. And
you know what Christmas means, right? Right.
These people are going to be alone
Christmas with no family. And they know
this. And they know this, bro. They're
going to be alone with no family
Christmas. It's that time of year.
People go mental. Just leave them, bro.
You know, and Joseph Ferrar, I'm more
than happy to meet you anywhere you
want. And I'm willing to call your
bluff. I am willing to call your bluff.
So, you know, I'm I'm really really
really really really
I'm willing to call your [ __ ] bluff.
Yeah. And and we'll see who won't show
up. And if you're not going to if you're
not going to escalate it, shut your
mouth. Simple. They do this every year around December.
Every year in December, these people do
this. Every year in December, these
people, these sad, lonely people with no
family, with no girlfriend do this. They
do this every December because they
ain't got no family. And you do, bro.
The community is dead. Do you not
understand? any other month no one comes
on here you will see that no one comes
do you understand like no one comes on
here like normal month December these
people are very lonely they got no
family they got no girlfriend so they're
full of hate they're full of hate
they're full of jealousy
there 40 year olds that taking their
[ __ ] ugly virgin lives out on other
people and they're going to be lonely
Christmas they're not going to stop bro
these people will never stop
never had anxiety in my life Joe okay
Joe I'll meet you anywhere you want. Why
are you avoiding the question? You're
saying that I've got anxiety, bro. You
can't even come on the Hangouts and
talk. Let's not talk about anxiety, bro.
Yeah, let's not talk about anxiety, bro.
The only one that's got anxiety is you.
You can't even come and talk on a panel,
Mr. Anxiety. You're scared of your own
voice. You're scared of your own voice.
Just like Lord Jay, you're full of anxiety, bro.
Yeah. They do it every December. Every
December. Every December. They do it
every December, bro. Yeah.
Because they're lonely people that ain't
got nothing. They know deep down you're
younger and better looking than them and
it kills them. These people, listen,
forget me for a second. Yeah. Forget
what I am, bro. Look at what these
people are. Look at what these people
are. Past 40, ugly as [ __ ] can't leave
the house, no money, and they want to
talk about me, bro. And they want to
talk about me. This Joseph Ra, this fat
nonsloving [ __ ] and I will say it to
his face, he won't even come in the
panel and talk.
He won't even talk because he's so much
of a [ __ ] with a downy voice. He's so
much of a [ __ ] And he won't meet me
either. I've said multiple times I will
meet him and he won't meet me. He won't
meet me. So, who's the one that's really
got anxiety when I'm willing to travel
300 miles and you're not and you're not
meeting me? You nonloving,
povertyridden, [ __ ] next genes. Next
genes. I actually can't believe
I have been in a relationship. I can't
believe you people are 40 and you've got
no girlfriend and you got no money.
I can't believe that you people in your
40s and you've never had sex. That's
tragic, bro. I know. Your life in your
40s, no girlfriend. 48, though. It's not
28. It's 48 with you people. You people
are 48 and you've never had a girlfriend
and you've never had sex. I can't believe that.
You know what I mean? But yeah, Joseph,
you will never ever meet me. You fat
povertyridden [ __ ] Keep going on
about your shitty little pension. Your
shitty little pension that you can't
touch and tell try to tell other people
that they live they're living under
[ __ ] poverty, bro. Yeah.
Joseph, worry about you, your fat
misses, your next gen, your 200lb phone.
Worry about your poverty life that
you're living before you try talking
about other people. Yeah, simple, bro.
Bro, join the group. But the thing is,
Smokey B, you can join all of these
groups all you want, but you're never
going to meet anyone. You and Joseph Ro
is never going to meet anyone. You
little lowlife ugly people that are
single are never going to meet anyone.
You want to join a group. How about
Smokey? You go get laid and go get a
woman and go get yourself some money, bro.
Bro, I've got more. You don't know how
much money I've got, bro. You've never
had Listen, bro. You've got You don't
even have 20 to your name. Worry about
your own 40year-old virgin life. Sado.
Lonely at Christmas. lonely at
Christmas. How does it feel, right? That
you people are going to be lonely at
Christmas. How does that make you feel?
How does that make you feel that you
people, your family hate you and you're
going to be lonely at Christmas? Lonely
at Christmas. How does that make you
feel? All alone at Christmas. Unloved
little victims. How does it feel? Yeah.
How does it feel that you fat, ugly
little victims are going to be alone at
Christmas? Mr. Lonely, how does that
make you feel? Projecting? Nope, that's
not me projecting. I've got my mom. I've
got my sister. Nope. I'm definitely
talking about you fat ugly people. I'm
definitely talking about you fat ugly
people. And you won't show your faces
either. You will not show your faces cuz
you're ugly. Let's see how many of these
people can show their face.
Make it make sense. I am making it make
sense. You're fat, ugly. You can't show
your face. You're going to be lonely on
Christmas. I'm making it make sense.
Ugly boy. Come and show us your face.
Let Let us laugh at your ugly looks. You
ugly little virgin that's going to be
lonely Christmas. A man in his 40s that
is single is trying to talk about a 28-year-old.
Bro, you you do need a girlfriend.
You're 48 and you've never had a
girlfriend. You need to get laid as
well. It must be hard being 48 and still
being a virgin. 48 years of age and
you're still a virgin on YouTube. You've
been on YouTube for eight years. You've
been on YouTube for eight years and
you've never had a girlfriend at 48. I
know. It's bad, isn't it? It's bad. But
the thing is, you keep getting the age
wrong. It's not 28. It's 48. You people
are not 28. You wish you was 28. No, no,
no. The thing is with you people, you
wish you was 28, but you're not. You're
48. You're fat. You're ugly. You're
wrinkly. You got no job. You got no
girlfriend. I'm ripping into you. All of
you people on here right now, you're not
28, you're 48, and your lives are over.
Fat, ugly, skinned, and single. Yeah,
I'm telling you, I I will prove your
40s. Come on. Come on the camera. Come
on the camera right now. You come on the
camera right now, bro. Okay, I'll prove
it. Come on the camera right now. Come
on link right now. Put your camera up.
Put your camera on. Put your camera on.
Put your camera on. Come on. You one of
you people commenting right now and
showing me that you're good-look. I'll
prove you're in your 40s. Join the link
and put your camera on. I will prove
that you're in your 40s. You're ugly. No
girlfriend, ugly face, and you're going
to be lonely Christmas. I'll prove it.
Exactly. Cuz you're ugly.
Woo! Proved it. The ugly 40 8-year-old
backs down. Same [ __ ] every time of year
with you lonely people around Christmas.
Bro, I'm 28 and I've been seen with
women. Prove that I've never been with a
woman. I can prove that you're 40 and
you're ugly. That's why you won't put
your camera on.
You can't prove anything cuz you're
ugly. You're ugly m. You're an ugly
bully victim and you won't do nothing
about it. You can't come on your camera
and show me what you look like, bro.
Because you're [ __ ] ugly. Back down.
You won't put your cameras on cuz you're
ugly. Ugly 40year-old won't come on
camera. The ugly bun won't come on
camera. This is why you must love saying
bunter cuz you are the bunters. You are
the alltime bunters. The all time
bunters. None of these people will come
on here and show their faces. Because
they're [ __ ] ugly. Imagine someone
having one over that rock. Listen.
Listen. I told you right now, bro. Yeah.
I've told you right now, bro. Yeah. If I
went on another community talking about
people's looks, I wouldn't be making
excuses why I can't show my face. You
won't show your faces cuz you're ugly
and you need to swallow that pill, you
know, because I do care. I do care. I
[ __ ] do care, bro. You people won't
show your faces cuz you're fat and ugly.
Stop trying to cover up, bro. You in
your 40s, no girlfriend, no money. Stop
coming on here around December just cuz
you got no family. Just because I'm
younger than you and I'm better looking
than you. Just because you've got no
family, you sad lonely people. You
moronic sad sad lonely people on
YouTube. Why don't you do yourself a
[ __ ] favor, bro? Get off of YouTube.
Get laid. Stop being skint. Get your own
money to look at and then and then
you'll be set. You'll be set. You know,
coming on YouTube in your 40s. Yeah.
It's [ __ ] ugly as [ __ ] trying to talk
about a 28-year-old who's better looking
than you. You people really really need
to get a life on here, bro. You won't
come on cab because you're [ __ ] ugly.
That's why you won't fat ugly people
with no family. And you know what I'm
saying is the truth. Every December.
This is every December with these fat
ugly people that have got no family.
Every [ __ ] December Trip H last year
they done it. They done it the year
before that. Yeah. every December with
these fat, ugly, familyless losers. With
these familyless losers every [ __ ]
December with these people, you know,
we're not with self-reflected on to be.
You come on your you come on the link
and show us your face. Show us that
you're not faulty and you're not ugly.
Tell show everybody that I'm wrong about
what I'm saying about you. Come on.
Come on. Come on, you little
self-reflector. Show you're not fat and
ugly. I'll put the link up again. And
until you come on here, I'm not
answering any more of your questions.
[ __ ] [ __ ] We're not answering your
little self-reflecting questions. Come
on the hangouts, you. Yeah. Come on, you
little self-reflector. [ __ ]
familyless loser. Yeah. Every December,
you generous people around Christmas
time do this. Every [ __ ] December,
you do it.
Come on out and prove you're not a fat
ugly manta or I'm banning you. Simple.
Yeah, that's it. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Women hate you as well. That's why
you're still a virgin. If you wanted a
question answered, come on then and put
your camera on. What are you scared of?
What are you scared of? What are you
scared of? Come on.
Come on right now and put your and show
us your face. And Joseph, come on here
and talk. I don't even want to see your
face. I just want you to talk. But you
can't even talk. Yeah, you can't even
Every year with you people, you do this, bro.
Right. And you're banned. Self projecting again.
See you. Self-reflecting again. Self-reflecting.
Self-reflecting. Low life people. The
people that have got no family. You know
what? We should do We should do a video
on this, bro. We should actually do a
video on this, you know?
You know, these people have got no
family. It's so obvious. It's so
obvious. These people have got no
family. It's so obvious, bro. It is so
You know, Smokeoky B is another one.
He's got no family. Just an ugly little
keyboard warrior. He was doing this last
summer as well. He's another little ugly
skit keyboard warrior with no family.
They're all the same on here. This is
what I'm saying. They are literally they
are all the same on here, bro.
All of these ugly old people with no
family. Do you know what we we need to
make a name for these people? Like one,
two, three, bro. Just like send it fat,
wrinkly people with no family. That's
what we need to do, bro, with these
people, bro. We need to think of like
three words to say,
you know? They got nothing. They got
nothing in their lives. Look, bro. Are
these people supposed to have families
and jobs? Sat on YouTube typing away.
They're [ __ ] ugly.
Why won't any of these people come on
here, bro? They won't come on here. Why?
You know, these people have got no
family. Look at them typing away. I know
it. Laney knows it. Everyone knows it.
Sad, fat, ugly people. Ain't got no life.
Ain't got no [ __ ] life, man.
These people have got no family, bro.
These people really have got no family. Every December, every December,
they preach. Every December, these
people do this. Every December.
Every December they do this, bro. Every December.
Have you not noticed that?
Family just losers.
Ain't got nothing. Anyways, [ __ ] these
people. I've got all of these people
right that are middle age obsessed with
me, but apparently they're not jealous
of me. All of these people that are
middle age obsessed with me, but they're
not jealous. Don't forget these people
are not jealous. Don't forget, Stephen H.
These people are not jealous. They're
not jealous at all, bro. They just waste
all their lives. Yeah. On me. But
they're not jealous. Remember that.
They're not jealous.
[ __ ] weirdos on here, bro. They are [ __ ] weirdos.
>> They're [ __ ] weirdos on here, man.
>> I said get in and bangers in the band.
Me and that Jimmy Jazz is a [ __ ]
disabled m as well.
>> Yeah, I was in there. You didn't listen,
did you? Nah, D couldn't find it going
to go all the way back. Take take too long, man.
>> Yeah, they're [ __ ] sados, bro. Sados, man.
>> I don't agree on a lot of things, but
you're right about that. It's about this
time every year they do this.
>> Yeah, it is December. It is. It's about
It's like mid December. Have you not noticed it?
>> Yeah, I remember it last year. It was
the same [ __ ] last year. Why not?
>> And the year before. And the year
>> What happens?
>> And that Joseph Ferrar. I said to that
Joseph for I'd meet him. And I'm being
serious, bro. I will meet him. But he
won't meet me.
>> Nafar's all right. Lad.
>> No, he's not. He's a little dick. He's a dick sucker.
>> Triple H. Did you have a girlfriend by
the time you was 28? Listen, go away,
self-reflector. You don't have a
girlfriend, bro. I've banned about 20
accounts today, you know.
>> Oh, Steven Jazz is dingle,
>> bro. You know, I've banned about 20
accounts. Steven, sorry, mate.
>> I've banned about 20 accounts today. You
know that? of the same people.
>> I'm just the same people.
>> What? Just constantly making different accounts all
>> making different accounts just to get banned.
>> This is what they do this time.
>> It's [ __ ] But they say that they're not
jealous and they've got good lives.
>> They've got nothing in life, lad.
>> They've got good lives, but they make
accounts just to get banned 20 times.
>> That if that doesn't that's all, lad. Don't know.
>> Yeah, just to get banned again. Sad.
>> Could you be asked doing that? Like that
was that's got nothing going for them.
>> Nothing. And and they Yeah, they've got
nothing going for themselves. It's so obvious, bro.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Did you hear Monty and Timmy earlier?
>> I No, I wasn't on earlier, mate.
>> They were arguing.
>> What on your panel? >> Yeah.
>> What about this [ __ ]
>> Yeah, it's always the same [ __ ] though, isn't it?
>> Yeah, it's a shame, man. It's always the
same [ __ ] with Timmy and that. And then
hopefully in 2026 it will be different in it.
>> I don't know why you say that. You say
this every year. Let's just continue on
through the next
>> because they say that they're smart.
They say that they're smart. They say
that they're smart people, right? So if
they're smart, why are they repeating
every day then?
>> They're not smart. They're low IQ people.
>> They say that other people's low IQ, but
they keep repeating.
>> They do. That's all they can do because
they've got no they've got nothing going
on for them, lad.
>> Nothing. What? Not even at Smoky B.
>> I don't know who he is. L.
>> You've seen it though, ain't it?
>> I've seen him floating about in that.
Yeah, but I don't know. Like
>> these people are [ __ ] sad, bro.
>> [ __ ] It's mad on here, lad. Mad.
>> Yeah, but you like it, isn't it?
>> I agree. I don't like it. I think it's
>> What do you What do you think the
definition of poverty is?
>> Poverty is [ __ ] when you haven't got
[ __ ] like Well, I wouldn't say that
anyway. I was going to say anyone got
mouth, but like when you name up on the
bones of your ass and you're struggling,
that that's poverty in my eyes. Like
>> cuz Joseph's trying to say that I'm
poverty when I literally have more money than him.
>> Yeah, but you've got to understand that
Joseph works and he's got that pension.
He's doing well for himself. Good on the lad.
>> He doesn't know how much money people
have and he keeps making posts.
>> Yeah, but he's clearly got more money
than [ __ ] you, hasn't he?
>> Listen, listen, Joe. Yeah, listen,
listen, Joe. Yeah. Hands of a fat man.
Yes, that is hands of a fat man, bro. Oh
my god, bro. Look at them fingers.
Listen, listen, listen, listen, listen,
listen, listen. One second. One second.
I'll show you my fingers. Right. This is
Yeah, that is hand Why does
>> Look, look how skinny my fingers are.
Look at my fingers. Look how skinny they
are. Look at your fingers, Joseph. Look
at them [ __ ] cumbling sausage
fingers. There's no vein. When you can't
see someone's vein on their hands,
they're fat. Do Do you know that? Do do
you know that, Joseph? Uh, do you know
that your bra?
>> I know what you're saying, but it
doesn't matter if his hands or fingers
are fat at the end of the day.
>> Literally, bro, if you got fat fingers
and you can't see someone's vein on
their hands, they're fat. Joseph, how
about this? Right. Are you getting
confident now? Are you getting confident
now, are you? Why don't you come and
hang out and talk to us, me and Triple? >> Yeah.
>> Why don't you have a conversation with
us? Come on.
>> You're not scared of your own voice, are you?
This is what these cowards are like. He
can't, bro. He can't even talk on a
panel for [ __ ] sake. You know what I mean?
>> And that Jimmy Jazz is always in that
bangers. He's got no life either. Has he?
>> They ain't got a life. These people
>> Oh, you live in So if I come to
Yorkshire, if I come to Leeds, are you
going to meet me then, Joe? Yeah. Are
you going to meet me?
Yeah, that is definitely hands of a fat
man. Definitely hands of a fat man. That
is definitely hands of a fat man, bro.
And I'm not even just saying that, bro.
Look at your fingers. [ __ ] look at my
fingers compared to your fingers. And
yes, I bite my nails because I've got a
habit of biting my nails. I don't have
anxiety like you and LJ.
>> This YouTube's mental.
>> It is. I bite I've always bit my nails.
Yeah, exactly. Cuz you know, bro, you
would never say anything to my face.
Just like nonslegs. You lot on here
would never say anything to anyone's
face and you know it. Yeah. Anxiety. You
have got anxiety. I don't have anxiety,
mate. I've been up and down the country.
I've traveled. I don't have anxiety. You
do, though. Yeah. Yeah. You've got
anxiety. Not me, though. Definitely.
Definitely. Definitely not me. You do, though.
You definitely do.
>> No, you definitely got anxiety. Just
like all of the other people's all got anxiety. >> Mike,
>> here we go. This is the 25th.
How many accounts now? 26th account
that's been banned. Is this the same?
>> These people are not jealous and they've
got a good life. 25th account that's been banned.
>> What? From the same person. >> Yep.
>> That's [ __ ] mental.
>> But don't forget, they're not jealous
and they've got a better life than me.
They just make accounts to get banned.
>> Yeah. Just one of them things, is it?
>> It's that time of year again, though,
PJ. Like, they do this
>> every December, bro. Every [ __ ] December.
Every December these lonely people do this
>> because you actually think these people
have got family, bro. No,
>> they can't. I've done stuff like this. No way.
>> No way. No way. What? What? Bro, why are
you asking Triple H? Yeah, to talk some
sense into me. What are we actually
jealous of? It's been explained to you
multiple mult I Triple H I generally
think these people do this cuz they're jealous.
Yeah, but that Joe's gotten out to be
jealous of you about as he's Are you
just triggered by Joe a lot and I don't
know why actually to be honest because you
>> I'm speaking generally they're jealous.
>> A lot of people are say they are. Yeah.
They've got like nothing going for them.
All they've got in life is YouTube.
They've got no family. But
>> obviously those I'm younger than you.
I'm better looking than you.
>> He's that Terry B.
>> See look it's the same people and and
and this is why I'm saying it's Genesis
Triple H because you've got all of these
middle-aged people that won't leave you
alone. It screams jealousy. I don't
think anything of myself, bro. But when
they keep doing this, this is why I'm
thinking it, you know.
>> All right. All right.
>> Like this, Terry. Look, the guy's ran
away from me. This guy ran away from me
and he's still coming back for more.
They will not leave you alone. This is
why I think they're jealous of me. This
is what I'm saying, bro.
>> Is that Terry trying to get in?
>> No. He's telling people to meet him when
he didn't show up last time. It's the
same [ __ ] And you're thinking to
yourself, hold on. If these people have
got a life, would they stop doing what
they're doing? But they don't.
>> Yeah. You'd think they'd give it up,
lad, wouldn't you? But
>> why didn't you meet Ghosting? Ghosting
didn't meet me. >> Yeah.
>> He didn't come last again. I'm not
explaining myself. We all He was
supposed to come Saturday and he didn't.
>> That's true, Joe. He was meant to make a
video, but he never made.
>> But the thing is with Joseph, he's a
[ __ ] He's biased. He done the
same thing with nonslegs. He's a biased
[ __ ] That's why I said I will
meet him anyway. I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
He's a biased little [ __ ] They
are jealous. He's been I'm coming up
soon anyways, bro.
>> So that's that in it. End of
>> cuz it's pathetic now, bro. It's pathetic.
>> That Terry lad,
>> you know, I went to this Terry's area
and he didn't show up and he's still
coming back for more. This is what I'm
trying to say to you, bro. Even when
these people take L's, yeah,
>> they will still come back for more and
they will not stop. This is what I'm
saying. Very true. Greasy. Yeah, that's
what I've just explain, mate. Yeah,
>> that's it.
But go to Roy. He's a dick sucker. He
loves nonslegs. He's a [ __ ] He's
a [ __ ] [ __ ] If you see, but
he's he's constantly sucking his dick
every time I'm going at him. And I told
him I'll say it to your face and he
won't beat me.
>> Oh, you'll get on with that, John. Does he?
>> He is a [ __ ] [ __ ] The amount
of times I have gone at him and he's
gone to up his ass, right, and said,
"Dude, he got a girlfriend. You know, he
got a girlfriend." There's been two
people today, bro, that that took L's
that come on my life. No one said
anything about it.
>> Listen, there's no explaining anything
to you. I went to your area and you did
not come out. You're a waste of my time, [ __ ] idiot.
Oh yeah. You didn't see that though, did
you Joe? No. You don't see things that
don't suit yourself, do you? Nah. Nah.
>> Yeah. But
>> just like you didn't see when I went to
Liverpool and Kevin didn't show up.
Yeah. You didn't see that either. Nah,
of course you didn't. Nah.
>> Now, now Joe knows he let it be though.
Like he knows the crack now. Like go.
>> It's like this Terry. Yeah. I went to
this Terry Z and he didn't come out. No
one says anything about it. They're a
waste of time. These losers are a waste
of energy. They're a waste of time, bro.
You don't understand.
>> Yeah, man. Yeah,
>> bro. I went to this Terry's area and he
literally did not come out. The same
thing with Mark Samson. They were waste of time.
>> I've seen the video when you called him
around the corner, but he wouldn't have
out, would he?
>> No, he wouldn't. No,
>> I've seen that, lad.
>> He didn't come out. This was what I
think it was two years. Was it two years ago?
>> Yeah, it was a couple of year back now.
years and a guy would not come out of
his house and he's still coming back
acting like he's one
>> they do this to get a reaction out here
you do know that don't you
>> but even if you don't react to them they
they will still do it they're still
going to do it they will still do it
whether you react or you don't
>> so I don't understand it when people say
that because even if you don't react
they will still do it
>> so it's not a reaction bro it's not I
don't think it is
>> they can't have any life can they fuel
you lad No, they don't. Because listen,
bro, if I'm This is what I'm saying to
you, bro. Yeah. I could stop going live,
post videos, not go on anyone's channel.
I could go back on their channel in two
years time and they'd be doing the same old [ __ ]
I watched that video, Terry. Um, there
was a bit of a scuffle in that, wasn't
there? Then he called you around that
the corner or something. I seen him
point down there, but you didn't want to, lad.
>> Yeah. [ __ ] knows, bro. And if you and if
PJ wasn't the wrong I'd say a lot. But I seen
>> people just need to [ __ ] get a life,
bro, at this point, you know?
>> Yeah. They need to [ __ ] they need to
sort theelves out, man. Like they've
been doing this.
>> It's almost 2026.
>> Yeah. It'll go on another [ __ ] It'll
go on years and years, man. This is
never going to end. Yeah.
>> So what when Lord So when Lord Jes on on
the first of January, we'll be the same people.
>> The same folk will be in. Yeah. You know it.
>> Writing the same comments.
>> Writing the same [ __ ] Yeah. Lonely
Pete. Um, no Christmas dinner. All just
all the same shitless.
>> Oh, Jesus Christ, bro. It's funny. It's
>> And it's the same new year, new me,
don't they're all bollocks. But
>> BJ, your life has been declined for
years and it's all because of YouTube.
But the thing is, Monty's life got
ruined over YouTube. Mine never. Is that right, Triple?
>> Say that again.
>> Monty's life got ruined over YouTube,
but mine didn't, did it?
>> Yeah. Yours has been ruined. You've had
posters. You've had people die. You've
had your mom and dad's wounded. You mean
lost his kids?
>> Say that again.
>> Yeah, but Monty lost his kids, isn't it?
>> What does Kevin Murphy mean? Pot noodle pizza.
>> Oh, he's just a self projector. He's
another one that didn't show up when I
went to Liverpool.
>> That Kev's all right though, is he?
>> No, he's [ __ ] He's a [ __ ] mug.
>> I went to Liverpool. The guy didn't show
up and he's still coming back like he's won
>> and no one says anything.
>> I didn't lose money over you people on
YouTube. No, I did not. I did not lose
money over you people. No, I did not.
>> Definitely definitely did not lose
money. You people have got no effects on
me whatsoever. I remain unbothered and
I've never lost money because if I lost
money over you people, I would have
killed one of you. So, stop saying that,
mate. You You don't even believe what
you're saying. You didn't stop my money.
You didn't stop my income. Believe you
me, you did not. And this is the last
time I'm going to explain this. You did
not stop any of my money. I've still got
more money than you. I don't need to
shop at Next. I'm going to explain this
again to you because you don't seem to
understand when someone's explaining
stuff to you. Bro, you people have never
made me lose money. The only person that
tried to make me lose money was Nons.
And I went to his area and I was and I
almost got him killed.
>> Yeah. You would never stop my money,
bro. Cuz I would have got one of you
people. Trust me.
>> Yeah. Joseph, we're not like you. We're
not like you, bro. some little [ __ ]
that can't talk on a [ __ ] hangout.
Yeah. If any of you's stopped my money,
what are you would be getting shattered
in your face, bro? Trust me. Yeah.
>> But it shouldn't matter.
Even if Joe goes to next at the end of
the day, he's got plenty of money and he
can you went out and bought 200 pound
pair of jeans. He could do that. He got
500 pair of jeans cuz he works. He
>> Yeah, he can do what I'm saying. But you
know, how can someone be Why is why why
is he bothered about what people get?
So yeah, Joe, you people have never made
me lose, buddy. Never in your in your
dreams. You did. I've still got more
money than you on here. I've still got
more money than you. And you're still
talking [ __ ] bro. This Joseph, right,
does not know how much money people
have. I don't know what it is with these
people on here, but they keep thinking
they know what money people have. And I
don't know why.
>> Yeah. What's Kevin?
>> I told them I got more money than you.
I've got money. And it doesn't sink in
their thick brain. It doesn't sink in
their thick fat brain, bro. You know
what I mean? had a pot noodle last
Christmas at skin.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
>> [ __ ] mental.
>> I'm not eating today. I'm not skin. I'm
>> You know, I'm not eating today. I'm not
skin. I just can't be bothered.
You know, Terry, listen. When you come
on my Listen, do you want me to Right.
Hold on, Terry. Right. How about you
come outside my mom's door right now and
I'll pay for your Uber? You know,
>> bro, it doesn't matter about 3K a month.
I've got more money than you. Don't
worry about what I've got. Don't you
worry about what I've got. Yeah, it
didn't. It didn't f Bro, I've still got
more money than you. I've got more money
than you. I don't know how many times I
have to keep explaining, Joe. I've got
more money than you. I can do what I
want when I want. I don't know how many
times I have to keep explaining, don't
worry about three grand a month. I've
got more money than you. That's all you
need to know.
I've got more money than you. 3K a
month, £200 a month, whatever [ __ ]
money I get, bro. I've got more money
than you. Let that sink in. I can do
what I want. Yeah.
>> Yeah. And you didn't stop the sublet,
buddy. [ __ ] the sublet. I got more than
you. Let's talk. Let's talk presents
right now, bro. Yeah. Simple idiot.
>> I wouldn't let it bother you, bro. Just
let them [ __ ] say what it is.
>> I'm coming off here. I'm sick of these
selfrelecting people. I'm coming off
here, bro. I am definitely coming off
here. Yeah, I'm definitely definitely
definitely coming off here, bro. I
really am. You know, because you know
the thing is, bro, if I ever find out
where one of these people live, I'm
boxing them in their face. I'm boxing
them in their face, bro. It's not just
YouTube to me. I'll box them in their
face. I don't care.
>> Don't worry about me, Joe. I'm younger
than you. I can go out whenever I want.
I can drink.
>> Yeah. Simple, bro. I'm not some fat old
man showing my pension like you. Yeah.
Your life has fell apart. You're showing a pension.
Yeah. Yeah. Nonsle showed his daddy's
money that he can't show now. Don't you
worry about that. Yeah. Nonsle showed
his daddy's money. Yeah. Guess what? I
showed you seven grand and I made you
all run away. Don't worry about your
boyfriend on legs.
>> Don't worry about your boyfriend's dick
you like to suck. Don't worry about that, bro.
>> Don't worry about what what daddy's
money that he showed. Yeah.
We're not sucking his dick. If you want
to suck his dick, you know where his
channel is, you little [ __ ]
>> Yeah, Greavesy. I've seen that through
King show a few quid to be honest. King
showed the most amount of money.
>> [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> That's £13,000.
Where's his 13 grand now? Same thing,
Jim. Where's his 13 grand? Where's his >> Fing.
>> No. No. Joseph. Joseph. Okay. Where's
his 13 grand?
>> You will never have that again. I've got
that buddy. You don't know how much
money I've got. I've got more money than
you. I can go out when I want. Isn't it
funny how you come on here, right? One
second, Triple H. Yeah. Isn't it funny
how you say I won't have this, but I've
got a better life than you when I go
out. Isn't it funny how I can afford to
go out and do what I want that you are
the ones that sat on YouTube and you
can't do nothing?
Do you not find that a bit weird, bro?
Come on. You will never see two grand
again. I've already got two grand. Try
again. You don't know how much money I
have. This is what I'm saying. Triple H.
They don't know what people have. They
don't know what people have. This is
what I'm saying, bro.
>> Guess where it
>> You know what I mean? Huh? They They do
not know people's lives. This is what
I'm trying to say, bro. I had someone,
right? What was that? I think about two
months. I think it was about 2 three
months ago. You can't afford to go out
every week. You can't afford to go out
every week. Bro, I can go out every day
if I wanted to, bro. Every day if I
wanted to. Prove it. I'm not I don't
need to prove myself to you ugly people.
You prove that you're not fat and ugly
and I'll get the money out. Yeah. Same
thing. Yeah. Simple. You prove that
you've got money and good looks and then
come back to me. Then you can come back
to me and then ask me to start proving
stuff. That Kevin Murphy's going in
hard, lad. I thought you and him used to
get on. All right.
>> You know what I'm saying, bro? Joseph,
don't worry about my life. I got more
money than you. I'm not going to be
starving, bro. Yeah, I've got no money.
Why don't you come in and show us your
money then? Why don't you come in and
show us your money then? Listen, why
don't you come in and show us your money
then, you fat ugly [ __ ] Show us your
face and show us your money. Come on.
Prove it. Prove it. Same thing to you.
>> Yeah, bro. Same thing to you, bro. Prove
it. Prove it. Show your girlfriend. Show
your money. Show you're not a
self-reflector. Prove it. Prove it. Come
on. Come on. Prove you got a bird. Show
us your money. Prove you're not a
self-reflecting ugly bastard.
>> Self-reflecting ugly bastard. Bro,
>> it's not just PDU, does it? Grieves that
they all do it. They all want to show
each other money and that. I I
>> Bro, prove you got a girlfriend. Show
you're not a 40-year-old virgin
self-reflector. Bro, Jack, listen, bro.
It's that's you never had a bird, no
money. That's your life. That's your
ugly people's lives on there, bro.
>> That's your ugly lives. It's true about
your ugly lives with no family. How does
it make you feel that Christmas you're
going to be sat there with no family and
no money? No family. Isn't that funny,
bro? Isn't that nice?
>> Isn't that nice, bro? Come on.
>> Yes, Smokey B. You are skin. It's not
let me let you in for a reason.
>> And Smoky B, you are skinned. You live
in Milton Kees. You are skinned.
>> You have money. I've got more money than
you. I've had more girlfriends than you
will ever have. You can't even come in
hangouts and show your face.
>> Yeah. You can't even come in and show
your face cuz you're [ __ ] ugly.
>> And you're letting me say that to you
and you're you're not doing anything
about it. You're not doing anything
about it, bro. You got no girlfriend, no
money, no family, a 40-year-old lonely
[ __ ] with no girlfriend trying to talk
about a 28-year-old every December, bro.
Every December with you single virgins
with no girlfriend. I know it hits a
nerve, but it's the truth, though. It's
the truth. It's the truth. It's the
truth. You don't have £25. You got no
family and no money. You get your
benefit payment next month. Debbie, I
have had a girlfriend. Like I said, come
on my front door right now then. Come on
my door now, [ __ ] boy. I'm gonna start
talking about this guy's kids, bro. If
he if he does not come out, bro. Listen.
Listen, Terry. Terry. Terry. Come on my
front door now and I'll pay for your
Uber. Come on. Come on. You ugly man
with ugly trainers with ugly kids that
you touch up. Come on. Come on. Stop
touching up your kids and come on now.
Right. Stop touching up your kids and
come on my front door now. Right. You
know where I live. You know where I live
and I'm talking about your kids. Yeah.
I'm talking about your kids. Stop
touching up your kids and be a man and
come on my front door. Stop touching up
your children for one second and come on
my front door. Yeah, come on my front
door, bro. Come on. Come on. Come on my
front door. You know where I live. Stop
typing and come on, bro. Come on. Come
on. Come on.
Joseph, you can't even come in the
hangouts and talk, you fat [ __ ] Yeah.
Shut the [ __ ] up, you fat northern
Yorkshire [ __ ] Shut the [ __ ] up. Yeah,
shut the [ __ ] up, you fat northern
[ __ ] You can't even come in here and
talk, you [ __ ] You little [ __ ] boy.
Yeah, you can't even do anything to
anyone's [ __ ] face.
anyone's [ __ ] face. Listen, Joseph,
you are a [ __ ] You can't even come and
talk, you [ __ ] Northern ugly [ __ ] and
your fat misses. Maybe you should
actually get your fat misses on here.
Yeah. And then she could actually talk.
Trying to call me a [ __ ] bro. Trying
to call me a [ __ ] [ __ ] You can't
even talk, you little poverty winner
man. You're scared of your own voice.
Yeah, you're scared of your own [ __ ]
voice, bro. You [ __ ] poverty
northerner. Next jeans. Next jeans.
Poverty Pete doesn't wear next jeans or
has a 200lb phone. Only Poverty Joe has
that. Only Poverty Joe with the fat
misses has a 200 phone. Not Poverty
Pete. Because Poverty Pete is not
Poverty Pete. Pete has got more money
than you. More money than you will ever
have. Yeah, more money than you will
ever have. I'm not with 200 pound jeans.
I've got 200 pound phone. My jeans cost
more than your phone. I'm not poverty
Pete. I'm poverty Joseph. 200 phone.
[ __ ] 40 jeans.
200 jeans. 200 jeans. [ __ ] wreck your
whole [ __ ] thing, bro. Really,
Joseph? You would know about being
poverty, bro. You'd know about being
poverty. Poverty Pete. £300 phone, 40
jeans, hardly been to any countries and
there's got nothing. You're the
definition of poverty, bro. You're the
definition of poverty. You got 40 jeans,
you got a £300 phone, you're going to
molum in the [ __ ] winter. You would
know all about poverty.
You would know all about that poverty
life, bro. That's the life you're
living. That's the life that you're
living. And I still got more money than
you. How mad is that? [ __ ] self-reflector.
I'm off after today. Anyways,
you know, bro, Joseph Ferrar, you know
all about poverty. You're living that
poverty life, bro. You're living that
poverty life. You're living that poverty
poverty life. 40 jeans, 300 pound phone.
You're living that poverty life. You
know all about Bro, I'd rather not have
sex with a fat ugly bunter. I'd rather
not [ __ ] I have never been with a woman
so fat and ugly in my life as your Mrs.
Poverty Joe. But then again, you haven't
been able to afford to go out when you
was younger going out and meeting
people. How does it feel though that
I've got more life experiences than you? You know,
you would know about poverty. That's the
poverty life that you're living.
Pension, Mr. Pension Boy. Joe, the
pension boy with Next Jeans is trying to
talk about other people. You know all
about poverty. That's your life. That's
your life, bro. That's your life.
Poverty Joe. Poverty Joe. Joe, I have
poverty. You would know all about it,
bro. You would know all about poverty.
40 jeans, 300 phone. You know all about
poverty. Bragging about a pension. You
tell me, right? One wealthy person,
right, that would brag about a pension.
Any any person that you might come
across or any person that you might
know, right, Terry? That's you. No
girlfriend, no family. That's you. No
girlfriend, no sex life, no trainers.
Listen, do you want me to show my
trainers again? Listen, Joseph, you're
living in poverty. The only person that
brags about, right, that brags about [ __ ]
that brags about uh that brags about a
pension is someone that's living in
poverty. This is what I'm trying to say.
And I'm trying to make it across to you,
bro, that you're the one with the£300
phone. You're the one with the 40 jeans.
You're the one that's got no money. I'm
trying to tell you this, but you're not
listening. You're not listening, bro.
You're bragging about a pension. You
know all about poverty.
You would know all about poverty. Your
life is poverty. You would know all
about poverty, bro. You would know all
about it. You would know all about it.
You would know all about poverty. You're
living it. You're living in poverty.
You're living that poverty life.
You'd know all about poverty. Joe Joseph
poverty. You'd know. 40 jeans, 300 pound
phone, dragging her out a pension. [ __ ]
what I've got, bro. [ __ ] what I've got. Simple [ __ ] [ __ ]
Anyways, I'm done with these little
jealous crow um clowns from today.
Anyways, bro, I'm done with these little
jealous people that won't leave me alone
cuz they're jealous of me. I'm done
anyways. Um after today, Greezy. So, you
best um hope that Suicide Mark comes
back, bro. I'm not wasting my time with
a bunch of jealous people that's got no
family over Christmas. So, yeah, bro.
Yeah, bro. So, you're going to have to
pray that C Mark comes back. Yeah,
simple, lad. So, you're That's if he's
not killed himself. I am not wasting my
time with these people anymore. Right. I
am not wasting my time with these fat,
ugly, jealous people anymore, bro. Sorry, man.
Absolutely no way. Like the guy in the
shop, bro. Absolutely no way.
Jumpers. Ah, do you know what? Do you
know the thing is right it's the age of
these people is which is the which is
the which is the mad thing about it is
you think that these these people are
older than me to think that these people
are actually older than me
they're older than me these people are
older than me broing
hell bro I thought I was immature
but like I said it it's around that time of year
I know it around that time of year that
these people are going to be lonely
Christmas lonely. No family. No family.
So that's why they come on here.
[ __ ] retards. [ __ ] absolute
retards. Well, like I said, bro, I hope
you really really do sort out your
jealousy problem. Um because it will do
you good in life, bro. It really will.
Yeah. I really really feel bad for you
people. That's all I can say.
I really really do feel bad for you
people. That's the only thing I can
actually say, man.
In your 40s, jealous of someone that's
28. That's [ __ ] mad. Never in my life
have I been jealous of someone.
Especially someone I didn't even know.
These people are so jealous of me. It's
unbelievable. But even do you know what?
I'm not the only one that says it. You
know, I'm not the only one that says it.
My mama said it. My sister's friend has
said it. They are jealous of you. You
can go out and drink. You're younger
than them. Ronald Pumper said it. These
people are in denial, bro. When they're
trying to sit there and say that they're
not Dennis of people. They are in
denial. In denial. You know, today, not
one of these people come on a camera and
put their come online and put their
cameras on. Not one person done that.
But one person come on, showed what they
look like. Enough said. So, yeah.
Madness. Absolute madness.
I can't believe you're still doing this.
Really? Really? I I really can't believe
you you you are still doing this.
Yeah. Anyways, uh I'm gone now. So yeah,
enjoy your [ __ ] shitty little [ __ ]
lives. And yeah, and that's that. So
yeah, three [ __ ] almost 3 hours.
Jesus Christ. Anything now as well,
Joseph, that you're right, whether I see
it or I won't, you're not getting the
time a day. Because everything now about
poverty, you're just self- projecting.
So, no one cares about your self-p
projecting community post. No one cares
about the silly little only wins that
you put up, I will not be replying to
any of it. So, um whether I see it,
whether I don't see it, I won't be
replying to it. So, uh, yeah, you can
try and try hard because, uh, yeah, we
all know why you people are doing this
around this time of year because you got
no family, you ain't got nothing. So,
anyways, yeah, I'm off anyway. See you later.