Yo,
won't be on for long, by the way. I'm
just uh on and off nowadays.
Just wanted to say thank you to Steven
Howard. Thank you, Captain.
Thank you, Captain. My head's had a
little rest. Ah, the brain damage these
people give you on here. Well, my head's
a lot better now, by the way. So, thank you, Captain.
Yeah, that's how we know Steven Howard
is not um
is not trolling
cuz uh yeah, thank you for that on
Timmy's yesterday, Captain. You was
literally the only one that said it.
Thank Thank you for bringing it up. Uh
the porno Steven Howard. Thank you, Captain.
It's nice to see an unbiased person on
here for a change, you know. It's nice.
Very, very nice.
Very, very, very, very nice. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] Almost hit a rock there. So, yeah, man.
I see the fat old man Joseph Fer still
trying to get my attention. The sado
the little nons lover.
[ __ ] hell, bro. These people. Hey, these people.
And that guy didn't get called out for
[ __ ] it either. Madness, isn't it?
Yeah. These people are not worth it.
You're not worth wasting your time on.
Yeah, I wanted to say thank you, Steven Howard, Captain.
I meant what I said in my video, by the
way, as well. So, yeah,
the stuff you come out with is so funny.
You kind of like have to retaliate to
some of it. You're saying about no
wonder no one takes my words seriously.
No wonder no one takes my words seriously.
Bro, you can't even come on a panel and
talk and you're talking about people not
taking me seriously.
Okay, let's let's let's okay, let's
let's use this analogy, right? How many
times have I proved that I've had sex on
air? This is a perfect analogy, right?
which Kieran knows about this as well.
This is the whole Steven Howard thing.
We'll use this as an example. How many
times have you come on here when you've
proved you've had sex?
By you, I mean me? One, two, three,
four. Why I did it, I don't know. But
how many times have I been on here
proven I've had sex?
How many times do people come on here
and call me a virgin? So, I mean, at the
end of the day, it just shows that
you're never ever going to win with
these biased people. That's that's
that's the end of that. I mean, the only
person that backed me up yesterday was
that Steven Howard. So,
cuz that's like one of the most words
called the most of one of the most used
words on here is um called uh a virgin.
You're a virgin.
You're a [ __ ] virgin.
So, but no one backs me up when people
call me a virgin but Steven Howard. So
they just they're just biased on here.
That's that's the end. We You know it. I
know it. That's the end. So
say no more about it.
I fancy doing a video. You know, oh god.
Person replied back to me. You don't
know who I was speaking to on Instagram
yesterday, did you? Jesus Christ. These
Oh man. I don't I hate to repeat, you
know. I hate to be the Peter Belly Bear
Repeater, but these [ __ ] women, man.
They they are generally all the [ __ ]
same. And to think a 45year-old woman is
more immature than me.
And I class myself as immature. You
know, I actually used to class myself as [ __ ] immature.
And then when I told her like, I know
that you're like bullshitting, she
blocked me. What the [ __ ] I wasn't even rude.
So, it tells you that they're so used to
talking to people that are like simps
and bullshitting people and talking to
naive people and then when you finally
show that you're not one of these
people, um, they they disappear. I
wasn't even rude.
Um, so it's it's strange, you know. It
is strange to be to be 45 years of age
and still playing these games.
No offense, you know, 45 is bad as a
man. 45 as a woman's even worse.
Uh, thanks for defending me on Timmy's,
bro. Uh, yesterday, captain.
Um, saying that I weren't a virgin. I
was just saying that like, how many
times have I proved I've had sex on here
and people still come on here and call
me a virgin?
So, it just shows that uh because Joseph
Farel, the non-slover, was writing on
his thing about how um no wonder no one
could take my word seriously. And I'm
thinking, what do you mean no wonder no
one can take my word seriously? I've
proven the most on here. You can't even
come on the panel and talk. So, you must
be self projection. And then he said,
oh, well, no wonder everyone laughs at
you. I'm thinking, no, you people laugh
at yourselves. Like people have proven
everything they've had to prove on here
and you still make up stuff. So
you're a waste of our time. That Joe F
is a nonslover, bro. Steven, he's a
proper proper nonslover.
He he goes on non legs channel as well,
you know, and it's just sad. These
people really are sad.
He's not go That Smokey Bee is not going
on my door. That Smokey Be is not going
on my door, Dusty. He even said
um no one saying anything about it. This
is what I'm trying to say that they're
biased on it. They were calling me a
virgin yesterday on Timmy's. No one no
one back me up except Steven Howard.
So it shows like I went on this thing
Dusty. Yeah. On this Joseph Farage
channel just to see the [ __ ] he's been
writing because he's so thick like it it
becomes almost addicting. Yeah. He was
like, "Oh, no wonder no one can take my
word seriously." And I'm thinking, "Bro,
you can't even talk on a panel." Yeah.
Like I've said, I'll use the same
analogy cuz it's the perfect analogy.
I've proven I've had sex. People on here
still call me a virgin
that shows what they're like on here.
So, at the end of the day, it's like
when people show you stuff, you make up
you know? So, what the [ __ ] are you talking about? But yeah,
never seen with a woman doesn't prove
anything. Oh, okay. Okay. So, me putting
So, me putting me putting my dick in a
woman's mouth doesn't prove anything. Me
being in hotel rooms with several
different women and them admin to
sleeping with me doesn't mean anything, though.
Okay, bro. That's nice. Well, learn
something new every day.
Okay. Interesting. Oh, that doesn't
prove anything. No. No.
M. Interesting. When you're like lying
in bed with a woman and she's literally
told you how you just come up her. No,
that doesn't prove anything. No.
>> That's surprising, isn't it? You learn
something new every day, lads.
And this is what I'm saying. They're
they're biased on it. Like all of these
people like Jo, they're just
non-slubbers, bro. They just they're not
even worth it. these people in here,
they are just just non-slers. That Jo is
a proper proper nonslover. Um,
and I'm getting jealousy vibes of him as
well, to be honest with you, bro. Um,
you know what I'm saying, lad. I'm I'm
getting it off him as well. Um, to be fair. So, yeah.
So, no one can say Steven now trolls me
cuz I've seen him backing me up. Cuz
that is the truth. How can someone be a
virgin when they've proved they've had sex
when you're trying to tell me you can't
take my word seriously when all you
people do on is lie?
Okay. Well, then if I've got nothing in
my in my life, then you can stop going
on about me then, can't you?
No, bro. You've got nothing in your life
and Lord Jay's got nothing in his life.
You don't know what I've got in my life.
You don't know anything about me. So if
you're not jealous, then shut the [ __ ]
up about me then. Is it simple. Go tell
yourself that. If you're not jealous of
anything, go tell yourself that.
Like you people have got nothing. You've
been on the internet now for over 10
years doing what you're doing. You
people have got nothing. You generally
have got nothing in your lives to be
doing what you're doing. So yeah,
simple. You don't know what people have.
I mean, bro, how how how many weeks now
has this guy been saying that I'm living
under poverty and he doesn't know how
much money I have? He doesn't know
anything about me, you know?
You don't know anything about anyone,
but you still come on here and chat [ __ ]
about other people's lives and you slag
people off that you don't [ __ ] know.
It's madness. Madness.
What do you people have in your life sat
on the internet repeating on a live
stream for eight for 10 years? What do
you go out, bro? Do you go out with your
friends? Do you do stuff? Because you
clearly clearly don't to be doing what
you're doing. To be doing what you're
doing, man. You clearly don't. Clearly
Yeah. Again, you don't know how much
money I have. So, that's the end of
that. We're not getting into this again.
We're not getting into this conversation
again. And I'm blocking these people,
these little nods lovers. So, I
And you're getting banned as well. See you later,
little nods lovers.
That's what we call them, Dusty. We call
them nodd lovers.
Little pests. That's what they are. Pests. Um,
I got a story for you, Dusty.
I got a story for you. I got an
Instagram story for you.
Try not to laugh too much.
So, I stumbled across this woman, right? Dusty. Yeah.
And she was 45 years of age. And I know
what you're going to think, right? And
what? We was talking for a little bit,
Dusty. And guess what her excuse was for
not meeting me. You're going to get it
wrong cuz I know I know what you're
going to say, Dusty. I know what you're
going to say. It gets better. Trust me. Yeah.
You never guess, bro.
I was surprised to be honest.
Nope. She turned around and said that,
"Oh, we live too far and she lives in
wheelchair." I'm surprised she didn't
try to use her age as an excuse. They
love using age as an excuse. And then
she was and I'm thinking, well, you
don't live that far, 130 mi. And I'm
thinking to and I'm thinking to myself,
Dusty, that listen, you could go out in
London right now and all of these women
would come out with another excuse. So,
I mean, what's the chances that this one
here, right here, is really, really,
really not getting you because she lives
[ __ ] 100 miles away? It's [ __ ]
They're full of excuses. Like, bro, I'm
telling you, they are full of so many
excuses. Um, no, it's not
understandable. But that's what she
said. But no, it's not understandable.
It's an excuse because that is not even
that far. No, no, no, no, no. You would
you could make it work if you wanted it
to work. That's what she tried saying,
but nah, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. If you went out today
and you only approached older women,
they would come out with another excuse.
Bro, I've been I've been in this game
now for many, many years now, bro. Many,
many years. Many, many, many years I've
been in this game now, bro.
Many, many, many, many years. Right. I
know how to I know how the cookie
crumbles, bro. And at the end of the
day, Yeah. It's not like they live in
America. It's not like they live in
Australia. They live [ __ ] 100 miles
away. I'm not buying that because if if
what they're saying is true, then every
single older woman that you come across
older women, they're not going to come
out with an excuse then. Huh? It's
always an excuse. Think of it, bro.
You're in London, for [ __ ] sake, and
they still come out with excuses.
So, you do you understand? So, I mean,
yeah, it's a train away, couple of hours
away. Like, don't you get these women
that claim they've got boyfriends in different countries,
but now they're saying that it's it's it
is it is I've been I've been in this
game now for a very long time, bro. And
I said to her, listen, right, let's cut
the [ __ ] Let's cut the crap, right?
I could be your next door neighbor and
you'd come out with another excuse. I
wasn't swearing at her. I wasn't being
rude. I just said, "Listen, right, at
the end of the day, this was all a bit
of fun because I was going along with
it. But we all know that if I was your
next door neighbor, you would come out
with another excuse. That's not being
rude. That's being honest." And then all
of a sudden, she listened to the voice
notes and blocked me. So, it's like they
It's It is narcissism. It is
narcissistic what they're doing because
they're they're trying to blame they're
trying to put the blame on something
else other than them being too shallow.
Um, and it's it is a it is a trait of
narcissism. Like you wouldn't you
wouldn't understand it unless you
actually um you know uh dealt with it,
you know, but it is it generally
generally is because they're trying to
talk to you like you're an idiot, right?
They're trying to lie to you like you're
an idiot. And then when you know that
they're full of [ __ ] then they they're
nowhere to be seen. It it is a trait of
narcissism what they when they do that.
I was telling her a story about [ __ ]
one that I met for 3 hours. Oh, I don't
want to get with you because I'm a
Muslim. Turn around and said to her, I'd
convert to a Muslim. Another excuse.
So, it's always going to be an excuse
with these people. And at the end of the
day, right, I think it's the second most toxic thing
is the excuses and the [ __ ] and the
lies. That's the most tox that's the
second most toxic thing. The first one
is leading people on, but that's the second one.
So, I mean, yeah, there's trains. I
mean, it's not America where [ __ ]
you know, you've got to [ __ ] drive everywhere. So,
but it is definitely a trait of narcissism.
And if you look into it, it is. It
definitely definitely is because so what
if you live an hour and a half away?
There's trains. Yeah. Like you said,
there's it's not greasy.
Uh I just want to say that can everyone
big up Steven Howard
um you know for backing me up yesterday
when people was calling me a virgin.
Yeah, Steven Howard's a real one. He's
not like that that Joseph Ferrar. He's a
noble bastard. That Joseph Ferrar is a
horrible little nods loving bastard.
Hate to break it to you, but he is. Uh
whether you like him or not, that's your
choice, but he is a biased nods lover.
So, um and I'll say it to his face as
well. Something that he could never say
to my face. So, yeah. G, I got a little
story for you.
I got a little story for you and and and
the brothers want to know what you
think, right? So, I stumbled across a
woman yesterday. Uh, he's not coming. He
said that he's not coming,
you know. So, yeah, he said that he's not coming.
No one said anything about it. He's
flipped it now saying that I need to
show him two grand.
So, and yep, he did get away with it
scotfree before you ask. No one's got a
problem with that, Grezy. I think that
shows how biased people really really
are on here. So, they're not worth our
time. Anyways, on on to onto what I was
saying, Grezy. So, I come across this
woman yesterday on Instagram
and she was 45. So, you're thinking to
yourself, you know, a woman that's got a
lower SMV than you, you know, can't give
you a baby. It's going to be somewhat
somewhat different, right? That's what
you'd think once just just hear me out,
Grezy. So, we was talking and that and
I'm thinking, do you know what? Um, I've
never been with an older person like
that before. So, you know, why not, you
know, start stop start the lad start the
ladder somewhere. Start climbing the
ladder somewhere. So, we was talking
and Greasy, you never guess what her
excuse was. It's not what you think it
was. It is it's really funny, you know.
You know, you got to laugh at it, you
know. a couple of days later. Um she she
was trying to say that um it's because
we live too far away and um obviously
she lives in Wilshshire and I live in
London. I'm thinking but that can't be
true because think of it grievy. How
many people do you go out and you meet
and they've got some different excuse?
You're not Muslim. You're too old.
You're too young. You're not this.
You're not that. So in my head I was
thinking, okay, so what's what is
honestly the chances that you're going
to go out today? Only approach older
women and they're not going to have any
excuse. None. So you are no different.
And at the end of the day, distance is
not an excuse. 130 mi is not an excuse.
We're in the UK. There's trains for a
reason. And then when I told her, Griezy
that like basically I know that you're
lying. like I'm not I know that like
you're just use I basically said to her
Grezy that if I was your next door
neighbor you'd come out with another
excuse and it's just there's no need for
it and I basically just said it in a in
a polite way and then she blocked me. So
it is mental that Grezy that you know
these pe these women that are older than
you are more immature than you.
Nothing to do with nothing to do with
distance. It's just an excuse with them.
That's it's always excuses with them
and that that becomes very unhealthy as
well, very unhealthy, very toxic.
Um that's the second most toxic thing
apart from leading people on.
So if that's the case, then
what do you think we It's definitely an
excuse, isn't it?
So you're because I said so you're
you're telling me right if I if I lived
where you live you'd get with me.
So if I
you'd get with me. I find that very hard
to believe because Greavvesy we live in
London and we meet people all the time
and they come out with a different
excuse. So you you can understand what
I'm saying can't you Grezy?
You know that they very much have all
different kinds of excuses why they will
not get me you. So you know they love
the distance one. The distance excuse is their favorite.
Am I am I am I lying though? Am I am I
am I lying or what?
Oh and that that one that I met last week
uh I messaged her again and she replied
I said oh do you want to go out for a
drink tomorrow? turn around and said,
"Oh, sorry. I'm I'm I'm looking after my
little girl. Sorry."
I'm thinking, "Is that all?" And I just
said, "Maybe some other time." Didn't even reply.
So, we got a single mother, which isn't
really the worst. And then you got a 45year-old.
Really, bro? [ __ ] really, you know,
it did it did it did make me laugh, you
know. Um, it did make me laugh. It's
It's pretty boring, bro. They don't even
have different excuses, you know? If I
If I come If I like heard a different
excuse. It It would actually entertain
me. But it's always the same [ __ ]
thing over and over and over again. If
you're not their exact specific
materialistic type that they go for,
they they they just will. It's like they
they are actually [ __ ] with you on purpose.
So yeah, that's a 45 year old and a
single mom. So mom was a single mom, one
mom was a 45 year old.
But yeah, it does seem like grievy they
block you and they don't want anything
to do with you when they realize that
they haven't got you they haven't got
you wrapped around their finger. Does
Does that make sense? I basically said
in in the kindest way possible that I
know you're just using it as an excuse.
I wasn't being rude. didn't swear and
didn't want nothing to do with talking
to me anymore
because it's a time to grow up and
actually at 45 you would have thought
that they would have been grown up you know
madness and madness isn't it is bad
it's always an excuse with him
that's why I gave up and it's not even
like you're fat and ugly in a
wheelchair. So, [ __ ] knows.
But I've been feeling better, Grezy. I
haven't been pissed off. No mood swings.
I've been feeling all right to be
honest. I was all right yesterday.
Sleeping pattern still a bit [ __ ] but
I'm feeling all right
cuz obviously not dating. You feel so
much better when you take away, you
know? It's like, yeah,
it's the dating that makes you
depressed. That's that's what makes you
depressed. Going out going out and
dealing with it. That's what makes you depressed.
So you you you you know what I'm saying?
Obviously, it would think of it, bro.
You go out and you drink a load of rum,
you get numbers. You're dealing with the
same [ __ ] from them. And then you've got
the side effects from the alcohol.
[ __ ] stinking, bro. [ __ ] that. So,
he's not coming. He said that he's not
coming. Now he's trying to say I need to
show him two grand. [ __ ] off, man.
Yeah, he's not coming.
Yeah, like I said, Grezy, you can say
that. You can like Joseph R all you
want. I don't like him. I think he's
nothing but a little biased little
nonslubber. Um, and I don't like him.
You can like him. Um, but I don't like
him. He's biased as well. Proper, proper biased.
And if you saw his last comment, you'd
see that he's just a biased dunce lover
undercover hater. That's all he is. Simple.
He's not blocked on nons uh nons's legs channel.
Um, they're just biased on here. That's
all they are, bro. Like, they're biased,
non-sloving [ __ ] That's what they are. You know
about you. No wonder no one can take my word seriously.
Seriously, bro. Coming from [ __ ] you.
Like, shut up, bro. I was going to do a
video saying, "Listen, tell me where to
meet and I'll meet you tomorrow."
You know, that's that's what I was going
to say, but there's no point because
people like Jojo and Fel will never meet
anyone. They're just fat cowardly little
keyboard warrior losers
and grievy. It's not about Listen, let
me tell you something. Yeah, let me try
and let me tell you something so this
Joseph Ferrar does not get in your head.
I can go out whenever I want. I can go
out two times a week. I can go out one
time a week. I can afford to go out.
Yeah, I can afford to go out. I have not
been going out for the past year. Yeah.
the past about well about 14 months I've
not been going out once a week or twice
a week cuz I can't be [ __ ] Yeah.
Nothing to do with money. Yeah. And even
if it was to do with money, which it's
not, I generally would make money. I
would do anything to make money if I
generally thought there was hope in this
country, then I would I would be going out.
I would be going out. It's cuz I can't
be bothered. I can't be [ __ ] Nothing
to do with money at all.
Nothing to do with money at all at all.
Just in case that's what it seems like. Nah,
nothing to do with money. I feel better
now anyways cuz since yesterday I've
been feeling better. So that's that.
It's nothing to do with money.
It is women and the [ __ ] experiences
with women. It's nothing to do with money, bro.
So trust me, bro. I've been I've not
been skinned for a very very very very
long time. And I'm not skin now. So So
yeah, it's people like to chill out. I'd
rather just not.
Doesn't matter how much money I get. I
was doing the same thing when I had the
house. I was just stacking more money
faster. That's all I was doing. I still
weren't going out. So
I like to [ __ ] stuff and make up stock
on it, bro. But yeah,
and like I said, I was worse back then
than when I am what I am now.
I was worse back then than I am now. I
was bad. Even in the house, I was bad.
So, but now I'm just like, yeah.
Yeah. But that woman using distance as
an excuse, give it a break, you know,
give it a rest, mate. We've heard all of
these excuses before. Don't forget
though, Greavvesy, apparently all women
are different. All women are not the same.
All women are not the same, by the way.
Remember that, Grezy. All women are not the same.
He's not coming.
Now he's asking people to show two
grand. So, he's not coming.
>> [clears throat] >> Yep.
Joseph Ferrar is a [ __ ] nons lover.
Pathetic fat old ugly nons lover. I hate
that little bias nons lover.
I hate that [ __ ] bro. Hate that [ __ ]
You don't understand, Mr. B. I hate that [ __ ]
Did you see him kissing [ __ ] uh Nons
legs his ass?
asked at first. No, the guy said that
he's going to be coming on the door
tomorrow and now he's asking to show
[ __ ] two grand. Seriously, bro?
Yeah. He's not coming anyways. So,
but he'll get away with it anyways. No
one will say anything
cuz they will biased just be another it
be just another day.
Greavves. It will just be a normal
another day on here tomorrow.
It'll just be another day. Yeah.
And Joseph Far is the only one that
lives in poverty. He's the one that's
got a 200 pound [ __ ] phone. He's the
one with 40 jeans, not me. He's
definitely the one that's living under poverty.
No one else.
Definitely definitely him. I had some
chicken and chips today. Greavvesy.
Yeah, he's nons's best friend. Uh, Joseph. Yeah.
Well, it doesn't matter. He's got a 200
pound phone and he got 30 jeans.
He is poverty. Simple. That is poverty.
That is poverty, bro.
But I mean, I can go out drinking every
week. I can do what I want. Am I living
under the poverty? No, I'm not. So, yeah. Simple.
No, he's definitely definitely
definitely I mean, he definitely is. I'm
not living under poverty,
bro. The guy is living under poverty
himself. How can he say that I'm living
under the poverty, bro? I I bought
expensive clothes. I can do what I want
when I want
at the end of the day, bro. I [ __ ]
How could I be living under poverty?
When I'm staying in by choice,
understand what I'm saying to you again?
When I'm staying in and I'm not going
out tomorrow, that's by choice. Not
because I can't. That's by by that is by
choice. And at the end of the day, if
you're doing something by choice, then
that's your choice, you know. At the end
of the day, that's your choice. When
it's not a choice, that's a problem.
That's what I think. But it is a choice.
I don't want to go out drinking
tomorrow. I can go out to a restaurant.
I can go out drinking. I can go out
passing the cat, but I don't want to. Simple. So,
so it's a choice. I don't want to go out
by choice. So, that's that.
You understand, Stephen Howard?
Yeah. But as soon as I call that woman
out for making excuses, Grecy, she blocked me.
So, it seems like everyone they they
talk to they think is a [ __ ] and
they're naive. And then when they
realize that they're not, they then like
either play the victim or just block
you. It It comes across that way, doesn't it?
about [ __ ] distance, mate. If it was
distance, you'd be meeting women in
London all the time. You'd be going on
dates all the time.
They're so full of [ __ ] It's
unbelievable, bro. You know, mad.
Very, very unhealthy. Grezy, I hope you
never ever get into this dating thing.
It's very very very unhealthy.
Very very unhealthy.
It's really bad, bro. It's not even
anything to laugh about.
It is mad.
45year-old. That is a madness, bro. And
they're still playing little women
games. [ __ ] me.
And the one that replied just didn't
really seem very enthusiastic.
I said, "Oh, no worries." Another time
didn't even reply back. So,
they're just not interested in this
country. Simple as that. Nope.
Nah, I'm just going to be chilling
tomorrow, bro. [snorts] Oh, I'm stacking
up the money.
That's what I'm doing, bro. And I'm
getting the [ __ ] out of here. That's
what I'm doing.
Oh, I still need to sign up for that
porn thing. I still haven't done it yet.
I need to do that and then stack up the
money, I think. But yeah.
So, yeah. So, this is what Joseph needs
to understand that people don't go out
because they don't want to go out. It's by choice.
I could put a 500 pound football bet on
tomorrow if I wanted to and I can go out
getting pissed going into steak
restaurants. I can do what I want. You know
it is bad. No wonder Antman left. I can
see why he actually left. Yeah,
anyone in their right mind would leave.
You know, it's [ __ ] bad, bro. Really bad.
But it is super bad, Greezy. It is bad, bro.
45 year olds thinking that they're
better than you. Single moms thinking
that they're better than you. [ __ ]
hell, bro. What's the excuse for them
ones, bro? [ __ ] me.
Maybe they just don't like me because of
like I don't look fully white and
they're racist. I think I think Ben is
right, you know,
cuz you're not ugly. You're not
overweight. You look normal. You dress
[ __ ] good. I think that Ben's right,
you know, man. I think they're just racist.
Cuz I definitely definitely don't look white because
and thingy says I look white, but I
don't think that I do. Cuz
everyone that looks at me, they're like,
"Oh, what have you got in you?" I say,
"I'm quarter Turkish, so I don't think I
look fully white." Maybe to some people,
but to most people, I don't. Maybe. I
don't know. But maybe it's maybe it is a
race thing and they're just racist.
Not the way I look. It's not the way I act.
So, I think they they just got to be
racist or something because Yeah.
I don't know how much I weigh, but I'm
not overweight. So, it's definitely
definitely got to be something like that
cuz I don't think I look pretty white as
much as [ __ ] Ant-Man says I do. I
don't think so.
[ __ ] using this as an excuse, lad.
[ __ ] madness. Oh, Franklin's been run over. Nope. 510.
Oh, don't say that. We're going to get
LT. Come on here now, [ __ ] Grezy.
We're going to get [ __ ] LT. Come on here, lad. Mad.
Jesus Christ. We're going to get [ __ ]
LT. Come on.
Don't say that now, bro.
So yeah, I think it is that bro. What
the [ __ ] man?
Bad, is it?
Using distance as a [ __ ] excuse. That
is pathetic, bro. Really pathetic.
Any excuse other than blaming their
shallowess and their racism, like
they will do. That's why it's a
narcissistic trait. It seems like it is
a narcissistic trait. If that makes
maybe they're not narcissist, but it is
a narcissistic trait cuz we all know if
somebody lived next to that person, they
would still come out with another excuse.
So, give it up. It's boring now. You
know what I mean?
No, I need to do it tomorrow. I forgot, bro.
I'll definitely be doing it tomorrow cuz
this has got to stop, bro. So, yeah, I
could go out tomorrow and and approach
and drink, but why? It's just going to
be the same old. It's nothing to do with
the money. It's always going to be the same here.
You know it and I know it. So, I'll be
out New Year's Eve. Um, but yeah, I'm
not going out before then
because it's pointless. You got 45 year
olds that think they're [ __ ] better than you.
You got a single mom
that is being unenthusiastic and not
interested. What the [ __ ]
Definitely. I think they're racist, bro.
That's what I think.
Oh, don't worry about that, bro. Why you
asking how big my dick is? [ __ ] weird question,
but yeah, who knows? Anyways,
probably a race spin to be honest. Yeah.
Yeah. Well, then I'm going to Yeah,
they're going to see my dick, aren't
they? I'm going to have to send them a
picture when they ask for it. Why are you asking?
I think it's not bad joining the porn
industry, though. It isn't bad. You get
laid, you get paid good money. I don't
think it's I think it's that or Thailand.
You know, it's either that or Thailand realistically.
[ __ ] escorts, bro. You You should have
to use escorts. You're a young man.
You should be having a healthy sex life.
Isn't that right, Grezy? You should have to [ __ ]
go with escorts.
Have to go with escorts. So that's um
I've never said I can't finish with an
escort. Never said that. I [ __ ] one a
couple of months ago.
What do you think about that 45year-old
woman using distance as an excuse? Slim.
They all do and act the same way, but
people say they're not all the same. [ __ ] hell.
probably if she blocked me just cuz I
told her that like I know that you're
basically full of [ __ ]
Oh, they will call me a virgin. Oh, they will gre
literally put my dick in two vaginas at
the same time
and then they and then they'll turn
around and say, "Nah, you're a virgin."
They'll say, "Nope, you're a virgin."
They [ __ ] will. They will still call
you a virgin. That's what they're like
on here. They're biased.
Just like Joseph Fer, the non lover.
He's biased as well. You know what
they're like. They're not They will call
you a virgin. They will still call you a
virgin. Timmy will go live, Timmy will
get triggered, and then he will start
calling me a virgin. That's what he
does. Timmy does it. Timmy's Timmy's the
worst for it.
He calls me a virgin even though I
proved I've had sex multiple times. But yeah,
they're biased. They will always call
you a virgin, bro. That's cuz they're virgins. So yeah,
like I said on my video, bro. Like I
I've got a nice Coke in the fridge. Rezy. So, yeah.
So, that was a week of nothing. Still
got no date this weekend.
Another week for no date. Grizzy. Mad it. One sec.
If I go out tomorrow, would it be any different? Greavvesy. Nah.
Yeah, go for it, Captain. Go for it,
I had chicken and chips, so yeah.
But Grezy, people on Reddit say that
I'll meet someone.
Grievesy, people on Reddit say I'll meet someone.
Should I believe them?
Yep. Little supper. Yeah. Yeah,
this woman was saying that I should join
poetry um classes to meet a woman, Dusty,
like dance classes and stuff.
I think they're trolling me on Reddit,
is it? I think they're trolling me.
Yeah, I think they're trolling me, bro.
They said join like poetry um classes
and dance classes
dance classes. They're definitely trolling.
She don't want to know you. She don't
want to know. She don't want to know you. Oh, Franklin.
Franklin's going around.
[ __ ] hell, man. That nonsex is a
horrible little virgin.
Um, he's not going a platform on my
channel ever again until he meets me.
So, you can bugger off. David Campbell
from Leads. Enough said.
David Campbell from Leeds.
I might have some digestive biscuits.
I don't know. I fancy some digestive biscuits.
Uh, I think we have some. Yeah,
I said I'm going to have some digestive biscuits.
Now, I read uh some of your comments
from like a year ago. Yeah. And you said
to me, "Oh, you don't need gambling in
your life, but you can't resist it." You
can't say that to me now, can you, Greasy?
You can't say that to me now, can you?
No. You can't say that to me now.
You can't say I can't resist gambling
now, can you?
What do you reckon, Steven Howard?
Should I go out tomorrow drinking? Do
you reckon I'll meet someone?
This Joseph Ferrar doesn't know
anything. He really doesn't know
anything about Peter Belly.
And another thing what I'll say about
him, yeah, is I don't care about buddy.
I don't care what people win, but what
he's showing is [ __ ]
What this guy is showing is [ __ ]
There is people do not win on fobies
like that, bro. Trust me. Trust me on
someone that's gambled for many, many,
many years. People don't win on fobies like that.
Nah, it's not a laugh. It's not a laugh.
I don't find any of it a laugh. having
no sex life. I don't find any of it a
laugh. I think it's [ __ ] depressing.
No one wins.
No one wins like he does on properties,
bro. Trust me, how he's making out. He's
a bullshitter. That Joseph Fra is a
No one wins [clears throat] like that on
Fies, bro. It's like stop and step. He
only shows wins. Why don't you show some
losses? Why don't you do some videos?
Right. Hey, do you know what this Joseph
Farah should do? Ask him to put put full
videos up. He won't do it. Have you
noticed he will never say when he loses,
which is all the time, and he makes it
out that he's won. I used to put losses up.
>> Nah, bro. [laughter]
Greasy, I'm having some uh digestive biscuits.
I'm having some digestive biscuits. Greasy.
Okay with you, boss.
>> Okay. Well, Grezy Grezy I like I like Chevzy.
Is that okay with you, boss?
Is that okay with you? [laughter] Yeah.
Got a copycat.
Yeah. So, this Joseph Barau has only put
wins up. He's not he's not he's not
winning like that. Trust me, no one is
winning gambling like he's making out he
is. Believe you me. No way.
There's no way, bro. Trust me. There's
no not a chance in hell.
Not a [ __ ] chance in hell. Nah. >> [laughter]
>> Not a chance in [ __ ] hell, mate.
So, if I go out tomorrow, Greasy, do you
reckon I'll be able to get attached?
Do you reckon I'll be able to get attached?
Yeah, I like um I like I like um Steven
Howard and Greavesy.
People can say they troll me all they
want, but Steven Howard actually backs
me up. So,
he's the only one that says I can't be a
virgin because I've showed plenty of
women. See, that's somebody that's not
biased. Whereas Joseph Ferrar, he's too
busy [ __ ] sucking nons's dick.
cuz he's probably a nons himself.
That's why he gets on with them so much
cuz hair pair were [ __ ] nonsers. I
had 20 chicken nuggets greasy at about
2:00 in the morning yesterday. I was a bit peck.
Yeah, I was a bit peck.
Yeah, I was a bit peckish. Yeah.
So, will you agree now Grezy that Joseph
Joseph Ferrar is biased?
Do do you agree now that he's biased?
You can like him. I don't care if you
like him or you dislike him, but would
would you agree that he's biased now? Yeah,
he's not bi So you don't think he's biased? So,
okay. So, you don't think he's biased?
So he calls when I call non legs a
virgin, he's straight to his rescue.
When virgin when he doesn't when he's
when he's when when virgin when people
call me a virgin, he's nowhere to be
seen. When I've stuck it on multiple
people, he continuously makes excuses,
but then when L doesn't turn up to
places, he justifies why he hasn't done
it. Um, and he's not going to give
Smokey B any [ __ ] tomorrow if we're not
turning up. But he would give me [ __ ]
You You really don't think he's biased, bro?
How is that How is that not biased?
Nons legs has never had him blocked. So,
how how is he not biased?
How is he not biased, bro?
No, I'm just saying that he's biased. I
don't care. I'm just saying that they're biased.
I really don't give a [ __ ]
But No, but you're missing Yeah, but
Dusty, you're missing you're missing the
point, bro. You're missing You're
missing the point of what I'm trying to
say. You know, I don't care if they
think I've had sex or not. I'm asking
why is he so fast enough to defense nons
legs when I go at him but he's not fast
enough to defend me. I'm just wondering
because he's biased. I don't care. I'm
just saying that's how he's biased. I
generally don't give a [ __ ] You know,
these people think I'm scared. They
don't know how much money I have. I
generally don't care. I'm just curious.
Why are you biased? I don't care. You
know, I don't care.
They think I'm [ __ ] skint. They think
I can't afford to go out. They don't know anything.
That's why I don't go mad at it, bro. I
don't get mad at it.
But he's saying, what annoys me is he's
trying to say that no wonder no one
could take my word seriously when I've
stuck it on men, shown more money than
anyone, and show more women, but you're
saying that you can't take my word seriously.
Somebody that can't even join a panel and talk.
So I mean it seems pretty biased to me but yeah
they are biased. They are biased
and why and the reason for it is why is
anyone going to prove themselves to bias
people? You know how many times do
people come on here and say prove this
prove that prove this prove that? But
why would anybody want to prove
themselves to biased people? you know,
why would anyone want to do that? That
doesn't make sense, you know.
Anyways, moving on.
But you don't think he's biased?
He is biased. He is definitely biased.
Whether you care or not, he is biased.
Even Kieran will tell you that he's biased.
And why is he commenting on Nonsex's channel?
He says that the guy's a nons. He says
that he calls him nonsle leg. So why is
he commenting on his channel? That's a
bit sus, isn't it?
No, that Joseph Ferrar is definitely
definitely a nonslover. Definitely a biased non-slover.
He is he is from [ __ ] Lavy so you
know he is from John Lavy side. So you
know you kind of expect it you know.
Same question to you then. Why why do
you care if I'm calling nonlegs a
virgin? Why are you so fast to defend
him if you don't care? I I could say
this. I could ask the same question then, right?
Why do you care if I'm calling other
people a virgin? Why are you straight to
their rescue? Like Superman, the new
episode of Superman. I could ask I could
ask the same thing, you know,
like it's clear you are biased on it.
It's clearly these people here are
biased. It's not a case of me thinking
I'm right. I mean, it's clear you are biased. So, yeah.
Clear as day. You are biased.
You're definitely biased.
Yeah. So, yeah. Nothing's happening on Saturday.
So yeah, which is tomorrow.
Yeah, that woman today was full of [ __ ]
proper for the [ __ ]
about distance. Oh, give it a break, mate. Yeah,
it wouldn't have been lost for him. It
would have been lost for you and me, but
it wouldn't have been lost for him.
Trust me, it wouldn't have been lost for him.
Now, he's saying that he wants people to
show him money again with you by his
people. No one's going to show you anything.
But yeah, I know you want to see some
content tomorrow, man. Me going out
Steen Howard, but I can't do it with
these women, bro.
I ain't dealing with them anymore.
These stuck up [ __ ]
So yeah, I don't know.
>> [clears throat]
>> Why doesn't that Joseph Ferrar do long
gambling videos as well? We actually
want to see gambling videos.
He can't do gambling videos because he
doesn't always win. It's [ __ ] This
is what I'm and I don't give a [ __ ]
anyways. I've got my own money. I've got
no one to be jealous of. But I'm saying
that he's he's not showing videos
because they're not what he's showing is
not actually real. You don't win that
amount of times on properties, bro. Trust me.
Trust me, you don't. And if you do, put
the videos up. Put the videos up of you
continuously winning. What I think he
does yet is
He chases his losses.
No, I think what he does is he chases
his losses, right? And every time he
wins, he says, "Oh, I've won." But I
don't think he's being real with him
being up. There's no way you can be up
that all the time on them machines, bro.
There's no way. You can't even do it on
football. So, what you're telling me
that he just wins all the time? Nah. No
way, bro. You can't always win on them
machines. I know it and anyone that's
played it knows it.
So, I think he's he's not showing where he's lost.
100%. Bro, listen. When was the last
time this guy has come on here and said
that he's lost money? Nah, there's no
way. Them machines are not there to pay
you out every day, bro. You know it and
I know it.
you know, so
he I can't remember the last time he
said he's lost,
but do you not see what he's trying to
do on this channel? I can see it, right?
And anyone that's got a brain sees it. Yeah.
He thinks that I've got no money when I
do have money. I've got more than enough
money. And what he's trying to do is try
to get me into gambling again. And it's
not going to work.
Yeah, I know about these people and what
they're trying to do. Bro, there's no
way people can win like that
continuously. So, when was the last time
when he comes on it, ask him the last
time he lost.
Don't forget, I played them machines a
lot. I lost 600 pound on fishing frenzy
over that Christmas, bro. Them machines
are not paying out like that, especially
nowadays, you know?
So, I think he just like chases these
losses and maybe gets and then he's like
200 pound down or 150 and then just says
that he's won because there's no way
somebody would have been on a big loss
by now, bro. Trust me, they would have
where they would have been on a big loss
by now with somebody that's gambling
like that, you know? So, it's like
stepping stop and step. He only shows
wins. That's what he does.
tell him to do like four sessions,
150 and 200 and and you'll see.
So yeah, bro.
Yeah, Joseph Ferrar.
He is biased
trying to say that we laugh at you, bro.
You little clowns don't laugh at anyone
but your [ __ ] [ __ ] selves.
Like them people on LJ's channel, they
laugh at themselves, bro. They're the
absolute fuckups in life. They don't
laugh at me, bro. They definitely
definitely don't laugh at me. They laugh at themselves. So,
and yeah, like I said, they're biased.
So, that's it.
They're just biased [ __ ] fat, ugly
people. There you go. Simple. That's it.
Is it? Yeah.
But yeah, no football bet tomorrow right
now. Just doing I got no plans. Um,
no, I got no plans. I'm not depressed
either. I'm good. I'm fine. I done some
house work and that. So, washing up,
washing and I'm good, bro. I'm not
depressed or anything.
I'm all right now. I was bad the past
couple days cuz Yeah. [ __ ] in it. So
had nothing to do with money. Nothing.
Nothing to do with money. Mad.
Yeah. Yeah. They're idiots. Yeah. Yeah,
that that Joseph Fastic, right?
They don't think that people can grow
older and not want to drink every week.
They these people's in these people's
minds, they've got to be skin, Steven
Howard. They've got to be skint. There's
no way you can just be sick of the
women, sick of the going out drinking.
There's no way that can happen. And
you've got to be skin
in their mind. You've got to be skin.
That's how they think. That's how these
people think, bro. They're weird. Absolutely weird.
In the summer time, I'll probably drink
a lot more though. But
do I like the summer? Do I not?
I don't know. I don't really, bro. I
don't know, man.
I remember I was drinking. I was doing
Uber in it and the summer and I was
drinking. The weather's been
I don't know.
I like October, bro. Yeah, the heat.
What I do like about the heat is you can
wear nice shorts and nice trainers and a
nice Reese top.
I think I like it because like what you
can wear and that, you know what I mean?
You can wear like nice stuff um in the
summer and it
>> I don't know. I don't know.
Do you like the summer? The summer?
So, when am I going to meet someone
greasy? Seriously, this is getting
[ __ ] pathetic now.
I'm 28 years of bloody age.
When am I going to [ __ ] find someone?
Had enough of this?
People on Reddit keep saying I'm going
to find someone,
but I never [ __ ] do.
No, but what about before that?
Yeah, but what about before that?
People on [ __ ] Reddit said I would I
was going to meet someone, you know.
People on Reddit says,
People on Reddit say that you can get
someone whenever you want, Grezy. They
say you can get sex whenever you want. On Reddit,
do you remember when Greavvesy had a little [ __ ]
Some women said that giving [ __ ] are
disgusting. Greavesy. Why do they think that?
Given [ __ ] are disgusting. Huh?
Tell you say it's disgusting. Is it?
I always come back on YouTube for greasy.
Yeah, I always come back on YouTube for greasy, you know.
I always come back for grievy.
Poor [ __ ] Can't deprive him of
content, can I? The poor [ __ ] Poor [ __ ]
You will never forget that comment, will
you, Greasy? Huh?
You'll never forget that comment, eh?
You should get tattooed on you. Poor [ __ ]
It's the way they wrote it as well, is
it? Oh, [ __ ] All right. When I put
the cat up on my uh as my picture, they
said that looks like the virgin [ __ ]
That looked like the [ __ ] No, it
wasn't. It wasn't Dusty. It was It was a
fake account. Well, Dusty is a fake
account, but another fake account.
It looks like the virgin [ __ ]
Jeezy. The greeneyed virgin [ __ ]
Yeah, you know who they're referring to. Grezy
agrees. I've gone on this um Cheryl
Cole's pictures. Yeah. And I'm thinking
she's quite attractive.
She's quite attractive. M man, this
[ __ ] Cheryl Cole was Yeah, she's quite attractive.
Grezy, she's quite hot, isn't she?
Grey, she's quite hot. This will call. Yeah, greedy.
You can't deny that she's attractive.
What have you got any opinion of me
thinking that she's attractive? Grezy,
any opinion on that?
You mean a big one there? Meow.
You're a big stinking copycat. Meow.
LT said that he used to have a crush on
her. So, was he copying as well then? Gay.
Indigo. You're gay. Gay homo.
Homo. Gay homo vibes.
That's what they used to say. They used
to copy each other
in school and college. They used to be
like, "Gay, you're gay." No, you're gay.
That's where the [ __ ] virgin [ __ ]
got him from, ain't it?
You just came out. Homo gay.
Where's Where's Where's Nons when when
you need him.
Right. I I was going to put up Yeah. You
know, David Campbell from Leeds, I was
going to put it up on my community post
and said, "I want to buy this man a pint
of beer." Do you get it, Grezy?
I'm going to put it on the community
post, you know, David Campbell from
Leeds and say, "I I want to buy this man
a pint of beer."
Yeah. I'd love to go on with this with
this fella. Do you get it, Grezy? Yeah.
Let me see if I can find him. David Campbell
from Leeds. That's what his stepdad's called. What's that?
That's his stepdad. Love,
where is this Sorry. David Campbell.
What do you think of that?
That's what the [ __ ] virgin fucker's
stepdad was called. David Campbell. Mad. Yeah.
Also known as Phil. Nasty [ __ ] He
was, mate. Nasty [ __ ]
Horrible old [ __ ] Over. [clears throat]
We usually hate women.
She don't want to know you. She don't
want to know you. She don't want to know
you. Why don't you hate women?
They're nasty people in general.
Why don't you You should hate women.
Oh, I found his stepdad.
I found his step I found his stepdad, bro.
I found him.
I love to buy this this man a pine. David Campbell.
I just think they're all [ __ ] Greasy.
I think they're all little nasty [ __ ] Yeah.
Oh, he lives in robber room now. I found his stepdad.
I found his stepdad, bro, on [ __ ]
on Facebook, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. He's in [ __ ] ro now. Jesus Christ,
man. I'm going to put it up. Yeah, I'm
going to put up on a community post. more.
All right, I'm putting this up. Yeah, two seconds.
There you go. I done a community post.
That was his stepdad. Yeah. >> [laughter]
>> It is coming up, bro. Try again. [laughter]
Did you get [ __ ] there?
I'll link you it. One second.
There you go. Found the con.
That's him. And that's the guy
responsible for it all.
There we go.
Yeah. Monty done something like that.
Monty's done something like that. Do you remember?
That's his stepdad.
Where was his stepdad? I don't know if
he's still with his mom. I'm not sure. [ __ ] hell.
That's his stepdad.
It's from Leads. If you look at the top,
it says leads, but obviously he's moved.
Says he's single.
I remember everything. I remember
people's birthday. I remember what
people tell me. You know what I mean?
Yeah. That's his stepdad.
We remember we remember small details.
That's his um nonsense. His stepdad.
It's his stepdad, bro.
David Campbell leads,
but he lives in Roin now.
Yeah, I've been I might put some
messages up to be honest.
I might put some messages up.
[clears throat] Yeah, message him. He'll
tell you everything.
He's got a very, very dark past.
Very dark past. Yeah,
that's the one that had him up against
the [ __ ] wall.
[ __ ] Carly. He chopped the [ __ ]
He had him up against the [ __ ] wall,
mate. That's That's his stepdad.
Yeah, give him a little message, bro.
He'll tell you.
He tried to help this little [ __ ] so
many times, you know. He tried to help
this little [ __ ] bag. Oh [ __ ]
It's Nons's stepdad
when he used to live at his [ __ ] um mom's.
It wasn't just him. It was his mom as well.
[ __ ] horrible. Oh,
you can you you can tell that by looking
at his face.
Very very dark past.
Very very very very dark past.
Yeah, he doesn't he [ __ ] he doesn't
know about the YouTube. I told him about
the YouTube. I was messaging him asking
asking questions and stuff. He told me a lot.
He told me a lot about this little [ __ ]
told me a [ __ ] lot, mate. David Campbell virgin. There's
some coke in a minute. [snorts] [laughter]
Poor [ __ ] You can't beat an ice cold
coat, can you? Crazy.
I don't hear. Don't [ __ ]
underestimate me, mate.
Don't [ __ ] underestimate me. [clears throat]
I fancy some digestive biscuits, man. Don't know.
Some digestive biscuit.
You're a big stinking [laughter]
crazy. You big stinking copycat.
You're funny. I love Grezy.
Greavves is a bro. Greavves is a bro
is a bro. You're a big stinking copycat. M.
>> Yeah. Anyone can message him. tell you
I've been speaking to him.
David Campbell from Leads.
Mad, isn't it, bro? Mad. Yeah.
He said that he never wants to [ __ ]
cross paths with him ever again.
That's what he said. Grezy was saying to
me, he never wants to see that little
[ __ ] ever again
cuz he won't be able to hold back. Yeah. [clears throat] Oh,
I've got a weak bladder. Do you Grezy?
Yeah, I've got a weak bladder.
I can't hold in weed though. Can you?
I can't hold it in.
I need some green now. All the caffeine.
I pee more than three times.
Yeah, I think if you held it in,
if you held it in, it's dangerous, isn't it? Uh-uh.
I'm having a digestive biscuit.
[clears throat and cough] Right. Here we go.
I don't know whether to get the Grinch
meal for McDonald's.
I don't know whe to get the Grinch meal. Not sure.
Look, look what I got. I got these digestive biscuits.
They're all right. Look,
I got I got digestive biscuit. Look. All right.
These biscuits are nice.
You know what? You can't beat biscuits
with a nice cold coke. It might sound
mad, but a nice cold Coke with some biscuits. Oh,
you [clears throat] can't beat it.
It sounds weird, I know, but it's actually nice. Enjoy.
You're still there, Stephen Howard.
You're still there, Captain.
I'm loving these biscuits.
What do you think you asylum? Do you
think um Do you think Joseph Fau is biased?
Who think Joseph Fo is biased? Press one
for yes and two for no. I'm putting one.
I think he's biased. I'm putting one.
I'm one is two. What's everyone else? That's all is true.
Who who thinks
and you need to give a reason why you
think he is as well? I'm one grievy
doesn't agree. You agree. So why do you agree?
You have to give a reason.
>> I have my reason. What's yours? Sure
Why? Why do why do you think she's
biased? She have to give a reason.
What's your reason, Stephen?
Why? Okay. Why? Let me put it this way.
Why is Joseph Farah not a brother?
I don't think he's a non-lover. What?
Why do you think he's not a bra?
>> [clears throat]
>> Whenever I go at nonsense, why is he why
is he up his ass like Superman? He's
like, "Listen, look, I say something to
nonsense." And this is Jojo Far
up his ass.
He's straight to his rescue. [ __ ] virgin.
He's like just he has his little tape
and he's like
straight to straight to the rescue.
[ __ ] fat old man. You know what I'm
thinking of doing? Yeah. To that [ __ ]
Jo said, "Listen, yeah, if you really
want to if you really want to test that
somebody will do nothing, how about you
meet me tomorrow
and we'll see what I'll do. We'll see
what I'll [ __ ] do.
You see what I [ __ ] do, man?
What do you think of that?
You want to say something? I'll travel
to you tomorrow. You come.
Do a video talking explaining where to
meet you and I'll be there.
I think that will pretty much prove it
with these clouds. I don't want you to
show your face. I just want you to do a
video saying that you're going to meet.
If you're not going to do that, then
you'll do nothing.
You and your little library boyfriends
will do nothing.
Know what I mean? Poverty Joe.
Poverty Joe with his poverty jeans.
Isn't that right, Stephen Howard?
We will see who will do nothing then.
Come on. I I I want a fun day.
I want a lovely fun day.
I'm sure you'd love to see that,
wouldn't you? Me versus Jo.
Me versus Joseph.
That's lovely content. We can't stop the
I'm going to call this little prick out.
I'm going to call this little fat prick out.
I I want to make room
for my content to pop back up.
>> Well, I'll call him out and see see who
will really whose word means nothing.
>> I'm willing to test a very well. Well,
Dusty Smoke is not coming tomorrow. It's
not my fault, is it? He said he was
going to come in the door and he's not
coming now. It's not my fault, is it?
It's not my fault, lad. You know what
the [ __ ] do you want me to do about it,
bro? He's the one that let let everyone
down. I want this Joseph F, this little nonsubber,
cuz he's got a lot of mouth for someone
that can't even talk. He's got a lot of mouth.
[ __ ] non flubbing [ __ ]
I I'll meet him and I'll laugh at his
face. I will laugh in his face. That's
what I do. But before you keep saying,
"I'll do nothing." Well, tell me where
to meet you then. At least if you're
going to say to someone that they're
going to do nothing, at least tell them
where to meet you before saying that.
You know, [ __ ] fat little non
flubbing [ __ ] I saw you on Nons's
channel earlier as well, you little non
lover. You fat little non lover. Yeah.
most loving [ __ ]
I'll laugh at you through your face in
front of everyone, bro. You know what I mean?
Explain to me what you mean by you no
one takes my word seriously.
You've been showing money, women, friends,
me going to meet people for fights. I
mean, like I said, we've already
established your bias on it. You make
excuses. Look at Look at the excuse you
made for the bouncer.
He was at work. You're full of excuses,
you little nub.
So, I mean, what does someone need to do?
I I do you know what? Yeah.
If you don't take me seriously, why
don't you tell me where to meet you
tomorrow then? And I'll meet you. Then
everyone will take me serious, won't they?
I don't like a lot of people on here.
Obviously, I like people on here, but a
lot of these people I don't like.
I don't like what they do.
You know what I mean? I don't go on L J
because this is the same repeat and I mean
my man can't even talk on a panel, bro.
And he's trying to talk about people not
taking people seriously, but he can't
even talk on a [ __ ] panel. Jesus Christ.
He's another nonsex.
is another non leg shows a bra.
Another non leg yummy one.
Another fat old man.
He makes excuses
for all makes up excuses.
He makes up excuses, bro.
He was like, "Oh, the bouncer couldn't
hit you cuz he was at work." Yeah,
bounces hit people all the time. He started it.
Then we give another example. Then we
give another example. The two people sat
down and it's another excuse and then
another excuse and then another excuse.
That's what they like on here, bro.
But Grezy don't think they're biased.
Okay, Greasy. Okay, Greasy. So, you're
telling you're telling me, right?
You're telling me that if L J
done what I done with that bouncer,
people would be making excuses.
No, they wouldn't. I I don't think he
really understands the definition of biasness.
No, I don't think he does. By the way,
Trip H, this Smokeoky Be's not coming
tomorrow and he's got away with it. No
one said anything about it. He's got
This is what I mean with these little
clowns on here. I'm going to call that
Joseph Ferrara out, bro. I want to start
some trouble tomorrow, bro. I'm going to
start some trouble.
Is that all right with you, Greasy?
It's a bit too quiet for my liking. cuz
I wanted a good oldfashioned punchup.
I wanted a good oldfashioned punchup,
you know. Is that okay with you, boss?
I'm just going to call out that [ __ ]
nons lover, Joseph. I'm going to call
I'm going to call out that [ __ ] nonsubbery.
Okay with you, boss.
Obviously, I have to I have to run it by you first
cuz I don't want to starve you off
content, you pucker.
I'm going to start on that [ __ ] Jo
cuz he's talking his [ __ ] again.
You You just do a video explaining where
to meet you, right? And I will come and
laugh in your face. I will come and
laugh at you in your face
and go live. And if you're not willing
to do it, just stop your stop your [ __ ]
talking, old man.
You fat little nons lover.
No, but he's talking [ __ ] bro. But this
guy's got a big mouth. This Joseph
Ferrar has got a big mouth, bro. I don't
like him, but he's got a big mouth and
he's a little nonsob
he gives it the bigger, bro. Like, he's
gave it the big. So, at the end of the
day, bro, I'll happily meet you
tomorrow. You know, it's not a problem.
I'll travel to you tomorrow if you want.
And if you're not, then you'll do
nothing. You'll do nothing. [ __ ] tell
me I'm going to do nothing. You [ __ ]
fat old man.
Trying to tell me I'm going to do some
nothing. You [ __ ] fat old man.
The only people that won't do anything
is you and your [ __ ] boyfriend on
legs. You pair of [ __ ]
That's the only pair of [ __ ] that won't do anything.
Well, tell him to shut his mouth then.
Tell him to shut his mouth then, bro.
Tell him to shut his little non-sloving mouth.
Stop acting like you're some kind of big
man then, bro. Stop acting like you're a
big man. Simple
cuz I'll happily come tomorrow and laugh
in your face.
If that's better than fighting, I'll
come and laugh in your face. It's not a problem.
Stop [ __ ] writing your stupid shitty
little bias comments, you know, simple.
But yeah, no one's going to call this
Smokey Be out for [ __ ] it.
Yeah. No one No one is No one is dusty.
Do I think they're biased?
I'll I'll just I'll just go and laugh in
his face. Yeah, no fight. I'll just go
and travel and laugh in his face.
I'll just go and laugh in his face. It's
not a problem. Little lavry, little nons.
I knew he was a [ __ ] anyways. He comes
from that channel. Anyone that comes
from that channel is a [ __ ]
Anyone that does, you see that doggy
account earlier? Anyone that comes from
Lav's channel is an absolute [ __ ]
You know what I mean?
little moronic morons. They got owned by
[ __ ] Laney. For [ __ ] sake, a 66
year old woman owned them.
And I'll say to him, you will never.
Yeah, that's why I'm not interested in
him, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] about him.
But this Joseph Ferrar, don't try and
tell me about people can't take my word
seriously when you can't even talk on a
panel. I have met more people than both
of your boyfriends combined, you little
[ __ ] But you still make up excuses.
You still make up excuses. You little
gay boy. So shut the [ __ ] up. You either
shut your mouth or meet me. Simple. You know,
and that's that. And he's he's also been
harassing me as well. Kind of, bro. A
few of these people have been harassing me, you know.
So, you know, like that Joseph Farra,
he's been harassing me as well, bro.
women me hard. Tell the guy to go. Tell
him to meet me.
Tell him to meet me. Simple, bro. Tell him.
That's what I've done. That's what I've
done. Delayed. But I just wanted to put
the stepdad thing out there.
Yeah, I have done that, bro.
But that Joseph Ferrar is no better, bro. You know,
it just goes to show no matter what you
do, they're always going to Oh, [ __ ]
They're always going to talk [ __ ]
They were calling me a [ __ ] virgin in
Timmy's yesterday. The only one that
defended me was [ __ ] Steven Howard.
So, I'm thinking, what? What the [ __ ]
Not that I care that people think I'm a
virgin. I don't care. But I find it
weird why they would call you a virgin
when you've proved you've had sex. But I
don't care that they do. I just think it
would be weird as to why they would
continuously ask people to prove stuff
if when they get proven wrong, they
still talk [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? I just don't
understand why they're still asking
people to prove stuff. When when they
get proven wrong, they they still talk [ __ ] So
yeah, that Joseph Ferrar is definitely a
proper proper non-slber.
The only one living in poverty is him.
And he needs And another thing, Triple
H. Yeah, don't be fooled by these
receipts that he's um showing you.
Nobody wins like that, bro. Nobody wins
like that. You know it and I know it.
Uh, no matter what form of gambling you
do, people are not winning all the time.
People are not winning all the time like
that. Do you not see what he's what this
little mug is doing?
Like it's trust me, bro. So, how long
Listen, when was the last time Yeah. you
heard this guy has had a big losing session
on a fy? When was the last time, bro?
Yeah. Not for a long time because the
guy is full of [ __ ] He's only showing
wins and he probably loses like a 10020
then puts money in to make it seem like
he's won. You can't win like that, bro.
You can't. I used to go to casino every
Thursday, bro. And I used to win a lot,
but with big wins come with big losses,
bro. Oh, some losses. He hasn't said
that he's lost in ages.
The guy is a [ __ ] bullshitter.
So, don't let that tempt you into I'll
put the link up now. Don't let that
tempt you into [ __ ] gambling again, bro. Cuz
he's full of [ __ ]
If you can't see what he's trying to do, bro, then
machines are the worst things to gamble
on, bro. They'll [ __ ] you over.
[ __ ] you over,
>> but he continuously seems to win on them.
You don't see what this guy's trying to
do, bro. I don't think you understand
what he's trying to do.
His channel is basically dedicated to
me. In a in a in an indirect way, like
indirectly, I don't think you get it, bro.
The guy's got a 200lb phone. The guy
wears 30 jeans. The guy's [ __ ]
holiday into motor and he's trying to
talk about people [ __ ] living under poverty.
Guy's an absolute [ __ ] clown.
Pennywise the clown.
I might title it Joe F the Pennywise clown.
It's It's not adding up, bro. You can't
win. And I don't care who has more money
than me, who don't. I've got my own
money. I can do what I want. I'm telling
you from experience that you can't win
the amount um of times that he does
and not lose. We've not heard any losing sessions
for I can't remember the last time this
guy said he's lost.
>> Oh, Triple H. >> Yo,
>> yeah. Yeah,
>> brother. This this guy Yeah. He's not
showing his losses. I'm just letting you
know that. Is it?
>> Yeah. I've come on to say that about
that you actually to be honest I don't
mind him I think he's all right but I
agree I 100% what you've just said he's
always winning and like he hasn't like
we haven't seen any loser like losers I
know what you mean and he's not and he's
not said he's lost as well for a very
very very very long time and bro anyone
that gles like that would lose as well
cuz I used to lose as well
>> and I agree with what you said yeah 100%
because that's never happened to me I
lose I lose nine times out of 10 when I
used to play them D's
when I and it's like when I used to go
to a casino like a land base, I'd win a
lot, but you'd always hear losing
sessions. I'd lose like a grand at some
type point as well, you know.
>> Definitely. But I agree what you're
saying that Joe doesn't seem to be
losing. Maybe he's on a lucky streak,
but it just still doesn't add up. But
he's got no reason to
>> It doesn't add up on a FBI. It doesn't
add up on a FBI especially, you know.
>> Yeah, I agree. Yeah. Yeah. Cuz they are
the honorable them days. But [snorts]
>> bless you and your little northeast dialect.
But yeah, I thought I'll jump on to
speak about that. Yeah, I totally agree
with what you're saying. Yeah.
>> God bless. Yeah. And he doesn't even say
that he's lost like a 100red or 200.
It's so weird, isn't it?
>> It's a win. It's a win all the time. And
I agree. Yeah. I
>> something something's not adding up in it.
>> There's something not right. Is there
like [laughter] But saying that like to
be give give him a bit of credit here.
He has been like a lot of money in and
then he's ended up clawing it back and
end up making a profit. But it it just
doesn't add up. I agree what you're saying. But
>> and they can and it can only like they
can only pay out like 500 of the bonus.
So like you know what I mean? [laughter]
>> At the end of the day if this streak if
this if he's winning every single day
that he doesn't need to work, does he?
The way I look at you don't need to work.
>> Yeah, pretty much.
>> You can live up machines, couldn't he? I
>> Yeah, [laughter] it's not It's not
possible, though. It
>> No, it's not possible. No, I've done
balls in plenty of times. Had to walk
home with me tail between me legs and
>> Oh, bless you then.
>> Are you having Are you having a little drink?
>> No, I'm not drinking, mate. No. Um, I'm
not drinking out of the boxing day.
>> Bless you then. Little accent.
>> I've just been doing the garage about
about half four. I've been a bit busy
sorting all the garage in that house out.
>> You've been where?
>> I've been doing the garage.
>> Oh, okay. Okay. Okay.
>> I've been sorting all that out. And
>> you're having you're having some digestive biscuits.
>> I've had a couple of Jaffa cakes about
10 minutes ago.
>> I had some digestive biscuits like 10
minutes ago. They were yummy, bro.
>> The halfcoated ones. Yeah.
>> Yeah. They're nice.
>> Oh, do you know someone Do you know
someone called Danny Dier?
>> I do. Yes. Um yes, I do know him.
>> How do you know who he is?
>> He was doing all them TV programs and
he's been in films and that before. He's
been in that um football factory. Good actor.
>> Yeah, he's a he's a cockley. You know
what that is? He's a cocky actor, isn't it?
>> Yeah, he's from down London. Yeah, he's Londoner.
>> And then you come here with your little
Jordy accent. Bless you.
>> So yeah, like I said about that John
Johnson, you need to um just [ __ ]
>> you need to stop giving him a platform.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] him. But no, no, that person
in the community post, that's his stepdad.
>> That's his stepdad, bro.
>> Have been nasty. I'm not I'm not
drinking, mate. 26. It's not Yeah. That
day for Campbell. He's a good fellow.
Yeah. Yeah. I've just
>> Yeah. That's That's the one that gave
him grief and [ __ ] is it?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I'm not drinking to New Year's
Eve. [ __ ] it in it.
>> Yeah. I don't blame you. It's not where
I felt, man. It's not where I left.
>> Oh, I was I was talking to a [ __ ]
woman on Instagram earlier. She was 45
and she was being a [ __ ] She was trying
to say she can't get with me because of
distance and she only lives like 130
miles away, bro. What the [ __ ] [laughter] Yeah.
>> It's weird, isn't it? It's [ __ ] 45y old woman.
>> This is what these people do, isn't it?
>> They're [ __ ] idiots, isn't it?
>> Bless you.
>> No, I've got a garage, Steven. I just
got it all. I've been down the skip and
things like that. I got all the [ __ ] out
the garage. I've uh
>> Oh, have you seen that police video
where that the police go on the guy's
door and says, "Oh, we're advising you
not to go to the football match." You
saw it, is it?
>> I've seen that. The Sunderland athletes
are beauty and the lad's already got his ticket. Yeah.
>> Oh, watch out. your accent. That was
your little accent, didn't it?
>> Yeah, I watched that last night. Peter,
>> please come on the door in it. [laughter]
>> Where did it come off on?
>> Say that again.
>> Where did it come up on?
>> Tik Tok for you to watch it.
>> Huh? Tik Tok. Yeah. [laughter]
>> Ah, you come up on there, lad.
>> Bless you then. Bless you in live. Bless you.
So what's going on with this Smokey B
then? Are you filling him in there?
>> He's not He's not coming.
>> He's not coming. No.
>> [ __ ] hell.
>> But no one's going to give him. See what
I mean? No. No one's going to give him
grief for it. See, they're biased, isn't it?
>> Of course they're not. No, they're not.
That's what they do, don't they?
>> Yeah. But what if what if I didn't turn
up? That never hit the last of it, is it?
>> Oh, it'll go on for go on for years,
wouldn't it? That's what they do.
No. So, but that Jo that Jo is biased
though. He is biased. Even if you like
him, you can like him. But I'm just
saying he's biased. Look.
>> Um to be fair, I don't mind that. I
think he's all right. But I agree about
um the them roulette them property
videos like like
he always wins, doesn't he? Just seem to
lose and that's the case. He doesn't
need to work then if that's the case.
>> It's like that stop and it's like that
stop and step. He only shows wins.
That's true. Yeah. Yeah.
>> When I used to I used to show wins. I
used to show wins and losses in it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. That's true.
>> So, it doesn't add up.
>> No, there's no way you're going nine
days on the bounce winning without a
loss. It just >> No,
>> I'd like Joseph Ferrar come up on the
box. We got we might have us talk about
this um situation. But
>> yeah, but Joseph
>> Joseph Ross get to talk. So that's not
going to happen.
>> Yeah, cuz it's not
>> I don't know why. We don't want to see
his face. Just talk in it. [ __ ] Don't
you don't have to show your face. Just
talk in it. You know.
>> That's it. Hi. Hi.
>> How's your How's your phone been? Is the
battery all right and that? Yeah,
>> battery's bang on. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Lovely.
>> Good. The LT doesn't
>> the LT doesn't come on anymore, does he?
>> I don't blame him, to be honest. I don't
blame Taylor not coming out here full of
[ __ ] lunatics, man. [laughter]
>> Yeah, it's true. And it's true. Yeah.
>> Taylor's got his own business and he's
got a family and hasn't he like
done the right thing in it. Done the
>> He did do the right thing. Yeah. Good on
the lad. If I was if I didn't break up
with my girlfriend, I probably wouldn't
be on here as much. But now I'm I'm on a lot. [laughter]
>> Yeah. Why not in it? [ __ ] it.
>> Yeah. Come up Joseph and explain explain
what what's going on in it. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Cuz even on football, say you've done a
double both teams to score on football.
Even then you're not winning all the
time. And that's like probably the best
odds. I mean, even then you're not
winning all the time, bro.
>> That's Yeah. But even a double both
teams to score it. That's still hard,
you know, of anything cuz you you need a
nil or one nil. You [ __ ] It's Yeah, but
it's it's easier on the on the crap
teams. Like say the national league
that's easier, but that like league one
and league two is hard. Yeah, it's hard, bro.
>> But on like a shitty league, it's easier.
>> That's just a guess game in it. Like
like football game. Even both teams can
score. Any team can score against
anyone. It just
>> Well, I my best ones are like the the
National League on the Tuesdays. I've
always won on the Tuesdays, but they
don't all play on the Tuesday. every
Tuesday. They don't always do it every
>> Yeah, they don't. Yeah. Yeah.
>> But when they do, there's always goals
on that Tuesday. Always.
>> I was going to have a bet yesterday on
the Europa League and had a one
actually. I was I was going to have a 20
just on um Celia. Both teams gone. I
think Rome Celtic there one, but I
didn't put the bet on. I didn't go to
the bench. No.
>> You said you never put you would never
put 120 on a bet in it. Probably not cuz
there's no reason for me to do that to
be honest. Like I'd have a shot of 20
bar like I don't know treble or
>> that's what Antman does. Antman said the same thing.
>> It's it's you put 20 quid on a on an
even money swap to wins that you've
doubled your money. But I just don't see
the point. Or but if you if you do the
120 on the double both teams to score
and it's got like 60% 70% chance of
coming in and that's you you um you
treble your money.
>> That is true. Yeah. But it's quite difficult.
>> It's a lot. It's a lot to lose, isn't it?
>> Well, it is. Yeah. Like all these people
who are here are millionaires, aren't they? So >> yeah,
>> that wouldn't bother them.
>> They say they're millionaires and it Yeah.
>> Yeah. That's what they're doing.
The problem with these people is if you
put £200 on a bet, you'd be skinting.
They'd put £250 on a bet. You can't win with them.
>> They're idiots, is it? Yeah. They give
you brain damage in it. But like, you
know, if if you put £500 on online
roulette yet, is there a chance you
could get it to three grand? There's a
chance, though. There it
>> actually. [ __ ] hell. There's another Sorry, P.
>> No. Do you reckon there's a chance?
>> Say that again. Sorry. If you put If you
put 500 pound on roulette yet online, do
you reckon there's a chance you could win big?
>> Of course, there's a chance. Yeah.
>> What? Online? [snorts]
>> It depends. You could do one spin. You
could have 500 quid in second, doesn't
that comes in at 1,500 quid? You've made
£1,000 within I know 10 seconds. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Or it could or it could missing it.
>> Or it could missing your 500 quid down.
That's just You've got a 33% chance of
winning then if you done it that way
because you've got your D, haven't you?
>> Yeah. I don't play that roulette anymore. Me.
>> Imagine doing that though. Having 500
quid on a dozen and it comes in, man.
You just [ __ ] rift.
>> That's what that's what Michael Basset
used to do. He used to do the dozens.
>> Yeah, probably is the best way winning
on gambling on the r.
>> Yeah, but zero can [ __ ] you up and other
two dozens can [ __ ] you up.
>> Have you ever tried that method before?
I know it could go bad, but this is what
this is my next next time I'm in the
casino. This is what I'm going to do.
I'm going to start with 20, but
obviously just have 20 quid and if it
loses or 20 quid red or black come
[snorts] and if it doesn't come in 40
quid, then 80 then 160.
>> It's called It's called a Sic system.
It's called a marin something.
>> Yeah, I know what you mean. That's what
it's called. Yeah, there's no way around
losing like very rare you'll see seven
or eight red seven or eight of the same
color coming in on a roulette table. It
does happen, but that's only on the FOB TE's.
>> So, you'll start with 20 and then keep
doubling it, isn't it?
>> So, even if you lose five times, what's
that? 20 40 then 40 80 160 320 and then
you've got that 320 and then on the six
spin you're going to make 320 profit. If
I lose 640, within them six spins, you
are going to rip a color. I don't care
what you say. And I'd like I'd like to
test our outlet in the casino.
>> Someone said it's like listening to Ant
and Deck. [laughter]
>> These people are sad, isn't it? They're
sad on it, is it? >> Yeah.
>> How do you remember that Tommy sideburns
account? That's weird.
>> Yeah, I can remember that from the
>> Yeah, they had like a picture of the
sideburn in it and he said he said to
me, "Why you always angry that you remember?" [laughter]
>> Yeah, he did. Yeah, I think that was
that a refra? Yeah, he got he's behind a
lot of accounts.
>> He's got a few accounts, Harry. Yeah.
>> Will he stop next year?
>> Nope. Never stop, Harry.
>> I'm literally going to go on Lord James
live the first of January, bro. See you.
And I'll just sit there and wait, brief
you. I'll wait until there's different
people in there. I'll wait until they
stop repeating it. I'll just wait, bro.
>> I'll never stop repeating these people.
It's hardly have man in life. [laughter]
You got a name because of through Timmy
El didn't it?
>> That's honestly that's the reason I did
I was watching like outside the gambling
videos me and used to watch um I watch a
few people and I come across this fruit
mad world one day
I went on his channel and then ever
since then I thought it was Tim Eldridge
who got me on here like
>> it [snorts] used to be uh that the
community used to be more active in it.
>> Oh it was good in the day wasn't it?
Remember when you used to go live on
playing that GT and B know and that used
to be in and there was brown sauce on Governor and >> Yeah.
>> that was when it was at its peak this
YouTube without fail at least someone
live wasn't there constantly.
>> Yeah. Craig Goodson.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> I wonder what that little [ __ ] is up to nowadays.
>> He was having a baby or something. Was that
>> I was I was watching Tim Eldridge. Yeah.
Yesterday he was making me laugh. He
says I'm sorry. Do you remember he was
in the pub drinking saying I'm dead in it?
>> I've seen that. Yeah. Quite a glimpse of
that actually. Sorry man. He was I think
he was saying sorry to Smokey Be or
someone in it.
>> Was Smokey there? Yeah. Did you also see
Tim Eldridge leave that pub? Because the
voice of reason rang the pub.
>> Yeah. He needs to get off YouTube. Is it
>> the voice of reason or Tim Eldridge?
>> Tim Eldridge in it.
>> Tim Eldridge you won't get off. He's
he's deep. And they even maintier,
you know, when he was fatter, he looked
more healthier then when he was fat than
he does now. You know what I mean?
>> He does. Yeah. Yeah. I think he's on
some hardcore drugs. [laughter]
>> He will never get off YouTube.
>> Nah. What they've done to Tim Elder on
the YouTube and he's he's still here to
this day, lad. So
>> he's still here, Grezy. He's he won't
get off. Why won't he get off YouTube?
>> They've wrote his auntie Rose. must have
wrote his brother's work. I think it's
that voice of reason behind it all, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> He was going to cash your betting as
well. Remember that?
>> He's a bastard. That voice of reason.
>> I beat I beat them to it though. I beat
them to it.
>> You did? Yeah. Did that come back on me?
Because look what happened at the train
on the train. That wouldn't have
happened if I didn't go and [ __ ] know
what I mean. I wouldn't have got in that argument.
>> Yeah, that's true. Yeah, but you're at
the you have to make sure you beat the
voice. the reason to that because
>> so you you so you reckon if I went at 1
pm it would have been cashed in
>> Oh most definitely I told you this
>> they would they would have done it just
to be a [ __ ] it yeah
>> I've seen an account um I think you end
of the live and I seen an account
kicking about on someone's chat and they
took a screen like they took a
screenshot to read your barcode so all
they have to do is put the phone under
the reads the barcode and they just catch it >> yeah
people do lad
They're sad in it. These people sad it
>> on that night. The R thingy, the R
speaking about it saying um hopefully
someone cashes his bet and like
>> Yeah, they're sad. [laughter]
>> No, they don't. They don't. They don't. These people.
>> Yeah, but you laugh about what it isn't
funny. It's [ __ ] sad, isn't it?
Really laughing. You're laughing. I'm
not laughing. You're laughing.
grown men wanting to go and cash and
runs betting to beat them to betting
shops. [ __ ] it's absolutely crazy.
>> You used to laugh at the account like to
me as a legend.
>> You used to laugh at the You used to
laugh at a Buzz Lightyear account.
>> I did laugh. I just thought it was sad
really what they're doing like grown men.
>> They're like old men making Buzz Lightyear accounts.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> You're watching You're watching that
You're watching that Toy Story 5, isn't it?
>> No, I won't be watching that. off.
>> Yeah, but you know what it is. It's a
kids film, isn't it?
>> That was when I was a kid. Yeah. >> Woody.
>> Yeah. Woody and Buzz Light you in it. [clears throat]
>> What you What are you doing on your
birthday? You say
>> I'm not sure. Probably going go I might
go for Sunday.
>> No one's really No one's really going to
be If you went out drinking, no one's
really out anywhere in it. That's the
problem. Oh, but I agree what you're
saying. Even like
even like through the air and that like
it's not massively packed like it's
bankers is is um if you're on a banker but like
>> as soon as soon as New Year's Eve as
soon as New Year's Eve is um over the
clubs and pubs they're not going to be
releasing until like midFebruary
>> the ear.
>> Yeah. But even now, even like before
December, the a lot of pubs were like up
here were shutting down that cuz no one
was going in. No one was.
>> Yeah. It's like it's like the pub near
where my mom lives. Yeah. Not central
like the pub near where my mom lives.
[ __ ] um No, you don't see anyone in them.
>> You don't? It's the same up here. Like
there's a pub next to me and it's uh
>> they don't have money. That's people
don't have money. That's why
>> no one has gotten It's a [ __ ] It's
not good, is it, lad? They haven't.
And obviously central London, the reason
they're open, they're able to keep them
open in central London is because they
get people coming from abroad like
France and that. So obviously that's how
they stay in business. You see what I mean?
America and that
not these people from [ __ ] you know
what I mean.
You should go to Newcastle triple
>> like on the night life.
>> Yeah. It's got to be busy, ain't it? New
Why don't you Why don't you give that a
whirl on New Year's Eve?
>> Nah, it's a good trek from me. London's
about 5 hours.
>> No, not London. Newcastle.
>> Oh, Newcastle. I'm
>> going to Newcastle New Year's Eve. >> Yeah.
>> Where was I think I was on I did get
mentioned actually with Dham as well
mentioned, but I don't know what I'm doing yet.
>> How How far was it in the car,
Newcastle? Like quite a while.
>> Oh yeah. No about [ __ ] it's about
about for me is about 20 minutes
>> more on the motorway is it?
>> Well yeah
>> and what about Middlesbrough 20 minutes as well.
>> I think B is a little bit further cuz
it's going the other way in it. So
>> B's about half an hour or something 35 minutes.
>> Bless you then. Yeah. So you could
easily get like an Uber back worse comes
to worse than it.
>> Yeah. It won't cost much like lad. Yeah.
Have you ever been leads for a night
out? You might like leads.
>> I've not been leaded. No, I'm good lead.
But Liver L.
>> That's a good night out. Yeah,
>> that's a good night out. And Liverpool
>> You've been Liverpool?
>> Yeah, only once.
>> Did you enjoy it?
>> Yeah, it was all right, but it was very
cold. It was in January. >> Hello.
>> Hello. Can you hear me? Yeah, this the
phone just went off there.
>> Yeah, I said it was uh I said it was
Yeah, I went in January. It was all right. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Did you enjoy Manchester better
than Liverpool? Liverpool better than Manchester?
>> Uh Liverpool, I think, bro.
>> Yeah, it's [ __ ]
>> I've been to Manchester like 10 times,
bro. And I've already been Liverpool
once. I need to go back some point.
>> I will be going back at some point,
right? But I do want to try Manchester
and Leads. Um but I went for the
weekend. Me I went um went we traveled
down on the Friday morning and we didn't
come home on Sunday like Sunday dinner
didn't [ __ ] good week on that.
>> You met you met some birds in it?
>> No, I was in a relationship then lad.
No, I didn't.
>> Did you get did you get any woman come
up to you?
>> Had a few mate. Yeah. Yeah.
>> What What do they say?
>> Yeah. warehouse. That's where I was from
and things like that at the moment. [laughter]
>> The trip rate's getting cold approach
and yeah, I speak to them as well. Like
it's just it's a natural thing. It's okay. Like
>> what did you what did you tell them you
had a girlfriend?
>> No, I wasn't. But didn't you get that
like that far into
like I like your accent and you're not
from here and then blah blah from
Newcastle and blahy blah.
>> Yeah. The Scouse accent is grim, is it?
Yeah, I like it. Me like
[ __ ] hate that scout accent. The
scout especially scout beds man.
>> I hate the Brmy accent. It's annoying,
isn't it? That's wild. That's wild.
>> Yeah, it's not the best that I
>> bless you then. >> Huh?
>> Do you reckon that Tim did you'll end up
getting off of you then?
>> Nah. What do you think? Uh Greasy
Steven, do you reckon Tim is coming off
YouTube? He'll die on here in it.
Yeah, they've got that Mag Edwards off, haven't they?
>> Yeah, there's rumors going about that
he's killed himself.
>> Is there [ __ ] hell?
>> Yeah, I think someone [laughter] went up killing himself.
>> Triple C and [ __ ]
>> I reckon I reckon someone went up
killing himself on it though.
He left that Steven George put Seaside's
last um last video up and he was he was
on about suicide. Really?
>> Yeah. But what these people have done,
the just what they're doing that is like
>> Yeah. Monty man's not been live, has he?
>> No. He hasn't been live for a bit.
Monty, man, has he? No. No. >> No.
>> I only I only jump when I don't even
speak in there, me and I. I just watch
it and it's just the same [ __ ] He's
just [ __ ] walking around in circles.
>> Yeah. What about the comments? Are they
Is that the same [ __ ]
Just say me mango and all that [ __ ] and
>> your skin.
>> Yeah. And he's a nons and all that [ __ ] said.
>> It's the same old it say Monty said it's
the same people doing the same [ __ ]
Monty's right. Yeah, it is. It's uh it's
Grevy Seaside used. I go with a few
people. Maybe ask one of them. David C.
Seagull. Oh, I didn't know that. Grevy.
Yeah. Um that [snorts] David C was a big
um big fan of Marks when he used to
always be commenting on that mate. Hi.
He used to send him a lot of gifts as
well, didn't he? That David C.
See, this is what I mean. Look at Nons's
post. He tried he tries to [ __ ] straight
the thing up with me and Smokeoky B. But
he would never meet anyone. I'm not
reacting. I'm just saying, bro. But what
I'm saying is these people on here like
him cuz these people on here are nons like him.
>> Do you know what? I know exactly what it
is. These people don't like Sean. They
know he's a wrong and he's a
>> Yeah, but even No, no, no, but no, no.
Even when you even when you come off,
bro, they still won't go for him. Like,
they go for Monty and that. That's what
I'm saying. I know what you I know what
you're saying. I'm saying I know
>> there's a reason behind that because
they hate you even more. So, if he's
saying, but what I'm saying No, but what
I'm saying is if I come off of it,
right, for like two months, three
months, they're still not going to go
for him. That's what I'm trying to say.
>> Oh, I know. I know what you're saying. I
know what you're saying, but what I'm
saying is they're still not going to go
for him even if I was off here.
>> Not necessarily. It depends how long you
were off here for. If you were off here
for 6 months and didn't no videos, no
live, no comment, they'd go for someone
else. But I'm telling you now, they'd
attack someone else.
>> Yeah, they might. Yeah, but
>> it take a while like But they would
>> What you reckon they would go for him?
>> They might do. Yeah, because they've got
now else no one else to go for if you off. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Did you see it before? Yeah. When
when the person that they used to go for
come off YouTube, they used to switch on
themselves for content. Did you see it?
They used to switch on each
[clears throat] other. >> No.
>> Yeah. They switch on each other. Yeah.
Didn't you see that, bro? Really? They
used to do it. Yeah.
>> We If you come off here like saying
Okay. Say me, Timmy. Mark's off here.
Me, Timmy, Mark, and Monty was off here.
Like, so was off here. They would start
arguing with each other. That's what I'm saying. [laughter]
>> Yeah. And and that's that's that's the
life, isn't it, man? It's so sad it is,
isn't it? Really?
>> Is it a normal community?
>> No, it's in a community like it. [snorts]
>> I wish I'd never gamble, bro. Then I
wouldn't be on here, you know.
>> How did you end up getting any of that
Tim Eldridge then?
>> Tim Aldridge. The old property videos, bro.
>> Yeah, that's what I used to watch as
well. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Cuz I used to play them because I I got
into it through my sister's like
boyfriend. and he introduced me to like
the machines I played. I was like, "Oh,
let me look at other people playing
them." And I found I found someone
called Timmy Eldridge.
>> Yeah. Fruit Madwell. That's what I did. I was
>> I got Monty on here. You remember when I
got Monty on here?
>> Yeah. You got him on here, didn't you?
>> Got me on this shitty community.
>> That was through lockdown, wasn't it?
You got that Monty man on?
>> Yeah. I said, "Oh, do you want to come
on this community? There's someone
called Timmy Eldridge. I think you would love it." [laughter]
And I think that was the start of
Monty's life getting ruined, isn't it?
Yeah, like what what they've done to
that money, man, is not right. Like cuz
it's like they're meant to have families
and [ __ ] they're meant to be grown
men and the
it's like crack in it. Like
>> these are grown men doing it. >> Yeah. >> What?
>> It is bad, is it?
>> Yeah. At the end of the day, they can't
have much in life, can they? They
continuously doing this everyday life. Yeah.
>> Well, yeah.
Grecy, how did you get to my get in the park? Steven
Timmy. Oh, did you get on here by um
Timmy? Steven Howard G. You got on here by G. >> Yeah.
>> How did How did G even get into the community?
>> [ __ ] knows. She didn't gamble, does she? Mm-m.
>> Nah, bro. No. You
>> Oh, [ __ ] me.
>> Have you eaten the day like?
>> Yeah, I had um chicken and chips.
>> I went to the um the skip earlier, lad.
And I um I had a Christmas
>> the skip to get all the skip to get take
all your rubbish down. And I went there and then
>> I went to that Morrison's and got a um I
got a [ __ ] meal deal. A big Red Bull
uh pasti and uh chicken and like an all
like Christmas wrap was nice.
>> Yeah. Nice. How much?
>> 375 me day. Good buy that.
>> Yeah. Nice. Bro, the Morrison's are
[ __ ] closing down here. There's one
in Shrapid where I used to live. I've
never been to another one.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I like Morrison's. Like it is expensive.
>> Yeah, it's nice. The steak's nice as well. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> It's good that. Have you ever shopped in
Aldi or little? Yeah.
>> Yeah. What? Yeah. I don't know. Maybe
you haven't. I don't. What do you mean?
Maybe you didn't. I don't like the food there.
>> I tell you what, I don't like from Aldi.
I don't like the chocolate and the
crystal [ __ ] but the [ __ ]
>> You know, you know the best bacon and
sausages is [ __ ] little. It is, bro.
It sounds I'm telling you, bro. They do
best sausage and bacon.
>> Just sh talking about meal dudes on a Friday night.
>> Oh, you know, listen. You know, I was
Triple H. I was looking Yeah. when I
first had this phone last November and I
was going back on old screenshots and
it's the same people from even then.
Like, come on now.
>> What? The same account? >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] madness. It's not >> Huh?
>> Go on. It's
>> scary. I know when you think of it.
>> Some of these accounts were made like 17
years ago. That's how you know they're
old people. Because when you look on
their accounts, right, some of it will
say 13 to 17 years. That's how you know they're old.
>> That's [ __ ] mental in it.
>> Yeah. You can see when the account was made.
>> [ __ ] unbelievable. That would ever
get off here, you reckon? I think I I
don't know. It's hard to guess who he
is. I I I think he's Harry Fraud, but I
could be wrong. I think that asylum's
Ari Fraud, [snorts] but I don't know.
It's hard to
>> Yeah, there's an account that always
comes in. There's an account that comes
on and says Peter Belly, you need to
find your mama. But I don't know who it
is. I don't know. I don't think it's
Joker. People saying it's Joker. I don't
think it is.
>> No, I don't think that's Joker.
>> I don't know who it is. I don't know who
it is. You know the kind I'm talking
about is it where it comes in a mox.
There's nothing there's nothing you can
do to change your [ __ ] in citro like mock. >> Yeah.
>> I don't know who it is.
>> Who would you guess it is? >> Um
if I was going to guess who I think it
was, I'd say I'd probably go for
Leaper Jones or Barra.
>> Yeah. Yeah. That Lee Jones remember he
was a leak. He's a freak in it.
>> Lee for free. Yeah.
>> Grey and Steven Howard. Who do you think
it is that account?
>> That's my two guesses. It's either
Barrist or Leaf for free.
>> You've seen it. Is it Greavvesy? It's
the one that said you can't leave
YouTube, Peter Belly. You can't leave
Greavvesy without any content. The poor [ __ ] [laughter]
>> That's what I'm saying. Yeah, that's
what he said. Yeah. I don't know who it
is, but it keeps coming back and it will
go for like a couple weeks and it will
come back on like another account and
you know it's the same person in it.
>> Yeah. I've not seen that. I haven't seen
the account for for a bit now. Like
>> you've seen it though. Is it?
>> I've seen it. Yeah. You haven't seen
>> What did What did it say again?
>> Something about your mama. You need You
need to find your mama. That's what I mean.
>> And it says it says elephant and Peter
Benny's got a lot of history in elephant and castle.
What's elephant in the castle?
>> Oh, it's a place where I had a one night
stand with someone. It's an actual place.
>> All right. Yeah. Yeah.
>> They know. They know. And And you can
tell they've been on it for years.
There's like I said to the account.
Yeah. How do you know about that? And it
said, "We know all of Peter Benny's
dates." That's what it said. We all know
about Peter Betty's dates. Weird.
>> By by the sounds that's been going on a
while. He's been watching you for a
while, hasn't he?
>> It could be just someone. Yeah. that's
gone on a night out that's gone on a
night out pissed come backs and like
types [ __ ] to mock you out. You don't
know is it?
>> Yeah. Don't know what is to hear exactly. Yeah.
>> But it's weird though, isn't it? Cuz
you're talking to them and they're
typing to you back saying was never your
mama here. Benny, it's weird, isn't it?
>> I think that new account came in the
other day was saying about your car
case. What was he called? Ryan.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah,
>> was a new person, but he knew a lot
about you. So, I thought it must be one of those.
>> A lot of these accounts were that Terry
as well, believe it or not.
>> Oh, is that Terry got a few? Has he?
>> Yeah. Do you know who that is?
>> Yeah, that [ __ ] one with the trainers. [laughter]
>> You know it. You know
>> they're off them trainers. Like,
>> would you wear them?
>> No, I wouldn't wear them. No, them green
big green luminous ones wear them.
[ __ ] madness. [ __ ] madness.
>> It's a mother, lad.
>> So, like when you found out Yeah. that
you was having a baby, did you cry? >> No.
Was happy that be like, but I didn't cry.
>> Yeah. [laughter] Yeah. But did you did
you did you actually want to keep it or not?
>> Yeah. I
>> Okay. Well, some people don't want that
kid in it. That's why I asked.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You you
>> Some people try it.
>> They do. Yeah. Yeah. Um I think what you
that could do you the world a good
getting yourself a lass and having your
own family and it probably would get you
off a year but [laughter]
no but some people still come on it is
it sad is it?
>> Yeah. Do you know where I thought Steven
Howard was that Barney Rubble? [laughter]
Bar remember Barney Rubble
>> vaguely. It rings a bell.
>> I could be wrong. I think that's that um
that guy who used to go to gu place and
eat the free food.
>> The only couch yet. It doesn't even seem
like it's it seems like a robot typing
um behind it because how can they do the
same thing for years?
>> It's because they've like it's clear,
isn't it? They've got nowhere else
better to do than come. They do this as
soon as they wake up then, didn't it?
When they wake up. >> Yeah.
>> Imagine having to spend a day in their
lives. Yeah. They'll get up on the
morning, they load the YouTube app up
straight away. Like,
>> yeah. 7 in the morning.
>> They'll even have notifications turned on.
>> And you can tell that they wake up at 7
a.m. in the morning because if their
patterns were [ __ ] up, yeah, you
wouldn't see them on Lar J's
>> if their patterns were really [ __ ] up.
But they always they're always the same
people. Do you remember? I'm going to
say this. Yeah. On the 1 of January, I'm
gonna say, "Same people, same story. See
you next year." And it [laughter]
>> one on John Lav.
>> Yeah. Because remember when Ben Furby said that?
>> Oh, Ben Fury. Yeah. I like that. Ben.
>> Same people. Same story. See you.
>> You know whenever you go on that Lies.
Yeah. It's the same people every day.
>> It is. It's that Jimmy Jazz Provident
loans and Yeah. It's the same folk, you
know. But how they take
>> Well, they take one day off of it.
>> Take a day off the >> Yeah,
>> the two might you need to throw on Lies
on the first is
>> new year same people. See you next year.
>> Yeah, I'm going to go. I'm going to go.
I'm going to I'm going to look and I'm
just going to wait. I'm going to sit
there and wait, Grezy, until it's new people.
I'm going to sit there and wait. I'm
still going to be recording the whole
the whole of next year. Grievy waiting
for a change.
Yes, it's that proent though, that Jimmy
Jazz, that uh Good Vibes Only. It's the same people.
>> That's C backup senior, whatever he's
called. That's Violet. [clears throat]
>> Yeah, same repeat. Do you remember
Monty? It's the same repeating people.
>> Yeah. Even I think Jeremy's getting sick
of it, didn't he? >> Yeah.
The idiots on here, he said, is it?
Yeah, they are. Jimmy Chip is D.
>> Well, I like it when Monty goes live. I
click on it.
>> You watch I sometimes watch a little bit
of Monty B.
>> I like it when he talks about the people
in the community when he says they got
no life for that.
>> True. Yeah. True. Yeah. I like them.
>> Do you ever be Do you remember when
Monty man used to argue with Mustard?
>> I do. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Hi. Yeah.
>> It used to get heated, didn't it? [laughter]
>> Oh, yeah. Didn't Yeah. That was when it
was like the good days that man. That
mustard was on all the time, wasn't he? >> Yeah.
>> He wouldn't take it off Mustard.
>> Nah, she's
>> remember Monty man used to make videos
to Pat Mustard. The [ __ ] fictional love man.
>> Yeah, man. Twopart Mustard. These
>> pe Yeah, these people repeat themselves
every day and I'm getting sick of it.
But he's still on.
He's still Monday man.
>> Yeah. Matthew Help his name was it. I
lost his Matthew Help.
>> Matthew Alen was it? Yeah.
>> You remember toasting?
>> Did you actually see the state of that guy, lad?
>> Yeah. Yeah. That's why these people do
what they do, is it?
>> That guy had a family and he was [ __ ]
He's had a family [ __ ] um he put some
hours on this YouTube.
All right, listen. [ __ ] um what was I saying? Um
what was I saying? You remember Toasty?
He was all right. Toasty.
>> Yeah, he's he's he's just a bit of a
troll. That toy, isn't he?
>> No, but no one could be worse than that
[ __ ] money Mike. He's an undercover
troll big time, bro. >> Mikey. >> Yeah,
>> he switches as well. He's a bit of a
cokehead, isn't it?
He's all right, Mike. Man, what was I
going to say?
>> You should meet Toast. I reckon you two
would have a crack. Good crack. >> Yeah,
>> I met him and remember when I went
Burger King together, me and Toaster.
>> Do you have that? Do you still have that video?
>> Nah, that was years back.
>> If you upload all them old videos, man,
it' be good. That like there was some
Goodens, wasn't the man?
>> Yeah. Yeah, the toasty. Do you remember
the Kenji one?
>> The Kenji one was the good. That one
when you're walking down the street of Ey.
>> Yeah. Isabella.
>> I'm sure someone's got that. Someone
must have the um one where I'm walking
down with Isabelle. >> Yeah,
>> I remember that. The greeneyed monster
nonslegs didn't like that, did he? The
greeneyed monster. Triple H.
>> I watched that. Yeah. Yeah, I watched
>> The greeneyed [ __ ] in it. The
>> You got Chenn and legs.
>> Dusty Shers. Yeah, you're bang on. He
did. Yeah, lad. But what these people
have done, they took Pat Mustard's side,
didn't they? But Pat must Mustard was no better than
>> You know what? I used to I used to like
that Candid Man. Listen, bro. I used to
like Candid Man. Yeah. But I stopped
liking him when he started defending
Pat. You know, he was trying to say,
"Oh, it's public domain what he's
doing." And I said, "No, it's not public
domain. He's putting kids up." That's
why I fell out with that Candid man.
>> Yeah. I seen that Pat mustard making
accounts going into Jamie Streamyards
like with his daughter's name. Do
>> you remember that? Hey,
>> you remember that candid man?
>> Yeah, the [ __ ] Canadian fella, wasn't he?
>> Yeah, that American one. Yeah. Yeah. He
used to he used to think think he was a
smartass, isn't it?
>> Yeah, he was all right to be fair.
>> Yeah, but then he Yeah, but he was the
he does what Joe does. But the thing is,
what makes these people not all right is
when they're biased. It's a bit like
what that Joe is, bro.
>> Yeah, I remember that Batman account. I
remember that Batman account, Dusty. I'm Batman.
>> Yeah, it was. Yeah.
Yeah, I do remember it. I do remember.
>> I can remember that.
>> There was another account. Remember that
Isabelle Eldridge one?
>> Yeah. I seen that postage.
>> Post a link and see if anyone else is coming on.
>> Yeah. You remember when Bomb was under
the Izzy Chambers account? [laughter]
>> How do you know it was the bomb? Was it
the bomb? It was the bomb because he he
told me to go somewhere and then when I
went there he come up laughing and
that's there you go. The link's there.
>> I want Joseph Ferrar. I want Joseph
Ferrar to join.
>> He might be at work.
>> Well, now I look like a [ __ ] night.
You silly goose.
>> Oh yeah, he doesn't like it. Sorry.
Yeah, you're right.
>> He finishes at about 56. Where are you, Mr. Ferrar?
>> He might be out having a a family meal
or something maybe. Oh, might be on the
>> Yeah, he might be back Monday. Sometimes
he's away over the week uh weekend.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> You're planning to get on the gear on
your on your birthday?
>> No, lad. Have give it up, mate.
>> Bless you. Bless you in life.
>> Yeah. Was that Tim El got me on here?
>> Yeah, same.
He ruined a lot of people's lives that
Timmy Elg if you come to think of it in it.
>> Yeah, I did just like his rule videos.
Like I'm not going to lie, they were
good. Then you
>> remember when he used to Yeah. Do you
remember the one where he was with Charlie?
>> Unworthy. Yeah. Yeah, I did. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Do you know who's all right on
this community? Charlie's all right, you
know. I like Charlie.
>> Yeah. He's a loyal fellow, Charlie, is
he? Yeah. Yeah, he is. He's all right. And
>> yeah, I've met him in Nottingham. He's
He's a good [ __ ] But he couldn't drink
because he was uh recovering from um
being an alcoholic, so he couldn't drink
and [ __ ] So he was drinking
non-alcoholic. I was drinking. You know
what I mean?
>> Oh. Did you just meet him on his own
like Charlie or was it a few years?
Yeah. Just by himself. Yeah. At a train
station. Yeah. It's cool.
>> I didn't know you met Charlie.
>> Yeah. Few years ago when I went
Nottingham. You remember when I went to Nottingham?
>> Yeah. I remember you going to
>> I didn't do a video though. I kept off YouTube.
>> Oh, [snorts] yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Cuz [ __ ] Yeah. He said, "Oh, just
leave it." And Yeah. I met him in
Nottingham once. I've only met him once.
He's all right, bro.
>> Were you scumbling?
>> No, I don't think we did. We just went
for a little drink and then I went to
the club and he went home cuz he
couldn't drink in it.
>> Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I Yeah.
>> We went to the Weather Spoons I think as
well. Yeah. Yeah. Cool guy man.
>> Yeah. He's a decent fellow Charlie.
>> But there's a lot of [ __ ] on here in it
now. How hard can it be all right as
well? He's still on here.
>> Blonde Steven lad.
>> How hard can it be? How hard can it be
all right? Is it?
>> Yeah. Yeah, another not a bad fellow in me.
>> You remember that Sarah?
>> Yeah, you remember a Sarah that died and
she went off.
>> Oh yeah, I can. Yeah, I can't think.
>> She was a [ __ ] wasn't she?
>> Yeah. What do you think of that Autumn
Rose then, Pete?
>> I think she's a bloody [ __ ] [laughter]
>> What do you think?
>> Yeah, she's not my cup of tea, but
for you. Oh, she bit I don't know. She
just like uh just isn't my cup of tea, lad.
>> What? Too fat? Not like you don't.
>> No, not like just just not for me, mate.
Really? Like I just don't know. I just
Well, before you She could be before you
were Gre Do you remember when Gregy said
um Autumn can be my mama for the winter?
>> Yeah, you commented that. I thought I seen that.
>> That's funny as [ __ ] is it? So is that
USA? is what about the USA is he was she your copper
>> she was wasn't too bad actually I'm not
I'm going I'm not going to lie yeah she
was all right there but um what else was
I going to say there
so did do you know when you got with
that USA Z
>> was in a relationship then
>> I think so maybe maybe not but I think so yeah
>> she liked the black dick in it
>> was she was with Charles wasn't she
>> yeah but you know when LT was messaging
her and stuff who who was the root cause of it. >> You [laughter]
not me. Why do you always blame me for everything?
>> He was Wasn't that London Taylor and
Natalie Garrett as well?
>> No, he he messaged her. Warning warning
um warning her. Yeah, but that that that
Morgan was stinking, son. Three out of
10. Yeah, Dusty, but she had Did you
like her boobies, Dusty?
>> That's why I'm getting mixed that's why
I'm getting mixed up with me. Was it Is
that Morgan who was seeing Charles? Is
that Is he?
>> Which one?
>> The one who was seeing Charles.
>> That's USA. Is he?
>> Yeah, that's who I want to know about.
Yeah, she was all right, actually, man.
>> Yeah. So, you would date her?
>> Yeah, she's not too [ __ ] bad at all.
>> So, what what is it with autism that
makes her not for you? There's got to be a reason.
>> Um, just stop your cup of tea.
God bless you then. Bless you in life if
she's not for you.
>> Okay. So, what about um Okay. What about Natalie Garrett? >> No.
>> What about Scottish Stacy? She weren't that bad.
>> She wasn't that bad. I know she was a
bad [ __ ] [ __ ] bonnie face and that
>> you remember her [laughter] Scottish
Stacy. You remember? >> Yeah.
>> Oh, bless you. Well, I with your little
with your little um dialect. Bless you
in life. Do you
>> you know your dialect? Huh?
>> What about that Jane? >> No.
>> Well, you like her in it. You get her in
>> No. Is
>> she a bit of you?
>> She's ty body and that like just she's I
don't know. She's got a bit of a rough face.
>> Do you know Cory Dak?
>> I've heard of him. I don't know him.
Like I've heard
>> he's a Jordy like you. Oh, he from this
way. Is he?
>> Yeah. And when I went to Newcastle, he
was staying out in the hotel. He
wouldn't even come out. I said, "Let's
go for a drink." See, [ __ ] [ __ ]
houses on there, bro. It
>> didn't come out in real life. >> Nah. >> No.
>> You should meet him.
>> Let's do that again.
>> No, I don't even know the lad, mate. Um,
what about Mr. G's crew?
>> Hasn't come on anymore, is it?
>> I know. I've seen him about for a while.
You don't remember the picture though? You don't?
>> I do watch them four people with the one one.
>> Yeah, but do you remember when he said
Yeah. when he said that he's going to
bend me over and spank me and that and
he said, "Oh, sorry. The beers have got
to my head."
>> That's what he said. Yeah.
>> Yeah. That's weird. No.
>> Yeah. It's a bit weird. Like, but he was
all right. Mr. G,
>> when I used to go live Yeah. When I used
to go and Yeah. And when I used to go
live on GTA San Andreas and they used to
come on and that with Craig, they also
used to come on in it. That was when it
was the that was when last YouTubers was
a good days of money.
>> And there was another account. What was
it called? Um Oh, I think there used to
be a Goona supporter. What was that
account? There was an account, bro. I
forget. He always used to come on.
>> Mikey Fraud.
>> No, no, no. I think it was Jason. No,
no, no, no. I think it was Aona supporter.
I can't even remember, bro. Uh,
no. I can't remember.
something, bro. It was something. But
yeah, that Mr. G. He was all right. Yeah.
On the PlayStation before where me and
he we joined. We all joined in that
[ __ ] party, didn't we?
>> Did you hear? Did you hear his accent? >> Scottish.
>> Yeah, I do remember Fizzy Reme. Yep. The
guy from Birmingham. Yep. I remember
him. That was over CO. That was over CO.
>> Yeah, I've seen that there. Dusty Shoppers. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Fizzy. Yeah. Yeah, that was over.
>> Dusty Shoppers if you are. Jump on lad.
>> Yeah, that how he's a nasty troll. He's
a nasty troll, bro.
>> Yeah, he's wild to you. He's relentless.
I carry a he
>> No, I think that is me. I'm not No, I
honestly think that [ __ ] Dusty So is
Arnold L. I think that's in me.
>> Nah, thinking now.
>> Not reckon. [clears throat]
>> I know certain accounts. There's an
account called, you know, that Lewis
Phil Slugger. I know when he makes new
accounts I know I know it's them. I can
smell them on my mate.
>> I can remember that account, lad. Yeah,
>> you can smell them on my loft. You know
what I mean?
>> Yeah. Right. I'll be back then. Like
tell me if I'm going to go and make a drink, lad.
>> All right. Don't Don't leave me hanging
too long. You know I get lonely and stuff.
>> All right. See you.
Bless you, Triple.
Bless you with your little northern dialect.
That's so cute. Ain't it? Triple's
little northern dialect. His little
northeast dialect. Bless him. What do you think?
Maybe Triple H can come for a sleepover.
Me, Triple H. Um, and I'll get King of Grinch Mill.
Oh, bless you.
Whose accent do you understand more?
Mine or Triple H's? Uh, Greavesy
to Whose accent do you understand more?
I think you can both understand us, isn't it?
Yeah. But who's who's more clearer?
The only accent I hate is that Brummy
accent and the Stoke accent. Oh, it's
[ __ ] vile, man. It's grim.
It is [ __ ] grim.
That Brmy accent and that Stoke accent
is grim. Have you ever heard it, Dusty?
That that [ __ ] Stoke accent.
You ever heard it? The Stoke on Trent
accent. [ __ ] that, bro. That is vile.
That is vile, mate. It's like cross
between [ __ ] Brummy and No, it's like
but then Staffordshire at the same time.
It's [ __ ] vile, bro.
Big up David Campbell. I don't.
How can you like a Scouse accent on a
woman? It's [ __ ] disgusting. It's
[ __ ] vile. They sound [ __ ] horrible.
I like the Scottish accent on a woman and
and an Americ
and and a little an American accent. Why
would you like a Scouse accent, bro? It
sounds like what this guy said. Rough.
Why would you want a woman sounding like that?
I think it sounds horrible that. But
it's not the worst accent. Liverpool's
not the worst accent. Bra is the worst.
Ramy is the worst. Ah.
Why did my mommy sound American?
Greavvesy. If that's my mommy, how can I
be British then?
So, how's that then? H So, why do I So,
why am I Why do I sound English then?
How can my mommy be American? Wooy. Hm.
Welcome back, Captain.
>> I'm back. >> Huh?
>> Don't you [ __ ] call me a [ __ ] I'll
kick you in your balls.
>> I'll come to Durham and kick you in the bollocks.
>> Yeah, bro. Hey. Yeah. Hey, I know. I forgot.
I forgot what I'm [ __ ] saying now.
But yeah, that Tim Eldridge got me on here.
>> What's your favorite accent? Greavves is asking. Yeah.
>> What's read the comments? What's your um
I don't mind um
the Scouse accent. Greavves.
>> I knew you were going to say that.
>> I like the scout accent, man. >> Yeah.
>> So, what did that Sean say? If he he he
said he like shar to fit in with the crowd.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Like
>> No, cuz he was No, he used to say not
that, but he used to say that if you
don't find her attractive, you're gay.
And that's what like people used they
used to copy each other in it like with that bit.
>> Oh yeah. Yeah. I know what you mean.
>> There's copy. Yeah. Do do you remember that trend?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> But you heard other people saying it to
each other as well. It's been a boat,
lad. Yeah. I I think she's all right, man.
>> No, no, no, no. You can find her. All
right. You can like her. He's not
copying for that. But he's when he's
saying that you're gay if you don't like
her. That's a copycat statement. [laughter] >> Yeah.
>> Cuz it doesn't make sense. How can you
if you don't like one person? Yeah. How
does that make you gay? Like I like you
could like big boobs, blonde hair, blue
eyes. You know what I'm saying? You
could have different types of women you
go for in it.
>> That's it. Everyone's got different
[ __ ] preferences having a lad eye.
>> But he was like, "No, you're gay. If you
don't like her, you're gay. He was
copying the crowd, didn't it?
>> Yeah. Trying to be like one of the cool people. Yeah.
>> Just fit in.
>> Yeah. Just the crowd.
>> I know what you're saying, lad. I >> Yeah.
>> Her boobs are not big enough for me.
>> Oh, you're a boob person, Peter. Are you?
>> Yeah. I need to get my vitamins.
>> Well, you you like you like Sh is it? I
think she's a tidy. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Because And you're both from like
the Northeast, so you'd get on quite
well, you know.
>> She is all right. The Grey likes to say
Gravesy's favor to Scouse accent as
well. So get in Grey lad. Yeah. I do
like the Scouse accent like decent them Scouse.
>> You like the Scouse accent, Grezy. You
said that what you said's favorite. He
said the um the [ __ ] the Scouse
accent on them Scouse Birds, man, is mint lad.
>> You like it? the scout sex on the birds. Grezy,
>> you should have seen it when I went to I
went to Liverpool for the weekend,
right? And I was talking this scout lad
in the air and the weather spoon through
there. That's his last [ __ ] mint, you
know. And I mean a solid nine out of 10, man.
>> You You should have tried setting her up.
>> That was his last one. >> Huh?
>> It was his last lad, was it?
>> Yeah, but you should have done it
anyways for a laugh, is it? Nah. Yeah.
>> Did you have to pay to get in any places?
>> Nah. No, lad.
>> So, what time did you finish the drink
at like 3:00 in the morning?
>> Well, we traveled down from about travel
down about half 10 and then uh we got
there for about just after 1, I think.
And then we were drinking on the way
down. We ended up stopping at Weatherbe services.
Um and then obviously we finally got
there and then we just we got our bags
in. I got a shower and I got started and
we were on the drink like the drink for
2:00 and then on the first night I was
on for 2:00 like I was [ __ ]
>> well in the morning.
>> Yeah, but I done 12 hours on it. But
well Mark considering I drink on the
morning but um the Saturday was messy. I
didn't get back on back to the hotel
about [ __ ] half.
>> What hotel was it?
>> He easy hotel it was called in Matthew Street.
>> Was it cheap?
>> Um yeah it was cheap. quite was quite
cheap, lad. Yeah. Yeah.
>> How much was it? Cuz I stayed in an easy
hotel in Sheffield.
>> I don't think it was I can't really
remember. Pier was about 20 of us who
went down and we we just all sent them
the money over [ __ ] night. It was
>> You stay in the same You all stayed in
the same hotel like the same like place,
not room. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. >> Really?
>> No. Like obviously different [ __ ]
rooms and that.
>> Yeah. Obviously different rooms, but
still that's mad. Like easy. Yeah.
>> Mad lad.
>> And you just were all send the money
over and one person booked it, I'm guessing.
>> You just booked, dude. Yeah, that was
what happened, mate. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I still prefer Newcastle though.
>> But you're probably used to Newcastle,
so Liverpool is just something different
to you. You know what I mean?
>> That's that's exactly it. Yeah. But a
lot of people do like Newcastle. But
when you've been as many times as I
have, you get
>> It's easy to get women in Newcastle. Not
like London. It's hard.
>> I think the best women best spouses and
spouse women have been, but
>> some [ __ ] bags up here as well, lad.
>> Yeah, it's true. You should go on the
drink with a and deck. >> Yeah.
>> Would you do it?
>> Yes, man. Yeah. Well, you you going on a
drink with them?
>> No, I wouldn't go on the drink with
Anak. No. Be realistic, Peter.
>> Why not? I haven't been realistic.
>> Huh? I'm Have you ever bumped into them?
>> I've never since No, I've not bumped
into them. No.
>> I asked that [clears throat] cuz you
live in the Northeast.
>> Yeah, they're from Newland. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I don't think they live there
though. I think they live in London, isn't it?
>> I'm not you're allowed to.
>> Yeah, probably. No, I'm just saying that.
>> Yeah, be realistic, Pete. Is [laughter]
that what you said? F. [laughter]
>> So, what have you eaten today then? >> Huh?
>> What have you eaten today?
>> This chicken and chips.
>> Oh, did you go to the chicken shop, lad? Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> So if you if you if you saw like Sher Co
on a night out, would you approach her?
>> Probably. No, I would probably wouldn't. No. No. >> No.
>> Well, why would you want to be with
someone like me? Like it's wasting your
time, aren't you? Like you need to be
realist realistic again.
>> Well, I'm saying would you approach her?
No. I'm saying would you approach her?
>> Well, no, cuz you just
>> Yeah. Just be real.
>> Just be realistic, Peter. [laughter]
>> That's a new saying, Grey. Won't let
that go. Yeah, he won't. Grezy, he'll
just go insert all.
>> Yeah, it's our it's our autism. Triple
H, it autism.
>> But Grezy, you know what I mean, don't
you? When I when um I'm saying to him,
be realistic. Like, >> yeah.
>> Yeah. But I've seen you comment about
the mama thing as well, Dra. You said
you need to find it in Mama.
>> Yeah, I posted that like Yeah. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> I've only got one account, mate. I'm
like I'm I don't make [ __ ] fake
accounts and that, man.
>> Money Mike's got about 20 different
accounts, bro. You got caught by Lisa, is it?
>> Oh, Lisa Gary catch you out. [laughter]
>> [ __ ] the world's gone mad, lad.
I don't think you'd be able to handle
Ny. She gets nasty when she's drunk. Is it?
>> Oh, I've seen what she's like on that
live. Yeah. Do you know what these
people do to send her money so she can
have a drink so they get a blip on?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> That's crazy, lad.
>> So, what do you remember? Other things
people used to do in school to fit in,
look good, look cool, and that.
just used to follow the crowd, don't
they? That's what they do. [laughter]
>> It's pathetic though, is [clears throat]
it? It is pathetic.
>> Yeah. When in my school, they try and go
in some popular guys and
>> they used to make like paper airplanes
and throw at each other it.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Well, you were [ __ ] skill data. >> Nah.
So what you're b So what you're
basically saying as well is that launch
leg sent that because he he didn't want
to feel left out in it.
>> Yeah. He wanted to just have a laugh and
joke with the crowd so he could fit in.
That was what that is. Yeah. [laughter]
>> Oh, you know every time I say yeah I'm
going to have some digest digestive
biscuits. Screamsy calls me a copycat
because you have them in it. >> Um
I don't want them again. Yeah, but I
tell you what I like. I like the I like
them rich tea biscuits, mate.
>> Yeah, I've got them rich tea biscuits here.
>> Lovely them, lad.
>> I like the Bourbon ones. Have you ever
had it? Chocolate ones.
>> Here's a question for you then. What
would you What do you like better
custard creams or bar bons? Because to
me, that's an odd choice.
>> And what do you reckon, Gra?
>> Probably borons. say,
>> "No, you can't. You can't choose them."
Like, obviously you've chosen them, but
I mean, you can't. Not that much better
than custard creams, are they? Cuz it's
hard. I think
>> they're different. Yeah, they're both different. But
>> yeah, but they're both heavy, aren't they? >> Yeah.
Here's one. Here's one. A kebab or
Chinese? Cuz I know you don't like
Indian much. So,
>> yeah. I don't.
>> What do What do you prefer?
>> That's another close one, but I'd go I'm
edging towards Chinese lad. all day long. >> Yeah.
>> I'm not really big on, you know, a lot
of people are big on kebabs. I'm not
really big on them like people are
likes kebab, lad. Um I don't like the
kebab. Like, don't get us wrong, but
>> yeah, but it's just But only the shis
kebab, which is a bit more expensive.
The donut tastes like [ __ ]
>> Yeah, you can get you can get some bad
donor, mate, lad, as well.
>> Um the chicken donut the chicken donut
um is nice, but the lamb one's too
greasy. I had it last week with my
sister. I had a turkey. I had a fish, a
mix, chicken and lamb. Lovely.
>> Lovely. It was [ __ ] lovely.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? What do you What
do you get from the Chinese again?
Chicken balls, isn't it?
>> I normally get This is my Chinese order.
I get portion chicken balls, salt and
pepper chicken, normal chips, egg fried rice.
>> Yeah. get spring rolls above it. And um
I get gravies at a curry, me, I know
that's a lot of people might not like
that, but I do. I always get gravies at a curry.
>> Do you know do you know what my order is?
>> Go on, bro.
>> So, chicken balls, chicken fried rice,
and beef chowine.
>> Well, I agree that that is a nice a good
order to be honest. I like the chicken
chowine. Like, but
>> yeah, I don't like No, I like the beef
chowine and the chicken fried rice. I
like the beef or I get beef curry and
rice, but normally it's chain and
chicken fried rice. The chicken balls
are nice, isn't it? Or
>> Yeah. Nice. There's that many nice
things you can get from the China. You
said chia and then you've got your uh chow.
Then you got your special carry. I like
the special carry, man.
>> And Indian. I always get the same thing.
I love Indian. My favorite.
>> You get a vindaloo, >> huh?
>> You always get a vindaloo. Yeah. Yeah.
Lj can't take it.
>> I watch that video. That was sad and
pathetic out of him like
>> Yeah. And he got it from [ __ ] Iceland
cuz he's [ __ ] skinn it.
>> So he was sucking that sucking on that
lolly to cool his mouth down. Michael
Basser commented saying,
>> "Yeah, he looked like he was sucking a
dick in it."
>> But you know said he's a gobbler.
Would you would you ever accept a
[ __ ] in an al anyway? Yeah,
>> probably not. No, because I've got a bit
more class than some of these people. No,
>> I've got one by American, but it was it
was too it felt too good. I couldn't
tell them to stop. It felt too good.
>> Well, yeah.
>> Yeah, it was in London in the alleyway in it.
>> But you got a boy in the alleyway in London?
>> Yeah. This American, I approached her.
She kept coming on to me saying, "I
really want you, but I don't think you want me."
>> I said, "I do, but we can't do it here.
You know, everyone's looking." So, I
took her around the corner, fingered
her, and took my pants down [laughter]
cuz obviously like it was in central
London, so there was Yeah.
>> You're wild, Peter.
>> It was lovely. Lovely. Triple H. Lovely.
You wouldn't do that. No,
[ __ ] I don't know. I was just
>> She kept coming on to me kissing me and it
>> Yeah, you bet. You have to be ready for
the post off Sean Johnson cuz he'll be
posting about this so morning on a
>> Yeah, everyone everyone knows anyways.
>> I didn't know that like to be honest. No.
>> Yeah, I've got some wild stories, bro.
But so you you you wouldn't do it. No, you said
>> no. Probably not like no.
>> God bless you then.
So, what would you do if you went out on
a night out? Yeah. Say you went out on a
night out at Newcastle New Year's Eve
and you pulled. What are you going to
do? Just take him to a hotel or like
back to your like mom's mom's. [laughter]
>> What would you What are you going to do?
>> It'll be in a hotel.
>> I would take them [ __ ] back here. Me.
>> What? Your Mars? >> Yeah.
>> Have you ever took anyone back when your
mom's been there and she said anything?
What did she say? [snorts and laughter]
>> Nothing. But I just said my friends, didn't it? >> Yeah.
>> And has she ever seen them before? I
like Peter like
>> Yeah, she come back on the door. She
come back on the door because um Yeah,
she lost her phone that she come back on
the door. She did see her. Yeah.
>> What did her?
>> Nothing really.
>> So yeah, there's no I would just take
them back out. Yeah.
Seems as well lad. [laughter] Yeah, look
at Grezy pe shagging upstairs. Laney
watching Cory on the sofa downstairs. [laughter] >> Yeah,
>> you heard Grezy
putting the earphones in. >> Yeah.
>> And Peter and Peter [ __ ]
>> funny, isn't it?
>> That's lovely though. Is it crazy? Lovely.
>> Yeah. Obviously, does your dad live with
you as well?
>> I mate. I
>> Oh, yeah. Sorry. It might be. It's
different, is it? If you only live with
your mom, it's only one parent, is it? So,
>> yeah, it's not too bad, is it? But like
it's awkward with my dark and I [ __ ] off.
>> If it's two, it's Yeah. Oh, how old your
dad? Is your dad old? >> 65.
>> Yeah. My mom's 66
and my dad would be If my dad was alive,
he'd be like 70 something.
>> He'd be old, right?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Is your mom old then?
My mom's dick
63 I think.
>> Okay. Okay. It's not not too bad, is it?
>> But I need to um I will end up get me
own place soon enough like just [ __ ]
[ __ ] on man is it?
>> No rash. No rash.
>> That's it captain.
>> You know what's what's the point?
>> It depends it like [ __ ] Yeah. Like if
I if I I can I can live by myself and
then it means privately renting and it's
just not worth it. You know,
>> it's too much money. All you got your
rent and all your bills and your
shopping [ __ ] I just pay lodges.
>> Yeah. Yeah. But it's it's pretty cheap
though where you are, is it? Like what,
five a month maybe?
>> Yeah. Five. You can get the
>> I know. We should neutral break me and
you. Yeah. We should move in together in
Middlesbrough. We'd be paying next to nothing.
>> Yeah. You can get [ __ ] cheap as
[ __ ] Middlesbrough. Yeah. Really cheap.
>> Like [ __ ] proper cheap in it. Rob a [ __ ] Jeep.
>> It's a [ __ ] all bor.
>> Yeah, but we could just travel into
Newcastle and go on our little weekly nights out.
>> We could call for Trevor Dawson.
>> Yeah, he doesn't come out though. [laughter]
>> You remember last time he didn't come out?
>> Did you call that Trevor out?
>> Yeah, he didn't come out.
>> I seen your video. Remember? Um remember that?
>> Yeah. So, if it's like5600 a month, we
could just go half. Me and you can move in together.
>> I lied. Yeah.
>> How do you feel about that, Captain?
>> It'll be lush, lad. Yeah, we're just
live streaming every day on the YouTube.
>> Yeah, going on nights out of that, is it?
>> Right. What's the What's the worst area
in the Northeast? Is it Middles?
>> It is dusty. It is cheap be mate. Um
>> Yeah, London is expensive.
>> What's the worst area? Yeah. What's uh
what's the worst area in the northeast?
Is it Middlesbrough or Sunderland? >> Bor,
>> but then second Sunderland, is it?
>> I'm not sure. What second? But borrows
the [ __ ] mass. There's loads of crime
in that middle bar.
>> Yeah, I know. It's scary, bro. I went
there. It was scary for a proper scary. >> Yeah.
>> Darlington. Well, Darlington's the
second. Yeah, but Sunderland is bad, though.
>> Is it?
>> Sunderland there. I'm not too sure about
Sunderland. Yeah, Darlington's a [ __ ]
all as well. Yeah, >> Sunderland.
>> Yeah, I've been to Sunderland. Yeah.
>> What for? For like the football?
>> Been in the Sunderland, but no, I don't.
>> Yeah, I remember. Yeah. when I was
getting a train. Yeah. Um to from
Middlesborough to Newcastle and I
stopped off at Sunderland, but there was
a train and you go over like water. I
can't I can't explain it. You go over
like a little thing and you can see the water.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I've been on it.
>> Yeah, Holland is bad. I've never been to
Holl. I've never been there.
>> Yeah, exactly, Stephen. I know.
I tell you where it go. The ball club in
Dham's a mint [ __ ] little boozy.
You're right. You go in, you obviously
get your drink and you come back outside
like like a [snorts] big [ __ ] like
the river with loads of like loads of
boats and mint lad especially in the summer.
>> How much is it a point?
>> 56 5.56 quid. Next I think in the summer
when I go I might make a couple of
videos of it.
>> I might come with you.
>> Yeah, come down. Yeah,
>> we can play a game of Paul.
>> All right, I'll have a couple of beers.
Was good, man. I don't.
>> We could find me. We could find me a new mama.
>> South Shields, Dusty. Yeah, South
Shields isn't bad either Lee.
>> Peter Lee. Yeah. Well, I
>> It's a funny place, isn't it? Imagine
Imagine living in a place called Peter Lee. [laughter]
It's funny, isn't it?
>> I used to go to the Peter Lee market. Me
going back years ago now. Like
>> why is it far from you?
>> Mark on every bank all that was decent lad.
>> Is it far from you? >> Um
no it's not far like I don't know [ __ ]
it's not far.
>> Have you seen that account? Smug on the time.
>> I have seen that account. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I went to Newcastle called them
out. They didn't even come out.
>> Have you seen that all night Mike account?
>> Yeah. He's been doing it years, bro. He
lives in Scotland. He's a little [ __ ]
>> Oh, is he Scottish yet? My
>> Yeah, he's Scottish. He's a little
[ __ ] bro. You've seen his comments in
it. He's been doing it for [ __ ] seven years.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Hopefully he won't be on here next year. Fingers crossed.
I'll be on Man January. Ping live. >> Yeah.
>> Another year. Yeah, but it's even Timmy
know when Timmy goes live. Yeah. It
takes two seconds for someone to
comment, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Cuz they've got the notifications
turned on as soon as Tim Eldridge, they
just press the button. That's what they do.
>> That's why when have you noticed, you
know, when Timage goes live within like
a minute or something, he's got like
[ __ ] 15 to 20 viewers cuz they get the notification.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> That's mental in my opinion that like But
>> is it what's what's the difference
between Yeah. a Peter Lee accent and
your accent. Is it much different? Nah.
>> The yakers aren't up that way. The yakas.
>> You know what? What they called yakas?
>> What they call the yaka? Yeah. Peter Lee up there.
>> No, no, no. Listen, the worst accent is
actually the black country accent. It's
actually the yam yam accent like
Wolverampton. That is horrible. That is
>> You heard it. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, I've heard it, lad. Yeah. Yeah.
>> It's like Nissa. It's [ __ ] viral,
man. And it's file.
>> Dusty Shers. I love YouTube. I've been on YouTube.
>> No, but it's not. No, no, no. But it's
not just YouTube, though. Cuz what they
do on here is not just YouTube. You know
what I mean?
>> No, it's not as
they try to get people's money stopped.
They try getting people killed. So, how
can it just be YouTube, you know?
>> Yeah. So, not the community is not well,
is it? Dusty Shaw. Do you think you'll
ever get off YouTube or do you reckon
you a bit deep then lad?
>> Bless you.
>> You know, you know, like he used to
>> remember career goods then.
>> Yeah, that ugly [ __ ]
He was trying to steal my little Isabelle.
>> So, do you think that Kendi and Izzy still talk? >> No. What? Why?
>> I think you ruined the friendship gap. [laughter]
>> Really? How?
>> Cuz you went to fill him in at his work
and I think he just said it's I think he
said to Rizzy Isabelle that um it just
isn't worth my job. So I don't think
this week lad you ruined it for [laughter] you.
>> Yeah, that's true. Dusty lad. Yeah.
What you saying, Peter?
Um, I was saying that uh, yeah, I went
to Kenji's work and he shot it in it.
>> That was a wild she was quite
good-looking then that is he
>> is he chambers? Not
>> even a bit. >> Nope.
>> Her ex [ __ ] talks to me on [ __ ]
uh, Facebook. He's weird, bro.
>> Oh, does he?
>> Yeah. He today was going to come and
fill me in before like when he was with
her but he's not with her anymore. I
said come on then. His name is Jos Brown.
Why do you write the these people's exes
and that man?
>> I didn't. He wrote to me. He wrote to me, bro.
>> Oh, he wrote you
>> that was cuz I think Izzy come on here
and I said, "Listen, yeah, stop lying."
And then he started messaging me.
>> Yeah, Dusty, that's true. She was rotten
there like um yeah he went to a bed a
bed sit with a [ __ ] uni mates didn't
he? Yeah cuz you got the train on my six
in the morning P didn't you remember?
>> Yeah you remember I had to climb the
[ __ ] thing in it. >> Yeah, you >> huh?
>> You have to climb out the window. I
climb through the window.
>> Yeah. No, no, not through the window.
No, no, no. There's a window.
>> Yeah, it was funny, wasn't it, Dusty? It was lovely.
I don't get why that like Sean writes
like writes to the the people you've
been speaking to on Facebook. It's weird that
>> cuz he's a [ __ ] virgin trying to get
[ __ ] bank material in it.
>> He grew up on here.
>> I didn't grow up on it. Monty did it.
>> Honestly, like real talk now. Do you
think you'll ever get off this YouTube? Truthfully.
>> Yeah. I just come on here to go live and
speak to the normal people now, bro. I'm
not getting involved with the drama
anymore, you know? Yeah. Yeah.
>> Like nons. [ __ ] Why? Why does he
message like people I've been with? He's
such a virgin, man.
>> Steven. Yeah. Like USA was tidy. I thought
>> USA is he. Yeah. Dusty said that she's stinking.
>> No, he said Izzy is stinking. She was stink.
>> No, no, but No, but Dusty said that USA
is he stinking also.
>> Oh, they I don't think she's that bad. They lie.
Yeah, you you should try and get with
her. Yeah. Message them. I love YouTube.
A lot of them do.
>> What would you do? What would you do if
she got What would you do if you message
me and she started messaging you and
said, "Come and see me in America."
Would you do it? >> No.
>> Why? It' be a little trick for you, is it?
>> Be realistic, Peter. Come on.
>> What do you mean be realistic? People do
go to different countries, you know.
>> You go to only you who does that. I
wouldn't get a [ __ ] plane to America.
Go and see a woman called USA.
Well, that's not her real her real name
from America. I'm not just stuck out. [laughter]
Did you go to America?
>> No. No. But you can do it though. No,
>> you could do Yeah, but I wouldn't do it.
>> Le what? Even for the love of your life.
>> Start a new life there and that. >> No.
>> Imagine you imagine YouTube right here.
Your little your little Jordi accent in
America. Oh, that' be cute, wouldn't it?
>> Huh? Yeah.
>> You ever met any? >> Yeah.
>> He's all right there. Yeah. He's all
right. I like Daria.
>> You ever met any American people in real
life? You haven't, have you? >> No.
>> I've met plenty, mate. Plenty. Cuz
obviously London, is it? They're here.
So, they're [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Is there a Is there a club in [ __ ]
London called Soho?
>> No. Soho is the place that this club's in. Yeah,
>> I don't want to be minted at that.
>> Yeah, you should come, man. You and your
little you and your little northeast
accent in America. Oh, for sure.
>> Hey, did Michael Well, you'd fit in well, huh?
>> Did Michael Basset end up getting the
train to London, done his balling on the
FBI, and go back home? >> Yep.
>> That's a madness that lad. Do you
remember when he used to sell you things to gamble?
>> Oh, Mike, did he? I didn't know. I
thought that was Tim me.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> I thought that was
>> Is it Dusty? I didn't know. I didn't
know it was full of G.
>> Have you ever sold your stuff?
>> [ __ ] nightclub, mate. Fell. You up.
>> Have you ever sold your stuff to gamble?
>> Never in me life. No.
>> Would you? >> Never.
>> Never. [ __ ]
Never. Have I? Never would, lad. No.
>> No. No. Have you? >> Nah.
>> Yeah. Have you put your phone into the
ex before, haven't you?
>> Maybe because I was broke but not to gamble. >> Hello.
>> Yeah. Maybe because I was broke but not to gamble.
>> Oh, wasn't it a gamble?
[ __ ] that. Any bets tomorrow? I don't
always do it, you know. Bit more.
>> You doing it?
>> I don't do it every week, man. Depends
what [ __ ] house.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm That's Yeah, same
>> my sleep been a bit [ __ ] man.
>> Really? What time you waking up?
>> Well, I was up early this morning, but
then I come home from the garage and I
went to sleep 5:00 and woke up about had
a couple of hours, man.
Yeah, I woke up at like 2 p.m.
>> Yeah, that's mad.
>> So, have you done anything today like or not?
>> Not really. No, just went to get some
chicken and chips and come back.
>> Yeah. Did your mom get home? >> Nah. >> No.
Is your mom away? >> No.
>> What are you doing tomorrow?
I've got me.
>> All right, Dusty. I used to live where I
used to live when I was younger. I used
to live 10 minutes away from Leight and
Orian. I actually I was actually born in
Leighton Stone and I lived in Leighton.
Leighton's my area. Then I moved to
Stratford. So I live, you know, Leon Oran.
>> I live I used to live 10 minute walk from there. >> Yeah.
>> He had to paint his garage. even know.
>> Bless you then. Triple. Bless you.
>> You should go. Can you do a Can you Can
you go Can you do a roulette session? Triple.
>> I was thinking about start doing some
bits in this for the for me channel like
Yeah. And putting um
putting a few I don't know drinking
videos up in the pubs and stuff like
that and uh like doing
>> maybe like Yeah. I don't want to go with
Alex to me.
>> Yeah, I lost 20 on Frankie uh last week.
>> Yeah. Did you get te bonus? Didn't even
get a bonus. Didn't even get a bonus.
>> Oh, didn't you? >> Nah.
>> Didn't just tease tease city.
>> Yeah, that's what Yeah, it's annoying, isn't it?
>> All of those lad.
>> Well, it happened to you as well.
>> Yep. even for a way yet.
>> You can never replace that buzzer. You
>> You can never replace that buzzer. Like
one scar, two scatter and a third one.
It's such a buzz, isn't it?
>> Oh, when the first three come in. Yeah.
And then you But you know you've got a
bonus. Yeah. It's no better feel than a
mega team, lad.
>> I used to put 150 on Frankie in it.
>> Yeah. You used to enjoy your game, didn't you?
PJ, when you first come live this
evening, you said you wouldn't be on it
because you were busy. That was 3 hours
ago, my guy. Yeah, I'm speaking to
Triple H. They were having a
conversation. So So what?
>> Limcogny or
you know some of these are the same
people, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Just under another account, lad.
>> Hopefully Harry Freud gets off here next
week. Uh sorry, next month.
>> Can't see it. [laughter]
>> So what you're saying that he's going to
die on here? Harry's
been on this quite Harry's been one of
the [ __ ] OG's on here and he >> Yeah.
>> You might struggle to get off.
>> People love giving Pete stick. Yeah. Do
you know do you need Are you going to
the dentist at some point, Triple? Do
you need to go to the dentist or [laughter]
>> dentist visit or what?
>> I go at the dentist every six month. Me, lad. Really?
>> All right.
>> So, what? Yeah, you have to pay like 60
80 pound in it.
40 odd quid I think it is. I check my
>> Yeah, but you've had surgery on your
mouth before, isn't it?
>> What the [ __ ]
No, I've never
>> You've Well, you've never had a filling. >> No,
>> you don't. You do realize if you if you
do, it's going to cost like £300, isn't it?
Yeah, I'll cross that bridge when I come
to I've never had like that mate.
>> You've been trying to avoid it. That's fine. It
>> I've just told you what happens. I go
every six months to get a checkup.
>> Yeah, but that's what I'm saying. But
you probably look after that. You
probably don't drink like loads of
sugary stuff in it to to to like reduce the
>> I don't drink loads of sugary stuff.
>> Yeah, that's why. Probably. That's what
I mean. That's why. Yeah.
>> I brush my teeth twice a day.
That should end. >> Yeah.
>> Look, triple skin. See?
>> Yeah, that's Yeah, I am slim cognito. As
long as that makes you sleep better,
lad. Yeah, I'm skin.
>> Yeah, but these these people don't know
us, though. They
>> Yeah, they're just going off [ __ ]
This is what they're doing it.
>> They make up stuff in it.
>> I don't know why you keep laughing at them.
>> I'm not. Why I'm laughing at them? Why would I
>> sad? Huh?
I'm not laughing.
>> They're not funny. The losers, lad.
>> Yeah, but you're laughing. You're
laughing as well.
>> [ __ ] honestly.
>> Now, are you serious about like wanting
to move in together? Cuz I'm serious. >> Yeah.
>> Why don't you want to do that?
>> We get We can get a nice gaff in
Middlesbr, bro. What? Why? What? So funny.
>> Would you move? Would you move up here? >> Yeah. Why?
>> Because we could have our own gaff.
And you sound like it'd be good company, in it.
>> Yeah. We'd have a lad, wouldn't we?
>> We'd have like a big nice house. Even if
it's 6 650 a month. Perfect. We just go
we just go uh we just go h.
>> He's off at Yogi Asylum in he lad. Paid.
>> We can have a house party as well, is it?
>> Yeah. We can get you.
>> You ever been to a house party? They
those house parties were the days, weren't they?
>> He does slim cogn.
>> Barely has better teeth than triple. [laughter]
>> Listen, when did you last go to a house party?
>> About four weeks ago. >> Really? >> Mhm.
>> I haven't been to a house party in
bloody years. They're the days though.
They were the days, bro. Well, house parties. Yeah.
Not a good idea. Imagine peon. He's read
it. Days go mental.
>> Tripper wouldn't know what to do. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Greasy. I
>> Oh, bless.
>> Hey, you're having a meltdown, Grezy.
>> Could find a new mama, isn't it?
>> You're good, lad. Yeah.
>> So, what if I go out and I approach in
Middlesbrough, Dusty? What What will
happen if I do some approaches in Middlesbrough?
You might get some, but I think it could
be same sad.
>> Well, [laughter] I reckon it could be
the same sad.
What? The same sad song as Dusty says.
>> You never know. Never know. Oh, bro.
I've got, you know, I've got a power
battery like right next to me and I got
that when I was in Middlesbr, bro.
>> The white power
>> think like 20 20 25. It was
>> not bad, lad.
>> No, I got it from Middles, bro. I
remember that cuz when I was there I got
it in it. Yeah.
Yeah. It was all right.
>> Dusty, stop asking me silly questions.
You'll not be
>> Well, it's not those Dusty, is it? You
bloody plonker. Because Reddit told me
that I'd meet someone. So,
Reddit said I'll meet someone. Or do you
know there's an account that come on
before and it said Laney said that we'd
meet someone because my mom said to me
years ago, you'll meet someone. So,
they're trying to mock me in it. Yeah,
you will meet someone one day. Just it
just depends when you will. It'll happen. But
>> so like So it could happen when I'm like 50.
>> That could happen next week for all you
know. Just just all just all depends,
lad. But it [snorts] could also happen
when I'm 50 as well.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Just depends, right?
>> Imagine you meet someone when you're 50
and you're too [ __ ] old to get a [ __ ] erection.
>> Yeah, it might. That might happen to
you. You never know. Just depends on
>> Well, I've got a pretty good feeling. I
think it will happen. You know, I've got [laughter]
I've got a feeling it probably will.
>> Not necessarily.
>> Yeah, I agree. Dusty is trying to What's
Dusty said? Stop asking me silly
questions when you know the answer. So,
what's Dusty's basically saying there's
the same sad.
>> Yeah, basically the same sad song in it.
>> you need to stop watching Porn Trip Rage. [snorts]
>> I don't really watch it, man. Like,
>> you watch it sometimes, I it
watches P. Yeah.
>> What do you watch?
>> What do you watch like realistic?
>> Do you watch it? Do you watch it on like
XXX and it
>> I don't watch it now, lad? Cuz you've
got to [ __ ] verify yourself, haven't
you? And [ __ ]
>> Oh, yeah. That's why I use VPN. That's
why I use a VPN in it.
>> Oh, do you watch the porn?
>> When I go on it, I use a VPN. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. That verify thing is annoying, man.
>> Be realistic be Triple H and belly and
flat would be great.
>> But you So when you used to watch it
before, did did you used to like was it
like a freom you watched? [laughter]
>> Oh, no. I don't really know. know when I
used to watch it was just [ __ ]
anything [snorts] really lad but like do you watch
>> some people some people some people
watch the wolf porn [snorts]
>> yeah you do just it's a maza lad
>> no there are still some sites though
there is still some sites where you
don't need to verify you can find them
>> well ones I've been used to check they
all [ __ ] need verification
>> yeah most of them are most of them are
but they are some it yeah some
>> what is that to do with the government would it?
>> I'm not sure, Pete. [laughter]
>> I'm not sure, Pete. I'm pretty sure it's
something to do with the government.
>> Are you a freaky guy asylum? Yeah, he's
he's not well asylum, is he?
>> You know, my favorite site is X videos.
I like the old vintage porn. I just watch vintage.
>> Antman said to me, drip rates, that's
Ant-Man said, "What? You watch porn from
the 70s? That's [ __ ] weird." He said it's weird.
>> Yeah, it is weird, lad.
>> Yeah, I was one from the 70s triple.
So, do you know you struggle getting
these women, Peter? You'll do a lot of
tugging then, do you?
>> You'll do a lot of tugging, won't you?
Because you don't really get much funny. [laughter]
>> Yeah, basically. Yeah. >> Yeah.
Yeah, I'm hamster gra like xxx.
>> Yeah, I use I use I use tube survi and I
go on all the vintage stuff.
>> I used to watch that al lad.
>> You used to watch Johnny Sins is it? >> No.
>> How do you know who he is again?
>> I don't know who he is to be honest. >> Huh?
>> I don't even know who he is.
>> You don't know who what the the board man?
No. [ __ ] me, lad. Oh,
>> do you watch the porn stars like Peter?
>> No, I don't. I I just watch Vintage
Born. I can't watch any I can't watch
any I can't watch any of the new stuff. [laughter]
>> Sh dusty's coming.
Used to wait for the
>> Yeah. Yeah. I used to when I used to
watch Babe Station. Do you remember Babe Station Triple?
>> [ __ ] going back some years that lad. Yeah.
>> You remember that? Yeah.
>> You used to do phone sex, isn't it?
>> No, I've not done never done that, mate.
>> Have you done?
>> No, but you you think watching vintage
porn is weird. Really? >> Yeah.
>> Why though? It's just porn.
>> [ __ ] old porn. Old [ __ ] really old porn. [ __ ]
>> Yeah, because it because it looks the most realistic.
Um you just you need watching modern new
newer stuff the modern day stuff lad like
>> you watch
>> I don't know why you watch
>> that's strange man said it's strange goo
I watched porn from 70s
and man's right it is he said that he
says that he knows a lot of people
that's watch porn but never from the 70s and 80s
but to be fair that's when the best
pornos were it's like the best films
were in the 80s and 90s. Think about it.
>> Not necessarily.
>> No, but like a lot of the horrors like
you know the Chuckies and that like they
were in the 1980s and [ __ ] You know
what I mean?
>> Do you know what? Have you ever watched
Smile the horror um triple?
>> That's a great I like that. Yeah, I like Smile. Yeah.
>> He said Antman said it's pathetic.
They're making horror films now and
people smiling. It's ridiculous.
>> I agree. That's right. Yeah. is a
[ __ ] It is pathetic the way it's all
being set up that smile. But don't get
us wrong. Don't get us wrong. It is
good. I like I like smile too as well.
Smile too is good.
>> Yeah. I like the little girl smile with
the little girl smiling is in it.
>> Smile. Yeah. [ __ ]
>> I'll make a third one. Yeah.
>> I hope so. Yeah. Cuz I know it's not the
scariest and it's weird how they how
they've put it all together in that.
>> It's something to watch. Is it something?
>> I like it, man. I rated me. I think it's
a good film. I know it's not the [ __ ] [laughter]
you know what's so funny when you you
know what's so funny when you come in
earlier and I asked you did you see the
police thing come the guys know about
the football that's so funny you saw it
>> yeah watch it yeah [laughter]
>> and he's said he said what method are
you getting there he says I can't tell
you that and he's like okay yeah did you
see the bit where he said h was it you
purchase ticket purchased the ticket he
said I can't can't disclose that information unfortunately [laughter]
Yeah. Oh, it's a barrel of loves. Bow of
>> It's good that Tik Tok.
>> Oh, it's it's addicting though, is it?
>> It is. Yeah. Like I'm like I can't get
off that Tik Tok, mate. When you're
scrolling, you can't stop scrolling, can you?
>> You're too deep in it, Triple.
>> There's a Steve.
>> You're too deep in it. Triple.
>> Yeah, that Tik Tok, man. I I Tik Tok
better than YouTube, man. >> Yeah. [snorts]
Oh, there Fraser was a good guy. Always
wanted your phrase.
>> Did you Greasy? Yeah, I like that. Um,
>> you liked Fraser, didn't you, Triple?
>> No, he's a melting him lad.
>> Yeah, I said that you and him could live
together. Do you remember? And do cocaine?
>> Yeah, just be realistic, B.
>> Well, I am being realistic. You were
phrase in the town.
>> You said you wanted You said that you
wanted to beat him up. that phrase it.
>> Yeah, he's a he's a melting lad. Um,
Grezy, do you what do you watch on that
Tik Tok? Do you go in anyone's live and
that? I go on a few of the lives and that, mate.
>> Do you go live, Peter?
>> I don't go on I don't use Tik Tok, bro.
>> You've just said you were on there.
>> No, I saw that on Facebook or Instagram. Tik Tok.
>> No, no, Tik Tok. Tik Tok. I don't use
Tik Tok, bro. Yo, last time I went on
TikTok, I think it was to find my mama,
but then I deleted it.
>> Did he just see? I can't remember. Did F
with a bagad? >> Yeah.
>> What the f you're in? >> No.
>> Why don't you like Fraser? Cuz he was
just a melt. Yeah.
>> He's a [ __ ] idiot, wasn't he? Really?
>> Do you remember his remember his voice?
He's like PJ brat. remember?
>> Yeah. All right,
>> but you know me me doxing him. LT said I
should do I should LT get in there. You
all right, lad?
>> Me and me and um Fraser was doing
cocaine together. Is that funny?
>> I'll have to have a look. He was good
that lad. Yeah. Yeah. [gasps] Didn't Tim
and Michael Basset make you pay for the
sniff last time he wrote with them?
>> Yeah. Monty man bought some [ __ ]
shite, didn't he? Or something? He got robbed.
>> What I don't understand. Listen, this is
what I don't understand, bro. Yeah. So,
you know Timmy um met Monty and Mike,
right? Remember? Yeah. They met?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> And they didn't do anything and it was
all good, right? So, you think that's
the end of it, is it? But now it's starting again. [laughter]
You know what I mean? How does that even
make sense? Do you see what I mean?
>> I know what you mean, lad. Yeah.
>> Because they're all like, "Oh, cuz Monty
was like, "Oh, I'm not going to hit
Timmy. He's a good lad." And now it's
all starting again. What was the point
of them even meeting?
>> What was the point of them meeting then?
>> That's it. I know. Pay. What's just on
about Yeah. I can remember all them
receipts. Didn't you try and buy sniff
it? It was in a wrap or something and it
was just there was just just receipts.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
>> How much did you pay for that?
>> Couple uh couple of years ago.
>> How much were on the quiz? >> Yeah.
>> What? for some reason. [laughter]
>> Yeah, it was a black guy, lad.
>> It was a black guy.
>> [ __ ] hell.
>> Yeah, it was a black fella.
>> Do you know where it was last week? It
was Nine Elms. I done a delivery of Nine
Elms um couple of months ago. Yeah, it's
Nine Elms. Do you know Nine Elms?
>> Yeah. Nice, man.
>> Yeah, it was outside Nine Elms stationed.
So, what do you do with this guy rob you then?
>> No, he just ripped me off.
>> Yeah, it's the same thing, Peter.
>> No, it's not. It's different.
>> Not really.
>> Robbing basically means when someone
just robbed you and run away, he you
know what I mean?
>> Yeah, but still the same is it? If you
said he's giving you stiff receipts, robbed you.
>> He coned me.
Yeah, he bought a bunch of receipts. [laughter]
>> Not good, is it?
Now that's crazy that like [ __ ] hell.
I've only got you banned from mornings
for kissing someone else. [laughter]
Just does she remember all this man?
>> Yeah, I do remember that.
>> She thought she told me she was Yeah.
>> Tik Tok accounts have all of them drama
on them like this.
>> Like what's the main one? Cuz I might
have to jump in and have a watch.
>> I like a bit of drama. Me.
Will Grievy ever come off here?
>> No, I think Greavves is a bit deep in now, lad.
>> Oh gosh, Greavves. Do you remember that?
Oh gosh, is that funny? >> Yeah.
>> You want to do a big double both teams
to score tomorrow? Triple.
>> Is that what you No, I'm not. I probably
want B on me.
>> Let's put Let's put £500 on two teams.
Let's give it a whirl.
>> I'll have to have a look. Rem Mr. UK Tik
Tok official after we'll jump in and
have a look. See what's going on, man.
>> You know what I'm saying?
>> I can't believe I can't believe I even
kissed that person, Dusty.
>> I can never go in that O'Neal. I can
never go in that O'Neals ever again,
bro. Unless the the staff will never
change. The bouncer will never leave,
bro. It's the same people.
>> What happened in there like Peter?
>> Oh, long story.
>> Tell me. Anyways,
>> no, it's just long story, bro.
>> Yeah. What was you saying?
>> Yeah. Just So, you're not on TikTok?
>> No, sir.
>> What time did you wake up today?
>> Why don't you make babies with USA? Is he?
>> No, I've got a baby. Me. That's all. I
want one baby. One kid. I
>> have two babies.
No, [ __ ] that.
>> It might be for you, Peter, but it's not
going to be for me. [laughter] >> Really?
>> Do you want any kids? Like,
>> no, I've already got a kid.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yeah. Um, King the dog.
>> You like King the Dog?
>> Yeah. The Goodman Dogger. Yeah.
>> He's a cute little He's a cute little whiffer.
>> Where's he at?
>> At my sisters. Oh, [laughter] is it your sister's dog?
>> Yeah, she let us keep it and then she
took the dog back. >> Oh, king of
>> Why would I be allowed Why won't I be
allowed kids? Uh, Dusty, these people
said if I had a kid triple, it'd get
risked straight into the care system.
>> More than likely, just the way you go on. Yeah.
>> Risk straight into the care system.
>> More than likely. Yeah. be swooped away
by social services immediately. But
that's mad though. You know the whole
Monty with the social services thing was
over YouTube. That's mad to think over
this app it got social services involved. It
>> ruins how brutal this app is, doesn't
it? Really when you think about it [laughter]
how scary it is.
>> You think it's funny.
>> Oh, I do think a lot of it's going on
here. But what realistically deep down
when you think about it like it
shouldn't be allowed to it really like [laughter]
>> well the same website you could watch
Mickey Mouse on is how Monty man lost
his kids. That's mad bro.
>> Yeah but like Monty man had time had
chance to get off of you when they were
doing all this and he didn't do it. So
>> he refused to come off.
>> He refused to come off. Yeah,
>> he did.
>> Couldn't get off there.
But now look, now look.
>> Exactly. But he'd still be with KK if it
wasn't for you.
>> Yeah, he'd still be with KK and the kids. Griezy,
>> that was funny the other night that when
you said when you messaged KK if she was
coming to ours to have a barbecue, pay
that legend, man.
>> Yeah, I think she likes me.
>> What did you text us saying? Like >> um
who who Kaye? Yeah.
>> I didn't text her.
>> She said you did. You ask for a bar if
you want to come to your house for a bar.
>> No, I said it. Yeah, I said it. Yeah.
When she was on here, I said, "Let's go
come to my barbecue." Yeah.
>> Oh, what would Mont want you man as well
or just care?
>> Uh, she's K.
>> Would you give her Would you Would you
ride her like?
>> Nah, maybe just a [ __ ] [laughter]
>> You are mad. Did I hear you?
>> You're mad here. Well, fella,
>> I think she likes me. Do you?
>> I think she does. Yeah.
>> What do you think, Grecy? Do you think
Kay? I think she does. Deep down.
>> Deep down, she doesn't like that race.
She She's just with him for [ __ ] just
for the entertainment on this YouTube
over Jamie Egg. But deep down, I think
she wants you. Me?
>> What? What? What do you call one? Jamie egg.
>> You hear me? Yeah. >> [laughter]
>> Why you calling in his full day?
>> I don't know. I just do m K will go and
he look at the state of R. Yeah, true, Dusty.
>> Yeah, that's mad. That is mad.
>> Post a link. See if Rice joins. >> Yeah.
So, he's a [ __ ] Mong, isn't it?
>> Yeah, he's not Well, that R.
>> What do you What do you reckon Grevy
looks like? Do you reckon he's fat? Triple?
>> Yeah, definitely Greavvesy. Um, sorry.
What did you say, P?
>> What do you think Greavvesy look? Do you
reckon Greavves is fat in real life?
>> I don't have a clue, mate.
>> Would you guess he is, though? It
>> Well, not really. You can't judge
someone when you've never seen them. So,
>> it doesn't make sense, isn't it?
>> Just a guessing game in it. Yeah.
>> I might get that Grinch meal from
McDonald's. I might treat myself.
I I was going to get it me the other
day, but I [ __ ] it off cuz you know
the you know the fries you know the
shake the salt you get with it's a gen
flavoring. Gens are rotten.
>> Oh yeah, but you get the socks. You get
the socks. Black socks.
>> Yeah, I agree. You get the socks, Peter.
But the gen flavoring is not for me. But
it could be for you.
>> No, I don't think so, bro. I don't think so.
>> Why is it not for you, fella?
>> No. You know, there's not much I don't
like here. But I tell you two things I
don't like here. And there's there's not
much I don't like.
>> I don't like Yeah. I don't like jam and
I don't like I don't like sweet popcorn
and I don't like sweet corn. They're the
only like three things I don't like.
>> I don't like sweet. Say that again.
>> I don't like sweet popcorn. I don't like
sweet corn. And I don't like jam.
>> I like I like jam, but I don't like the other two.
>> I don't like sweet popcorn. It's
stinking, bro. Like it has to be salt or
butter or has sweet is nasty.
>> Sweet corn's the worst food known to
man. It shouldn't ever ever be.
>> I love peanut butter. I love I love
peanut butter milksh. I like peanut
butter though. I do like peanut butter.
>> What's your favorite milkshake?
>> Probably peanut butter and Oreo. You?
>> Yeah. I'm not a big Oreo. I like peanut
butter. I'm not a big Oreo lover. Like I
I like Bueno White. Me.
>> Me and you can meet up and have a milkshake together.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> How do you feel about that, Captain?
>> That'll be lush, lad. Yeah. >> [ __ ]
appreciate some of Greavvesy there. Um,
hey, you remember when Grevy used to do
the uh the food videos? A bit of me.
They were good videos. I used to like them, mate.
>> Yeah, I do.
>> Yeah. Greasy. Greasy was the me man.
>> What do you What do you get from McDonald's then?
>> What do I get from McDonald's, Peter?
>> Yeah. I get um
I know I get all different but if I was
going now I'd get
I get a big tasty now like
>> yeah that's what I get but no but the
thing is bro I had that yeah uh I had it
not yesterday the day before but it
comes dry bro when you order it in it
>> I've noticed that yeah I agree with that
yeah but [ __ ] still ner
that's the one I get
I'm going to look on the menu once A
second. Is that cute? I'm going to look.
>> Are you asylum? >> Captain,
>> is that okay with you, boss? It's
>> fine [snorts] with me.
>> Does your mom like a Macky's pate? >> Yeah.
What does your mom get? >> Nookshake.
Oh, does she like a milkshake? What one?
>> Chocolate one.
>> I like the banana.
>> I like the banana one. The banana one's
lush in it.
>> The best, isn't it? Yeah, it's the best.
>> Yeah, it's [ __ ] lovely. That I've had
them all. The banana one's the best buy in mile.
>> Right, let me have a little Let me have
a little look. Hold on a minute. [snorts]
>> Oh gosh, little Grinch.
>> The Grinch Big Mac build. The Grinch
nine chicken nugget meal. Medal McPlant.
Have you seen that Mclant?
>> Would you ever have a McLant? [laughter] >> No.
>> Have you had it?
>> No. I've never had a Mcl.
>> Well, there's one here, but this isn't
the Grinch. This is a cheesy
chicken stack. That looks all right. No, I'm
>> It does look nicer, Peter. I've seen
that. Yeah. Have Have you seen the
cheese melt dippers? They look nice. I like
>> You've had them?
>> Yeah, the Lush.
>> I could get them, but that's not with
>> Grezy. What was that Mc Pineapple Burger
like from McDonald's? I seen you review
that, but I didn't see what you said about it.
I I hate pineapple as well, me, but
>> Oh, I love pineapple. Nice.
>> I like pineapple.
>> You like pineapple?
>> Juice. Only the juice. Nothing else.
>> No, bro. They they put pineapple in
[ __ ] pizzas. It's disgusting.
>> Yeah, I [ __ ] I agree with that. Yeah.
[snorts] Hawaiian pizza in it.
>> It's [ __ ] vile. What What do you like
on your pizza?
>> I like a don a pizza, me or I like a um
chicken tiger, garlic butter.
>> What I like on my pizza? I like
jalapino, onion, tandoori, uh chicken, and ham.
[ __ ] beautiful, man. Beauty [ __ ] fool.
>> Is that what you get from Papa John's?
>> Anywhere? Yeah, anywhere.
>> Yeah. Do you get any sides with it or not?
>> No, just a pizza. That's enough cheese.
>> I like cheesy chips, mate.
>> Bless you then.
>> I like
>> Yeah. So, on the Grinch, I can either
get uh I can either get the Big Mac meal
with the nine chicken nuggets or the
Mclon. Why don't they have more? That's weird.
>> You've got to get the Big Mac meal value
for money cuz nine nuggets are no good,
man. I can eat 20 of them with a meal, mate.
>> Yeah, I ate I ate 20 yesterday. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. They're too easy. They go down too
quick in that door. No,
>> I think I'm going to get a Big Mac.
Yeah, I'm going to get this um Grinch
meal. Is that Is that okay with you, Greasy Boss? Okay, Captain.
>> I think I'm going to have a Chinese tomorrow. topless.
>> Why don't me order this?
>> That was nice. It worked well.
Surprisingly, the the pineapple was
pretty juicy. I said I would have that.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, you did gravely saying
that. Yeah, you did say have it again.
>> I know. Do you know Timmy? Yeah, he
calls Monty Man a virgin. That's how
>> Peter Peter one minute was the second
best thing in that menu. What was the
What was the best thing on that menu
then? Graves you tried, would you say?
>> Oh, one second. Come in.
>> Oh, someone wants to come in. Yeah, get
them on one sec.
>> Hello, PJ. I've never heard something in
my life. I've been listening for the
last 10 minutes.
>> Yeah, you're right.
>> What do you want, PJ? [ __ ]
>> like you
what? What is this? Oh, I wanted to sh
Katie, but she's good for a bird job. I
want to give you one.
>> Yeah. [laughter] Yeah, you would.
Oh, are are you are you upset that I
wouldn't [ __ ] you, KK?
>> I don't want to [ __ ] you. There's
nothing to [ __ ] I've seen you.
>> Yeah, remember that.
>> Yeah, I've got I'm Well, I'll have you
know, KK, that I'm joining the porn
industry. So, haha,
>> you can't get one. [laughter]
>> I'm joining the porn industry. [clears throat]
>> Would you give Peter a one? What?
>> One second. One second. One second. I
need to I need to edit this burger. A
second. One second. [clears throat] I
don't want no sauce, no pickle slices,
no lettuce. I just want onion and
cheese. That's it. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry about that.
>> You did look nice.
>> I'm going to get an extra cheese sl I'm
going to get an extra cheese slice uh
for 60 p.
>> Big mac.
>> Yeah, man. I don't, bro. The Philly
cheese steak. Well, that was a nice one,
the Philly burger, but they stopped
doing it. The cheeseburg I used to get
that. Well, it was lush.
>> It was [ __ ] nice, but they stopped
it. Sorry about that. Yeah. Sorry, KK.
>> No. Doing yourself a happy meal. Yeah, that's lush.
>> I I'll [laughter] buy you a happy meal.
>> I'll buy you a happy meal.
>> Yeah, Grezy the do, lad. I I
>> I really I really I really want you, but
I don't think you want me.
>> Wait, if you get um the Grinch menu for
adults, I think they do [ __ ] items
with it, don't they?
>> That's what I'm getting. I'm going to
get socks with a kit.
>> Yeah, I'm just ordering it now.
>> Oh, you get some Grinch socks. Yeah, that's lush. >> Yep. >> [laughter] [snorts]
>> There [clears throat] we go. Lovely.
That's ordered. Be coming soon. Lovely. [laughter]
>> Do you have a McDonald's app then? >> No.
>> Hey, Curly. Did Peter message you before
asking if you're going to for a barbecue?
>> I didn't message. I said it. Yeah.
Yeah, we can have some nice T-bone steak
in the summer. Kaye, what do you think
of that? [laughter]
>> Someone said the new wank socks for your PJ. >> Sorry,
>> new wanking socks. That's why you're getting them.
>> Nah, never w sock in my life.
>> I think Ker likes you, Peter.
>> Yeah, I think so, too.
>> Triple H.
You are. [laughter]
>> I've never toelcome
to the mad house. [laughter]
>> The mad house full of [ __ ]
>> Change menu. Can't wait for you to get the screenshot.
It'll be green. Greasy one there for the
Grinch. They'll be green, lad.
>> Actually, Righty is not in the skip.
He's sat next to me being quiet.
getting rice triple hol.
>> Yeah, Rice is nice today. Are you Rice? [laughter]
He's got his head in his ass today. I'm not joking.
>> When are you coming to see me, K?
>> Never. I only saw you once and that was
years ago and that was enough for me. [laughter]
>> We met in real life, didn't we? Yeah, unfortunately.
>> Yeah, I think we make a good couple.
>> I feel sorry for Monty man.
>> Oh god. Why?
>> He's had a bit of stick on this YouTube,
hasn't he? He should have got off when
he when he had the chance. But
>> well, we're talking about [ __ ] here. He
should have come off years ago. But hey, [laughter]
>> it's not as easy as that when you're too
deep in it.
>> Oh no. Wonder why whose fault is that? PJ. [laughter]
>> Yeah, you got him on here, Peter, didn't you?
>> Yeah, but hey, but Katie, how did you
get on here? I didn't get you on there.
>> Well, actually, you got [ __ ] on here
and then [ __ ] drove my name in the road
and then they all started hassling me
and then there you go.
>> This is what [laughter] they do on here, Kly. >> What?
>> This is what they do on here.
>> I know.
>> [ __ ] mad. Yeah, but your brains
and decided to join. I don't want a [ __ ] McDonald's.
>> You're not having a McDonald's care.
>> I don't want a McDonald's. To be fair
with you, I don't really like
McDonald's. Like, it's very rare. I eat it.
>> No, I don't. I'm only getting it for I'm
only getting it for the Grinch meal.
>> Yeah, cuz you want your wanking socks. [laughter]
>> I might go I might wear them tomorrow
and go approaching in the sock squeezy.
Hey, you know what you should do, Peter?
You should wear wear just wear some
shorts, right? You wear your socks so
everyone can see your new socks. >> Huh?
>> Why don't you just wear some shorts and
then wear your socks and everyone can
see your new Grinch socks for your trainers, lad?
>> Yeah, I could do. Yeah, [clears throat]
>> that'll be good content.
>> Socks. Yeah, I could do [laughter]
that. Would you like that, Grezy? Poor
[ __ ] So instead of going out pulling
birds, PJ, you sat at home waiting for
your McDonald's and your wanking socks.
That is rush.
>> Yes. Yes, sir. I don't I don't need to
pull women. I've already got a woman. You
>> Peter, why don't you send Monty Man the
link to join your live?
>> Oh, you trying to start a pot now,
Triple H? [laughter]
>> No, I don't mind that Monty man, me. I
think I don't mind him. I don't have a
really bad bad to say about the lad, but
he just should have got off you when he
had the chance. [laughter]
>> He said he should have got off you when
he had the shot.
>> Cuz you know what these people do, don't you?
>> If he turns on the exit button, right?
>> I'm not drinking now, Katie. I'm not
drinking now, Katie, till New Year's Eve. >> Why?
>> Because I can't be bothered. [sighs] Well,
>> box resolution be not to go out. Uh PJ,
>> how about your new year's resolution not
to go out for a full year?
>> He needs to go out. He needs to go for a
full year. I can't do it for a full
year. You mad? No.
For [laughter] a full year? >> Nah.
>> Like your mom said, Peter, that the time
will come. You fancy salam.
>> Wait, she's trolling me. Kaye,
>> I'm not I'm being serious.
>> I can't wait to get my little socks.
>> Wait, she sounds all right.
>> I can't wait to get my little socks. Uh,
my little Grinch socks.
>> Well, let's just hope they fit your feet.
>> Hopefully, Kaylee. >> Kaye. >> Yeah.
>> What do you think of these people making
Leslie accounts on this YouTube? >> Pardon?
What do you think of these people making
Leslie Hag accounts on this YouTube?
>> Talking about Leslie H.
>> I'm saying they used to make Monty mom's
mom like Monty mom's Monty man's mom
accounts on YouTube and go in people's chats.
>> They still do.
>> Well, does that does that still happen? Does it?
>> They still do it.
>> Well, it is bizarre. But to be fair,
these people are just bizarre anyway.
>> Yeah, they're not well, are they? [laughter] H
what do you think? Right. I I can't
believe Monty man introduced me to nonss, man.
>> He introduced me to [ __ ] nonss.
>> So PJ, you and [ __ ] friends again now.
Yeah, cuz I can't up.
>> No. No, we're not.
>> Why' you say that?
>> Oh, I'm just saying it's just talking
nice of him this time. The other day you were talking. No,
>> no. [laughter] It's just sad what these people do.
>> Clearly, do you think you'll beat
Natalie Garrett in a fight? [laughter]
>> You know what? THAT WOULD THAT WOULD
actually be [ __ ] epic to watch,
wouldn't it? [laughter]
>> It would. Yeah, I was thinking that myself. I
>> I can't wait to get my little sock squeezy.
>> No, [clears throat] I don't I don't have
no reason to fight Natalie. I mean, it's
not I don't have beef with her. It's him.
>> I think I think you're better than Natalie Katie.
>> You know what, PJ? I think you should
nick Natalie off [ __ ] That'll make it better.
>> No, I had I had my chance with her years
ago, but I prefer you. I think you look better.
>> Oh, shout out PJ. Stop shouting [ __ ]
>> No, honestly. Honestly. No. You know, I
had a chance with Natalie years ago when
you were still with Monty. Did you not remember?
>> Yeah, you did actually. Yeah. Yeah. Do
you not remember when I was like 22?
>> Well, you are the same age as me, but I
don't. You know,
>> maybe I don't think No. Yeah, he was.
Monty was on here then. Maybe he wasn't
when it first. Maybe he wasn't. Maybe not.
>> But definitely. Yeah, maybe. But yeah, I
think you're better, Kaye.
>> Look, PJ, it's never going to happen. I
don't see you like that. So,
>> I think you'd be a better candidate for baby Peter.
>> Oh my god. [laughter]
What do you think, Grezy?
Katie, you could be my mama for the winter.
>> You're disgusting. [laughter]
>> I'm not disgusting. How's that disgusting?
>> It's not disgusting at all.
>> You know what? You put our generations
to shame. I'm ashamed that you're the
same age as me. >> You're
Kayie. You're two months older, ain't it,
>> PJ? PJ,
>> wait. Are you Wait, Kayla, are you two months older?
>> Yep. So, respect your elders. PJ.
>> Yeah. So, you could be So, you could
technically be my mama then. >> PJ.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
>> You can hear me. >> Huh?
>> Can you hear me? >> Yeah.
>> All right. That's good. Nice to meet you. Nice.
>> Yeah. No, I was on about you. About
Katie. Enjoy sitting here.
>> Yeah, but we thought you was gone.
>> Well, Katie doesn't sh for free. She sh
for a bargain bucket. [laughter]
>> Brains likes it. Is it? >> Yeah.
Oh my god. Fingerl looking chicken.
Yeah, that's nice. Really?
>> What you So, what you going to do? So,
what are you going to do? Um, Kayie.
Yeah. If one day you go on the internet
and you watch porn and I'm and I'm on
the I'm on the porn as a porn star. What
would you do?
>> She's gonna have you [ __ ] [laughter]
all you do. What would you do?
>> Oh god.
>> Might watch it. >> What?
>> If Peter's a porn star, you might watch
him, might you?
>> What if might watch him? No, thank you.
I've already seen his prize and I don't Nah, [laughter]
>> it's quite big.
>> It's not PJ. You can't even see nothing.
>> Am I being funny? Right, P? [laughter]
I don't want to make you feel so small
like I'm not that horrid, but
it years ago, right, and [ __ ] showed me
you getting a [ __ ] right? I could
have seen your [ __ ] I've just seen a woman.
>> Well, obvious Well, obviously Well,
obviously you can't see you couldn't see
my [ __ ] It was in her gob. So, She was going to
>> No. If it was that big, right, like you
say it is. Yeah. You would see at least
a quarter of that [ __ ] going in their
mouth. There was just nothing to see. It
was just gobbled in one.
>> Yeah. Very big.
>> How could you make them any smaller?
He's already small, aren't they?
>> What do you think, Trip H? Who would be
a better partner to Kane? real do you think?
>> Um I think Monty man who's typing the
private chat here. Big up rise rise bro.
Can you link the channels you and KK do
the lives on in the back? Please [ __ ] off.
>> Would you would you ever get back? You'd
never get back with Monty in it. K. >> What?
>> You never get back with Monty in it.
>> No way. [ __ ] that.
Monty man. Monty man used to go live and
used to talk to all his new addresses
and that didn't he?
>> Yeah, I remember that.
>> Would be your new mama.
>> Oh, it's nearby. It's near the the
food's here, I think. Grezy, the food's here.
>> Wow, he's getting that deliver.
He's getting excited for his wanking socks, peep.
>> Don't need to wank. I've got you.
>> No thanks.
>> It's coming. It's here. It's here.
>> Are you okay, Captain?
>> A look at your socks, Peter.
>> Yeah. See,
got the goods. Got the goods. Got
Show your view is your socks.
>> One second.
Hold on a minute.
>> Yeah. In it, Stephen. Lad.
Oh, one second.
>> What color? Why people asking what color
you going to be? Green one. One second, brother.
>> Oh, here we go.
>> What drinks did you get? Cork.
>> Yeah, one sec.
>> You know what? I like the banana
milkshakes from McDonald's. I'm not
going to lie.
>> So do I. So do I.
>> We've just been on about them. Curly.
Yeah, they are. Where's my socks?
in the you got them.
>> Where are my socks?
>> Oh, he didn't get his wanking socks.
What a shame.
>> Well, I didn't get the socks.
>> You going to have to ring them then and
say where your socks?
>> I didn't get my little socks. [laughter]
>> Are they in the bag? PJ from PJ PJ McDonald's
socks off. [laughter]
>> What the hell? Where's my bloody socks?
>> Oh no. You know what? I was actually
open to see them socks. Actually,
>> where my bloody socks?
They must have run out of socks.
Oh, Triple H, come back, man. You left
me with PJ.
>> Love you, baby.
>> I love you, Bubba.
>> PJ, you need to sort your life out.
>> No, you love me.
>> I don't love anyone. PJ,
>> you what?
>> I don't love anybody.
>> There you go. She doesn't even love you,
Rice. Stay alone. So, [ __ ] you, [ __ ] [laughter]
>> That just goes to show she doesn't love you either.
>> They must have run out of socks.
>> Unless the delivery drivers nicked them. [laughter]
>> That's not funny. I was looking forward
to my little socks. [laughter]
>> I'm still a baby.
>> I'm a baby.
>> Yeah. You know, you're not fully
developed yet, are you?
>> No, cuz cuz I got starved of my um
nutrients. Isn't that right?
>> I don't know.
>> Oh [ __ ]
>> K admitted what? What did I admit?
>> You know what? You admitted
>> You don't love anyone. No, I don't. It's
too much [ __ ]
There you go. [ __ ] go. [laughter]
>> No. What? Sometimes I wish I was gay. I might succeed. >> What?
>> You eat porky piggies,
>> huh? What?
>> You eat piggies.
>> Piggies? Look. Right, PJ? You can't
troll me for [ __ ] Yeah. So, this is your worst.
>> I'm asking I'm asking you to eat bacon.
I mean, do you eat pork? I'm asking if
you eat pork. It's a normal question.
>> Why are you calling me a bacon? Are you? That's lush.
>> No, I'm saying do you eat pork? Cuz I
eat pork. I eat bacon.
>> Yeah, I do.
>> Why are you always so defensive, ma'am?
No, to be fair, I thought you were
trolling me. And if you were, you
>> Why would I be trolling you?
>> Cuz you are trolling me anyway.
>> I'm not trolling you. I'm asking you
what you eat. I'm trying to get to know you more.
>> No, it's not that I'd rather be Ben than
be with. It's just that sometimes men
are just more whack than what it's worth.
>> Yeah. You haven't met me yet, Katie.
You'd love me if you met me again.
I don't know. You know, PJ,
you got too many problems, bro.
>> Yeah, I won't have any problems if I was with you. >> See,
>> he said Greasy, Greedy, what the [ __ ]
you call your name. Next time you're
out, you have to knit some Macky's in
Paris and explain you didn't get your socks.
>> Yeah, I was looking forward to socks.
>> rebound. Rice isn't a rebound.
N G is a rebound for [ __ ] She slept
with him within two, three weeks. [laughter]
>> Yeah. Natal's got black flat.
>> Actually, actually, did Mango actually say that?
>> Yeah, he did. >> Wow.
>> Multiple multiple times.
>> And yeah, I'm supposed to be jealous of
her. She's got black flaps. That makes sense. >> Yeah,
>> I think deep down is still like me. >> What?
>> I think deep down me.
>> Look, PJ, you're playing with fire, bro.
>> I'm not. I'm being serious. I swear to
God. I'm not told, bro.
>> Where's Triple H gone? Quite like him,
actually. He's just ran off. Yeah, his
his little voice is very soothing, isn't it?
I like his little voice.
>> He's getting your ass back on this panel now. >> Yeah.
Bless you, KK, with your little farmer
accent. Bless you.
>> You love this farmer accent. Most people do, actually.
You sound like a little farmer. And and
and Triple H sounds like a Jordy.
Rice is whatever. I'm over reading that comment.
>> You like writing accent. Um K. >> Yep. >> Yeah.
Bless you. K.
>> So, what's your plans for the weekend
then, PJ? Um
probably having a wank and sleeping.
>> Oh, lovely. Don't want to know. >> Yeah. [clears throat]
>> Not a lot really.
Not this weekend.
>> What about next weekend?
>> I don't know. I don't plan ahead. >> No.
It's about a week or so now. It crazy. Huh?
>> Christmas is in about a week and a half
now, is it?
>> I know. It's depressing, isn't it?
>> You done your Christmas shopping yet, PJ?
>> I bought my mom Ugg boots and that's it.
>> Ugg boots. Oh, nice. What color? >> Right.
>> How do you know Ugg boots are? How do
you know what they were?
>> How do I know what UGG boots are? Cuz I
used to wear proper Ugg boots when I was younger.
>> Well, if you play your card right, I
might buy you a pair. >> [laughter]
>> You did. [laughter] >> Yeah.
>> PJ's doing
>> they were £165 pricey.
>> You can get old slippers now as well and sliders.
>> Yeah. Lord J got him the silly bugger.
>> What did you What did you ask your mommy
for Christmas and PJ?
>> Well, I've got so far I've got um
electric toothbrush. I've got a link
set. And my mom's my sister's buying me a t-shirt.
>> Well, you're not supposed to know your
present. So, I'm only asking you what
you've asked for, not what you've got.
>> Well, that's what I asked for. That's
what I got.
>> Wow. So, Christmas and you already know
what you got. Wow.
>> Yeah, but I'm not but I'm not um having
until Christmas. I want to open new.
>> What? What are you getting?
>> To be honest, I'm not really in the mood
for Christmas. Not after the year.
>> It It doesn't even feel like Christmas
as you get older. >> Nope.
I'm just not in the I'm not in the
festive mood at all to be fair.
>> No. When I was like 11, 12, I used to
love Christmas, getting the presents and
I couldn't sleep, you know.
>> But yeah, you get older, it's different.
>> Who's that?
>> Steven come to London New Year's Eve.
>> No, I don't like London. I've been
through it so many times and in it. I
don't like it. It's too busy, too many
people, too much traffic. [ __ ] that.
Too many [ __ ] as well.
>> It's just too busy for my liking.
>> You prefer Plymouth. Le
>> I'm not in Plymouth. I'm in Leicester.
>> I know. I know. But I'm saying you prefer Plymouth.
>> Well, I prefer different places. But
there you go. But I wouldn't live in London.
>> I would like in London.
But I couldn't live in London. [ __ ] that. >> Yeah.
>> Okay. Get your presents off rice and
start fresh. That's not nice, is it?
That's like me saying to you,
you get your presents off your
girlfriend UK asylum and then she breaks
up with you. Wow. Bless you.
Bless you in life.
>> Can you buy me a present for Christmas?
>> You know what? If everyone was good this
year, we got a selection box each with a
Christmas card. [laughter] Okay. Would
you live in Cornwall?
>> Look, PJ, I'm not done. I'm not giving
nothing. I'm in Leicester.
>> For God's sake, I'm trying to have a
normal conversation. You think I'm
trolling you? Fine. [ __ ] hell, man.
Don't have a Why are you Do you know
what? You always been this way. You
know, even when you was with Monty, why
are you so [ __ ] defensive? Jesus Christ
where you are.
You're the one who started all this mess.
>> No. How? How? I tried to get you off
YouTube, Kaylee, and you wouldn't come
off. It's not my fault.
>> Come off. Why would you leave me in the first place?
>> Jesus Christ.
>> KK and PJ on the train scene. Wow.
>> Yeah. Me and K would be cute together,
to be fair. Yeah, though. Me and PJ was quite obvious.
>> We got like we got like a lovehate
relationship, isn't it?
>> Well, to be fair, I don't really hate
anyone. Well, I do.
>> You know, then
>> I don't hate you, PJ. I mean, hate is a
big word. I mean, I hate people
literally on here, but not You're not in
that category hate. [laughter]
>> So, you hate people on here?
>> Yeah. With a passion. But you're not in
that category hate with a passion. So
you mean like you mean like Pat M you
mean like Pat Mustard and Truman or that? >> Yeah.
>> I hate I tell you who I hate that
[ __ ] nonslegs and Lord Jay. I hate them.
>> Oh Lord Jay. Oh my god. You know >> and
>> people I hate on as well. There is
>> White s wanker that [ __ ] [clears throat]
>> Yeah. And he does he does that tune
every morning. Good morning. It does my
[ __ ] edging. You know what? I sub to
that [ __ ] because I can't you ever go on
Have you ever been on his live stream?
It's the same repeating people, is it?
>> No, I went on his live stream on panel
once and then he was like, "Oh, Katie,
do you want to go on a date with me?"
No, thank you. You're too old and you're
ugly. [ __ ] off.
>> That's lovely. That's what I like to hear.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> That's lovely, isn't it?
>> Franklin's going in the truck now.
>> You behave yourself, >> huh?
>> Steven Howard. >> Yeah,
I think me and KK would be good friends at least.
>> PJ, you're the opposite offline, but you
do need to sort your egg out. And
>> you haven't you haven't met me for
[ __ ] years. Okay. You know that for
>> You are quite you you're quiet when I
met you. Well, that was years ago to be fair. >> Yeah.
>> What did you want me to say?
>> I don't know. You're just timid.
>> I think I think you secretly love me cuz
I helped you with the suitcases.
>> No, that was just a kind gesture. >> Yeah.
Oh, look. Triple H is back. He's done
trolling me now. If Triple H
doesn't troll. He's a good son.
He doesn't troll. [sighs]
[ __ ] We can hear you.
>> Mate, if if me and you met up again, um
KK, you know who would be messaging you,
don't you? Nonsex.
>> I can't stand that bastard.
>> Same. I hate the [ __ ] ugly little
brat. But he would he would be messaging
you. You know that.
>> I don't know why I won't speak to him.
>> Cuz he stalks everyone that I meet and
[ __ ] So that's why
>> get in. Yeah, I was just saying to KK
that if me and KK met yet that um
[ __ ] nonslegs would be messaging her that it.
>> Well, actually PJ, you were meant to meet us
>> months ago. Actually, you said you was
going to meet us in Birmingham when it
all kicked off in [ __ ] and you didn't turn up.
>> Yeah, true. But did you want me to come?
>> You said you was on your way.
I think KK likes Peter Benny.
>> Oh wow. [laughter]
>> How do you think you like Peter By? KK,
what do you think? Triple H.
>> What do you think, Triple H?
>> I don't know, lad.
>> Why does everything come down to me
fancying everyone? You know what?
>> You know what? On this community, right,
I've shagged everybody. That's how
people have come across with me on here.
I've shagged everyone. All right. No,
>> you you you haven't you haven't shagged
everyone, but Natalie has. >> No,
>> you haven't, but Natalie G has.
>> Don't speak to a one here without
getting accused that you want to jump in
bed with them. It's insane.
>> It is. So,
>> oh gosh.
No, Natalie G is a slag.
>> I said that as well. But that's why I
fell out with Molly cuz I said that
Natalie G was ugly and he started like
going at me and [ __ ]
>> Oh [ __ ]
>> Thing is everybody's got their own
preference of women and men, what type
you're into, blahy blahy blah.
>> Yeah, that's true.
>> Yeah, but you used to like that Natalie Peter.
>> No, I [ __ ] did not. No, I didn't.
>> At one point you did.
>> No, I Well, why didn't I meet her then?
Then I would have met her then, would I?
Cuz I had a chance.
I know. I don't know why you met didn't
make it to be honest. She didn't have
the chance. I agree. Yeah. Yeah.
>> That's what I'm saying.
>> She was like 32. I was like,
>> what do you think of this YouTube then?
>> Why do you want me to go into it? [laughter]
>> [ __ ] you.
>> They've been doing this on here for
years, haven't they? >> Yeah.
>> What would you do, Kylie? Yeah. If we
was walking down the street and I was
doing that little voice.
>> What voice?
>> This one?
>> I tell you, as you grow up. [laughter] >> Really?
>> Yeah. Really?
>> Well, you don't like them little voices.
>> No, it's embarrassing. I won't even walk
next to you if you were talking like that.
>> What about you, Triple?
Yeah, he like he likes he likes that
Reddit Gravesy, doesn't he?
>> What would you do if I if I met you?
Triple H and I was doing them silly voices.
>> I just told you to go here. [ __ ] it off.
>> Triple H.
>> Yeah, but you used to like the voices.
>> You're from the Midland area. Triple H.
You got like an accent going on.
>> No, I'm from up north. M. >> Yeah. Or Liverpool. near Newcastle. >> Newcastle. >> What?
>> Near Newcastle.
>> Oh, Newcastle. Jordy. >> Yeah. >> Jordy. [laughter]
>> You reckon? Do you reckon Monty's watching this?
>> Hopefully not.
>> Monty man might be watching this. You
know what? What do you think we've seen?
Hopefully not. No.
>> You know what? I've been through
Newcastle, but I've never actually been in it.
You've been what? Sorry, Kelly.
>> I've been through Newcastle like not
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah.
>> But I've not actually been in it like Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. We get you. We get you.
>> Yeah. I think I think the Monty man is
watching me like [laughter]
>> maybe. Oh, [ __ ] Monty man. [ __ ]
hell. What is he? Nothing. >> [laughter]
>> It was a love of your life at one time. Kaye disaster. A disaster.
>> He's all right. The Mont the Monty man
is all right. I don't mind him. Me.
>> Why is that?
>> Not wrong for me. You are like him cuz he's funny.
>> No, he's just he's just he doesn't
deserve what's happened to him on here really.
>> Oh no, I do. That makes sense.
>> No, I'm not saying you do. I'm just
saying like I'm not saying you do
either. Like it's not like But you had
chance to get off here though, Kelly.
And you chose not to [laughter]
come off here and I gave up. [laughter]
>> The money man will never leave.
>> What did you What did you say to your
face? They had the chance to come off.
You're You're a troll. You're a
>> No, I'm not trolling. I'm talking
[ __ ] sense at the end of the day.
I can't tell you.
>> Had the chance to get off here.
>> It's, you know, it is what it is. I'm
not going to dictate to you who you talk
to, you know. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But what about Cai Mark? He could
have got off as well.
>> They're writing to Mark now, aren't
they? for threatening that mark to send
you know his new his new last know that
Ellen he's seeing they've sent loads of
stuff on that Facebook saying um he's a
he's a wrong and all that and he's a
[ __ ] seen a woman with seen a woman
disabled woman and that
>> yeah but you do realize that woman he
was dating is an adult right she's just
got mental issues
>> yeah I agree but it's still wrong like
he shouldn't have been
>> well no because if you watch one of his
videos. He even said that he's already
spoken to her dad. So, her dad knew he
was dating him.
>> Would you go to his funeral if she sign Mark dies?
>> Yeah. But shouldn't really be allowing
that early should he realistically like stop doing.
>> Yeah. Yeah. But he's not Yeah, that is
wrong. But at the same time, he's not a
nons like so.
>> Yeah, that's true. Yeah. Yeah.
>> I'm saying they're making it out that
he's a nons. They're not making out.
>> It's like they made the Monty man out to
be a nons. I don't think Monty man is
Monty man, isn't he?
>> I don't agree with what they done to
Monty man and like obviously getting
losing his kids and I don't agree now. I
think it's [ __ ] totally wrong me personally. >> Yeah.
>> Out of order, but this is what these people do.
>> Triple H. Are you missing the subject?
They're my kids as well.
>> Yeah, know you know what I mean. Yeah,
but if he is, it's not [ __ ] right. I
agree with that. Like [laughter]
they shouldn't be doing that, Curly. Oh,
at the end of the day,
>> if you went to if you went if you went
to Suicide Mark's funeral yet, what
would what would the cause of death be? >> What
>> what would what would what if Suicide
Mark died? Yeah. And people went to his
funeral, what would the cause of death be?
>> Probably als
Yeah, but what? Yeah, but what would it
be over though? Like, yeah. Over what?
You know the RL YouTube?
>> No, I don't. I don't.
>> YouTube's absolutely [ __ ] mad.
>> Yeah, but it can't be over YouTube cuz
you can watch Scooby on it.
>> How can it be over YouTube?
>> You can't It's not over YouTube cuz you
can watch Scooby-Doo on this side. It's like innocent.
>> I didn't even know how bad this [ __ ]
this um community was, mate. Like it's
it's it's rife in it. [laughter]
>> How long have you been on here then?
>> I've been on here for how long now, Peter?
>> Quite quite a few years. Yeah.
>> I've had my I've had my windows done in
over YouTube. Um Grezy,
>> oh [ __ ] up about windows, will you?
>> No, my windows did get done in. They did.
>> Yeah, so did mine and my front door. But
hey, everybody knows that. you know, [laughter]
yeah, it's not funny. It's scary. No, it
ain't funny. It's scary.
>> Yeah, but you laugh about I think it's
funny, Peter. It's not like people are
putting people with YouTube, man. Like,
>> it's scary. Hey, is it like when it
happened, my mom my mom listen Kaye,
when it happened Yeah. At first, my mom
was was in I wasn't in Yeah, and the
windows went in. It's not funny. It's scary.
>> Well, no, it's not. sat there laughing
because it happened to yourself but your
mother was home at the time. Don't you
find it was [ __ ] rental for me? My daughter
>> That's not funny. Yeah, it is. Yeah, but
Right. Yeah. But the thing is, Kate, but
the thing is, Kate, Rice brought that to
your door. So, you you knew that was
going to happen.
>> No, it didn't. It's this app. People are
making it personal over false
accusations and allegations and I think
it's wrong. I mean, people on this
community, right, should be taking the
law into their own hands is wrong. Do
you know what I mean? I agree with that,
Kelly. I agree. Yeah. Yeah.
>> So, what was you do? What was you doing
um when it happened? Was you just on the couch?
>> Well, I was in the hallway talking to
Rice. He was in the front room. The door
was obviously open.
>> Windows getting smashed and people
>> That's mad.
>> It's not even funny.
>> I'm not laughing. This is the way you're
I can just imagine you being imagine
being sat down here minding your own
business and you're hearing bam over
this stupid site. [ __ ] that.
>> This is grown men who have went out
grown men who went out the way to do
this all like it's [ __ ]
>> you. That's [ __ ] mad. Imagine you
like your family sat sat on a couch like
you know how the Simpsons sit on the
couch and then the windows get in.
>> That's mad. That is mad. said, "Anyway,
people in this community shouldn't be
taking the law into their lands and
[ __ ] [ __ ] It's just disgusting."
Like the trolling side of it is [ __ ]
heavy and like to me it just like funny
with just the takeaways, you know, that
that is just, you know, whatever. But [laughter]
>> yeah, I agree, Curly. You take away and
that is a good laugh, but when they're
putting windows and that through like a
[ __ ] No. No. No, no, but No, no, no.
Listen, listen, listen. The takeaway
thing is not a good laugh, though,
because it's ruining the company's
business, bro. They're They're losing
money because of these people.
>> I know, but would you rather have a
takeaway or smash windows?
>> Obviously a take Well, how about just
having none? How about having just none, is it?
>> Yeah, but if you had to have one.
>> Yeah, obviously a takeaway, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Mad
reason for you as well. You are
They send takeaways to you as well, Kayie.
>> You know what? It's a joke, right?
Obviously, Triple H likes Bongo, but
this is hard for me to say, whatever.
I'm going to say it. So, when Mong say I
like him, Kayie, he's just he's
>> No, but just like logically, right? What
[ __ ] got with Natalie, right? No one
put no windows in, no nothing. I get
with Rice and I move on and then it all
goes off. Like, that just doesn't make
sense to me. Like, that it's just Yeah.
No, cuz they've done this to Natalie and
Jeremy. They've uh they've done a lot to
Natalie and Jeremy was up He's been he's
up at C that one over this and [ __ ] >> Yeah, >> they
over these people.
>> No, no, no. Cuz No, but that court thing
weren't over YouTube.
>> No, that court thing was over a riot. He
went to a protest down in Devon when we
was living there.
>> Yeah. So, it wasn't YouTube, was it true? No.
>> Yeah, true. Yeah. [clears throat] I
didn't think of that. Yeah, he's right
there. Yeah. Yeah. Mommy, I got locked
up for the right [ __ ] mad.
>> No, but I think the people No, no, but I
think it was people on YouTube that
grassed him, was it?
>> No, he grassed himself cuz he live
streamed himself throwing stones and
that at people. [laughter]
>> He's a [ __ ]
>> He said he's already gone to court and
they gave him a warning, but then he's
saying that he's going court in a couple
of days. Who knows?
>> Well, he hasn't. No, he hasn't been to
court. The other day he lied about it.
He's actually he's got caught in
January. And I'm a gonna say how I know
this, but I know it. And he's
>> in trouble. What do you reckon?
>> Loads of people have been locked up over
them riots. So, you know, so
>> yeah, but yeah, but people been locked
up over this site as well. Look at that faith.
>> Yeah, he wasn't well though, wasn't he?
He was a [ __ ] fruit loot him.
>> So, what do you think is going to happen
TO HIM, KATE?
>> THAT faith though was an idea. Who sets
fire to a door like of a court?
>> Like, what is going on?
Ky, who do who what do you think is
going to happen to Monty? Do you reckon
he'll go to prison?
>> To be honest, I don't care where he goes.
>> Well, even if he does go to prison, he
won't do long anyway. [ __ ] hell, I
think. M got [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Well, six months with [ __ ] now, is it?
>> What do you do? What do you get six months for?
>> Right. You got a year, but you under
half sentence, don't you?
>> Yeah, you do. Yeah. Yeah. It's still
[ __ ] though. It's still [ __ ] any month.
I know for writing is mental, but
they've clamped down on it, haven't
they? Like a lot of people have been
arrested and [ __ ] banged up over them, right?
>> I've been to prison.
>> You haven't, Peter.
>> I have [laughter] been to
>> You'd have been locked up, Peter, in the
custody suite. You want to have been
inside a proper
>> I've actually been to proper prison.
>> Well, PJ, have you ever been nicked and
in a police?
>> Yes, about 20 times over this website.
That is not class as going to jail. Jail
is a bit different. You know, you're
>> not been in proper jail. I've been in
>> What's happened with Peter? He's been
locked up, I think, and then he's been
let out the next day.
>> No. Have you you've been licked in it,
Kayie? It's not nice.
>> No, twice.
>> It's hor How long was you in the cell
for? 24 hours.
>> Well, put it this way. They kept me in
longer than I should have cuz I was
kicking off. [laughter]
You're banging on the dark early.
>> Yeah, I was like I was like I'm not
paying my council tax. You could get [ __ ] [laughter]
>> It is quite funny to be fair. [gasps]
>> I still [snorts and clears throat] [ __ ] the
I don't I don't I don't I done eight
months in prison when I was younger. [laughter] [snorts]
>> Yeah. And he was like, "Come, if you
want to act like a child, we'll treat
you like one. We'll keep you in longer."
And I was like, "Oh, great.
>> He doesn't understand. Greavves lad."
>> I do understand. I do understand.
>> Yeah, man.
>> So, yeah. Um,
>> by court. Have you ever had that? Yeah.
He's full of [ __ ] crazy whatever
your name is. [laughter]
But that is mad windows. That is mad
windows getting done in over YouTube. [ __ ] that.
>> Yeah, but you and Jamie egg have a
poster sent around your area. That's
[ __ ] mad as well.
>> Yeah, he had it before me. That's a mad
thing. He He had all this [ __ ] before me.
>> Do you know what it is? You laugh about
that, Peter, right? But you know like someone
>> I don't laugh about it. I don't No,
listen. Listen. I don't laugh about the
posters. Do you know why? Because you
can walk out that door and carry a
[ __ ] knife through you.
>> Course you could posters going about
that [ __ ] there's some people who
aren't right in there. They'll [ __ ]
stab you in that know stuff like that.
Like it doesn't go down to where [ __ ]
nonsome at you know.
>> You know [ __ ] mad [laughter]
>> you know Gre house listen you know the
old house you know the old house that I
was in the Albert Square right? you
know, you know, when the windows got
done in and stuff, they shouldn't really
um be able to re um refurb that house
and and sell it. You know why? Triple
>> go on
>> because new people that go in that
house, they could easily walk out and
they get hit, you know, because of the YouTube thing.
>> Yeah, I agree what you're saying. Cuz
people on your still might think you
live there, so they could Yeah. Could
it's not fair. I agree, lad.
>> Yeah. Yeah. They get hiding in it. Yeah.
stalking me. Him and his cousin was
stalking me for a long time, bro.
>> Taylor Jun, your house over. He called
that bike, didn't he? [laughter]
>> You ran out the back door.
>> It wasn't my bike. Yeah, but that wasn't
my bike though. It was a tenant's bike.
>> That Taylor was like, Peter, was he?
>> And I looked out the door one day and I
see some black guy standing waiting for
me. I swear down through the spy hole.
>> Was he looking through the hall?
>> Yeah. Yeah. And I see some black guy
just stood still. Grezy waiting.
>> What a
>> Yeah. I swear to God, Grezy, that
weren't YouTube, was it?
>> It was YouTube. Yeah. [laughter]
>> It's funny, isn't it? I really like KK,
you know. Do you ship us
ship us triple?
>> Say that again, lad. She She said Katie
said she doesn't love anyone. She did.
She just said that. So I think she likes me.
>> PJ Sh.
>> No, I think maybe. [laughter] >> Yeah.
>> But if she liked you, she'd went to your
barbecue, lad. Wouldn't she? >> Yes.
>> Triple H. She said it with one. There you are.
>> Not necessarily because you might not
want to get the backlash from YouTube.
>> Yeah. You would have videoed that as
well, wouldn't you? [laughter]
>> I'm barbecue.
>> You know what? I swear people think that
you lot to me is a catalog on here. I swear >> what
>> I swear you lot think that like you lot
have a catalog from me. Like choosing
who to go out with on here. I swear.
>> No. I've always liked you.
>> PG. [ __ ] off. >> [laughter]
>> He did used to talk about you a lot on
that PlayStation days.
>> Lonely on PlayStation. I didn't even
really know him. I met him.
>> No, but Monty man was on with us, wasn't he? >> Yeah.
>> Hang on a minute.
>> Do you like Hey, do you like Tim Eldridge?
>> Am I missing something? She was on
PlayStation with them. >> Yeah. >> Huh?
>> That's lost me. That's who was in my
chat with them the other day. [laughter]
>> What the [ __ ]
>> I'm not on PlayStation now. Was [ __ ]
going back about
>> W thinks it's funny.
>> I was going back about going back years
ago now. But there was still on that
PlayStation. I didn't end up going back
on the PlayStation. I just come come off
the PlayStation. But there continued
continued on for years. But I used to go
on now and again. Used to join parties.
There was me used to be me, Monty man.
Mr. G's [laughter]
going to be in
>> I don't know
the dog house you watching video the other day.
>> That's not him.
>> It is asking.
>> No, it's not.
>> Ask him.
>> That's not him. That's a different voice.
>> What? [laughter]
>> He used to be in a chat showing anyone.
>> You know what that means in the dog house.
>> Triple chat's not his real name. You
just have a different name. Ask him
>> what's rising.
>> He says that's not your name. You've
been on here for years and you're just
under a different name or something.
>> I haven't been on here. I've been on
here for [ __ ] four, five. Yeah. No, a
bit longer than that actually. But now
I've always been under this account, mate.
>> I've never heard this guy's voice before
him. Have you had a different info, Triple H?
>> No, I haven't lad. No, I've only ever
got this account, mate.
>> Loads of people have got them troll
accounts now. I've only ever had this
one account, mate. >> Hello,
Triple H. It's always going to be the
same day. You know this.
>> Say that again, lad.
>> It's always going to be the same one
here. You know this,
>> Pedro. When are you going to grow up and
get off here yourself?
>> When we get when we get married.
>> Get out in there. Grecy.
>> Don't think so.
>> That's not nice.
>> I'm not getting married. I'm not
>> You could be my You could be my new man.
>> I'm not getting married, folks. Stop me. [ __ ] that.
>> And you're going to marry Rise?
>> I'm not. I'm not.
I'm not marrying anyone. I'm sorry, but I'm not.
Marriage only lasts what? What? What is
the new marriage rate now? That last
>> Why are you saying Why are you saying
Why are you saying you don't love anyone though?
>> I just don't want to get married. We
don't not want to get married.
>> Do you love Rise?
>> Yeah, I do love him. Yes. But I don't
want to get married.
>> What? What? Rice wants to marry you. I
have to marry his [ __ ] cuz I ain't getting married.
>> That's not found right then, is it?
>> Well, he's got a ring. He's just going
to shove his finger into his bum. He
>> probably if you pick Rice over me.
>> Did you ring Did you ring McDonald's
about your socks, Peter? No, I can't be bothered.
>> You chase ugliest men on here. You could
have been PJ's car for a few quid. Very funny, L.
>> You could have You could have been my
car and you could have been my mama.
>> No, thank you. I'd rather die. [laughter]
>> I bet you have to look after me.
>> You have to look after me. Kaye,
>> what do you think of that? Sean, Jonathan, Kurley
doesn't like him. Donnie >> who?
>> John Longlegs. [clears throat]
>> I don't like him. He's a weirdo. He's a
creep. He looks like a nons to be fair.
>> Yeah, but these people like him.
>> Hey, he looks like a creep.
>> Yeah, if you if you live with me, um K,
I'll give you 20 a week. [laughter]
>> Why you Why you laughing? even give you
50p. So [ __ ] off.
>> So say say for example we was dating and
I went to clubs and I done approaches.
What would you do?
>> I do not fancy you. Get it in your head.
>> No, I think you do.
>> Oh my god.
>> Nah, she does triple. She just put it on
her face cuz of rice, you know.
>> No, I'm telling you straight. % 100 fucking%, bro. >> True.
>> I'm not fancy you.
>> Bro, how can you fancy someone like Rice?
>> That doesn't make any sense.
>> That doesn't make sense.
>> When have I ever
>> streams? When have I actually
>> you said when have I ever really come
live streams? Oh, the whole time I've
been doing my own channel. Not really.
Never have done because I have no reason
to really chat to you cuz I don't fancy
you. Don't you think if I was streaming
for a whole year, I would have been on
your panel constantly flirting with you? Duh.
>> Well, no, you can't do that on YouTube.
People in it.
>> Two seconds, lad. Hey, read egg meal's comment. >> Wow.
>> You know what? Egg is probably [ __ ]
fried egg on that account.
>> What did you think about Pat Mustard, Kelly?
>> Pat Mustard. He's a [ __ ] weirdo nons
who [ __ ] started all this [ __ ] Actually, [laughter]
>> he's a queer blog, wasn't he? PJ PJ was
getting bullied by Pat Mustard and Timmy
Eldridge and then he brought [ __ ] on
and then they went to him. [laughter] >> Yeah,
>> that's bad.
>> DJ called the Monty man for backup and
then all this all this happened to Monty
man then. [laughter]
>> And you know what PJ did? He [ __ ] off
because all the heat left him. That's
what he did. [laughter]
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> It doesn't surprise me that way.
Yeah. [laughter] And then that's when
Monty met the coach station and had a fight.
>> But what I don't understand is seven
years later it's still going on before.
>> I agree what you're saying. Yeah. Like
>> I got a new friends with him now cuz he
was on your panel.
>> What would you So what would you do?
Yeah. If a black guy come and dug your
mom's windows in, would you would you go
out with a weapon?
>> Oh god.
>> Well, obviously I wouldn't go with a
weapon. I'd go out though. Yeah. [ __ ]
gosh. Well, obviously it's normal thing to do.
>> You killed just killed someone, did it?
>> Well, not really. That shouldn't be
happening over YouTube, blood, but
>> I don't know why you were sp looking
through that key, man. That guy came to
your mom's door. I don't know why you went straight
>> Taylor cuz it was London Taylor.
>> [ __ ] hell. It doesn't matter who it is.
>> Yeah, he was st Yeah, it was stalking
me, bro. They they they broke the
windows and come in the house and that.
>> You [ __ ] on here like Peter, haven't
you? So, so now then, PJ,
>> would you say dribble?
>> He'd have had some [ __ ] on me over the years, lad.
>> Yeah. And if I was in that day, I could
have been. He said he was going to kill
me now, too.
>> Did he actually?
>> You reckon he would have? He said he
went in the room and that
>> I don't know. He [ __ ] I don't even know Lel
seen him out, mate.
>> Yeah. Someone done your parents house.
You'd have to do something triple. You
have to, would it?
>> Obviously. You never though. [laughter]
Yeah, but you might have the back door.
>> Yeah, but you might have a triple. You
might have not done anything. [laughter]
>> Oh, it sounds about right, doesn't it,
PJ? When the heat gets rusty, you run away.
>> Yeah, when things get a bit heated, Peter's gone.
>> Yeah, but look at Rice. Your windows got
done in, Kayie, and Rice didn't do nothing.
>> J only had one exit and the door was
being broken into, you know. >> [laughter]
>> Yeah, but Trip R, what would have you
done if it was three black guys with a
weapon? What What could you do in it?
>> We didn't have exit back door. You >> reckon spy all?
>> No, but listen, Triple, do you reckon
the neighbors heard it when the windows went in? >> Obviously, [laughter]
that was all over YouTube. Triple
>> and you're still on. Like so they were
all sleeping and then bam the windows went [laughter]
>> I don't know why you find it funny man
your mom's house Peter
do you find it funny [laughter]
somebody who's had traumatic experience
you laugh at it and it's it's just mad it's madness
>> I've I've had a few close calls on this
website I could have died a few times
>> so why do you laugh at it then
>> cuz you're not frightened to death
>> [ __ ] me
He's a dangerous
>> He's a dangerous camp.
>> No, [laughter] no, but Katie, it's when
I was watching your video and the window
went in. I thought, why is someone
breaking your window?
>> No, PJ, you need to go and get sectioned
because this is serious [ __ ] It's
nothing to laugh about.
>> You said someone tried to break the door. [laughter]
>> You know why I'm laughing to break? Cuz
it's the same [laughter] website you can
watch Scooby-Doo on. the same website
you can watch Stitch on.
>> Can you just be quiet for a minute?
Yeah. I'm going to explain something to
you. Yeah. Listen to me for once. When
you sit there and tell this stream,
"What would you do when there's people
broken in your house? You would do this
and you would do that. [laughter]
>> What do you mean?"
>> Let me tell you, when four people
on your door, what are you going to do? [laughter]
You know, Jay, you are a [ __ ] mate.
All right, Triple H. Do you remember
when L come and he was shouting? Do you
reckon the neighbors heard that?
>> Obviously, but you you should have went
out first L.
>> Yeah, but okay. What about what about
the the Timmy one and the tiger? No one
saw that. I don't think
>> I saw that. I watched on Vinnie's
videos. Yeah, when you
>> neighbor saw it. The neighbors never heard it.
>> All the neighbors have seen it. Yes.
>> Was in broad daylight. [laughter]
>> Come on then. That's what I said. Come
when you can. Jimmy was dev.
>> I really like
>> I can't believe Katie don't like me but
she gets with that [ __ ] s of [ __ ] sloth.
>> K has left.
>> Yeah. I can't believe she gets with him
and not me.
>> I thought she was going to give me my vitamins. >> [laughter]
>> What do you think about that tiger not
giving me my vitamins?
>> Oh gosh.
>> Grezy, it was lush lad. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Do you think that's funny? Katie's
windows went over YouTube now.
>> Well, I don't understand. Gravy is all
the [ __ ] Peter's had on this YouTube and
he still won't get off her.
>> What about
>> she's had a bit of [ __ ] Yeah, I imagine
>> you should laugh at my mom's windows
getting done in. You shouldn't laugh at that.
>> It's not. I know you agree with that.
It's not funny. No, but you
you shouldn't have allowed that happen.
>> I was I was in the police when it
happened that day. The first time it
happened, I was.
>> What? When? What? When they done that?
>> Yeah. My mom was sitting down and she was scared.
>> Not funny.
>> You shouldn't be doing that. Your mom's mom's operator.
>> She was sat down chilling watching TV on
the phone. And bam, the windows are [ __ ] going. [laughter]
>> Right. Well, I'm going to jump off that.
I'll pop in the chat and that.
>> All right then. Not a problem.
>> Yeah. See you later.
>> I like KK Grezy.
KK don't like me.
Why doesn't K like me?
I thought she could be my new mama.
for the winter.
I thought she could be my mama.
Would you like to see that? Me and Kay together, Grezy.
What do you think? Me and Kay doing like
videos and stuff. Would you like that?
>> Oh gosh. Oh, lovely.
Would have you like that? Oh gosh. Oh.
Oh, would you like it though? Greavvesy.
That's my mama.
She's my mama.
You're giving me vitamins, isn't it?
That's my mama.
>> What do you think of that, Grezy?
I think KK likes Peter belly deep down. Oh gosh.
I'm in my little nesticles now.
Oh gosh. Oh gosh.
I can't believe I didn't get the socks.
Why didn't I get my little socks?
I wanted to go out approaching with a little socks.
Oh gosh. I going to make a little
complaint. Hold on a minute.
Let me make a little complaint.
Oh, my socks.
I can't believe KK doesn't like me, but
she likes him.
One second, bro. Um
orders. One sec.
I ordered McDonald's twice. I ordered it
early morning hours in the morning today
and then today [snorts]
all the help
I'm going to say
going to say arrive cold.
I get some money back
cuz it doesn't let me pick the other
one. I wanted my little socks.
If approved, it can take up to 10 days.
Delivery credit. If approved, credit
will be added to your account within a
few minutes. If approved, okay, we'll
get the delivery credit.
This credit will be
okay. Delivery credit,
right? So, how much credit have we got? Oh gosh.
Oh gosh. How much credit have we got?
Says we've got credit, but it doesn't.
I'm going to try and get the socks tomorrow.
I wanted to approach in the socks.
If me and Kayie done a video and Monty
wouldn't see it, would he Grezy?
I can't believe Kaye [ __ ] has got
with him Rice but not me.
That's [ __ ] stupid.
She said that she doesn't love anyone. Greavvesy,
maybe I could write a little poem. Grievesy,
Do you like my little poems, Grezy? You
like the one that I wrote to USA? Is he
the little poem?
That was so cute.
You remember Greasy the little poems? Oh gosh.
You used to like the little poems, didn't you?
Oh, Joe F is in Newcastle.
Oh, I just went on his channel. He's in
Newcastle. Is he
like out of Newcastle? Sod London.
Get to Newcastle.
All right. I think this guy here is
definitely trolling, bro.
I think this Jo is definitely trolling, bro.
Why would you say sod London? London's
better than Newcastle. Not in terms of
the people. Obviously, the people stuck
up in London, but London's way better,
bro. When I went to Newcastle, when I
was approaching in the mall, it was
nowhere near as as as as good as London.
But in terms of the people, yeah,
Newcastle's better. But in terms of the [ __ ]
No. London's got so many different
restaurants. So many There's so much to
do in London. What do you think, Greezy?
London or Newcastle?
If you was forgetting about the women.
Nah, London, bro.
What do you think?
Yeah, I like that. How hard can it be,
bro? He's a cool guy. I'm seeing some of
his comments. He never hates or anything.
I might message him and say, "How is he
doing and that, but I don't think he
ever wants to talk to me again because
of that Sarah thing.
Yeah, I remember that was bad, bro.
That [ __ ] ended life. Dude, dude.
I won't be live tomorrow. Uh, Grezy,
okay with you, Captain.
Greavvesy okay with you captain. What's
Okay, one second.
cross the crazy woman again. Uh
Greavves uh Greavvesy
where she's defending a woman again. I
showed her the one that I showed my dick
to and she's like, "Oh, she's 100%
right." I said, "She's absolutely not
100% right. She's a dickhead." and she's
acting like a [ __ ]
She's a [ __ ] just like a lot of
these women. Um, so she's she's like
shouting and raising her voice.
Typical feminist, isn't it, Greasy?
No, she definitely definitely isn't
right. She's a [ __ ]
She's a proper [ __ ]
She's talking about kids being raped.
What's kids being raped got to do with
me saying that someone's being rude for ignoring?
What What has that got to do with people [snorts]
[ __ ] ignoring a message? What what
what is that? Is a mad thing to say,
Grezy? Who comes out with that? Oh,
well, you're mad when you're mad that
you're getting ignored, but there's kids
out there getting raped. What the [ __ ]
bro? How does that even even come to
that? What the [ __ ] bro? Like, who even
comes out with that?
She's She's shouting at me, bro. She's
another one that can't admit when women
are in the wrong and they're being
[ __ ] She's another one.
She's Do you want to listen to the voice note?
Another one again. Oh my god. Another one.
doesn't like when women are wrong. Oh, Jesus Christ.
She's trying to be a victim. Really?
She's trying to be a victim again.
Has to be the victim. She says, "I make
people feel [ __ ] about themsel."
What the [ __ ] I didn't say anything to
her. All I said to this other one is,
"Stop being a [ __ ] and ignoring. How
am I trying to make people What the [ __ ] bro?
You've got serious serious issues.
Talking about kids being raped. What the [ __ ] bro?
I think she's got a victim mentality.
She says, "My energy is toxic." No, no,
that's women. No, no, no, no, no. That's
That's definitely definitely definitely
women. No, that's definitely definitely
women. No, no energy of mine is toxic.
What have I said? What the truth about
what women do? How does that how is that toxic?
How how the [ __ ] is that toxic? What the
She just doesn't like women being shown being [ __ ]
That's That's what it is. They just
don't like it when they're in the wrong.
It's the truth, isn't it?
Yeah, believe you. Listen to what I'm
saying. She's being a [ __ ] again.
She's not She's not She's not [ __ ]
right. She's being a [ __ ] Like the
one that replied back when I showed her
my dick. She is being a [ __ ] which
is what I showed her. That is being a
[ __ ] I'll give you an example,
right? Uh I said to someone today,
right, you're not going to come to
London to see me. That's lazy. As a
joke, you know, like a bit of banter
greasy. She said, "It's not lazy. That's
practical. That's being a dickhead."
Would you not agree? Yes. They're
[ __ ] vibes. Yeah. It's dickheadness.
Stop being a [ __ ] Stop writing and
stop acting like a [ __ ] You know,
it's it's the truth, bro. It's I'm not
making this stuff up. [ __ ] off, man.
What? What? Do you not agree with what
I'm saying? Crazy.
She says that I'm disgusted. I haven't
even said anything. Right.
You women are the ones that are toxic.
You are the ones that are toxic.
No. No. They're definitely the ones that are toxic. What?
Okay. One second. One second. One
second. Shut up. Yeah. You're the You
are the ones that choose to go for these
abusive men. She's a [ __ ] idiot.
She's a [ __ ] idiot, Grimsy.
She is a [ __ ] idiot, bro.
Apparently, I abuse women apparently.
Apparently, I'm just listening to this.
Apparently, I abuse women because I show
when they when they do bad things. Okay. Okay. Whatever.
She's shouting. She's triggered. She's [ __ ] triggered.
It's mad, isn't it? Bezy, why? What did
I say to Triple H? Um, go for a drink
with Ant and Deck.
Go for a drink with Ant and Deck in it. [clears throat] Oh
yeah. So I got like £1,200 left now.
Greavesy. Am I going to starve?
Am I going to What am I going to do with
£1,200, bro? To last me 3 weeks?
What if I starve, Grezy? What if I starve?
Will I starve, do you think?
I've got £1,200 to last me 3 weeks. I've
got all my bills paid. What am I going
to do, bro? What if I starve?
Can you lend me a fiverr?
Can you lend me a fiverr, please? Cuz
I'm living I'm living under poverty.
You sure I'm not going to starve? You
sure about that? Cuz Joseph Farra said
that I'll starve. He says I'm living under poverty.
Yeah, he must be talking to himself.
He must be talking about himself.
I'm going to do a video on that. Joseph
Ferries. I'm going to start a little bit of trouble.
So, do you think I'm living under
poverty, Greavesy, or no?
Do you think I'm living under poverty? Nope.
No, I don't I don't have any debt.
No. I know that.
I'm living under poverty, bro. How's
£1,200 going to last me three weeks?
[ __ ] I'm living under poverty, bro.
How's £1,200 disposable money going to
last me 3 weeks? Can someone explain?
I'm living under severe poverty, bro.
What am I going to do?
What am I really going to do, bro?
I'm going to starve.
How's £1,200 going to last me 3 weeks?
Does that sound silly to you? To you yet, we
does that sound silly to you yet?
Does that sound silly to you yet?
Does it sound silly to you yet? It
sounds [ __ ] silly to me.
I feel like I've got more money now than
when I [ __ ] had the house,
to be honest.
I think I think this Joseph Ferrar
trolling me, bro.
I don't give a [ __ ] about money, bro.
He goes He's the one that goes on about
money, bro. I don't care about money.
You have over a grand. the save in it.
Griezy, what do you think? Yeah.
Peter Belly's smart. That's how Peter
Belly's got money cuz Peter Belly's very smart,
isn't he? Greasy. Peter Bell is very
smart. Yeah. So I only bought my I only
bought my mom Ugg boots. Squeezy. That's
all I bought for. Is that all right?
Just buying Laney Ugg boots.
I think so. Yeah. How much do people
normally spend on Christmas? Two300.
is about two 300 people normally spend.
Well, I only bought the UG boots and
that's all. I haven't bought anyone else
anything. I wouldn't even if I had a lot
more money, I still wouldn't do it. Do
you know why I greasy? Cuz this year is about me me, you know.
Yeah. I'm not I I I wouldn't I wouldn't
do it even if I had it. I wouldn't do it
even if I had it because I knew what
people were like.
So no, I wouldn't I'd keep all the money
to myself. I don't give a [ __ ] about
Christmas. I swear to God, bro. I swear to God.
I could spend 600700 pound on Christmas.
I'd still have a couple hundred pound
left. It would be enough. But I wouldn't
do it. I wouldn't do it, bro. The only
person I buy for is Laney.
I'm going to be very very selfish now,
you know. Very selfish.
I don't think this I spent a lot, you
know, not not last Christmas, the
Christmas before that Greezy. Yeah. I bought my
niece this, my sister this. Like, bro, I
spent a lot of money. And I didn't
really get much thanks for it.
So, you know, when I had like the two
grand and cash from the casino and that
and I was still depressed then cuz of
the women. I was still depressed even
then when I had more money. I still still was
I was still depressed.
So with the women.
Yeah, that's good. You shouldn't buy
anyone anything. Keep your money to
yourself. Be selfish. Be a selfish little [ __ ]
What do you reckon USA would have done
if I if I bought her Ugg boots and a
spliff? Rezy, do you reckon she would
have spoke to me again?
If I bought Ugg boots and some weed.
Yeah, I think so.
What do you think?
If I bought her the Ugg boots and a load
of weed, 300 pound of weed. Yeah, definite.
So what? She would just take it and not
and not talk to you.
She's so mean. She is, Grezy. I can't
believe she done that to me. Did you not
feel sorry for me, Grezy?
Did you not feel sorry for me?
We're just talking about Christmas, lad.
And we're just talking about presents. Um,
and uh, yeah, I just bought Lady the UG
boots and I'm not buying any more presents.
Yeah, this woman was shouting voice
notes to me
and she was like, "Oh, that woman's
right. She's not being a right. She's
not being right. She's being a dickhead."
Yeah. Like the other one. Like the other
one was saying, "Oh, I said you're lazy
for not coming to London." And I said,
"You're," she said, "It's not lazy. It's practical."
[ __ ] You can You can sense the
dickheadness in them when they're talking.
But no, we're not We're talking about
Christmas. We're just talking about Christmas, bro. Yeah.
Anyways. Yeah. So
yeah, that's that. No one's getting
anything off me for Christmas.
You like that talk, Grezy?
Yeah, my money is my money. I'm saving
my little money for a rainy day.
Okay with you, boss. Captain. Captain C.
Uh because this year is about me.
This year and next year is about me. Me
me me me me me me me me me me me me me
me me me me me me me me me. No no one
wanted to know when I was almost
homeless, so I bought Laney the UGG
boots and that's that.
My money's from me me. Yeah,
I've got about 1,200 to last me 3 weeks.
So yeah, I want to start building some
of my a little fund. So that's that.
Yeah, I'm not doing a football bet tomorrow.
I'll just be chilling, bro. Yeah,
Grevy, you need to be my witness. How
long have I been doing this? Not going
out every week. Like 14 months, Grezy,
have I been doing it for like 14 months?
It's been over a year I've been like
this now, hasn't it, Reevesy?
So, you need to tell Joseph that it's
not about the [ __ ] money.
You need to get into his thick head that
I can do what I want when I [ __ ] want.
You know, it isn't about money. You need
to get in his thick head.
You need to You need to get that in his
thick [ __ ] head. And if I wanted to
make more money, I could.
I've actually got a thing where I can make money.
Yeah. And how long has this stopped for?
How long has it stopped for, bro?
So, how long has it been where I've got
where I go out like every 3 weeks or
every month? How long has it been?
You know, before I lost the house. Yeah,
Yeah. You got about a year. Yeah. I lost
the house 3 months ago.
So, what are you on about, bro? I
stopped that. I stopped it
about proper like proper proper trying to think
proper proper maybe. Yeah, about a year
and a half ago
whilst I still had the house. So what
then mate? What then?
But yeah, like two years ago I was going
out twice a week.
I used to do it twice a week sometimes.
Back when there was hope in this
country, but there is no hope. So then I
felt like there was no hope. So there
was no point me going out.
So it's not nothing to do with money, bro.
If you want to do something, you will do something.
Yeah. Do you agree with that, Greasy?
The money I have is not even bad. I
don't mind, bro. I'm happy with what I have. So,
you can't live the same lifestyle forever.
You know, as you get older, you're not
going to live the same life forever,
bro. Like, because you just grow out of it.
You think if I had loads and loads of
money, I'd still be gambling and doing
what I was doing, Grezy. No. Uh-uh. No way.
My sister, she's got tons and tons and
tons of money. Tons of money. And she
barely does anything.
I should be settled down with someone now. Greasy,
starting a family. You know,
this is a this that is a young man's
game. Going out, drinking, approaching.
It's a young man's game, bro.
Not for me, you know, anymore.
Oh, Timmy's deleted his channel.
No, Dustin. I was just saying, bro,
listen, hear me out here, cuz I know you
watch this. I've stopped going out every
week for over a year, bro. Even when I
had that house, it would be like every 3
weeks or every two weeks. I stopped this
[ __ ] Even when I had the house, when I
was doing Uber, I stopped this [ __ ] You
can ask anyone. So this Joseph tries to
make it seem like I don't go out now
because I don't get as much money, which is foolishness.
That's definitely definitely definitely
not the [ __ ] case.
What do you think I would do right now
if I won 500, bro? Save it.
I wouldn't ever
go back to that [ __ ] bro. Back to that
But I had money. Even when I lo even
when I lost the house, I still had
money. I bought a TV and [ __ ] I still
had like two I had a couple thousand. So,
no, I stopped this [ __ ] over a year ago, bro.
I've only been here like two, three months.
No, stop. I think it was. So, yeah. I
was doing Uber, getting money, and
getting the house money. I still weren't going out.
Nah, bro. No, no, no, no, no.
Nothing to do with money at all.
Nothing to do with money at all. That's
my preference, bro. I mean,
I'll never forget the last days in that
house after I was going to order an escort.
I was going to order an escort, bro. Um,
but they were asking like £300. I think
I had like two grand. And I was like,
I'm not [ __ ] paying £300 for an
escort. I was in the house by myself.
It was lush. Scary though. It was scary,
but it was lush. So, I just went up the
road to get an escort.
And I was like, "Oh man, we've had some
good times with this house." I was in
the house greavves. I was like, "Oh,
this house is lush. I had some good
times in this house. Thank you very much
for the money house."
Then um then I was going before I went to sleep,
I was like, "Oh [ __ ] hold on a minute,
Dusty. Why didn't we meet anyone?
Why are we not in a relationship?"
Cuz I just lying in bed thinking about
like the uh the um
what I basically done with the house,
you know. I was actually it was actually
depressing to be honest. And the story
actually was depressing
before I adjusted.
I was like, "Now I've got to live off
[ __ ] shitty money." But it wasn't
that bad. So
no, now it doesn't even feel like any different
cuz I used to be really skint
dusty. And I mean really skimp like not
be able to do anything. Not be able to
afford to do anything. Um
really skimp, bro. Back when Laney was
at the house. Really [ __ ] ski.
I used to do all sorts. Even when I had
less money, I'd still gamble. I'd still
go out drinking. You If you want to do
something, you will do something.
If you want something If you want to do
something that bad, you will do
something that bad.
>> [clears throat]
>> But what no matter what money you got,
you'll find ways to make money. I don't
I'm happy just chilling over the winter
and I probably do a lot of stuff in the
summer, you know.
I've done my going out days basically.
I still like to go out now and again,
just to, you know, let my hair down and stuff. Yeah, but
yeah, I stopped that [ __ ] ages ago to
going out, bro. Ages ago. I like to be
in bed now by 11. By 11:00,
what do you think of that? Be in bed by 11:00.
Okay with you, boss.
Yeah, I like to be in bed by that time,
bro. [ __ ] when I go out drinking.
No, no, no, no. Oh, we got some movies
coming up in the cinema soon. Oh gosh, I can't wait.
Oh [snorts] gosh.
So yeah, that that he doesn't know what
he's talking about that Joseph. I've
stopped doing this for over a year.
Well over a year.
Nothing to do with money at all. I can
do what I want when I want.
I got an electric toothbrush and I've
got a link set.
You reckon I could afford Christmas this
year, Grey, if I wanted to? Yeah.
Yeah. In a minute, bro. I think I've run
out of sugar, though.
I think I've run out of bastard sugar.
I could do Christmas this year if I
wanted to. Yeah.
500 maybe I could spend, but I wouldn't
spend money on no one.
It's all about me.
Me me me me me me me me me me me me me
me me me me me me me me me me me me me
me me me me me me me me me. I might You
know what? I might get the Grint socks
tomorrow and go out approaching with
them. Give her a little whirl.
What do you think of that, Grezy?
Yeah, but it's trying to [ __ ] get in
somewhere. The bastard shorts.
No, I don't want to go out, bro. I don't
want to go out.
I know you'd love the content though,
wouldn't you, Greasy?
Yeah, I just got lane the Uggs.
Why the [ __ ] did that USA Izzy have to
leave me, Grezy?
I was [ __ ] craving my vitamins um
last night. [ __ ] sake.
My daily vitamins.
Peter buddy doesn't know where to turn. Yeah,
you'll probably have to go to a [ __ ]
branch where no one [ __ ] goes to.
going to a [ __ ] McDonald ranch that
[ __ ] no one. You know what I mean?
I tried approaching people, giving them
flowers. They said I had a boyfriend. Grezy.
Yeah, they said they had a boyfriend.
I don't approach. I don't approach.
Dusty, I don't I don't do it.
If I really thought there was hope in
this country, Greavves, I'd be
approaching every day. Every other day.
Do you believe me? I would be doing it
every day. every other day.
That's how you know that there's no hope
here. If I go out cuz I'm bored
drinking, then then I might approach
because why the [ __ ] not? But I don't
make this my life or or effort into it
because I know there's no hope for me.
So, yeah, they say they got boyfriends.
They might not like me cuz I don't look fully white.
Yeah, but people on Reddit told me that
I meet someone. Every I show them
videos, Dusty, but they just dismiss it,
lad. They just dismiss it.
I'll try when I go out drinking when I
can be bothered.
And you know why I try? Because if you
go out drinking, why wouldn't you try anyways? Because
it just you if you don't try, say you go
out drinking, right? And you don't even
have a number to text the next day. It
just feels weird. It just feels out of
the routine. You can't go out [ __ ]
drinking and not even do any approaches. It's just
any I could go out and not do them
sober, but I'm not going to go drinking
and not even do one. That's just like
nah, bro. Nah. That's like Yeah,
USA. Izzy is stinking dusty. Yeah,
he's got yummy boobies though.
She's got very yummy boobies.
I like boobies.
I like boobies. Dusty
boobs. I like boobies. Haley's got big Yeah. Yep.
I latch on to new ones, don't I? Greasy. Oh god. Well,
they they do owe you something.
If you put effort in and you're
approaching women, they do owe you
something. Just like if you go to work,
you get money. If you go to the gym, you
get [ __ ] ripped. They do owe you
something. They do owe you something.
They definitely definitely definitely do.
And it doesn't matter if they do or they
don't. They're ignorant. They're
ignorant. It's not a case of people
owing people anything or not. They're
ignorant. But in theory, they do owe you something.
They definitely definitely definitely
do. It's like with anything.
You go out, you put the effort in, you
should get results. So, you are owed something.
If you put the effort in, you are owed
something. Yeah, they definitely do owe you something.
So yeah, they do owe you something.
If you put the effort in, they do owe you something.
If any any other aspect in life, if you
put effort in, you get something out of
it. Job searching, working, the gym, and
there's and that's no different with approaching women.
They do owe you something.
That's the way I see it and I don't even
try anymore. So
they seem to think men owe them something.
Isn't that right, Gregy? They seem to
think men owe them something. They seem
to walk around with an attitude.
Am I lying?
You need to use that in the right
context, bro. Don't use it to cover up
their shitty behavior
or their ignorant behavior. cuz that's
used to cover up shitty behavior.
No, they do owe you something.
Definitely. They definitely definitely do.
So, they do.
[ __ ] them, bro.
They lead people on as well.
I don't understand that one, though. I I
don't understand that one. She said,
"Drop me a message." And she didn't even
reply. I said, "Do you want to go out
tomorrow?" She said, "Oh, I'm looking
after my little girl. Sorry."
Which is Yeah. Okay. Well, they didn't
even they didn't seem very enthusiastic, but
No, they definitely do owe you something.
They definitely do owe you something. Number.
Men don't owe them anything.
Uh, so yeah,
no woman's asked me that. No. So then,
so yeah. So you're basically saying no
one owes them anything either then.
So you're basically agreeing
So then you're basically agreeing, Greasy.
By saying that, you're basically agreeing.
It doesn't matter what I can offer.
They're not owed anything.
I could have a BMW. I could be a
millionaire. They I don't owe them anything.
So why why does If you want to if you
want to use that, I can use it as well.
Then I don't owe you anything. If you
can't have me at my worst,
um, you you can't have me at my best.
That's the way I see it.
So, it's okay for them to think men owe
them something, but when a woman does a
shitty act, it's okay for them to not
owe us anything. I don't understand, you know?
I mean, it works both ways.
You don't owe a woman anything.
Same as what you're saying. So, yeah,
Dusty, that word is used to basically
cover up their shitty behavior. It's
used in the wrong context. It's like a
woman ghost you, she doesn't owe you
anything. A woman ignores you, she
doesn't owe you anything.
That's not the That's not used in the right context.
You can't say it every time they do something shitty.
I don't I've never agreed with that
saying. Never. Never agreed with that
saying because it seems like such a lame
attempt to sugarcoat everything that
they've done, you know? Oh, well, they
don't owe you anything anyways. No,
that's not how that works. It's not how Really?
So, someone agreeing to meet you and
then backing out is not giving false hope.
I don't think so, bro. I think it
definitely is false hope. Definitely
definitely is false hope. The one in
Finland gave false hope, which is why I
sent her a picture of my dick. Um, and
others, I mean, it definitely definitely
is false hope.
No, it definitely is false hope.
Just like the one in Birmingham. No, it definitely is.
Definitely definitely is.
Yes. And they led me on. Yes. Yes. And
A lot of them numbers did lead me on.
They do lead you on. Everyone can see
it. They do lead you on.
They're [ __ ] They do lead people on.
I don't know. What do you think about that, Grezy?
Do you think any of the numbers led me on?
Do you think getting a number
from approaching in a pub, a bar, or on
a street and then messaging you, they
don't owe you anything? Sorry, not that
that's not leading you on. So when
they're messaging you saying that
they're going to meet you and playing
games, that's not leading on.
I mean, they they they literally do it on purpose.
I mean, they literally do do it on purpose.
Don't know what you think, Greavesy.
Tiger says that they've led you on.
They definitely have led me on. They
definitely definitely have.
>> No, but it's not about being No, no, no,
no, no, no, no. You're not. You're
missing the point, bro. It's not about
being drunk. We're talking about text messages, right?
We're talking about text messages.
We're not talking face to face. And they
have led me on. It's like that one in
Birmingham proper led me on. They like,
"Oh, I'll have to see this. I have to
see that." They literally lead you on
just to [ __ ] you over in the end. They
do lead you on. If someone's not leading
you on, they would make their intentions
clear within the second, third or second
or third message
straight away. Cuz you're me, you're
approaching someone comp. When you
approach someone, you're complimenting
them. You're not trying to be their
friend. So if they're not saying
anything within a second or third
message and they're asking you
questions, they are leading you on.
So it's the finished one led me on. You
know, it's all games. And if they're not
leading you on, they're playing games. It's simple.
Even this 45year-old was playing games
today, using distance as an excuse. You know,
I'm going down to waxies. Dusty,
what do you think about that? Going to waxies.
You like the idea of waxies?
[ __ ] waxies, bro. Get yourself down
to waxies, lad.
Yeah, I've been to waxies. I got some
numbers in waxies.
Yeah, I've been to Waxies a few times.
People on YouTube can try to get me
banned from there, but I don't think it
would work. No, there it seems more laidback there
than that O'Neals. Yeah, I don't think
they could get you banned from there.
I don't think so. That's going to be a lot harder.
It's 8 pound a pint in there, Dusty.
They found a pine.
It's Taylor Swift's birthday today.
I wish I could get with Taylor Swift.
I'd be rich.
I'd be very rich.
I'd be a billionaire.
Oh gosh. Grezy. Oh gosh. [snorts] Yeah,
I'd be rich.
I'd probably [ __ ] her over though. You
know what I'm like, Grezy? If I ever got
with a woman, I'd probably [ __ ] one over
in the end. You know what I'm like,
ain't it, Grezy?
I used to meet these women of God about
USA. Izzy, they thought I was mad, Grezy.
It's so mad to think that like I had to
literally stop going on dates and now I
can't even get a date. Like two years
ago, Dusty, I literally had to stop
going on dates. I literally had to stop
going out and meeting people. But now
you will never meet anyone. Now you will
never meet no one.
It's a different ball game now, bro.
It's a different ball game now.
That was back then. But
yeah, man. One sec. I will. Now you
won't meet anyone. Yeah.
I haven't heard from my friend in
Manchester for ages. You remember Pete?
Do you remember Pal? I hope he's all
right. He come off social media. I don't
think I ever got his number, but
hope he's all right.
>> Hey, Kaye. >> PJ.
>> I don't want to talk to you. I want to
talk to my mama.
>> Listen, you will know. Yes. Listen. You
ever speak to KT filthy like that again,
right? I'm going to break your legs. You
dirty little wrong. Don't you dare.
>> Do Do I ever fight over Kayie? my
partner again. You wrong on me. I'm
going to bust you up. You skinny little [ __ ] weasel.
>> I'm not skinny.
>> Mommy. You filthy bastard, mate. How
dare you speak?
>> How can you call me skinny? You silly [ __ ]
>> You dirty little virgin boy.
>> How can I be a virgin? I'm sexy,
>> mate. You got the smallest dick, right?
Known to [ __ ] YouTube.
>> Known to YouTube. Oh, do you want to see
a picture of my dick?
>> Do you want Do you want to see Do you
want to see a picture of my dick? Don't
you ever speak to anybody like that
again, you filthy bastard.
>> Listen, your your windows got broken and
you done nothing. Shut up.
>> What? The way you treat women, right?
You should be
>> Bye-bye. See you later.
I don't know. Yeah. How he's arguing
with me when she she even said she
doesn't love anyone.
She literally said that she doesn't love anyone.
I think she still likes Monty.
That's what I think.
I think I know it's on