Batman. Batman. Batman.
I told you if you didn't leave me alone,
I would show my pecker.
Back in the little nest of calls now.
Safe and sound. Batman.
out. I like Batman. I prefer Superman. I
told him to stop. Oh, I was going to get
my Pekka out. I told him to stop.
I think it's quite a lovely Pekka.
Grezy, would you agree? I had to end it
in case I got banned.
It was lovely. Lovely little Pekka. Gosh.
It's bigger than yours. My dick ain't
small. My dick is lovely. Yeah,
Autumn came just at the right time. As
soon as I said about sending my show my
dick, she appeared. She appeared out of nowhere. Greavvesy.
Yeah, 100% he probably did. Yeah.
No, she wasn't. No. D.
Yeah. It wasn't even fully hard either.
It gets quite bigger. Sometimes it
doesn't fit in people's mouths.
I'm not circumcised autumn, so I have to
give it a bit more cleaning than the
average person. Otherwise, it smells
like cheese and stuff. So yeah. Ah. Oh.
Sorry, I was catching my breath. Sorry
about that, people.
3-in Becca. No, not mine.
No, not mine. Mine's lovely.
Just getting in the mood for the pool
now, you know. Jew, [snorts]
I didn't put it back until I was 19, actually, Dusty.
Yeah, I didn't put it back until I was 19.
It's only a peeka mover. Yeah.
Yeah. I didn't put it back until it was
19 because people I was showing people
my Pekka and they were like, "Why does
your skin not go back?" I said, "Is it
supposed to?" And they were like,
"Yeah." And I looked it up and it said
you have thromosis. Here's how you cure
it. You have to go in a bath and pull it
back gradually. I hope you're listening
to this. Autumn.
You have to pull it back gradually
and then after two weeks it basically Yeah,
that's my Pekka story. Greavves. Maybe
I'll do a video one day explaining Peter
Belly's Pekka story. You know how
everyone's got, you know, everyone's got
a little story, you know,
and it was really sensitive the first time.
Yeah, very sensitive.
How much do you weigh, Autumn?
Cuz you got big boobies, but you know,
it might you might be very very
overweight and stuff. So, in that case,
it won't count.
So, how much do you weigh? Gosh,
what are you doing today, Franklin? You
silly little car. Yeah, basically
I'm not circumcised. Squeezy, my my pec
is my pec is tanned. It's more tanned
than my skin. Squeezy,
what do you think of that? It's more
tanned than my skin.
But I'm definitely doing a video to that
Joseph Raw. I don't like that [ __ ]
Is that all right with you though,
Stephen Howard, if I can call that [ __ ] out,
mate? You're only going to Newcastle
cuz it's the northeast and you live in
the northeast. You could never come to
London. You're scared of London and you
wouldn't have the balls to travel that
far. You wouldn't have the balls to
travel that far, you little non-slber
firstly. So, of course you would say
Strod, he only goes to basically leads
and Newcastle cuz it's all the Northeast.
N Dusty, I don't like that Joseph Fra,
bro. That little nonslav. I'm going to
bring up his gambling um the gambling
[ __ ] as well.
He needs to stop showing wins and only
wins. He needs to show everything. You know.
Do you like my peeka? Grezy
grievy. See my little peeka.
My little potter.
No, I don't hate about I don't hate his
winning, but he's only showing wins,
bro. Do you not understand that his
whole channel is dedicated to trying to
troll me, bro? I don't think you get it.
I don't think you understand that the
whole point of the channel,
but he's doing it he's doing it undercover.
No, no, no. But you're not
understanding, bro, that he's doesn't
he's not winning as much as he's saying,
dude. I don't think you understand.
Jealous of what? I've got my own money,
bro. Jealous of what? I have my own money.
Why would I be jealous when I've got my own money?
I don't need any more money. I have
money to do what I want to do. I can go
out tomorrow and meet new people. I can
get drunk. Why would I be jealous
of of what?
I've got my own bloody money.
If I wanted to bloody gamble and try to
win, I could do it.
I'm not worried about what he bets. I'm
saying that he only shows wins. because
no one that plays their machines is constantly winning.
I'm not I'm not worried. I'm not
jealous. I'm stating facts. You know,
I'm stating facts, bro. No one can
continuously keep winning on their machines. You know,
tell us [ __ ] what? Jesus Christ. I
got my own [ __ ] money. I can do what
I want. You know what I mean?
[ __ ] Would I going to be jealous of
someone, bro? Huh?
No one's calling this [ __ ] out.
No one's [ __ ] calling this [ __ ] out
for not showing up. No, no,
but anyone Wonder why people like waste
their time on these people in here, Dusty.
But then you wonder why people don't
waste their time on these people here.
I might ban that Joe, you know, soon,
bro. I might ban him from the whole
channel. Not now or not today, but I
think eventually I will. Yeah,
we don't like lavry fans. We don't like nonslovers.
You know what I mean? All right.
So yeah, people are allowed to critique
someone dusty and not be jealous. Yo,
why would why would I be jealous of a
fat old man?
This is the same thing with you. Why Why
would someone be jealous of a fat old
man? I've got enough money to go and do
what I want. I can go out tomorrow. Why
would I be jealous of someone [ __ ]
I'm more than happy saving money, bro?
I'm working if I need to get buddy. I
don't [ __ ] need I don't need to be
jealous of anyone.
Then you're saying about how you can't
take people's words serious. Your
boyfriend ain't coming tomorrow.
Your boyfriend ain't coming tomorrow.
He's lying about how much he wins. Yes,
bro. Because people don't constantly
keep winning on them machines. It's not possible.
Yeah. Remember when I used to gamble, I
used to win and lose, win and lose,
lose, lose, win, win. Yeah. That's how
gambling goes. You don't you don't
continuously keep winning. And it's like
Triple H said shed. If you win so much,
why are you working? You wouldn't need
to work. If you if you apparently win so
much, why are you working? Because it's all [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] When was the last time
this guy said that he's lost, you know?
He doesn't he seems to never lose. I'm
saying that's not realistic. It could be
anyone that posts that. It's not realistic.
His whole channel is basically trying to
troll, bro. do not understand.
I don't think you understand, bro. Like,
you don't understand it. You might not
be smart enough to, but I know what he's
trying to do, bro.
And I caught him commenting on his
boyfriend's channel as well, nons legs,
cuz he's a nons lover.
And I call him a nons lover to his face.
So, that's that.
And I don't care. You can even bring
your money. I wouldn't even rob you. I
don't give a [ __ ] about your money. I've
got my own money. Do what I want when I
want. I don't get jealous of people.
Never have, never will. I can't. I would
never get jealous of people.
Okay. But it's not showing a realistic
side of gambling.
That's not a realistic side of gambling.
And people are allowed to say that
without being jealous.
It's like all of them people that say
about stop and step, you only show wins.
You only you're allowed an opinion
without being jealous.
People say to stop and step as well.
Yeah. Why doesn't he post any losing ones?
That's another one. I don't know how he
seems to never lose. You know,
you could win 20 grand and I still
wouldn't give a [ __ ] I'm not like these
people here. I don't get jealous of
people I don't know.
I don't get jealous of people I don't know, bro.
Doesn't happen. Doesn't happen. So yeah,
why would I be fat jealous of some fat
old man that ain't got a life?
Yeah, when that Joseph is a [ __ ]
non-leg s. Why is he commenting on his channel?
Cuz he's a non like him, bro.
Cuz he's a little n like him. Anyone
that's It's like what Kieran said. You
not trust anyone unless they've been
[ __ ] blocked by nonslegs.
The only one that's living in poverty is
him, bro. The only one that's living in
poverty is him.
He's living in more poverty than I could ever live.
[ __ ] [ __ ] That's definitely him,
bro. Definitely him.
Yeah, I gave that [ __ ] up ages ago,
Dustin. I couldn't be dealing with it anymore, bro. Yeah.
He's another little non-sl.
So you can't take me serious, but you
can take Smokey Be serious. Someone that
says he's going to go on someone's door,
but now he's not.
But you can take him serious.
Bias little nons lover.
Now nothing. We're just talking about uh
Joe only showing wins.
Yeah, Eldidge is not the only one
though, is it?
Joseph Ferrar does it as well. Bro,
we're just talking about how that Joseph
is like full of [ __ ] bro. One second.
One second, brother.
So, this guy's bottled out and he's got
away with it.
But they can't take my They can't take
my word seriously. Apparently,
this Joseph Ferrar is a fat [ __ ]
little nonsel loving [ __ ]
I want I want some entertainment, bro. I
really want some entertainment.
Tomorrow agrees with you. I want this [ __ ] Really?
Owned. Once again, pathetic.
No, the only people that get owned is you people
showing showing fake wins.
You know what he probably does, Bob? He
probably plays on [ __ ] demo mode.
That's what he probably does.
No way people can keep winning on slot
machines, bro. You couldn't even keep
winning on football.
Give it up, Joseph Ferrar. You little nonslav. You know,
£700 is nothing. Why are you talking about 700?
£700? What are you talking about, bro?
Why are you talking about £700?
I'm not hating at anyone. I don't care
who wins. I'm show I'm saying that he's
showing fake videos. Bro,
no one can win like that. It's not It's
not hating. It's being real.
I'm not hating, nor am I jealous.
I've got enough money to do what I want
to do. I'm younger than this [ __ ] I'm
not fat like this [ __ ] Why would I be
jealous of what? Why would I be [ __ ] jealous?
You don't You can't continuously win on these machines, Dusty.
He's a king of [ __ ] That's what he is.
Joseph Ferrar is definitely definitely
definitely the king of [ __ ]
He's a little nons.
He's a little He's a little nonscat.
That's what you need to make an account of, Grezy.
You need to call him Jo the nonslegs lover.
That's what you need to do a little uh account of.
Nah, he's not, mate. He's [ __ ] not.
Oh, that that's cuz you got so many accounts, Grezy. Yeah.
That Joseph F is the one that's living in poverty.
He can't even come on a [ __ ] He can't
even [clears throat] come on a hangout and talk. Jesus Christ.
I fancy another Coca-Cola Greavesy, but
I don't have one.
She don't want to know.
She don't want to know you.
Yeah, that's never going to happen.
But yeah, this Joseph Ferrar is a bullshitter.
put money on my head and
I showed my Pekka.
USA is he seen my Pekka.
Is that cute? Greasy. USA. Is he seen my Pekka?
We've seen each other's private parts.
What do you think of that, Gregy?
What do you think of that, Grezy? We've
seen each other's
um private parts. Yes, he did miss it. I
got my Pekka out. Triple H, you missed it.
I got my pecker out. Autumn come just in time.
Seeing each other's private parts.
What do you think of that, Greavvesy?
If you meet someone once and you and you
see each other's private parts, do you
think that's disgusting?
Do you think that's vile the first time
you meet someone or do you think it's lovely?
I said I I showed my dick on camera,
Triple, before you rejoined.
Yeah, I got my dick out.
It was lovely.
I had to give it some air. Oh gosh. [snorts]
I don't know. I thought it was fun to break.
I don't know. I just thought it would
have been lovely to get it out.
Autumn saw it. I think she liked it.
Ruby, what do you think? Do you reckon
she liked it? Yep.
My little Pekka.
Do you reckon autumn likes my Pekka?
I don't I don't care if it's
unsolicited. I get my Pekka out whenever I want.
I'll do it whenever I want. Greavvesy,
get my pecker out. I do what I want.
Is that all right with you, Grezy? Yep.
No, I know it doesn't.
Yeah, my Pekka is uh it's darker.
I know. I don't know why my Pekka is like that. Yeah.
Did you like it, Grezy?
Yeah. My I don't know why my PKA. Oh gosh.
I need to wash my Pekka. Boozy. >> [laughter]
>> Oh gosh.
Oh gosh. Triple. I just wanted to show
Kaye and Al my Becca, you know.
No, it was quite brown. Oh gosh.
I wrote USA is a poem, Dusty, and she
just blocked me.
She just blocked me. Dusty.
She didn't care.
She left me.
Abused me. Dusty.
Yeah, I don't care.
Yeah, I don't really care.
No, it wasn't. It was to my mama.
I don't really care.
Yeah, probably that red star loser. Is it?
Yeah, probably the Yeah, probably that loser. Red Star. Dusty.
Red Star's got absolutely no life
outside of YouTube, does he?
Dusty. Red Star's got absolutely no life
outside of YouTube, does he? No,
Red Star's got absolutely no life
outside of YouTube, Dusty.
Let me see if he's still stalking me. No.
No. football back tomorrow.
Do these people not get bored, bro?
Oh, this lad and
she got that good.
There's no good national leagues playing, lad.
[ __ ] man. There's no good [ __ ] team playing, bro. No.
What would you do if you had a daughter
that had one night stands, Griezy? Would
you would you disown your daughter if
she had one night stands
on hookups or what?
Say you had a daughter. What would your
What would your opinion be?
What was your opinion on that be
Greavves? Uh yeah, Grey. [gasps] [snorts]
Yeah, there's no good teams playing
tomorrow anyways. There's no National
League. There's only two. There's only one.
There's like four games in the National League, bro.
Yeah, there's like four games in the National League.
Yeah, women are evil though. Id Ray Penny.
Why? Cuz I was talking to
Cuz I was talking to Reddit.
Talking to Triple H. Sorry,
Adre Penny. Women are evil though.
Women are evil [ __ ]
Yeah. Who is that guy stalking me?
Thoughts off Peter F. Evil Mike.
Do you reckon I should quit Reddit? Uh, Dusty,
these the women are not innocent, Dusty.
Women are not innocent.
Shush. Women are not innocent. No woman is innocent.
Children are innocent. Babies are
innocent. Women that are leading people
on and [ __ ] people over aren't innocent. [ __ ] off.
They are [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] not innocent, bro.
Did you see them numbers that led me on Penny One?
They leave people on and [ __ ] have bad attitude.
Yeah. Treat women like queens. You get
[ __ ] mate. I'm not a white knight.
This 45year-old was being a [ __ ] earlier
on um Instagram. Idra Penny.
She was being a [ __ ] She was trying to
say, "Oh, I can't get with you cuz the
distance." She only lives in wheelchair.
I said that. I said, "Oh, yeah." And
then what would the next excuse be?
They're full of excuses, these women, lad.
She was 45 and trying to use distance as an excuse.
Yeah, I know. It's bad, isn't it? You
got 45 year olds acting like that. I
know. It's mad.
And then when I told her like, "Oh, I
know you're using excuses." She just blocked me.
Yep. I know, bro. I know. I know all
about what these women do in Ray. I know
all about what they do, lad. You don't
need to tell me.
You don't need to tell me, lad. I know
all about what they do. I've been doing
it for years.
Cuz think about it, bro. Think about it.
I thought to myself, yeah, this was
yesterday, which was Friday. Yeah. This
was yesterday, which was Friday. And I thought, okay,
so she's trying to say it's the distance, right?
And I said to her, if I was your next door neighbor,
you would say that I'm too young for
you. So I said, "Listen, if I was your
next door neighbor, you'd still make an excuse."
I told her that in the most polite way
and then she blocked me cuz it's the truth.
It's the age gap. Yeah. Like, bro, think
about it. I could I said yesterday I
could go out today and try to meet
someone and they're going to come out
with another excuse.
They're going to talk they're going to
come out with another excuse.
Definitely definitely not definitely not
coming across too needy.
Like I said, I've put messages out
there. If you don't uh if you don't want
to read them, you don't want to
acknowledge them, that's that's your problem, bro.
Nope, I'm not showing messages.
I don't need to show messages. When I've
shown messages before, you just missed it. So,
I said, "We can go out of Bristol one
day," she said, "But that doesn't change
the fact you live in in London and I
live here." And then when I basically
told her that I know she's full of [ __ ]
she blocked me.
One second. Hold on.
Sorry about that. Yeah, they would say
the age gap.
If you if you only went for older women in London,
they will sit there and say age gap. Age
gap, age gap. Even if they were like 33.
Yeah. If they're in London
and if they live in like Leicester or
something, they'll say, "Oh, it's the
distance." They're [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
Yeah. They're [ __ ]
They're proper [ __ ] lad.
It's always an excuse. Yeah.
Yeah. What's wrong with that? Don't
these women claim that they've got
boyfriends in different countries? Idray.
Yeah. Okay. And if I went out
approaching in London, they would use
age as an excuse. So what's the difference?
So what, bro?
Nothing wrong with having a girlfriend two hours.
Doesn't doesn't matter about having a
girlfriend two hours away. You can see
each other every two weeks. You could
move in together.
I'm sure there's people that date people
that live hours away.
No, it's not too far. No, it's not too
No, it's not too far. Plenty of women
say that they're dating people. There's
women that study abroad, right, that say
they've got a boyfriend,
that live back in their country. So,
which one is it, bro?
Which one is it? You need to make up your mind.
It's not too far, bro.
It's not too far.
They'd say another excuse if they lived in London.
Okay. Okay. Okay. So, what if I went out
yesterday and I approached older women
in London? What would the excuse be
then? The age gap.
They even they would or that you're not
Muslim. I had one. Do you remember that
one Greavves? Right. Do you remember
that one? You remember that one before
Greavvesy, right? That I spent a few hours with
and I was like, "Oh, yeah. We This is a
good date." And she's like, "Oh, I can't
date you cuz you're Muslim." Cuz I'm not
Muslim. Then I saw her again. I'm not
Nah, 2 hours is not too far. Women date
people that live further than that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. Listen, listen, listen to me, bro.
She said she wouldn't date me cuz I'm Muslim.
Because I'm not Muslim. And I said,
"Okay, well, let me I'll convert to
Muslim." Oh, I'm not looking for anyone.
So they always make excuses
cuz they're narcissists.
That's that. Yeah. They will always talk
[ __ ] They talk [ __ ] Even the ones
that live here.
So if it's too far, why is there women
that are studying abroad that's saying
they've got a boyfriend in a different
country then? If that's too far then,
why have you got these women saying that
they've got a boyfriend halfway across
the world then? if it's too far
because they talk [ __ ]
I don't I don't think, bro.
I don't think I don't think that if they
lived in London, they would get me with
me somehow. Idra. Okay. Okay. Listen.
Okay. 2 hours. 2 hours, right? 2 hours
is Okay. 2 hours is far. Yeah. Idray.
Okay. Whatever. Let's just say that
they're genuine and it is too far. I
can't see them getting with me if I live
there. Somehow I can't.
Somehow I can't see me getting with them
if they live there or they live here. I
can't see it happening. Um,
I can't see how
because IDRA, what I was thinking is
that if I went out London yesterday,
they'd have another excuse,
Idray, they would have another excuse
not to get with you.
No, I wasn't going to. It was a test.
No, no, I No, I didn't want to. I was
using it as a test to see what she would say.
just to see what she would say.
But yeah, it would have been the age gap
thing. They're so full of [ __ ]
They are so full of [ __ ]
They're so so so full of [ __ ]
Yeah. And if she lived in London, she'd
use age as an excuse. So, it doesn't
really matter, does it? They're full of
[ __ ] bro. I had one on Reddit say, "Oh,
I won't get with you cuz you're 28 and
I'm 23 and I don't get with anyone
that's not a Muslim." Went on her post
call out, saw that actually got with a
28-year-old before that wasn't a Muslim.
Then she started calling me a [ __ ]
stalker. They're liars. They're bullshitters.
Everything they say is [ __ ] bro. Toxic [ __ ] So yeah,
but it doesn't matter because even if
she lived here, she'd use another excuse. So
she would use another excuse anyways.
Even if she lived there or she would
just lead you or ghost you um lead you
on or ghost you.
No, you don't need a vehicle. There's
trains. Trains take you can get to her
very fast on a train.
Trains are there for a reason. I can get
to Manchester in no time.
I could literally get to Manchester in no time.
Just like I get to wheelchair in no time.
Trains are very fast. You can get
anywhere quite fast.
So yeah, it's always an excuse. It's
You're not Muslim. You're too old for
me. You're too young for me. It's always an excuse.
I don't think you're suddenly going to
start getting women if you got a car. I
don't believe it. Cuz people told me
when if you live by yourself and you
work and you go to the gym, you'll meet
someone. I done all of them things and I
still never met anyone. I went to a gym.
I worked. I lived I had my own gaff.
Never made a difference. Never made a
blind bit of difference.
Nope. Never made a blind bit of difference.
I don't think a woman's ever asked me if I've drove.
Never ever come up in conversation.
But yeah, they'll always um
they'd always come up with some excuse.
The Muslim one is the funniest.
It doesn't matter. I still had a job.
It's not about It's not meeting people.
No, no, no, no. I was still working. I
was still working, living by myself. So, yeah. Yeah.
So, every time a woman says, "Oh, you're
too old. You're too young for me." This,
I just automatically think they're all
liars now. Any woman, anything a woman
says to me now, I just think they're lying.
Yeah, they're just liars.
Now to think of it now, every time I
come across a woman, I just think, "Oh,
they're lying. They're liars." Uh, Ed Ray. Yeah.
The proper liars, lad.
Not like them. No. Not like them.
No, I don't lie.
Nope. I'm not giving any of them the
benefit of the doubt. They're all lies
and they're all bad.
They are all bad. All right. Do you know
the I I met one last week in Ray. Yeah.
I approached her last week and she's
like, "Oh yeah, drop me a message." I
messaged her. She didn't even reply. And
I always do that thing where I'll
message them one more time a week later
or two weeks later. I messaged her. I
found out she's a single mom, by the
way. I said, "Oh, do you want to go out
tomorrow for drinks?" She said, "Oh, I
can't come out tomorrow. Sorry. I'm
looking after my little girl.
That's it. No trying to reschedu, no
enthusiasm, no nothing.
I should have to I should have had to
message someone twice for them to respond.
So that's that's another thing.
And I would message them one more time
and if they don't reply, then they don't
reply. It works sometimes.
Sometimes it was worked in the past
though. Then that's it. Done. Delete the number.
You know, but these women definitely definitely lie.
You're not Muslim. It's sick. They use
their religion as an excuse. That's quite sick.
That is quite sick. Then when you're
like, "Oh, I'll convert to Muslim." Oh,
it's another excuse.
So toxic being in the dating game it so
toxic. So so so toxic.
So toxic, bro.
The dating scene is toxic. Yeah,
very toxic, lad. But no, women are all
bad. They are definitely all bad. They
are all bad. They're all shallow.
They're all full of [ __ ]
So yeah, I've not heard that one for a
long time though. Using distance as an excuse.
I ain't know he know that one for ages.
Nope. I'm not going out this week and
I'm not going out next week.
I've tried Tinder. It don't work.
I've tried Hinge. It doesn't work.
Believe it or not, I know the internet
says this, but you can't just go on
dating apps and get sex. I found out the
hard way. They're they're liars on Reddit.
Yeah, I've used Tinder. It doesn't work.
And I've used Hinge. Doesn't work.
Yeah, I've used that. It doesn't work.
Hopefully, it works for you, lad.
might be the way I come across
any of the
any um opinion on the women leading me on Dusty.
Just completely dismiss that. What about
the ones that I approached from the
street and they said straight away
they're not interested.
Just dismiss that one. Just dismiss it.
It's probably easier just to dismiss
these things to be fair.
another struggle dismisser. And that's
another thing is that in these debates,
it's not even that they dismiss
struggles. They actually dismiss your history.
Are you still there, Greavesy Captain?
What these people do is they actually
dismiss your history with women.
They talk to you like you're some kind
of newcomer, like you've just started or
you're new to this, you know, two months
in. They actually dismiss your history.
um with women as well. That's another
thing that gets dismissed
cuz they're stuck up [ __ ] with unrealistic standards.
What do you think, Gregy? Do you think
they dismiss my history?
I think they dismiss my history with
them as well.
I don't know. It seems that
a second date. I've not been on a date since April.
I don't know what you're talking about, bro.
Uh, well, Dusty, I've not had a date since April.
So, I don't know what you're talking
about. A second date?
Uh, I've not had a date since April. So,
I haven't been on a first date since April. So,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. It way. No, no, no. They give
their numbers and they lead people on.
There's women that have conversations
with people and then they say they got a
boyfriend and they don't. No, no, no,
no, no. Like I said, bro, it's not just
one thing that they do.
So, no, no, no, no. And believe it or
not, they're not all scared of men. Yeah.
Dusty, can you step in here? Cuz it
seems like people are dismissing my history again.
It seems that people are dismissing my history again
and just resort to making stuff up
again. That's what usually happens.
That's what usually happens. Everything
that you put up,
they dismiss it and then just make up
stuff. That's just typical though, isn't it? Right, Dusty?
I've put messages up of what they've done.
I mean, if you was that interested, you
would have paid attention to the
messages that I put up.
Why are you talking about a second date?
Wait, why are you talking about a second
date? You're making stuff up. Who Who
said second date?
Uh, Captain Dusty. Dusty's making things up.
So you just you're just going to make
your own mind up anyways. So I don't
know why whatever you're shown, you're
going to ignore it
and make stuff up.
Anyone going to stop dismissing my
struggles? Reevesy, anyone? No. Just
keep dismissing my struggles. No.
Just dismiss the approaching videos
where they've said they're not
interested straight away. Ignore the
ones where they've led me on.
Just keep ignoring that. Yeah, probably
easier to be honest. Yeah, to be fair,
it probably doesn't suit you, my
experiences. So, yeah, just just keep
dismissing my struggles. It's probably
easier that way to be honest. I'm used
to it now. I'd be very I'd be surprised
if you done anything different.
I sent one message the other day and
they didn't reply. I've had
conversations and they led me on, but my
experiences don't interest you. So, um,
you're obviously not interested enough,
otherwise you wouldn't dismiss my struggles. So,
Tiger Tiger seems to be the only one
that doesn't dismiss my struggles.
He seems to be the only one that doesn't
dismiss my struggles and make stuff up.
He's not on here much, but but it's nice
to see him.
Why do you dismiss my struggles, bro? [ __ ] hell.
Why do you dismiss my struggles?
People dismiss Peterbelly struggle. It's
not nice. It's not good. It's sad.
Why you just missing Peter Belly
struggles? It not nice. It not nice. But yeah,
it not nice.
So yeah, I rate it's not about them
panicking and saying they're not
interested cuz not all of them are
scared to talk to men. Some of them are just [ __ ]
I've approached people sober and they've been [ __ ]
like a month and a half ago. So,
the excuses are going to are going to run out.
The excuses are really really going to run out.
Trust me, the excuses really really are
going to run out.
It all comes to an end, bro. Hello. [clears throat] So, yeah.
See, when when it's do with dating
women, right, it's always to do with
trying to put the blame onto you.
That's basically what the crux of it is.
They're always trying to blame you. You
need to go to the gym. You need to live
by yourself. You need to approach
differently. You need to do this
differently. That they're they're
constantly picking on people
to change things
when it's these women that need to change.
And that is deep down what it is. It's
nothing to do with you, but they will
never admit that. So that's that.
That's why I say it's always a blame
game. They always want to put the blame
onto you. No matter what you do, what
you show them, they will always somehow
find a way to try to blame you again.
No matter what it is. It's [ __ ] ridiculous, bro.
That's why I gave up.
Maybe they're just [ __ ] racist.
We don't say that. Jesus [ __ ] a woman
being racist. Don't [ __ ] say that,
mate. You get [ __ ] the white knights after you.
Let's stop talking about this anyways.
It's depressing, bro.
Yeah, let's move on, bro. It's [ __ ]
depressing as [ __ ] [snorts] Uh,
so what do you think, Steve? an hour. Do
you reckon? So, do you reckon a
45year-old would have got with me if I
lived in her area?
Just the last thing I want to know. Do
you reckon she'd get with me if I lived
in her area?
Uh, I'm not giving you my birthday. [ __ ] off. >> Yeah,
because I always say then what about all
of the ones in London that make excuses?
They've always got an excuse why they
won't get with you. So,
[ __ ] you're not Muslim.
My brother, she's 45.
She It's not for her place to not be
into people. She's 45, bro. She can't
even have kids. She's got a low SMV. So,
you can't even use that as an excuse as
they weren't into you cuz they're not
going to get better. A 45year-old woman
is not going to get better.
So that doesn't even make any sense. I'm
better than her. She's 45. So how can
someone, And that's not even being rude.
That's not even me trying to be nasty.
How can someone that's 45 that can't
have kids think they're better than you?
That's my whole point. That doesn't make any sense.
They have literally got no options
cuz a 45year-old is not better than you.
There's no way. somebody that can have
that can't have kids. So
there's no reason for it.
No, but I wasn't. Yeah, but the thing is
I wasn't going to go see her. So she
didn't reject me cuz I wasn't going to
go and see her.
Well, she didn't reject me cuz I wasn't
even going to go there anyways.
But there you go.
One sec. I am way better than her. I'm
28. She's 45. She can't even have kids.
How can a 45year-old think they're
better than you? A 45 year old woman is
not better than a 28-year-old man.
Doesn't m doesn't m doesn't matter what
the 28-y old man has. So, it goes to
show that if you've got 45 year olds
acting like this,
yeah, you got no chance.
And I weren't even going to go anyways.
Well, I was just testing the waters.
I wasn't even going to go there anyways.
I was only joking, but I just wanted to
see how she would act
cuz I couldn't believe how a 45year-old is acting.
So, that doesn't even make sense. How
can a 45year-old not be into you when
you're literally better than them in
every way? That does not make sense.
No, they're just all women are the same.
It's not about being a cow, bro. See,
the woman, all women are the same.
And I'm decent looking as well. How can
a 45year-old think they're better than
you? It's a [ __ ] joke.
It's a [ __ ] joke, bro.
and I would have not met her anyways.
But even even still, yeah,
well, she needs her wise tested cuz I'm
better looking than her.
Well, she needs to get her eyes tested.
Simple as that.
But I wasn't into her.
I wasn't actually going to go meet her.
I wasn't into her either.
And it's not a kick in the teeth. I I'm
just saying that if you've got 45 year
olds acting like this, then what chance
does someone actually have?
If you've got 45 year olds acting like this now,
what chance do you have? You know,
these women are full of [ __ ] bro. I
would advise everyone to just give up.
Anyone that that tries to date that's
having these experiences, I would just give up. You know,
they're [snorts] just [ __ ] That's
all they are is absolute [ __ ]
Evil [ __ ] They're all the same.
They all say the same [ __ ]
And then she blocked me. Why did she
block me? Just cuz I said that she's
full of [ __ ]
All I said is, "I know you're making excuses."
All I said was, "Oh, like I know you're
making excuses." And I weren't even
being rude, so you blocked me because
you can't wrap me around your little finger.
It's the same story with these women every time.
There's this tenant before she was
trying to use it as an excuse. Oh,
you're too old for me. Oh, they're so
narcissistic. They actually get off on
hurting people. That's what these women
are there. There's no good women out
It's like with this tenant. She was
trying to say she had a boyfriend
before. She doesn't have a boyfriend.
Like a tenant from years ago. And then
she was trying to say, "Oh, you're too
young for me." [ __ ] off with your
excuses. You're not better than anyone.
They actually think that they're better
than people, bro.
They are all the same as well. It's like
what Ant-Man says, they do and say and
act the same way. They are all the
[ __ ] same. And they do do it to other
men as well. And I've seen them do it to
other men. They are literally all the same.
They are literally all the [ __ ] same,
bro. How people can say they're not,
they need to get their head examined.
They are literally all the same.
How anyone could say they're not is
[ __ ] beyond me. And I don't care if
there's people in relationships. I don't
give a [ __ ] I'm telling you, they're
all the same. I don't care. Simple.
I was going to stick it on this tenant,
bro, but I just blocked her dusty cuz I
couldn't be bothered.
And they're no one to not be into people
cuz they're not better than you. They're
no one to be into you to then start
complaining about men cuz they're not
better than you. They literally are not
even better than you. and they're not
even on that level to put themselves on a pedestal.
They literally are no one, bro.
But they think they're something.
And I'm telling you that about that
45year-old. And I don't want to be with
a 45year-old. I weren't even going to meet her.
Uh, Triple H, do you remember the
approaching videos and the messages?
Yeah, it does say something that they've
got unrealistic standards and probably
are [ __ ] racist.
Yeah, it does say something. It says a
lot of things. Racism,
uh, unrealistic standards, stuck up
[ __ ] like what Reddit said. It says
a lot. Yeah,
it says a lot. That's why I'm leaving.
That's why I'm going to Thailand. That's
why I'm leaving.
I'm out of here, bro.
Yeah, that's is And it tells me exactly
what I need to do as well. I'm leaving.
No, she wasn't. I weren't even going to meet her.
And the reason it's like you, this is
what I'm trying to say to you. You've
got 45 year olds that think they're
better than you, that can't even have
kids, that can't do anything basically
at that age. Even now you think that but
people on Reddit Oh, they tell you you
can meet someone on Reddit. Dusty, idiots. Yeah.
But yeah, it tells me a lot about them.
They might not even like me for simply
because I don't look like I'm fully
white. We was talking about this earlier. You know,
it could be like um
it could simply be just racism
because you don't look fully white.
That's how shallow. And that tells you
basically how shallow they actually are.
It could be simply as you don't look
fully white. It could be as simple as
something as simple as that.
You know, it could be something as
simple as that. You know,
it could be Yeah. something as simple as that.
I wasn't going to meet her, bro. I was
just using that as an example. Jesus Christ. [ __ ]
But yeah, it could be something as
simple as that, bro.
You have a beard, you look
Mediterranean. So would that not tell
you how shallow they actually are and
contradict the whole world? They go for
personality. No, no, no. I mean, that in
itself, right? Okay, let's put it this
way, right? Say you had to shave your
beard and you started getting success if
you shaved your beard, Dusty. Would that
not tell you how shallow they are
if they wouldn't get with somebody just
for having a beard?
But people on Reddit, they try to make
it seem like
women don't go for a certain kind of
ethnic. They they they will make it seem
like it's not important to women,
but it is because we've done so many so
many social experiments on this. They
will always make it seem like it's not a physical thing
when it very very much is. Could just be
simply your race, you know? It really
really is. Strange. Yeah.
Yeah. You got 45y olds thinking they're
better than you.
So, how do you know if she wouldn't meet
me if I was in her area?
You never know, Stephen Howard. You might have
Well, I'm leaving, isn't it? I'm leaving.
But women are definitely evil. How
people sit there and say they're not
evil is beyond me. They will literally
do stuff just to make people feel bad about themselves.
Like they literally there's certain
things they do just to make people feel
bad about themselves.
But they say that women aren't evil.
Okay. Of course they're evil, bro. Oh. Uh,
yeah. I'm leaving, lad.
No, she used distance as an excuse. Triple,
she made she made uh she made it she
made distance as an excuse. So, she
actually done the opposite but made it clear.
But yeah, they could just be racist.
Uh, it could just be because you don't
look fully white. But don't forget,
women don't go for any of that stuff.
It's all about personality.
No, I think they're definitely
definitely racist. 100%.
Therefore, cuz I ain't ugly, bro.
[snorts] I wear good stuff. I'm
confident. So even Ben says the same
thing. It could just be cuz the you know
you don't look fully white
which contradicts the whole thing of
them not going for appearance. It
contradict it contradicts all of it in
the washing machine. That would just
contradict everything. But it probably
is something like that to be fair. Uh
um probably just something like that to be honest
which is which is odd. Which is odd cuz
people on Reddit say they don't go for
these kind of things. Dusty.
Yeah. They're full of [ __ ] bro.
want to give one [ __ ] bro, on [ __ ] uh
on uh WhatsApp,
but no, I can't be bothered. It was
somebody that started on me, but no, I
can't be asked, bro. So, yeah, it could
just be cuz they're racist
because you don't look fully white. It
could be just something like that
which would say a lot about them to be
honest. It would say a lot about them.
I think that is what it is to be fair. Yeah.
One sec, bro.
on Reddit said that you'd meet someone though. Steven Howard
Steven Howard. People on Reddit said I'd
meet someone, man. The link
I think a lot of the stories they post
is fake, bro.
Monty had plenty of chances to get off here, bro.
That was so rude though. That was very
rude blocking me just cuz I knew that
she was full of [ __ ] Very rude.
Very rude by it.
I'm looking forward though to uh the
first of January. Steven Howard, new year,
different [ __ ] on YouTube. It's not
going to be the same people. I'm looking
forward to it. Steven Howard.
I'll be going on LJ's channel seeing different people,
different comments. I can't wait.
Yeah, what I was saying, bro, is I can't wait
because it's not going to be the same
people on Lord Days, is it Steven Howard
on the first of January?
Cuz it's going to be a new year, is it?
And they've got a high IQ, so they're
not going to be repeating, are they?
No, but listen, Steven Howard, you
reckon it's going to be different people
on uh Lord Jay's?
Do you reckon it's going to be different
people? I think it is.
No. Tell me. Do you reckon it's going to be
Do you reckon it's going to be different people
on large days?
So, what do we do about these women,
Steven? They're [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
[ __ ] using age as an excuse.
Why don't they just say they're not
interested? And the actual reason why
they're not interested.
Is it because they're narcissists?
Steven Howard, is it because they're narcissistic?
I really want to stop engaging with
them. They're [ __ ]
these women, bro.
They're all the [ __ ] same, bro.
They're all the bastard same. Cuz
someone's not [ __ ] because someone's
not fully white. Someone's not fully English. Uh
prove the what?
All women are the same.
Definitely all the same, bro.
I did I wouldn't have even got with her.
That was just a test. So you got 45 year
olds thinking that they're [ __ ]
better than you.
Mad single moms.
[ __ ] 45y olds. They're thinking that
they're better than you now.
Yeah. She was white. Yeah.
So, not only are they shallow, they're actually racist.
So, not only are they shallow. Yeah,
they're actually racist.
There's nothing wrong with the way that
Peter Belly looks when Peter Belly
scrubs up. Lovely.
When I scrub up lush, what's the color
of my eyes?
Green. They're like green. I think
they're like greeny brown.
Yeah, greeny brown. I'm trying to look, bro.
Yeah, there's nothing wrong with the way
that I look.
Obviously, I don't have blue eyes. I got
green eyes. What color do you think they
are? My eyes?
I think they're like green. Uh, I think
Green or something.
Yeah, I think they're like green.
Probably more brown now. They used to be green.
[ __ ] that virgin [ __ ] should have
been born with [ __ ] green eyes. The [ __ ] virgin.
Who knows would suit that virgin [ __ ]
Yeah, they're green, bro.
What do you think? I think this is a
race thing, lad.
I definitely think this is a race thing.
So, not only are they shallow, they're actually racist.
I'm looking at my face, bro. I'm [ __ ]
looking at myself, man.
When I'm scrubbed up, and there's
nothing wrong with the way Peter Billy looks.
To be fair,
you know what I mean?
So, they've got to be [ __ ] I'll do it
here as well if you can't see. One sec.
Yeah, they're like dark green.
These [ __ ] are [ __ ] racist, man. [snorts]
So, what are they? What do you think it
is? Do you think that that they're just racist [ __ ]
I'm starting to think Ben was was right.
I'm starting to think Ben were [ __ ] was
[ __ ] right, bro. You're virgin. [laughter]
You're virgin. Yeah.
What do you think, bro?
I think Ben 10 was right.
I'm okay. I'm okay. No copy.
>> Confirmed. Copycat.
CCC. That's CCC.
CCC. Steven Howard. Confirmed. Copycat.
Nothing but a little copycat.
I want it. Yeah, that's another thing.
They tell you to lower your standards
and even when you lower your standards,
you're still dealing with the same problem.
So, what do you think the problem is? Is
it Is it because these [ __ ] are racist?
That's what I'm saying. Even if you
lowered your standards, you'd still get
them. You'd still get rejected.
I think that's why USA is like me
cuz we would like to the heritage. You live
Oh god. I'm just I'm just watching my
little I'm making myself a cup of tea.
Yeah. Making myself a cup of tea. Oh gosh.
That's what it is. They're just racist [ __ ]
That's what they are. Just racist bastards.
I think it's good that I think it's
race, bro. I'm not even joking.
Adman says that I look pretty white, but I don't.
So, not only are they shallow, they're
actually [ __ ] racist.
You get all of these people that sit
there and say they're not shallow.
They're [ __ ] more than shallow.
They're [ __ ] racist.
But I think that's what it is as well.
They're racist, bro. They're [ __ ]
racist. How can they sit there and say
they're not chat with a [ __ ]
racist? I might do a video on this.
But I wouldn't have even got with that
45y old, bro. That was just in He
says I look says I look white. I don't
I don't look white.
It was actually Ben that said it. Ben
said, "Oh, it might be because you don't
look fully white. This is why you're
having these problems."
So, that's another thing that he said,
"Oh, maybe Ben Furby said that it's
maybe because you don't look fully
white." And I thought about that as
well, to be honest. That man says I look
fully white, but I don't think I do. Nah. Uh-uh. No.
So, not only are they shallow, they're [ __ ] racist.
That's what they are. They're [ __ ]
They're not shallow. They're [ __ ] racist.
But then you get all of these people
that say you need to go to the gym and
you need to improve yourself with them,
you know, when they're [ __ ] racist as
Cuz it could be the matter of you not
having blue eyes. That's how shallow they are.
I might do a video on this. I might do a
video on this. Um, my experiences with
these two people.
I'm going to title it. Yeah. Lower your
standards in quotation mark. You know
how these people tell you that you need
to lower your standards? It could be
simply because you don't have blue eyes,
but apparently they're not shallow. They
are [ __ ] shallow as [ __ ]
They are shallow as [ __ ] I've run out
of [ __ ] sugar now. Oh gosh darn it.
So how can they not be shallow when
they're downright [ __ ] racist? What the [ __ ]
They're more than shallow. They're
racist. And then you get all these
people trying to put the blame onto you.
They always try and put the blame on to
you, Stephen Howard.
You're [ __ ] You need to go to the
gym. You need to [ __ ] work on yourself. [ __ ]
>> Yeah. No one cares.
When the [ __ ] wants to meet me, come
back and tell me. I don't give a [ __ ]
what that little virgin does.
Uh, but yeah, that's where we're at,
lad. Did anyone reply on this? No.
Yeah, Steven Howard's a brave. He backs
up Peterbellies on Timmy's. He backs me
up on Timmy's. Steven Howard's a proper brother
now. He's a proper brother.
Joseph F is a little na lover.
See, if if I was mad, right, if I was
mad as I was years ago, I would I would
have went Newcastle tomorrow.
Like back in the bomb days when I was
actually a mad crazy [ __ ] I would have
just went there tomorrow and called the
[ __ ] out because he says he's in
Newcastle. I would have been like, "Oh
yeah, come on then, you little nonslover."
I mean, I'll be I'll laugh in your
[ __ ] face now, you little nonsloving
[ __ ] If I was like if if I didn't know
these people was like a waste of time and stuff.
I would, bro. No me. I was [ __ ] mad
[ __ ] bro. You know, but we know what they do.
Nope. I'm not checking it. I don't care. Not interested.
I'm [ __ ] stuck on this Reddit thing
now. I'm not interested in a little keyboard warrior
who cries to the police like a big baby.
You are not coming in.
You are banned. See you later, nons. You
are not coming in.
Bye-bye now. I'm still stuck on this
[ __ ] Reddit thing.
Content coming up. If you got anything
to say, you can meet me face to face. He
likes to try to stir fights and host
them and antagonize people. So when you
grow a pair of balls and meet me, you
can come in.
Oh my god.
Yeah, you're not coming in.
Sorry about that. Say a lighter.
Say you're lighter, mate.
Nope. He ain't coming in.
Right. You want to come in? You can meet
me face to face. You're not coming in.
You little keyboard warrior.
You little gay boy. If you got anything
to say, you can meet me tomorrow and say
to my face. I'm free all day tomorrow. Steven Howard.
Nope. I'm not entertaining little keyboard warriors.
And you're banned again. See you later.
See you later, Virgin.
by Steven Howard. Why do these Reddit
mods ban people, you reckon?
Why do these Reddit mods ban people? You think?
>> Yeah. The virgin boy is not coming up
until he meets me face to face. Until he
meets me face to face. Got nothing to
say, mate. You want to stir up fights
between me and Smokey Be. [ __ ] off, you little virgin
antagonizing two people to fight when
you're never ever ever going to meet
anyone. [ __ ] loser.
Yeah, you prove you're a man and meet me
face to face and you can come in anytime you want.
Do you really want to come? Okay. You
really really want to come on?
Message me right now
and I will come to your area tomorrow
and if you come out, I'll let you I'll
let you on.
That's as fair as I can be. You message
me right now on WhatsApp and I will go
to your area tomorrow. You stinky little
chicken [ __ ] so you can't get the police
involved and then you can come on out.
Until then, you're not coming on.
[ __ ] trying to get Smokey be in
trouble. Trying to get me in trouble.
No, no, no. You message me on WhatsApp
right now and I'll go live tomorrow in
your Virgin area. I'll travel the two
hours and you can say whatever you want
to my face. Until then, you're not
coming on, you little keyboard warrior.
Try to get [ __ ] Smokey Be to [ __ ]
meet people whilst you're in your shitty
little virgin beds.
I'll come to you tomorrow.
That's as fair as I can be, mate. That's
as fair as I can be.
I can't be any fairer than that. Uh Steven,
if you ain't got a problem, you'll do
it. You can message me on WhatsApp. you
got my number?
Message me on Facebook, message me on
Instagram, and then I'll come to your
virgin area tomorrow
and I'll call your little [ __ ] ass out
so the whole world can see it again, you
little coward. And until then, you're
not coming up.
That's the best way with these people,
bro. That's the best way with these people.
Don't sit there and try and stir fights
trying to get people to meet when you
haven't come out [ __ ] five times when
someone's [ __ ] come your come to your area.
You [ __ ] little [ __ ] Do you know
what I mean? Steven Howard, he tries to
[ __ ] stir fights up between two
people, right? Me, my neighbor, Smokey
Be, but the little [ __ ] doesn't come
out when you go to his little virgin area.
So yeah, message me and agreed to meet
me tomorrow and I'll meet you tomorrow.
Yeah, [ __ ] coward little virgin.
Well, why would you why would we even
need to entertain a police informant?
Who would even entertain a police
foreman? Someone that has to run to the
police cuz they've been owned on YouTube.
Someone like that shouldn't be given a platform. [ __ ] virgin.
>> He shows that he can't be owned without
running to the police. He's a loser.
Just like that [ __ ] Joseph Ferrara. Oh,
>> so anyway, Stephen Howard, lad, what do
we do about this women situation?
So yeah, it could just be cuz it could
just be cuz uh yeah, you don't look
fully white. It could just be something like that
cuz I'm not ugly. So ah yeah,
what do you think Steven would we should do?
I would never ever have a child in this
day and age
in case it's a boy and the boy had to go
through what I went through, you know,
with these women and stuff. Nah.
Nah. Crawl, lad. [ __ ] crawl. Yeah,
you're right. Fruit Mad World. I've had
some more bad experiences with women lately.
Nah, there's no hope.
It's bad that it's just because because
you don't look fully white.
But they say that women aren't shallow.
This is what makes me laugh. They sit
there and say that they're not shallow
when they're more shallow than men.
They act like these women aren't shallow
when they [ __ ] are.
They're beyond shallow, bro. What the [ __ ]
So yeah, it could be them reasons.
Yeah, there's definitely no hope, Dad.
What do you mean there's no hope for Mad World? Listen,
bro. I told this [ __ ]
No, I'm not doing that. Why? I shouldn't
have to do that. No, I shouldn't have to
do that. I'm not doing that, bro.
Anyways, if this [ __ ] wants to meet me,
he can message me on WhatsApp and I'll
go to his area tomorrow.
No, I don't need to do that. I should
have to change myself,
you know. I should have to change myself, lad. English, please.
I shouldn't have to do that. Steven Hour
with that. Nope. If you've got anything
to say, you can say it to my face.
If you've got anything to say, you can
say it to my face.
Simple as that.
Nope. Stop being a keyboard warrior.
Stop [ __ ] stirring. You you want to host
fights and get people to fight, so you
message me on WhatsApp and I'll come to
your area tomorrow.
[ __ ] trying to go fights, you [ __ ] ugly bastard.
[ __ ] trying to go and host fights
when your little [ __ ] house self will
not meet anyone when they come to your
[ __ ] area. Get [ __ ]
That annoys me. That does them kind of
cowards annoy me, bro. You don't
understand. And them little cowards
annoy me. You know what I mean?
Little virgins like him. Like I didn't
go to the [ __ ] area three times and had
them run into the police. Virgin cowards
like that annoy me, bro. I hate cowards.
Like, you don't understand. I hate
cowards like that. I hate little virgin
cowards like that, bro. You don't
understand. I hate that [ __ ] man. I
try to put up fights on your channel
when your little [ __ ] ass don't come out
when people go to your virgin area god
knows how many times. [ __ ] that annoys me, bro. You know.
Yeah, I'm not showing you nothing. Go
self-reflect on another channel.
Yeah, go self
Go self-reflect on another channel, you little clown. >> [snorts]
>> Um, see if there's any response to this. Yep.
What the [ __ ]
Look at him. He's such a loser. Look,
he's messaging He's messaging his
stepdad, bro. Yeah, when this is
actually stepdad and he's trying to tell
him to run to the police. Why are you
even telling people uh Triple H to give
this little virgin a platform?
when you know that he's a proper proper
coward. He's a proper grassing little
coward. Why are you even telling people
to give people like that a platform,
bro, when you know what they're like?
You literally know that they're a
coward. You know that they're a little
[ __ ] house. You know that they host
fights for other people, bro. Why are
you trying to get him on this panel? You
know he's a little grass. You know he's
a little muppet.
So why are we going to let someone like
that on our panel, bro? [ __ ] the biggest
cowwood ever. You know what I mean? Get
the hell out of here, bro. That [ __ ]
ain't ever coming on it
until the [ __ ] meets me in person. I ain't interested.
I'm not interested, which is never going
to happen. So it's never going to happen. Simple. So yeah,
I hate cowards like that, Stephen
Howard. I hate cowards like that, bro.
Proper proper hate cowards like that no.
But yeah, anyways, as I was saying, I
shouldn't have to look I shouldn't have
to do anything to my beard and that, bro.
I shouldn't have to do anything to my
beard and that.
He's a loser. Think of it. He's a [ __ ] loser.
Listen, Steven Howard, say I let this
[ __ ] right on my panel right now. Let's
just say for argument sake, right?
Right. This is why you shouldn't give
this loser a platform. Yeah. Say you let
this [ __ ] on your panel right now, right?
Yeah. Say you let this loser on your
panel right now and the [ __ ] doesn't let
you on WhatsApp and this [ __ ] starts
winding you up and winding you up and
winding you up and winding you up as an
example. And then you go to the Virgin
area tomorrow and then he's going to
call the police.
That's literally all that's going to
happen. He's a loser. He's a coward.
[ __ ] absolute loser. And that's an
example like let's just say that
happens. Oh [ __ ] it. I'm bored. Let me
go to this [ __ ] area and he ain't going
to come out. He's going to call the
police and play the victim. He's a loser.
Proper proper loser. So they can try to
join. They can do post. Don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah. It's the same self-reflecting. Same self-reflecting.
Yeah, we've heard it all before. The
same self-reflecting. It's boring.
And I did say on that video, bro, I'm
never going to let them on my panel ever again.
Rice can come on, Timmy can come on,
Monty can come on. You know,
people that show have shown himself can
come on. Look, even Rice met Monty,
Steven Howard, even Rice. Yeah. Even
Rice met Monty. Think about that.
Even Rice gave it a go. Think about it,
bro. Even Rice. But this little virgin
has been on that virgin channel for
[ __ ] god knows how long and he will
never meet anyone. He's just a little
police boy. A little police informant.
Obsessed little police informant,
you know. Even these people gave it a little go,
you know, in fighting and stuff. Even
they gave it a go. They might have not
won, but they gave it a go.
Are we going to let some repeating
bastard up just to repeat the same
self-reflecting [ __ ] that we've been
hearing for years with these little
virgins? No thanks.
That is that is not happening, bro.
[ __ ] virgin. You can't win against
people like that. Unless you ignore
them, you're not going to win against
people like that, bro.
Think about it. Yeah.
You keep going to the police on this
[ __ ] they're not going to do anything.
He keeps going, they're not going to do
anything. He's never going to ever meet
anyone. He just wants to be a keyboard
lawyer. So, you might as well just let
the [ __ ] show himself up.
Just let them show himself up for what
they are. Bro, you can go back and forth
and back and forth and back and forth.
They're never going to meet you.
Yeah. What's that? >> [snorts]
[sighs and gasps]
>> Oh, [ __ ] they banned me, didn't they?
Yeah. So, yeah, like I said, the
content's changing on this channel
anyways, bro. So that's that.
We not let little virgins on.
Ronald Pump said, "You're better looking
than them. You've got a better life than
them. You've got more money than them
and it kills them."
Do you remember? Do you remember
[clears throat] that Steven Howard?
Big up Ronald.
Big up Ronald McDonald.
Yeah, bring up Ronald [ __ ] Donald, bro.
What happened to that chat?
No, it was ages ago.
He said that you're young. He said that
you're better looking than them. You got
a better life than them, and you got
more money than them, and it kills them.
He said, "Get off YouTube and live your
life." That's what he said.
But obviously, I can't leave Greasy
without content, poor [ __ ] I can't I
can't leave the brothers without any
content. You know what I mean?
And it kills them. Mad, isn't it? It's
true though, is it? It is true.
I don't know. Do you think these people
will ever stop?
He said that they'll never leave you
alone. That's what he said, Steven Howard.
He said that these people will never
leave you alone. Is he right?
How do you know they'll never leave me alone?
>> Yeah, he's talking about that Jamie
Thompson as well, is it?
Steven Howard, you think that Jamie
Thompson is jealous of Peter Belly?
Leave me alone.
You think Jamie Thompson is jealous of
Peter Belly? Leave me the [ __ ] alone.
Leave me alone, you weirdo. Yeah,
he keeps stalking me. Steven Howard,
does Stephen H um Dam Thompson keep stalking me?
Do you think he's jealous of Peter
Belly? Do you think Jamie Thompson is
jealous of Peter Belly?
No, it's [ __ ] weird, lad.
What the hell?
They all keep saying that I'm broke.
Why do these people keep saying that I'm skinten Howard?
I'm not skin. Why do they keep saying
that I'm skint?
I'm not skint. Steven Howard. Why are
they saying I'm again.
cuz they're skin.
Cuz they're broke. Yeah. Do you remember
that one? Because these people are skin
cuz they're skin in it. Yeah.
$,500 without any bills is not skin, is
it? Steven Howard.
If if you've got £1,500 and no bills,
that's not [ __ ] skin, is it? Steven Howard. No.
Yeah, bro. I've got I got some money,
I get money every week as well, so you know. Yeah,
I like Sher Cole. Steven Howard.
I like show.
Yeah, I just saved though. I just saved Steven Howard.
I saved. I just tried. I tried to save.
I like shovel. Oh,
>> is the only other way to get extra
money, Steven Howard? Gambling. I think
I think it is, isn't it?
Gambling, isn't it?
That's the only other way in it. Stephen
Howard gambling is it?
But who's really going to do that, you know?
I don't need any new clothes, do I,
Stephen Howard? I've got the money
jeans. I've got the nice trainers. I
don't need any new clothes for a while. Nah.
What? Like 120 on two teams?
Yeah, but what about roulette? What
about online roulette?
Yeah, I would never put more than 120 on
a bet. I don't think I was thinking of
putting 180 on a double both teams to score
and try and win one every week. And try
and win one every week, Steven Howard.
That is lush. Try and win one every
week. That's like an extra grand a
month, isn't it? 50 pound.
You think that's cute that USA is he saw
my dick? Steven Howard.
Is that cute? Huh? God bless.
You're better looking than them.
You got more money than them and a
better life than them and it kills them.
I'm getting a tattoo of that, bro. I'm
getting a tattoo of that. Yeah.
So, do you reckon you'll ever play
roulette again, Steven Howard? Oh gosh.
Believe it or not, I think you got more
chance of the borrow that than [ __ ] online.
Yeah. I think football's the only way in it.
What is the maximum you'd actually put
on a double both teams to score though,
Steven Howard? What is the absolute maximum
What is the actual actual max? Uh, no. I
haven't seen it, bro.
What about 150? No.
When's it going to be a crazy league
again? Do you think next Tuesday?
Would you would you put 150 on it?
All right, bro. I hate Do you hate that Jo?
So would you put 150 on two team Steven Howard? Huh?
Would you put 150 on it?
N 120 max isn't it?
I think 120 max.
I put 120 on it.
I remember when I met [ __ ] US. I
remember when I met Finn Finnish Izzy,
bro. I put 120 and I won 380 back. I was
so lucky, bro. So lucky. I was getting depressed.
I was kind of like short of money. I had
like 200 left. I was getting paid the next week.
And it come in, bro. It was nice. 380
from 120. It was lush. [ __ ] lush.
Imagine I had 500 quid on it, Stephen. I
would. But no, I wouldn't do that, bro.
I would just try and win some every week.
I would just try to win a football bet
every week, you know?
No, I would just try to win one every
week. Say you won one three weeks in a row.
It's like over a grand, isn't it? Sir, come in.
Yeah, I am up, bro. Of course I'm up.
I'm well up, man. Of course I'm up. And
have you noticed you don't give it back
when you win on the football? You don't
give it back as quick. It's harder to
give it back.
It takes longer to give it back in it,
bro. Have you noticed that?
I'm saving money at the minute, bro. So,
I can't do any uh football bets. Well,
not big ones.
My friend said that's too much to put on
a football bet. 120.
Is he right? That's too much to put on a
bet 120. Is he right? Adam Thomas. Adam Thomas,
I want to play some online roulette. Steven Howard
Adam. Posh Adam.
Remember Adam? Oxford. Oxford. Adam.
No, I'm not playing with that. I'm only joking, bro. Huh?
What do you say you prefer, Steven
Howard? The winter or the summer? The
summer is good for drinking in like
shorts. Nice fresh trainers shorts.
What do you think?
Two years ago, summer was so good, bro.
I had all the money in the world. Nice
gums. It was lush. [ __ ] lush, bro.
Yeah. April is USA is his birthday.
No, it was lush though. It was lush.
April's [snorts] USA is his birthday. Steven Howard.
Yeah, April's good, but sometimes April
can be cold.
When's your birthday? Like the month?
Not the date, just the month.
Mine's October. Greavves is March. What's yours?
Not the day. Just the month.
It's not like anyone's going to find you
from the [ __ ] month, you know? Jesus Christ.
What about you? I'm October.
Oh, you're the same as Laney.
You're the same as Laney. Laneie is 2nd of September.
Lane is a Virgo.
Yeah, I used to be able to do what I
want. Go out gambling.
Nice gums in the summer. Steven Howard,
summer was good, bro. Summer was good.
Not last summer. The summer before that was lush. [ __ ] lush.
You remember the Reese clothes, the five
grand money. It was good, bro. Ain't it?
No, it was good, bro. It was good.
Hopefully again next summer.
Well, I won't be here next summer, but yeah.
So, that's what I might that's what is
good to do, bro.
Maybe you could just save money until
the summer. Save money until June, is it?
You could save money until like June.
Then you'll have loads of money in it.
Live off £50 a week until June.
Buy some nice summer garments. You know
what I mean?
I still got my summer clothes.
I still got my summer ones, bro.
I got my receipts and everything.
That's why I don't want to go out. I'd
rather build the money up and just go
out New Year's Eve.
I'll go out New Year's Eve, but I'd
rather just save the money now, you know?
Yeah, I get £1,100 a month. Steven Howard,
I get like £1,100.
That's not poverty, is it? Steven Howard.
£1,100 a month. That's But I only have one bill.
Joseph Farra says that's poverty. That's not poverty. Is it?
That's not Poy, is it? Steven Howard.
That's not poverty, is it? 11 uh 11,200
a month. Stephen Hwood, is it?
Yeah, exactly, bro.
we going out New Year's Eve, though.
All right. Why does Jo keep saying that
I'm living I'm living under poverty? Steven Howard
I had loads of money, bro. I had loads
of cash. I had money coming in as well.
It was sick, bro.
That's not that bad. Uh £1,100 a month,
is it Steven Howard?
It's not that bad, is it?
Yeah, I'm saving anyways, bro. I want a
good summer next month. Uh, next year, sorry.
All you need is two pair of trainers,
nice shorts, nice top from Greece.
And I have a bit more money as well,
Steven Howard, because of um
I've got more a bit more money anyways
because of um
because of the football bets in it.
You know what I mean?
You like my Ammani jeans?
Yeah. We'll have some time to save, bro.
Cuz don't forget January, no one goes
out, do they? So January, nobody goes out.
Well, obviously I still need to get a
phone, which will cost like 200 and something. So
yeah, but don't forget.
Yeah. Not in the summer.
Not in the summer, bro. You like my Ammani jeans.
Get out my trainers.
When do you reckon I'll need to buy new
trainers? Steven Howard again.
When do you think
pro. Nah, not two years. Maybe a year.
I'll show you some of the stuff I've
got, but it probably won't be good for
this summer. One sec. Go. One second. [snorts]
Look, bro. These are these are my summer garments.
And obviously virgin boy by can't afford
this cuz he's skinty skin.
Why? Why can't he afford it? cuz he's
skint [ __ ] skin.
These are my summer stuff. I don't know
if they're still any good.
I'll probably wear this under my blazer.
I'll probably wear this under that for
New Year's Eve or something. These are
my like stuff.
These are my summer stuff.
These were expensive, bro. Like £100 each.
They lasted though. They're quality.
Probably have to buy some new stuff next
summer though. And my shorts. My little summer shorts. I like
Yeah. And I got my shorts as well. I got
some short shorts, too. My stonies.
I love my Vapor Maxes, bro. They're so so lush.
They're so lush.
I like Chev.
I don't I hate Chev Cole, but I'm not a copycat.
I'm not a little copycat.
Virgin boy is messing his um messaging
his um stepdad.
messed in his stepdad. The [ __ ] virgin.
Maybe next year we'll get laid. Maybe
he'll get laid next year. Steven Howard,
you never [ __ ] know, mate. You could
easily get laid.
Loses Valentine's card. What do you think?
What do you think, lad? You reckon he'll
lose his [ __ ] Valentine's card?
You'll be thinking,
"What the [ __ ] bro?" I'll be [ __ ] proud.
I'll be proud, mate, if he loses his Valentine's cards.
He's no longer a big virgin.
What do you think?
He might actually get like Monday one day.
Steven Howard, what if he gets laid?
What are you going to do if he loses his Valentine's card?
So, what month do you reckon I should
save until like May?
Like until what do you reckon? May maybe
he kind of got lied. He's going to lose
his Valentine's card.
So what do you think until like May?
January, February. We got January, February, March,
April, May, and then what? Just start
going out in like May.
May is good. You could start going out
around May, June.
No, April's too early, bro.
No, I still think that's a bit too
I think this is still a bit too early, bro.
No, no, mid April. Maybe like late
April. Late April.
Live off 50 a week until midappril.
go to the gym as well.
So, midappril. Yeah. you know.
Yeah. But what if we lose? We could lose like £120. Then what?
Yeah. You don't want to lose too much
money, do you?
Maybe I'll start doing Uber again. Steven Howard
It's hard work, but I've done it before.
Do a lot of hours, Steven Howard. Do a
lot of hours and wait for the weekly
money to come in. [ __ ] lovely, eh?
Sat there having a drink, waiting for
the money. Whether it's 170, 180,
it is hard. You saw I done it in it. It
was [ __ ] hard. But worth it.
Yeah. You get money weekly if you do it
though, is it? Or you can get paid
straight away. But
yeah, well, you got it coming in every
week in it if you do that.
I had like I made like 160 in 3 days.
Steven Howard 160 in 3 days.
Yeah. 160 3 days. Yeah, bro.
So, I didn't spend my own money, you see.
Yeah, it's hard trying to do it in this
weather. It is hard trying to do it this
I like I made 90 pound in like 10 hours, bro.
Steven 92 pound in 10 hours. It was long. Oh, [ __ ] hell.
I come back. [ __ ] bro. My back and
everything was [ __ ]
I was [ __ ] bro.
I made 90.
Still good though. I don't 90. Yeah.
Yeah. What about 150?
Yeah. But what about one? No. But the
what I'm what the plan is though,
Stephen. Now, the plan is I'm just going
to autopilot it for a week straight,
bro. But I just do seven hours a day.
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday. Seven hours.
like six or seven hours
and by the end of the week you should
make good money in it,
7 hours a day.
Six, seven hours a day. Yeah.
Just do it like a crackhead, bro. For
just like a week, you should make good
money doing it.
You can make like 150 in one day. Some
days you can. What about 150 in a day,
Stephen Hour? That's decent, isn't it?
150 in a day.
I went everywhere around London. I was [ __ ]
I kind of miss that house, boy. Going to
work, coming back, watching the TV.
I do miss it, bro. I actually missed
that house, you know, man.
That house was good. It was good in the
winter. That house. Yeah.
Yeah. But you got to be careful cuz if
they block the road up, you're [ __ ]
If they block the road, you're [ __ ]
You know, if you block the road, you're [ __ ] bro.
You will be [ __ ]
Really [ __ ] Because you won't be able
to do it.
Bro, they don't It wasn't these people
on YouTube. I got the account back. It
wasn't these people on YouTube. These
people on YouTube don't know what I'm
doing, bro. They don't know what I'm
doing. They don't know how much money I
have. They don't really know anything.
I only just tell them stuff.
Trust me, lad. They don't know what I'm doing.
Funny enough, that's not even what I'm
going to be doing. I tell these people.
I only told them after it after they
banned my account. After they banned my
account, that's when I told them, "Bro,
after I told them after they didn't know
what I was doing, bro, when I was doing it,
these people don't know my business,
bro. They didn't stop. They didn't stop
my sublet of money either, even though
they say they did. Trust me, they never.
These people don't know anything, lad.
But they didn't stop the house, brother.
They didn't stop the house. It was the
landlord that was trying to get it back
for years. It had nothing to do with YouTube.
YouTube didn't stop the house. I don't
know how many times I have to keep
explaining this and explaining this and
explaining it. It was nothing to do with YouTube.
They did not stop it. They were trying
to get the house back for years and
years and years and years and years and
years and years. It wasn't anything to
do with YouTube.
[ __ ] they stop they tried getting our
house back for years, bro. And they kept
getting delayed and delayed and delayed.
It wasn't anything to do with these people.
And I didn't even tell them. It was when
the whole LT thing was going on. So yeah.
No, bro. These people didn't they didn't
know that. They they did not stop my
money, bro. They did not stop the money at all.
They wish, but they never. They [ __ ] wish.
Yeah, that's that.
I had a house for three and a half
years, bro. Three and a half years.
They never stopped my money.
Yeah, they knew about it, but they never
stopped it. They did not stop my money.
They did not stop any of my income.
They didn't stop no bit of my income whatsoever.
All right. Even though they like to keep
saying that they did, but they never.
How long was that landlord trying to get
that house back?
ages and ages and ages. It had nothing
to do with YouTube.
Why do you think I'm so calm about it,
bro? Because I knew it was nothing to do with YouTube. [laughter]
So, that's that, bro. I don't give a
[ __ ] I had my life out of that house anyways.
Yeah. I had my life out of that house,
bro. I had my life out of that house
more than many years. So, and none of
these people stopped it. Sir not asked. Yeah.
No ways to make money now. it. Steven
Howard, there's no other ways to make
money now, lad. Is there?
So what? They're just going to let
someone stay in a house for free forever,
bro. Even they were sending like letters
and mad [ __ ]
They were sending letters and everything.
They were sending like letters and all
sorts. These people didn't stop my income, mate.
They definitely definitely didn't stop
my income. 100% never stop my income.
Definitely definitely didn't stop my income, mate. Yeah.
Definitely definitely didn't.
Yeah, it's good money that house. Three
grand a month, bro. But yeah,
that's that start in it, bro.
That's the only way or you um
are you gamble and risk losing on
roulette which I'm not willing to take that risk.
Yeah, it's a good thing that house it was good.
It's all right, bro. Yeah,
but it was annoying as well. So was
good, but it was annoying.
It was, bro.
>> Yeah. Three grand a month for doing
nothing. Good in it, bro.
But I could still do it. I can still
gamble if I want to. I can still do what
I want when I want. Bro, this Joseph doesn't understand.
I could still do what I want when I
want, bro. You know what I mean? [ __ ]
He really really doesn't understand.
Really doesn't understand. I literally
could do what I want when I want. So
he doesn't understand anything.
Guy saying, "No, you don't go out now. I
haven't been going out every week for
the past year, retard."
You know what I mean, bro? The past [ __ ] year.
the past year. Steven Howard.
Steven Howard. Why does this [ __ ] keep
saying that I can't go out
when I can go out whenever I want? Steven Howard.
Why does he keep saying that?
That Joseph Raw doesn't think I can go
out drinking and gambling every week.
Yes, I [ __ ] can
if I wanted to. Yes, I [ __ ] can.
Yeah, I could go out and gamble every
week if I wanted to, bro.
I go out drinking gambling every week.
[ __ ] multiple. You know what I mean, bro?
But why am I why am I going to do that,
bro? Like, seriously.
Steven Howard, why am I going to do that?
I had loads of escorts, bro. Loads of
escorts as well.
Do you reckon I'll ever be able to be a
landlord again? Nah. That house thing
was once in a lifetime, bro.
It was that was once in a lifetime. No, bro.
No, that was definitely once in a lifetime, bro. And
once in a lifetime and
it was once in a lifetime and
people had to go out working
and I was just having the house money,
bro. It's funny, isn't it?
Yeah, it's funny as [ __ ]
Yeah, that was funny, bro. Yeah.
One of them.
I had a sick time, bro.
Yeah, I had a sick time out of that
house, bro. A [ __ ] sick time. And I
was happy to be left with something as
well, you know? I was happy to be left with something.
You know what I mean?
Yeah. Well, I think I left like two and
2K something, bro. I just bought a TV and [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah, it was all right, man. It's all
Yeah, it was good.
But if I still had that house, bro, I
wouldn't still I still wouldn't be I
still wouldn't be out gambling and that.
I would just [ __ ]
I would just um
just be stacking, bro. I wouldn't I
wouldn't be gambling. Like I said, if I
was going to do something and I if I
wanted to do something, I would [ __ ]
do it, bro. I would find a way to do it.
This Joseph Far is the only one that's
living living in poverty, bro. Not me. Yeah,
you had a nice food and Yeah, it was good, bro. Yeah.
No, more than that. I had that house for
years, bro. I had the house for years, you know.
I don't mind. I don't mind saving a bit
slower, bro. I don't mind
slow saving up a bit slower.
I don't mind at all. It is what it is, isn't it? Yeah.
No, you couldn't buy the place, bro. The
place is worth like a [ __ ] million,
bro. What the [ __ ] You wouldn't be able
to buy a house in London with 40k.
So, do you think it's worth doing the
Uber thing then, Steven Howard?
I think it is. Even if you can make 200
pound a week. Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
If you can make like 2 250 a week,
it's pretty good now.
Yeah. So, how how will you make extra
how will you make extra money?
You would have to either save or gamble
in it. There's no other way.
No, you can make money from that
delivery thing. I reckon you definitely could.
No, you definitely can make money from it. 100%.
Do you reckon you can make £500 a week?
I think you could if you put the hours in.
Yeah, I reckon you could if you put the hours in.
4500. I think you could Uh,
did I know?
Yeah, there was one time it was raining,
but I just put the bike inside. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm skinn. I don't have any money.
No. Can you give me some?
Yeah, I don't have any money. Can you
give me some?
Yeah, I'm proper skin, man. Give me Can
you give me some money?
Yeah, that'd be nice if you give me some money, man.
Well, not from you cuz you don't work.
I did buy a Christmas present. I bought
my mom some U mug boots. £165.
Same question to you. Why don't you get a job?
Yeah, of course you do. So, do you
reckon you can make £500 doing that job, Steven Howard?
Yeah, maybe some point. Yeah, I haven't
had to. I've had money, so I haven't had
to do it. Triple H. I haven't really had
to do it. So,
I haven't really had to do it, bro, cuz
I've had money. So, yeah. Yeah.
No, because that's your life, not mine.
No, bro. Cuz that's your life, not mine.
No, cuz I'm not skin on I'm not skin on
benefits. That's you.
That's your life.
Would you ever think about subleting Triple H?
See you later.
Would you have a sublet, Steven Howard?
There is another way to get money.
Get univer get university loans.
You can do that like five times. get
like 15 grand, but I can't be annoyed
with it, bro.
I can't be bothered to do that.
No. Why don't you do that, Ste? Get like university loans.
No, I probably I'm not doing that.
I wouldn't do it. Hey, would you
Yeah, I was banging escorts all the time
in that house. Banging escorts, [ __ ]
going getting [ __ ]
No, I wouldn't do it, man.
2K is enough for me. I don't need any
more money, bro. I can just have the 2K
and just earn money on top. You know
what I mean? Steven Howard.
I think the only way is like say for a
month and a half, two months and then
just start delivering food.
There's no I don't think there is any
other way, bro. Unless you gamble and
win, but that's a risk. So, I don't
think there is any other way, bro.
That's literally the only way.
There's literally no other way, bro.
It's not that bad, it think about it,
man. You know,
yeah, I don't tell them anything. They
don't even know how much money I have,
bro. I just tell them what I want them
to know. They don't know anything.
They don't know what money I have. They
don't know nothing.
Don't want to keep trying to say that
they stopped my sublet money. They
didn't stop any money of mine, bro. They
didn't stop any money. And I've still
got money and I still got a better life
than them. But they still talk [ __ ]
You know what I mean?
Peter belly the landlord. Steven Howard.
But a lot of my money came from
gambling, bro. It wasn't even the
subleting. It was actually gambling cuz
I used to win a lot of gambling. If I
didn't win the money gambling, I
wouldn't have all that money all at once.
So yeah, literally is the only way is
just to try to build some kind of fund up, bro.
That's what I'm doing. That's why I
can't be bothered going out.
You know what I mean? That's why like
I'd rather just chill, you know?
I could go out every week. I could go
out and live the high life if I still
want to. Steven Howard.
Seriously, bro. I really could. If I wanted to,
I could still go out living that high
life if I wanted to.
But I'd rather save and have the freedom
of money, you know, as well. You know
what I'm saying? Right. So that's what
that is. And I'd still be doing it. Even
if I had the house, I would still be
doing it. I'd still be sat in saving. Mhm.
Promise you, Stephen. I would absolutely promise you.
100%, bro. 100 million%. I mean,
no, it's going to take me a while to get
to 5K, but yeah. No.
Maybe. Maybe. Maybe.
Maybe April, maybe.
But I'm going out New Year's Eve.
Hopefully that don't [ __ ] the savings
up. It shouldn't be.
Shouldn't be. No.
No. It should be all right, bro. It
should be all right. No. Again, I can
afford it, but I'm very like I have I
like to try to save a certain amount. I
was the same even when I had the house.
This whole house thing, bro, has not
stopped me not doing anything.
Really, really hasn't. Once I get a
phone again, I'm laughing. So,
it really really hasn't stopped anything.
They ain't stopped no madness. Thus,
if the madness gets stopped, it gets
stopped by Peter Belly, you know.
soon in the house.
No, I need to get a phone. My phone's
blocked, bro. I'm I need to get a phone
at some point.
Even if it's like a [ __ ] £300 one.
Not now. Maybe next month. I'll get it
next month. I don't need it this month
or maybe the month after. Yeah, I don't
need it for a while, but at at some
point I will because this phone's blocked.
I'm waiting for this phone to go down to
like £300 and I'm going to buy it. I'm
not paying £400.
Yeah, it works, but it doesn't work off
Wi-Fi. Yeah, it's not I'm not I'm not in
any hurry to buy one, bro. I'm not in
any hurry to buy one.
I'm not in any hurry to buy one, bro.
But I will need one at some point
because obviously if I'm traveling and
that this phone is blocked.
I mean it's not important.
If I need to work I'm going to need it as well.
So I will need to get one at some point, you know.
Not in a hurry though. Not in a hurry.
And I'm going to get the Fold 8. What?
You need to give me uh some advice with
this, Stephen Howard. So, I'm going to
get the Samsung Galaxy Fold 8 when it
comes out next summer. Yeah.
When it comes out next summer. Yeah. Um
when it comes out next summer.
Listen, but you either pay it outright
151,600 pound or you pay £200 a month
for a year. I think £200 last year was
saying it's too much. I don't think it
is. £200 a month for a year, that's
worth it, bro. It's only a year contract,
but paying 15,600 for a phone, you know
what I mean? So,
I'm saying, bro,
yeah, I'll buy it at another point. I
I'll buy it in another at some point,
bro. You know what I'm saying? Don't
need to rush it. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
I like the fold phones though, Steven
Howard. This phone should still last me
like another year to be fair. This
phone's blocked, but you just use it on
Wi-Fi, don't you? Yeah.
What did you say the most you would ever
pay for a phone again, Steven Howard?
What did you say the most you'd ever pay?
See, that phone I had before was down to
£250. I should have bought it when it
was £250 [ __ ] pound.
But I just wanted to save so I didn't
buy it, bro. 250 [ __ ] pound it was.
Now it's gone back to 400. £250 is a
good deal, bro.
It's a good phone, bro. It's a good phone, man.
For £250 [ __ ] pound is worth it. So,
I've got this phone and then the
unblocked [ __ ] phone. I should have
bought the bastard, man. Yeah.
Yeah. So, basically what happened was
with the house. So, do you want to know
the story of the house? I'm Steven Howard.
You want to know basically the story of the house
in case these mugs try to keep telling
you that they got my money stopped? You
want to know? Yeah.
So Laney moved house
and I stayed in the house for like a
year and then this which which I should
have been staying in the house cuz it
wasn't a house right. So then
the land and then there oh you know you
could sublet this house and make more
money. I said really? So then we got rid
of the rooms. We was making money on the
house. Then the landlord kept sending
letters. Yeah. before the whole thing
with LT sending letters, sending
letters, sending letters, coming on the
door. They were coming on the door at
some point. This [ __ ] all happened
before anybody knew cuz obviously they
wanted the house back. It was their house.
So eventually they got it back after
years because they were trying to get
the house back for years
cuz it obviously
my mom moved so I wasn't paying for the
house. I was staying in the house for
years. These people didn't stop any of
my income, bro. And I don't know why
they keep saying it.
No one cares about that nons, bro.
No one cares about nons legs.
No one cares about the skin [ __ ] But
yeah, Steven Hour, that's basically uh
that's how it how what happened
basically, bro. I might get a spoons
breakfast, you know, in a couple of
hours, man. I fancy a spoons breakfast.
I might do a football bat and a spoon breakfast. Yeah.
Yeah. They never
These people did not get any of my money stopped, bro.
My trip 8 might not know what that
means. Sublet is it subletting.
I wish they would have given that house
back, bro. Even if it meant not
subleting it. I wish I could live in
that house again, bro. That house was lush.
I'd live in the house by myself, bro.
[ __ ] the money. I would just live in
there by myself. [ __ ] [ __ ] man.
Taking that house back in it.
They ruined a lot of people's lives
taking that house back. I was laughing.
The tenants were crying, bro.
The tenants were crying when they found
out about the house.
Steve and I were the tenant was crying.
I was laughing, bro. I was laughing my ass off,
which is not funny cuz my a lot of my
income got stopped, did it?
You think that's funny?
Yeah, the house. Yeah, obviously that's
why they were crying. They like the
house, bro. I like the [ __ ] house. I
like living there. When Laney chucked me
out, I was never going to come back
here. Never going to come back here.
I was never going to come back here, bro.
I was never going to come back here.
The house was lush.
Nice food, nice sleep.
It was good, bro.
Yeah. He's never going to lose his Valentine's card.
Would you have a sublet? Um,
Triple H, would you have a sublet?
You sublet when you triple H.
So, what are we going to do about this
women [ __ ] Steven Hwood, lad. Yeah.
What What did he say to fit in then?
What did he say to fit in? Trip uh What
did he say to fit in? Triple H.
What did he say, lad? Yeah,
I've still got money as well in it, Steven Howard. Mhm. Yeah, man.
I got a bed, TV, Xbox.
Can do what I want when I want.
It's lush, isn't it? Lush.
You like my TV? Yeah.
I've got money as well, don't I? Triple.
I got some lovely trainers, some lovely jeans.
Trip is a troll.
No trick. No, Albert Square was good, bro.
This is nothing compared to Albert Square, bro.
This is where I live now. Yeah.
and it kills them. Hey Billy D. Hey, hey, Billy Dy.
I hope Mark's all right. Horrible.
what these people have done to him.
Is it what these people have done to
Mark Edward is is no laughing matter,
Triple H. It's no It's no laughing matter, lad.
But he could have got off here, couldn't he?
She thinks she's an absolute virgin.
I put up the messages from me stepdad.
Yeah, I might put up the messages from
me stepdad, bro. Yeah. Mhm.
David Campbell. Mad.
He needs to get lied.
The virgin needs to get laid. He's such a virgin.
Anyways, I'm gone. Yeah, I'll be back later. Maybe and a