Yeah,
just wanted to see if it's the same people
or if there's new faces, you know. You
never know, really.
If it's the same people or new faces,
hopefully some new faces.
Be nice to see some new faces about
Oh, it's cold. Very cold.
going on frozen.
What the [ __ ] is going on here, bro?
Yeah. I just wanted to see if it's the same people
or if it's different people. Yeah.
I was only on for an hour earlier. Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, mate.
Yeah, I was in a bad stinking mood earlier. better now.
Oh, I want [ __ ] ammo in my [ __ ] gun, bro. Yeah.
Why you need to get sleep, bro? It could
really [ __ ] your moods up.
You know, I was on Reddit as well. They
were pissing me off.
So, yeah, just chilling, bro.
Had a phone call from the police.
any progress with what?
You know the answer. If it's what I'm
thinking, you already know the answer.
So, I don't know why you're asking
questions. You already know the answer to
if you're asking what I think you're
asking. By the way, the police called me
and I um yeah, I told him about my
little evidence pack.
Um they they wanted to know uh the the
the channel. So, I called the channel.
So yeah, bro. Our life doesn't need to
It's not our love life. It's our It's
not our life. It's our love life that's
in the gutter. I don't need to improve.
I don't have any addictions. Don't have
any bad habits. There is
a love life that's in the gut. I need nothing else.
I need to probably wait until I message
this person. Oh, the old Bill called me. So yeah,
about this little virgin. They call me off unknown. Yeah,
my little evidence back.
But yeah, no, your life will never
improve in this country. It will never
improve. You'll always be annoyed. You'd
always be frustrated in this country.
It's a shitty country.
I had to go to three places today just
to [ __ ] print something. The country
is a joke.
It's a [ __ ] joke. Yeah.
And then when you say this stuff, people
say that you've done your balls in a
madness when I didn't even gamble today.
I can't remember the last time I [ __ ]
gambled. It's a [ __ ] badness, bro. Badness.
But yeah, life never will never improve
in this country.
It will always be the same old. It's
been the same old for 6 years and it
will be the same old for another [ __ ]
18 years. So that's that depressing shitty country.
Everything shitty about it. [ __ ]
annoys me. Puts me in a bad mood. So yeah, co.
It's not good, is it?
could go out for a drink today if I
wanted to. Nah.
Nope. I'm done with them evil [ __ ]
I ain't been out for a couple of weeks
and I was only out because I cuz I got
forced to go out. I hate them [ __ ]
[ __ ] Evil bastards and I'm sick of
hearing about them on the [ __ ] TV.
I've heard about him again. Oh,
misogyny. Misogyny. Let's talk about the
double [ __ ] standards, mate.
I've heard it again when I woke up. Oh,
misogyny about women. [ __ ] women. Let's
talk about the double standards in the
dating game. Oh, don't say anything like
that because that must mean you've
gabble all your money and you must be
ski. It's madness, isn't it? You know
what? The stuff that these people on
here come out with is [ __ ] hilarious.
Like they think because you have an
opinion, you you've lost all your money
or you have no money. And I'm thinking I
was thinking about this yesterday and
I'm thinking, bro, I could literally win
the lottery right now and I'd still be
saying the same [ __ ] thing.
[ __ ] that. They're [ __ ] evil [ __ ] I
stay clear of them evil bastards. I say
on [ __ ] Reddit as well. I'm sick of
them. I'm sick of the double standards.
I'm sick of all of it, bro.
So that's me done forever. So yeah.
Yeah. I hate him, bro. I hate them.
Yeah, that's that. You know,
I really, really, really, really, really
do. Some people are just in an aisle,
though, aren't they? So,
I really do hate them. They're all
[ __ ] NPCs as well. I saw it earlier
when I was out. They're all [ __ ]
nonplaying characters. They're like
[ __ ] Star Wars [ __ ] droid. Druids?
Are they druids or droids? I think
they're called droids. Them them [ __ ]
cream robots. That's what they are, bro.
They're [ __ ] NPCs, non-playing characters.
Yeah, you can go away, you little
keyboard warrior. Get banned.
Sad little [ __ ] [ __ ] off. Not going
to argue with stupid people that write
stupid comments that's never going to
meet me. [ __ ] off, mate.
Yeah, you could have said all of this
when I was in your area. I'm not going
around in circles. [ __ ] off. Simple. Yeah.
Don't want them on my channel, bro.
Don't want them come to my channel, bro.
You know how it is.
And when that Joseph Ferrar comes on it,
I'll be telling him about himself as well.
I'll be telling him about his [ __ ]
self when he comes on here.
Yeah, [ __ ] try and tell people they
weren't doing nothing, you little [ __ ] Yeah,
simple. That's all I'm going to say. I'm
just going to get straight into that,
bro. Like, I got to go back and forth
with these people.
Um, so that's that.
Um, so yeah, I do hate them, bro.
They're evil [ __ ] They are evil little
bastards. And I don't contradict
anything I'm saying cuz I don't go out,
bro. I don't try. I don't go out and try
cuz I don't want to. They are evil.
I don't contradict myself, bro.
You know what I'm saying? They're just
evil scum of the earth.
That's what they are, bro.
So yeah, I really do hate them.
Seriously, I do hate them, bro.
So yeah, I don't even want to go out New
Year's Eve, but I'll have to cuz I've said it
sure takes it to you in it.
Cuz one day you're going to wake up and
smell the coffee, which is what a lot of
these people need to do when they're
[ __ ] defending them. Be any age,
could be older, could be younger.
Um, and then you'll think to yourself,
"What the [ __ ] is this [ __ ] still going
on?" one day you'll wake up and you
you'll see it, bro. You will actually
you know, and that's that.
More needs to be said about this as well.
More does need to be said about this,
about the double standards.
It's bad. It's a bad um
bad uh you know day and age to be born in.
But all of these people like Terry and
Joseph Fod, they're just little
non-lovers. So if they've got anything
to say, they can say it to my face. Simple, bro.
Simple. They can say it to my face. If
they've got anything to say, they can
say it to my face. That's that. Yeah. man.
Don't know. Don't care. I don't go on
the losers channel, bro. I generally
don't give a [ __ ]
I don't go on the losers channel, so I
don't know. I unsubed from Joseph
Ferrar. I don't bother with any of them
them losers, bro. So, I can tell you, man.
Yeah, I can tell you.
I'm not going to go back and forth with
someone that's a keyboard warrior that's
never going to meet anyone. It's a waste
of everyone's time.
So, if they can't come and be normal,
then [ __ ] off. Simple as that.
The guy's a [ __ ] house. He was supposed
to meet me. He didn't. That's it. I'm
not going to go back and forth with some
stranger online that's never going to
meet anyone, bro.
Yeah, they only put up their wins. They
only put up their wins. They will never
put up their losses.
Joseph does it as well.
They don't always win.
They don't always win, bro. They just
put up [ __ ] wins to make it seem like
they they win. Yeah,
that's what they do.
How the [ __ ] do you get ammo in this
[ __ ] game, bro? [ __ ]
Yeah, he's talking [ __ ] bro. He's
He's talking bollocks.
Yeah, he's talking absolute bollocks.
Yeah, they're only showing wins.
They're only showing wins, bro. That's
all they're doing.
Do you not understand the point of their
channel, bro? Well, I don't know about
the Smoky Bees cuz I don't got channel,
but this Joseph Rod, do you not
understand the point of the channel, bro?
I don't think you actually understand
the point of the channel.
I'm int I'm intelligent enough to figure
it out. I know what he's trying to do,
bro. I unsubed for him, but when I went
on it, I knew what he's trying to do.
He's show trying to show wins
only when he wins. But we all know that
he loses cuz I've gambled probably more
than him and people do not win like that, bro.
People don't win like that, trust me, on their machines.
So that's it. Yeah,
I was going to play a FOB T today, bro.
I was in a [ __ ] dirty dirty mood,
bro. A dirty vulgar mood. But I never. So
cuz I realize that's what this country
wants you to do. It wants to annoy you.
It wants to get under your last nerves.
It wants to put you in a bad mood. an
even worse mood. So, obviously, I
naturally didn't do it. So,
that's what it is. It's always a
negative when you're in a country like this, you know,
always put in a bad mood full of
[ __ ] bad weather, waiting around
for things, [ __ ] people, [ __ ]
women. Like, you're always Yeah.
I don't know, bro. I don't I don't I
don't go on his channel.
And to be honest, I'm not really
interested in gambling, bro.
Cuz how I am when I lose, people like me
shouldn't gamble, which is why I don't
The last time I gambled was a couple
weeks ago. I put 50 in the FBI and I
just took the 50 back and it was winding
me up and I didn't even lose any money.
So for me it's not uh
it's not ideal basically
to uh gamble. So that's why I don't.
>> Yeah. But I didn't I was I felt like
doing it earlier but I never.
It's just a cycle. That's all you are in
this country. You're just in a cycle,
bro. That's all you are.
Bad experiences with women, [ __ ]
people, then you want to gamble. It's
the same old [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? It is the same
old [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] that.
Not going to put up with this [ __ ]
anymore. So, yeah. What's that?
I had McDonald's. Yeah,
that's that. Yeah,
I don't even have any [ __ ] coke. Oh,
That's all right. I can go without it.
Not a problem.
Yeah, not a problem, bro.
Can't believe it's almost 2026.
Nope. I'm not doing nothing tomorrow,
bro. I'm chilling in bed.
I'm chilling in bed tomorrow, man.
Yeah, I'll be in bed tomorrow, bro. Yeah.
No, it's not. It's going to be the same
old just like it was this year. Just
like it was last year. Just like it was
the year before.
Nah, it's not going to be a good year.
It's just the same [ __ ] Different year.
What's what's what's going to be so
different about 2026?
The people don't change. The women don't
change. The waiting around for things
don't change. What's going to make it a
good year, bro?
What's going to make this year out of
all the other years so good? Nothing. One second.
ear is going to be the same.
My ear is going to be the same.
I hate this country, bro. I hate
England. I hate it. Yeah.
Yeah, sorry typed. Yeah. So, basically
what I'm saying is it's always going to
be the same
pretty much. It's been the same for many
years and it will be the same this year
as well. No, next year, sorry. Yeah.
But they say it happens.
They say it happens on Reddit.
But yeah, no football bets tomorrow. No
drinking tomorrow. I'm just going to be
a boring fart.
Just going to be bored. Bored out my head. Yay. Great. Yeah.
I can't believe these people on here are
still doing this. Like Terry and that,
they're still doing this.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Still being a low
life on YouTube. Little keyboard
warrior. It's a madness, bro. Who
thought these people would have grown up by now?
It's going to be busy tomorrow, bro. Absolutely rammed.
Going to be absolutely [ __ ] rammed.
Read to more people. No, I don't like
most of the people on here. They're just
[ __ ] idiots. self projectors.
Most of the people on here, there's a
few people that are all right, but nah.
Joseph, idiot. Smokeoky beat idiot. L J
idiot. They're just idiots.
They're just old wrinkly keyboard
warriors. It's [ __ ] weird as [ __ ]
I've been doing this for years now as
well, bro. You need to think, you know.
So yeah, I need to sort my sleeping
pattern out as well. Like I was saying,
can't make me [ __ ] print this thing
for no [ __ ] reason, huh? Mad.
Yeah, tomorrow will be rammed. You go
out drinking tomorrow.
I'd even not go out no New Year's Eve.
If I could get out and not going out New
Year's Eve, I'd do it.
I literally would do it.
But like I said, never hear the last of
it. So, cuz there's nothing left to
prove here. This is that's the point I'm
at now at this stage is there's nothing
left to prove. You've done it. You've
been there, done it. You've worn the
t-shirt. You know what women are like
and [ __ ] So it's like it's like what
are you really trying to gain, bro? They
are all the same despite what anyone
says. So it's like, bro, your your job
here is done. What I'm saying?
That's the way I see it, bro. It's done.
My [ __ ] work here is [ __ ] done, bro.
So yeah, it's no way anyone should live
though, really, is it? Yeah. So, yeah, that's that.
No, I just b idiots like Terry and
Smokey B because they're just idiots. I
don't want people to be Yes, man.
I just don't like stupid idiots on here
like [ __ ] Terry. The same [ __ ]
people that don't show up when you go to
their area. I just don't want to go back
and forth with keyboard warriors.
Yeah, I don't need a yes man. Grievy is
not a yes man. Me and Grevy disagrees on
most things. I just don't want idiots on here.
So that's that. Most of the people on
here were just idiots.
Well, Gregy doesn't agree with me with most things.
He doesn't get banned. We literally
disagree on 99% of things.
He's not banned. No, I ban Terry because
he's a [ __ ] idiot. He's a little keyboard warrior
that just wants to be an online keyboard
warrior for the rest of his life and I'm
not entertaining that. So that's that's that simple.
So yeah. No, no, no.
Joseph Far is not banned, I don't think.
Really? Well, I'll talk to myself then.
Well, then I'll just talk to myself.
That's fine, eh?
I'd rather talk to myself.
That's all right.
Not a problem at all.
I'm tired, man.
same repeating people
just clicked on large uh cuz it popped
up. Yep. Same repeating people, right?
Close that down.
But remember, these people are supposed
to be intelligent. These people are
supposed to have an high IQ.
Yeah, man. Nothing Nothing screams
having a high IQ than sitting on the
internet for [ __ ] over 10 years
repeating the same [ __ ] You tell him.
You tell him, man. You I reckon you
could get into Oxford Uni, mate, with
that, to be honest with you. And these
people try getting into Oxford Uni. I
think they'd manage it. Just tell them
that you sit online for 10 years
repeating the same [ __ ] every day.
That's an IQ, lads. That's an IQ.
[ __ ] idiots. Do they not get bored?
They've got they they've got to be
alcoholics, bro. They have got to be
alcoholics on here. They have to be to
sit for years and years and years from
the time they wake up to the time they
go to bed typing the same. They've got
to be alcoholics.
And they're disabled as well.
No, I don't. No, I don't. This is
literally the first time me being on
here for days. No. And that's Terry and
your band. Bye-bye.
Yeah, I'm just Yeah, I know. I'm just I
know I'm just on there just seeing who's on there.
>> I'm just seeing who if it's the same people
>> because they say they've got lives.
>> I'm not so [ __ ]
with yours. They haven't got that.
>> Yeah, I'm not going to be on it for long.
I don't sit on it all day every day like
them. You could literally be on there
two hours a day and have a life. They
don't have a life. They sit on it from
the time they wake up. They don't sit on
it for two hours
>> or one hour. >> Yeah.
>> What about first of January? >> What?
>> Would it be different than the first of January?
>> Well, they said they've got
But they say they've got IQ.
>> No, but no, I'm saying they said that
but they say they >> Yeah.
>> on YouTube. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. True, true. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I'm coming off in a bit anyways. I
won't be on long. Leave the door. Leave
Yeah, it's true.
>> Yeah. So what you're basically trying to
say is that it's the same repeating people.
>> It's the way Yeah, it's the way it's the
way Monty said it though, Mom. On on the
Yeah, it is the same people to be fair.
Yeah, it is the same repeating people to be fair.
Yeah, it is the same people to be honest. No live.
Yeah, it's the true. If they've uh if
they've got an IQ, why are they on here
repeating themselves every day? It's
true, is it?
It is the truth. It is the truth. Yeah.
think of the double standards UK asylum.
I'm to I'm 28 and I'm having my mom
advise me to come off of YouTube because
of what you people like on here. Yeah,
that's that's called being a good mom.
You would know that cuz you don't have a mom.
Yeah. I mean, yeah, you're 28 and your
mom's giving you advice to get off of
YouTube because it's the same people.
Yeah, that's a good mom in my opinion,
bro. That's uh that's a
Why don't Why Why don't you come on the
Hangouts and show us your face? Oh, you
can't do that cuz you're too ugly. Yeah,
exactly. And you're banned. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't agree with it though. Like
I actually want to speak up on this um
UK asylum because I think it's
absolutely disgusting to blame people
based on gender.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Just to
uh blame people just because of their
gender and not as individuals.
So like I was saying earlier, you say
that women are evil. Oh, you did sell.
Oh, you did sell. Women moan about men.
Oh, poor her. You are the lucky escape.
I think it needs to be uh it more needs
to be said about it
cuz I keep hearing on the news about
this misogyny and [ __ ] I've [ __ ]
heard it earlier and I heard it I heard
it earlier today and I heard it when I
woke up. We need to start talking about
the double standards
when it comes to their dating game.
We really do need to really start
talking about it cuz it isn't fair.
people should be judged individually and
not based on their gender
cuz that's called sexist and biased. So yeah.
yeah, cuz how could we take what they
say serious then?
But yeah, it is bad, bro. It is it is bad.
Yeah, they defend women just for being a
woman. It's mad.
I just find it mad how like you're not
allowed to basically um
say your struggles
without being called anything, without
being called a name. Right.
But they're allowed to moan about men
when they've not gone through nowhere
near as much [ __ ] as you have been through.
And then obviously the dismissing the
struggles as well. Like I had this woman
on Reddit yesterday, UK asylum. I showed
her about 10 screenshots about what
these women done. She weren't having it.
Uh she was making up stuff. Uh they
changed their mind, same excuses. These
these people, which is 85 90% of people,
will not have that a woman's [ __ ] you
over. They will not have any of it. even
if it is in black and white evidence.
Um, you know, they will not ever ever
ever admit it that a woman's [ __ ] you
over. Um, they will never or led you on
or played games or wherever the where
it's about the where it's about the
women taking accountability, they won't have it.
Um, they will not have any of it. Um,
even when it's shown in black and white
evidence. That's the problem.
Um, so yeah, this needs to be [ __ ]
talked about cuz it's disgusting.
It's like that that woman, right, I told
you about on Instagram that's been
seeing this guy for 3 weeks. All he said
to her was, "Oh, um, yeah, I don't I'm
not ready for a long-term relationship.
He didn't cheat on her. They weren't
married. He didn't abuse her. Why is she
getting sympathy?" when you whenever you
tell them your struggles, people call
you a [ __ ] incel. What the [ __ ] You
know what I'm saying? So,
yeah, it's uh
Yeah, it's bad, bro. Really bad.
Yeah, but she was still dismissing
struggles. She was still dismissing my struggles though. Um
yeah, she was still dismissing my struggles
basically, bro. Yeah, they do dismiss your struggles.
So why does she get sympathy but our
struggles don't get acknowledged? I
would love to have a debate about that. Yeah.
How can we be equal? They say that we're
equal, but how can we be equal when a
woman has been seeing someone for 3
weeks? He dumps her. He didn't even
ghost her. Like, he literally said, "I'm
not ready for long." He didn't even
ghost her. He didn't even do anything
that bad. Yeah. And she gets all this
sympathy. But yet, when I've shown all
of my experiences, it doesn't even get
acknowledged. It doesn't suit people.
People start playing dumb when they're
not. So, it's like, what the actual
[ __ ] bro? People
start playing dumb when they're not
dumb, trying to act like they don't understand it.
So why is it a woman that you your [ __ ]
don't even get acknowledged?
What the [ __ ]
You know, that's what made me give up.
That when you know the game's [ __ ] up
like that as well, bro. That's when you
know you you just give up. The game is
literally [ __ ] up. And like I said, if
I ever did meet anyone, I would just
ruin their life. So there's there's no
point in me even meeting anyone. That's
how strongly I feel, bro, you know,
about this thing. So yeah,
and yeah, it's just a sexist, biased
world we live in. That's that's it. You know,
they make up excuses. It's like they
they they have
how do I explain it, bro? It's hard to
explain, but yeah, they just act stupid.
Yeah, I wouldn't meet if I met the right
woman, I'd [ __ ] her over. Simple. I
would use her and then and and dump her
now. After all the [ __ ] they've done to
me over the [ __ ] years, bro. Yeah,
that's exactly what I would do. Or just
rob one. Something like that. I I
wouldn't stay with them. They're evil, bro.
I don't give a [ __ ] what anyone calls
me. At the end of the day, I don't care
what anyone calls me, bro. Because if
someone someone can sit there, bro, and
call you an incel, but it doesn't mean
anything because we know that if you was
a woman moaning about men, they'd feel
sorry for you. So, why would you take
anything that they say um serious when
they're clearly sexist, they're clearly
biased. So it's like and we've proven it
as well when a woman has moaned. So why
if they even call you these things? It's
like oh yeah whatever. It's like it's
not even anything bro because Yeah.
No, that annoyed me the other day though
when that woman and she's like, "Oh, I'm
sick of the dating game. I'm a bit
depressed. I'm lying in bed a bit
depressed." You're depressed when you're
actually going on dates and you're
actually seeing people and you're
depressed. What about me? What? What
about [ __ ] me? You know, what about
this [ __ ] here? My my struggles don't
even get [ __ ] acknowledged.
They just make up stuff.
And there's a and there's a big And
there's a big difference between um
uh sympathy and uh
stuff get um
things just being acknowledged. There's
a big difference, you know. So yeah,
mad. It is mad.
Yeah, I shouldn't have to though, bro.
There's, you know, I'm norm. It's like
what I told you, Ant-Man's girlfriend
saw a picture of me. I said this earlier
and she was like, "Oh, he's
good-looking. He's handsome." She
couldn't believe that. Like he was
saying, "Oh, no, he struggles." She
didn't believe him. And he was like,
"No, he does." She Yeah, she didn't believe
she didn't believe um that basically
I've been having having the same
problems as him.
So, um yeah.
No, she she didn't believe cuz you
wouldn't believe it. A lot of people
don't believe it, but yeah,
they're just [ __ ]
So, not only are they are they shallow,
they're actually racist. But no one
tells you that. No one on Reddit tells
you that they're racist. No one tells
you that, bro. So,
and that's that, lad. like it's um
it also tells tells you that they're
stuck up and racist, you know,
madness, bro. They're actually racist as well.
So, they're actually racist. That's what
they are. They are actually racist,
which um we don't, no one on Reddit will
tell you that. Oh, women being racist. No.
Um, they will not have a bad word said
about any woman,
these people, bro. Even when they're
shown what they've done as well. So,
they're actually racist,
which is uh Yeah,
that's mad, bro. That is actually mad. Oh god.
I have more of a chance than others.
Uh, do you remember the approaching
videos and the messages? Bro,
I can assure you that I don't have any
chance in this country.
Uh, maybe I'll I'll walk you down memory
lane with Goldilocks and the Free Bears.
Uh, do you remember the approaches?
Do you remember the messages?
Do you remember the not going on a date
since April? I don't think I have any
chance in this country, bro. I would be
delusional to think that um after all
the bad experiences I've had, there was
no chance. I mean, I would actually
rather be fat, bold, and ugly. I'd
rather be like in a wheelchair because
then there would be an excuse for it,
you know? Then at least if you was
disabled, then you could know why, you
know, you could oh well, you know, so
you could basically uh blame your um self.
So yeah, if you if you remember it, then
you wouldn't be telling me that I've got
more of a chance.
So if you if you remember it, why would
you be saying that I've got a chance
when I clearly don't
in this country anyways? No.
So, so you think that if I go out right
now or I go out tomorrow, it's going to
suddenly be different? Really, bro? Really?
I don't think so, bro.
Oh my [ __ ] Oh, my body's aching, bro.
You've got faith in me. Wow, bro.
really after all that? I don't think so, bro. Oh [ __ ]
my eyes, bro.
So, yeah, bro. There is there is
literally no hope. So, yeah.
Yeah, I'm not long woke up and I'm still tired, bro.
I need some coke, but I can't bother to go out.
Why do you think I'm mad, bro?
I might be mad, but at least I'm not a little copycat.
At least I don't say things to fit in
with the crowd.
Nah, that's never been me, bro. I've got
a bloody mind of my own. I need to copy the crowd.
I don't care what anyone's got to say
about me, bro.
I'll never have to copy someone.
Follow the crowd.
[ __ ] Cheryl Co. What a copycat with
no mind of your own. Imagine. Imagine
caring, right? What other [ __ ] people think copycat?
What's the point of copying? I just
don't understand why people would copy.
What do you get out of copying someone?
It's just [ __ ] mad. You know,
you said that she's attractive to fit in.
Sorry. It pops to mind sometimes. It's
just so it's so silly, you know,
when they all when they always when they
all used to call each other gay, Cory,
they used to call each other gay.
Fit in. You're gay. No, you're gay. No,
you're gay. They used to copy each other.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Copycat. Oh. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, they all had that NPC look in
their eyes today. Um, Corby, when I was out earlier,
they all look like [ __ ] Star Wars [ __ ] droids.
They all They're all [ __ ] NPCs. Non-playing characters, literally. Yeah. Never mind.
It's the same people doing the same [ __ ]
Money makes me die.
Oh, my back. Oh, my back is [ __ ]
Oh, he's got to pee.
I need to go.
Yeah. One second. Oh, [ __ ] That's crazy. Every time is
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
I'm going to put my my little t-shirt
on, I reckon.
This is getting quite cold. Oh gosh. Oh god.
Oh [ __ ] hell. Oh gosh.
Yeah, I think you're uh New Year's
resolution should be get to get off of
YouTube and get alive.
A lot of these people here Absolute freak.
Weirdos on there. Yeah. Um, Oh [ __ ]
Most people on it they are disabled.
Most people on here are disabled. Yeah. Mhm.
Cuz only a disabled person would do what
these people do every day for years.
They are disabled, bro.
Oh yeah, they are
they are bro disabled. Yeah, sorry bro.
But they are Yeah, they are disabled. disabled, bro. Proper disabled.
Been doing it for years as well, these people, bro.
Years. This account was made eight years ago.
These disabled people have been doing it
for years on here, bro. Yeah.
I'm [ __ ] exhausted, man. [ __ ] exhausted.
Might go down the pub.
Yeah, right, bro.
[ __ ] Going to do that. My [ __ ]
And my monkeyy's [ __ ] bro. Nah, brother.
He's going to see them more on Monday.
First thing, at least it's a Monday as
well it comes out, so
won't be seeing many couples and stuff. So
my eyes are [ __ ] hurting bro.
a massage. I think. [ __ ] B.
Where's this Joseph Ferrar?
He knows he won't he won't come on here
cuz he knows.
I say to him, I won't do nothing but I.
Huh? I won't do nothing. Will I? You
[ __ ] [ __ ] Let's [ __ ] meet today,
you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, [ __ ] idiots.
absolute idiots. And what makes it the
most saddest thing but funny is that
they don't even know you. Oh yeah, this
is the thing. They don't actually know you.
So you tell me what people with an IQ
come on here doing this every day for
years to people they don't even know.
They're [ __ ] idiots, man. They're actually idiots.
I [ __ ] got into this community
because of [ __ ] Timmy Eldridge.
Yeah, Timmy [ __ ] Eldridge. Jesus Christ.
It's going to be so busy as well. If I'm
out drinking out, it's too busy, bro.
We'll leave it till New Year's Eve and
then midFebruary. I think
probably Yeah, probably midFebruary,
March after that. I think
better to be honest.
Better that way. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that. [ __ ] that. [ __ ] that.
You got waxes right now. You won't even
be able to [ __ ] move, mate.
I remember when I was living thingy. I
went to the local pub around the I think
it was the first day I think I went. It
was [ __ ] rammed. Rammed. Yeah. I like
Yeah. So, old Bill rang me. Yeah. I told
him about my little evidence pack. Gez
would be proud of me.
He had a [ __ ] load of old Bill call
me. They said, "Oh yeah, watch this
guy's channel." I told him the channel. >> Yeah,
cuz obviously they got mixed up. I said,
"No, no, it's the virgin one."
The virgin. They want to know the virgin channel.
You nasty virgin.
you nasty skin virgin.
But yeah, these people in here, they
hate on people that they don't even know.
Like hate and jealousy onto people that
they don't even [ __ ] know, bro. And
I'm not even talking about just me. I'm
talking about there's only to a couple of people.
What is the point, bro? I don't get it.
What's the point? Why can't we all just play noise? Uh,
Well, why don't you just plain noise? Yeah.
Now these people don't know how to play
nice on here.
Oh, [ __ ] idiots.
Oh, I think I'll be going back to bed in a minute.
Oh gosh. Sleepy.
I must retired, man.
I might be able to uh yeah fix a
sleeping pattern this
Yeah. Anyone talking or what?
I've worked in bad city as well.
Yeah, I've worked in bad sea.
[ __ ] long it is, mate. Yeah,
I'm going off in a bit anyways. No one's joining.
Oh gosh. Oh gosh. Snuggle that. Nas.
Who believe the bloody nas calling me? [ __ ] hell.
Wow. So, she said that she's going to
therapy cuz she feels lonely.
What about how people feel that can't
even get a day?
How is it going? Uh, same old, same old. You
Oh, [ __ ] My legs are aching, bro. My body's aching.
Uh yeah, that's how it's going. Same
old, same old. Boring.
Just can't wait for Christmas to end. Hate Christmas. Yeah.
Yep. No sex life is very depressing.
Iva. Yeah, it's very depressing.
No sex life.
Having to be 28. Having to I give up
with it. Going out drinking, bro.
I giving up with it. Iva. I'm going out
New Year's Eve only cuz I planned it,
but I don't really want to cuz Yeah.
Women are all the same and this is just
toxic and I don't want toxic [ __ ] in my
life. Bro, I was in a bad mood earlier.
I felt like gambling, but I never.
I was in a really bad mood, bro.
Really, really bad mood.
Well, considering I'm not Muslim. No.
It's depressing as [ __ ] IVA, bro.
What's the solution?
I I should have to try again, bro. I'm
28 years of age. I shouldn't have to try again.
That's the way I see it, bro. I woke up
one day, looked myself up and down, and
think, what the [ __ ] I shouldn't have
to be trying again. No reason.
There's literally no reason for me to be trying again.
So, that's that.
Yeah. And I'm not Muslim.
I'm not half Turkish. I'm quarter
Turkish. And I'm not Muslim.
I'm not half Turkish. I never ever said
I was half Turkish. Yeah.
Yeah, same, bro. I'm doing it as well. I
shouldn't have to though. Iva, I
shouldn't have to. What is it? Why
in the freezer? Don't forget to take it
out in like 20 minutes. Then
don't leave it in there cuz you'll [ __ ] it up.
You going Thailand? What you living
there or [ __ ] What are you doing? I
you you living there or what? Uh oh gosh.
That's what I'm doing.
It's not even that. I had to go to three
different places earlier to print something, bro.
literally to print something.
Country is a joke, bro. The country is a [ __ ] joke.
And everyone just dismisses your
struggles, Iva, and every and they're
sexist and biased.
Oh, you got Thailand January 5th.
All right, Ben, you're going to laugh at
this. Yeah. So, Ant-Man's girlfriend in
Thailand saw my picture and she's like,
"Oh, he's handsome. He must uh he must
get women. he must get uh yeah he and uh
he was telling her obviously the
struggles and stuff like back like what
he had and she wouldn't have any of it.
She didn't believe she didn't believe him.
She didn't believe him then.
Says it all, bro. Says it all.
But I think you're right what you're
saying, Ben. I think they are racist.
And it's the beard and that. I think
they are just racist little [ __ ]
They're stuck up [ __ ] as it is, bro.
And that's bad enough.
They are definitely definitely racist.
100% they're racist.
And I'm not shaving my beard for them.
Are you [ __ ] mad? [ __ ] that. Why
would I get rid of my beard for them?
Think about it, bro. No way.
I would rather
literally go to another country than
have to shave my beard for anyone
because you shouldn't have to. You
shouldn't have to change yourself for anyone.
I I'd rather leave the country and be
accepted rather than have to change
myself. Do you get what I'm saying, bro?
You shouldn't have to change yourself for anyone.
Yeah. They're all [ __ ] here. They
all and and the people are [ __ ] as
well. It's not even just the women.
There's so many [ __ ] things about this
country. The people, the weather, the
women are [ __ ]
Yeah, it's [ __ ] It's [ __ ] bro.
And like I said, Ben, I shouldn't have
to be trying again. I shouldn't have to
be trying again, lad.
I was in a bad mood earlier, Ben. Like a
stinking dirty mood, bro.
Yeah, he lives there. He lives there. He
said he he'd rather work there, live
there, and work there
um than come here and get free money,
which is sad to think really.
But it's the women, it's the people, the
weather, the waiting around for things.
Ben, I've I've been hearing on the news
uh earlier and when I woke up not so
long ago about this misogyny [ __ ] and
I'm thinking, when are we going to start
talking about the double standards, Ben?
When are we going to start talking about
the double standards? Like I was saying
to all of these people, there was this
woman who said, "Oh yeah, I've been
seeing this guy for three weeks and he's
hit me with, "I'm not ready for a
relationship." Everyone felt sorry for
her. Everyone was giving her sympathy.
But when you've been dealing with [ __ ]
with women for years, no one even
acknowledges it, Ben. They all act stupid.
That's how you know the game's [ __ ]
up, bro. That's how you know the game's [ __ ] up.
I won't be drinking out to New Year's Eve.
Um, and then probably after that will
probably be March, midFeb, March to be
fair. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that, bro. Yeah,
I could literally go out right now if I
wanted to, but yeah. [ __ ] that, bro.
It's [ __ ] man. It is [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah, I know, bro. I know. I know.
But they need to start talking about the
double standards, bro.
Cuz no one seems to talk about the double standards.
They all seem to think women are angels
when they're not. They're [ __ ]
You'll get like 15% of people that are like unbiased
and not sexist. But 85% of people think
women are angels. And that's very scary,
bro. when 85% of the population I was
talking to is to Izzy's boyfriend or
ex-boyfriend, sorry, yesterday and he
weren't having none of it. He weren't
having none of it, bro. I was telling
him what she's done. He weren't having
it for toffee, mate. You can show these
people black and white evidence, Ben,
and they still will be like, "Nah,
they're idiots. They're absolute [ __ ]
Yeah, [ __ ] bro. A lot of people are leaving.
The only tire that I've got here is Laney, obviously.
So, if I leave and if I leave and live
there, then obviously no more Laney.
And then Laney could die.
It's not good, is it, bro?
Yeah. I don't know about living over
there. I don't know what I'm going to do.
cuz this is not normal at 28. It's all
right when you're 24, 25, Ben. You know,
you go out twice a week or when I used
to go out twice a week, but I shouldn't
have to keep doing this. I shouldn't
have to still be doing this
cuz obviously when you're 28, you don't
go out as much.
So why am I going to keep going out and
trying when I've already tried?
Got the money to do it. I have the
punish to do it, bro. It's been this way
for a very long time.
When I was 24, 25, I used to go out like
twice a week. It was Thursday, Saturday.
It never used to be Friday, Saturday cuz
the hangover. I had to have a day's rest.
I used to be at it, at it, at it. Then
26, I think it was like once a week.
Then when I was almost 27, it was like
every two, three weeks. Now it's like, bro, hardly.
I shouldn't have to keep trying, bro.
This is what I'm trying to say.
It's [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. I'm not 24,
25 anymore, mate.
You know, [ __ ] hell. Should be [ __ ] settled, you know?
And it's not money. I've got money. I've
got like I'm saying, I've got money. I [ __ ]
I've got money [ __ ]
it ain't about that at all.
So my life's not [ __ ] when it comes to
money and it's just normal. But like
it's just this whole thing is it the
whole thing is [ __ ] up. You know
what? Go out today have the same thing
again. No, bro. I'm not doing it again,
bro. You [ __ ] off.
I even had a 45 year old playing games
with me, Ben, last week.
I just wish they would just turn around
and say, "Oh, I don't like you cuz
you're beard or I don't like you because
you're this race." I would actually
because they don't realize that when
they're lying, we know they're lying. We
know it's [ __ ] We know they're all
full of [ __ ]
like they and and to me that is
underestimating my intelligence
when you're when you're lying because
you think I'm stupid.
You know what I'm saying? It's hard to explain.
Bro, I just Bro, I was talking to this 45year-old
on Instagram. Yeah, Ben. Um, and
don't forget I'm better than her. I've
got a higher SMV than her. Like you just
said, she can't give you babies if you
wanted babies, which I don't want
babies. So, realistically, a 28-year-old
is above her because of her age, no
matter what anyone says. And, bro, I
told her like, "Oh, we should meet
that." I wasn't going to do it anyways.
And then she was using distance as an
excuse. I was like, "Oh, really now?"
Oh, is that the excuse? 100 mile
distance. Usually it's the age gap. And
then I said like the in the most polite
way like we know that you're lying. I
could be your next door neighbor and
you'd come out with another excuse and
then she just blocked me.
Strange. They've always got some excuse, bro.
Cuz they're [ __ ] racist or just [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, they're [ __ ] idiots, bro.
But yeah, I think it's what you said,
Ben. I agree with that. I think
I definitely do agree with that.
Weird though. It is weird. A normal
trimmed beard. That shouldn't stop someone
going with someone because of a [ __ ] beard.
But yeah, I think it is that, bro.
Maybe I'll shave my beard one day and go
out and try.
But then but then if that then but then
if that would happen, I would just I
would just use them and dump them if
they got with me. Yeah. When I had no
beard, I would just I would just use
them and then dump them for being so shallow.
So I'd get the last laugh. So I wouldn't
even say up because I'm thinking what
obviously if you've got like a bin Laden
beard and you don't groom and that then
that's different but a groomed beard.
It's strange, isn't it?
My mommy used to call me cat eyes Ben
cuz I got green eyes.
But yeah, 45 year old um
Thailand will be finished though in 10
years, Ben. In 10 years, Thailand will
be finished as well.
Yeah, it's not as good as it was uh
10 years ago, Ant-Man was saying.
So, it will be finished in uh
oh yeah, 10 years.
to therapy because she's feeling lonely, right?
Then how how does it how does she think men feel?
It's mad. It is madness. It is madness.
They're so selfish, bro.
I wonder if Ed's going to go live today.
I watch his live streams. I watch Ed.
Even he deals with this [ __ ]
and he's [ __ ] fully white looking and [ __ ] famous. Yeah.
No, no, no.
Yeah, I'm going anyways. Yeah, see here they are.