[Laughter]
Oh yeah, it was a [ __ ] good day.
[ __ ] the football bet lost.
Yeah, but you win some, you lose some.
Eh, win some, lose
some. So they say, they
say, don't put too much on it. I had a
[ __ ] lovely meal as well. I'm [ __ ]
knackered. I was having some chicken
balls. I was thinking a lot whilst I was
eating the chicken balls, thinking that
we can share it,
man. And some you lose some. So
this man's like, "Oh, well, when you bet
on the football, yeah, you shouldn't
expect to win." Well, with my bets, you
you would expect to win. because it's
only a double both teams to score. Think
about it. They're not like three, four,
both score, no draw. Cuz obviously you
don't expect them to win. They don't really
win. That's [ __ ] [ __ ] Good.
Anyways, jaming kills a vibe. I noticed
that any sort of vibe that you got going on [ __ ]
it repeating it as
well. Sick of it,
man. I'm sleepy after that meal, mate.
What did that
Yeah. Yeah. Be on here as well. Stop self
projecting. Stop self projecting.
Yeah, that's why you're you're on my
live talking to me, bro. This is Bro, honestly,
man, this really is just such a downy
community. It is such a downy community,
bro. I'm gone tomorrow 100%, man. Leave
these little losers to it. I'm not
reacting to these clowns no more. I
swear down, bro. I'm not reacting to
these little clowns. I let them do
whatever they want to do,
man. I'm not reacting to these clowns. yourself projecting
clowns. Basement dwellers. What I call
them little basement
dwellers. Basement dwellers.
Eye after that meal.
We had a Chinese. It was good. Yeah. Good. Very
good. Bye-bye. You just hold on a
minute. You just said I even got a
carpet. Oh my [ __ ] god.
These people are such
dies. No, hold on. You just said No, I
didn't tell her. It was a good date, by
the way. We had a
Chinese. Um, she said, uh, we mean
again, we had a Chinese and a wine. I
only had one wine, come back, had a
shower, and I'm [ __ ] tired, bro. Oh,
yeah. My football bet lost, by the way,
£40. I just needed Fleetwood to score
and they never I'm done with this
gambling [ __ ] bro. I was just saying to
Antman, I'm sick of having the same
conversation every time. And he's like,
"Oh, like with your football bets, you
don't expect them to win." Well, I
expect mine to win. She's here for 3
months. I expect mine to win because
it's a double both teams to score. So, I
actually expect mine to win. He does
three double. He does three. He does
four teams, both score, no draw. Of
course, that's hardly going to win. But
my one should be winning. I'm done with
it anyways. I'm buying
an I'm going to buy an electric bike as
well, man. I'm going to take up a new
hobby. This is boring as [ __ ] this
gambling, bro. It's so boring. Like, I
won't get I won't get mad. Yeah. Or
nothing, but it's just boring. And it's
boring having the same conversation
about it every time as well. It's so
boring. I'm [ __ ] booking a holiday
next week. [ __ ] it.
Yeah. 40. But £40 is nothing to me. You
are mug. You are a loser. Go
self-reflect on another
channel. Yeah. Well, it is longterm
because I'll go to
America. Oh, I'll go to where she is in
America when she goes back. She's She's
here. She's here for
work. Yeah, bro. I'm actually done with
it now. Anyways, the gambling
lad. I'm done with it.
It honestly is so boring
now. It honestly is
so It honestly is so boring. Is
it And it is boring. It is boring. I'm
going to buy an electric bike. It's
boring. It's boring. I'm going to buy an
electric bike and pic next next
week. It's [ __ ] boring, bro.
Yeah, I need to start the
gym. Yeah. Well, at least I found
somebody that's going to do it.
E, she lives in California. She's from California,
so yeah, it's a lot longer than [ __ ]
Boston, mate. But be it, is
it? Yeah. Not for a few months when she
goes back. So, we'll keep meeting and
when she goes back, I'll just go over and see
her. Mate, you've just said, Hold on a
minute. You just said that I come on
YouTube cuz I got no one else to talk
to. You've just been blocked on four
different accounts. You see how these
people do nothing but
self-reflect, Gary? You see how these
people do nothing but self-reflect? You
just said, "I come on YouTube cuz I got
no one else to talk to." You're You just
got blocked on four different accounts.
You [ __ ] loser. Do you know what?
Yeah, Gary. I might actually post some
content videos. Like, that's the only
thing, bro. I'm not going live anymore.
Yeah. Yeah. For a long time, bro. I'm
just going to post content videos, I reckon.
Maybe my new electric bikes or
something. Leave these little losers to
themselves, to be honest with you.
Yeah. Yep. Leave these little losers to
themselves. I know. He's such a virgin,
isn't it? Well, if he wasn't autistic
and he wasn't ugly, he might he might be
able to lose his virginity. You know
what I mean, Gary? You know what I mean,
Gary? Buddy, he's such a virgin. I call
him the YouTube virgin. The biggest
going. He's such a virgin. You need to go get
laid and go off for YouTube. That's what
you need to do. [ __ ]
virgin. You don't know what to do.
Why? But yeah, I'm done with the gambling
anyways. Yeah, you're right. I can't handle
it. Why does he obsess over Why does he
me? Um, do you want me to tell you the truth?
He obsesses over me because I'm better
looking than him. I've got more money
than him. I've got more family than him.
And I've had more women than him. And
because he can't accept it, he'd rather
just sit on YouTube all day and hate. I
know it's weird, bro. But anyways, I'm
done with the live stream today after
today, bro. I'm putting some content
[ __ ] on my
channel. That's why he does it. He's a little loser.
I'm younger than him and and I've done
better than than
him. Wouldn't it be crazy if you fell in
love and ended up going to America for
for a new
life? Two. Imagine bumping into each
other after three, four or four
years. Who will I who will I be bumping
into after three or four
years? What what are you talking about?
The person lives in England. They're
from California. I met her earlier. We
had a nice Chinese meal. Now I'm
stuffed. Oh, [ __ ] me. Do you know what,
Gary? I'm actually starting to pre
prefer Chinese than Indian, you know,
cuz with Chinese, they do that succulent
beef. With the Indian, they don't do
beef. They only do lamb and chicken. I
like lamb and chicken, but my favorite is
beef. So that's what's good about the
Chinese, but they're [ __ ] tight
bastards. They're tight bastards. I'll
tell you that for nothing, mate. I had
chicken balls. I had chicken
balls. Benefit waster. Stop talking
about yourself. It's not good for your mental health,
man. It's not good for your mental health.
I'm I'm I'm going to train to be a
psychologist. These people really are
sad, man. These little basement
dwellers, they have nothing but calling
people for a living. Yeah. I had chicken
I had chicken balls and uh a beef
curry. But they're so I remember Yeah.
the other uh a few it was like two weeks
ago. Yeah. I went to the Chinese and
they only accept cash. Yeah. Bear in
mind I've been to this place a h 100
times. Yeah. I don't live too far from
it and they only accept cash, right? And
I said, "Oh, none of the cash machines
are working." And I said, "Oh, I'll come
tomorrow and give you the money cuz I'm
going to order again tomorrow." She
wasn't having none of it. I was like,
"What the fuck?" Like, I've been going
to these places, this place for years.
Yeah. I was like, "What am I going to
do? Run away with
£7 and we'll never come back to your
shop. Like, what the fuck?" So, I had to
walk like [ __ ] 25 minutes to a
[ __ ] cash point. It was a madness,
bro. Who's really going to run away with
£7 worth of [ __ ] and never come back? That's [ __ ]
mad. They're [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. They
must think people are going to rob them
or something. It was over £7 as well.
So, um I think it was a beef chain. It's
either beef made or it was like literally seven
quid and I literally had to go and find another cash
point. It's madness, bro. Like, what the
[ __ ] Why would I run away with £7 and
never come back when this is my favorite Chinese?
Crazy. Yeah. Well, I would be good at I
would be a good uh psychologist because
it's like I know what these like I know
why these people do what they do on here
every day. They're fat. They're
unattractive. They got nothing going for
themselves. They got no money. So, they
they uh No, we went for Chinese and had
a wine. We had a little kiss. She might
have not seen me before. She has seen me
before. I've been going to that Chinese.
I've been going to that Chinese for
ages. I used to travel to go to that
Chinese. She has seen me before. It's
the same woman every time. So what? You
think I'm going to run away with
£7. It's She has seen me before because
it's been with the same It's the It's
been the same person for years. I even
know what her name is, you know, like.
And what? So, so you've been coming to
this place for all this time, right? And
literally all the ATMs were out of
service. So, what am I going to do? Run
away with £7 [ __ ] 50 and never come
back to the shop?
What? No, this was another time, you
idiot. And you know what? Yeah, it's a
shame because that's the best Chinese.
Like, after that, like I didn't ever
want to give them my money ever again. I
didn't want to give them my money ever
again, but I feel like that is literally
the best Chinese. There's no other good
Chinese around the
area. So, but no, we're talking about a
different time. Yeah, we
kissed. We're seeing each other again,
LJ. Ah, I'm going to make a baby. A baby from California,
LJ, what a lovely night.
That's going to be a lovely sight. Lord
Jay, I'm buying an electric bike, by the
way. Plus, I have a
wank. No, I'm going to be seeing this
19year-old again soon as
well. 19year-old again
soon. Yeah. I'm going to buy electric
bike, by the way. I'm buying an electric
bike to get around quicker. RJ.
Yeah. To get
quicker. You're not getting no woman
around. Stop these football bets,
bro. It's coming around tonight. Maybe
tonight. Maybe tomorrow.
Well, yeah. Grievy, do you not? No.
Greavvesy, do you not understand how this
works? You, me. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. Listen, Grezy, do
you not know how this [ __ ] works, buddy?
Right. You have different options. Yeah.
So you take it slow with one person and
before you're official, you go with
another woman and have sex with another
woman. That's the way it works. You have
one slag and one person that you take it
slow with. That's what happens. Then
when you become official with that
person, then obviously you stay with
them. That's the way it works. Listen,
say you've got two different women. Say
you go out on a Saturday and you get two
different women, right? Yeah. and you
get two different women, right? Listen,
as an example, and then they both meet
you. You go slow with one of them and
then the other one you go fast with and
you see which one works better. You
know, like, well, you you know, how else
are you how else are you going to get
sex? That's what I'm going to be using
this 19year-old for as my
[ __ ] until I find someone else until I
find someone else that's going to give
me sex. Like hopefully when I meet this American
again, you know, we we'll [ __ ] But it
might take three, four dates. So that's
the way it goes, bro. Or or you can use
escorts. One of the two. One you go fast
with, one you go slow
with. That's the way it
works. But to be fair, I don't really
get a big sex drive anymore like I used
to, man. I don't really care about it. I just want
to Bro, like I said, I'm booking. I'm
booking a holiday next week anyways.
So, got the old passport back and I can
afford an electric
bike. They're not out there. I might buy
my friends one to be
honest cuz this gambling greasy is no good,
lad. It's annoying as [ __ ] It's
annoying as [ __ ] man. You might as well
just get a different
hobby. I I was saying this to Ant-Man as well, man.
Like, it's no good,
man. Is it Greasy? It's no
good. They always come back in the
end, don't they? Mhm. Yeah. Yeah,
man. So, what do you want me to do anyways, Greasy? You
know, you seem to know all of these
things, Greasy, but in reality, you
don't really know anything, do you?
Because who's the one that's actually
been with women
myself? Oh, it's almost April, so it's
about time you got these dating apps, is it, Grezy? Oh my
god, this guy has a date today as
well. Um, no. But sometimes I think of
like, right, he's going to be really
jealous cuz I've met this woman. Like
whenever I meet a new woman, sometimes I
think, "Oh, like if this virgin found
out about it, like he'd get jealous and
and ruin it because he's such a
virgin." Sometimes I think of that though,
Gary, you know, cuz of Morgan, cuz of
Izzy, cuz of uh that one from
Manchester because he's jealous that
he's too ugly and autistic to get
anything himself, which is why he's still a
virgin. You understand, lad? Yeah. You understand? That's it. [ __ ]
virgin. I still got that video, by the
way. Me getting a
[ __ ] Still got that
video. Still got that video, lads.
Bye-bye. Crying. What was I crying
about? Yeah, [ __ ] off. You're boring, mate. You're
boring. Stop boring
me. It's all It's the same spastics every day.
Like I've actually noticed that like Tim
Slots I've just gone on John West's um
thing, right? And it's the same
people from even like years ago, bro.
I'm on it here. Look, it's literally the
same spastics every
day. They got to be old, in it, these
people. It's going good. I went on a
date. I'm back now. I'm [ __ ]
knacking. I'm [ __ ] exhausted.
Yeah, I am tired, man. That [ __ ]
Chinese KO'ed me, lad.
Yeah. Oh, I'm so sleepy.
They're all freaks, bro. They're all
obsessed with me, man. They're all
freaks. Virgin, Virgin Legs, Jamie.
They're all [ __ ] They're all weirdos,
man. They're all obsessed with me, bro.
That's the norm, man. You know, that's
what they're like,
lad. I got KO'ed by that [ __ ]
Chinese, bro. I feel like I've took
about a million [ __ ] colonos.
They're all just, bro. They're all obsessed with
me. Spoke to my sister earlier. Spoke to
her yesterday as
well. Oh, it's right, bro.
It want to get an ebike. I want to go to
the gym and I want to get an ebike. Yeah.
Cuz he's a
coward. Because he's a Cuz he's a
coward, lad. He's a keyboard
warrior. He's a coward. He's a keyboard
warrior. He will never meet anyone. Yeah. Mhm.
Hey, wild super. I don't like that copy
sauce, bro. I had a bad experience when I was
um when I was um young with it, lad.
Uh, mate, you've made How many accounts
have you made? You [ __ ] [ __ ] Get
alive. Get alive, you little [ __ ]
Get off of
YouTube. [ __ ] basement
dweller. Did you see how jealous they
was the other day? Um, Gabby, when I was
in the pub having a Guinness, they were
trying to get me kicked out of the pub. How
sad do you have to be to try and get
somebody kicked out of a [ __ ]
pub? That's mad, isn't
it? Like, how sad do you actually have
to be, bro, to actually do that? It's crazy, isn't
it? Yeah. I just commented on this
thing. A wild s
appears. A wild s appears. Wild
simp. Yeah, they've been doing it for
years. Yeah, it's the same free force
bastics. They've been doing it for
years. Your skin, your this, your even
though it's they are all of these
things. Yeah, it's the same. They've
been doing it for years.
There's an account, I don't know if it's
still on it, called Now Then
Cheese. Well, well, tough [ __ ] I'm
going to go near many women because I
can get women unlike you. You [ __ ]
ugly bastard. Anyways, [ __ ] off you
little nons. You little weirdo. [ __ ] off
you virgin. Anyways,
um yeah, what was I saying?
Um yeah, it is the same people, bro.
There there's an account called uh now
cheese and he used to troll
um he used to troll uh
uh Ant-Man about six years ago and if
you look around it you'll still see that
[ __ ] on YouTube.
Think about it, bro. Look at in all of
them six years, right? Ant-Man, as an
example, right? He was eating cold
beans. He had not a pot to piss in. Six
years down the line, he's going Thailand
three times a year. He's moving to
Thailand. He's got money. He's living
the life. And now then, Cheese is still
on YouTube trolling. Think about it,
bro. These people have got nothing in
their lives. I'm sure you've seen that
account now then. Cheese. 6 years later,
six, seven years later, and he's still
on there. Back before I even had facial
um before I even had facial hair, you
know, they're just losers, bro. That's all they are. Yeah.
Like I said, it's a it's a set it's the
same three to four people, fat little
losers that never made it in life that
are too old to change and they've all um
they've all stumbled across a community
to project their life onto. Like I mean
it'd be if they said it to people's
faces then I mean fair enough, you know,
like then it'll be like oh whatever, cool.
Yeah, lad. Like, and they've stumbled
across a community where they can
self-reflect without any consequences
cuz that's all they are. They're little
self-reflectors. Yeah. Even this even
the Izzy times. Your skin. Your skin.
Your skin. But the thing is is that the
only people that are skin the the only
people that are skin are these
people. They're the ones that bring it
up, you know. Like,
yeah, I am in shape. I'm not
fat. I I already am in shape. I'm
actually pretty fit. I just don't have big muscles.
Yeah, I am in shape. I just don't have
big muscles. I need to get my muscles
back. I am in
shape. I have loads of things to do,
man. I need to get an electric bike. I
can just go back to the gym. I'm going
to keep seeing this woman. I'm going to
[ __ ] off to Thailand for 2 weeks as
well. I got my passport back.
So, probably try out some new restaurants, you
know, quit gambling. E. Yeah, I was
ripped then. I'm not ripped [Music]
anymore. Yeah, I know. It's expensive,
bro. It I know. I know. I know.
Yeah, bro. But it's so hard to get
t-bone steak now. Like, the butchers
stopped doing it. My favorite used to be
the t-bone steak, but they're [ __ ]
hard to get now,
man. I can gain muscle without even
working out. But obviously, I'm going to
go to the gym
anyways. I really want to have a baby
with this American woman. So, Maybe I
could immigrate to
America. I would do it. I would do it,
bro. If I could immigrate to another
country. I don't know about a third
world country. I would do it. I would genuinely do
it cuz I don't speak to Laneany anymore. So, I
mean, I'd start my own life, bro. And
it's not because of these little
weasels. I just don't I speak to my
sister and that. See my sister, but I
just don't speak to. I'd start a new
life, bro. I would. be like, "Fuck it.
Done in it. I'm I'm out of
here." You know, I I generally
would I would have nothing to lose, bro. You know, self projection
block. I know. He's so and and and have
you seen the state of his face as well?
He's so [ __ ]
ugly. He's such an ugly bastard. I'm
surprised he keeps going on about my
nose, mate. He is Giny Germany one ugly
[ __ ] Like I'm I'm not even saying
that yet. It's a troll or it it's his
whole face. He's ugly. He's
lanky. He's just one ugly bastard. Like
it's it's a madness, bro. how someone
that ugly can come on YouTube showing
their face. I wouldn't even show my face
if I look like that. If I was as ugly as
that, bro. I swear I wouldn't show my face, you know? Yeah. Yeah,
lad. He thinks Yeah, Gabby, if I got
arrested, he would take me to
court. He's such an idiot. Yeah. that he
thinks that if I put up posters, right,
and let's just say for the for example
the police come out, he genuinely thinks
that he's going to get me in prison. He
generally thinks that's the way the law
works when no. All the police have got
to do is look on your channel and see
what you've been doing over the years
and then you'll get NFA again. That's
literally what would
happen. You can't go to court, right, as
a victim. Yeah. Yet you're the one
that's on YouTube every day harassing
someone. It doesn't work. It literally
would never go to court
ever. It literally would never. It's six
of one half a dozen literally. And if
you get done for it, they're getting
done for it as well. That's literally
not the way the world works. He really has no
clue. He really, really, really, really
has no clue about life. And then he
thinks the the [ __ ] that he does on
YouTube is legal. It's not legal. No,
it's completely completely not
legal. You know, just because the police
don't have resources to do anything
about it doesn't mean what you do is
legal. And actually, you should get it right. You
you Yeah, it's boring now. Big nose.
Yeah, you're borrowing now, man. Come up
with some new insults. Anyways, stop
talking about your ugly self. And
another thing is right is that uh uh yeah
like and then the only reason the police
come the last time is cuz he played on
his mental health. I've never told the
police I was [ __ ] disabled. You told
them I was [ __ ]
disabled. So like nothing would ever
happen because what he does right is oh
this guy's put up posters about me. I'm
autistic. I live in a shared home. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. And then
what happens is the police listen, the
police come for you, then the police go
down your phone and see what he's been
doing, and then they just NFA you and
that's always the way it's going to
be, you know, because obviously the
police don't know because he deletes
most of his stuff, but I save
everything. Like, why would you even
waste the police's time like
that? Why don't you actually get a life
and get a hobby and actually go and lose your virginity?
and actually get laid for once in your
life and you would have to do this
weirdo creepy ass [ __ ] on YouTube. It's
weird, bro. It really is
weird. It is weird. Very weird.
Yeah, she is disabled. Of course, she
is. Don't let him know about this
[ __ ] woman from California. [ __ ]
Gary. Don't [ __ ] let him find out
about this [ __ ] woman. This little Virgin
Mary. [ __ ] know them. Find out who she is,
mate. Jeez. Yeah, it's scary, bro. It's
scary. But you'll be dealing with it
anyways cuz I won't be on here for a
while unless I'm post I'm posting
content. So, they'll be psychologically
[ __ ] their own lives up and wasting
their life posting about
me. You know, that's what they do,
Dad. They're the ones that are psychologically
[ __ ] You You only have to react some
of the time. These people are obsessed
all of the time. So, they're the ones
that are psychologically being tormented by your
existence, you know? So, yeah. No one
else. They're tormenting themselves.
Yeah, I know. He's been doing it for
years. He's a little
virgin. Yeah, of course he would, man.
That's what he does with every woman
because he's still a virgin and he hates
the fact that other people can get laid and he
can't. Yeah, bro. I
know. Cuz he's a jealous little
virgin. Look what he done with Sig and
look what he done with Well, he didn't
actually speak to Morgan. He made that
Morgan account up himself. But uh
yeah. Yeah. He's obsessed. He needs to go get
laid. Seriously, I've been saying it for
ages. He literally needs to go get laid.
Get off of YouTube. Lose his virginity.
Be a happier
person. Peter Belly's advice always
works. Yeah, he did last time. Yeah, cuz
what he does No, no. What he does,
Gabby. Listen, he went to the police.
Yeah. Cuz the police wouldn't normally
come out for that. And he's like, "Oh,
I'm autistic. I'm diagnosed autistic.
This guy is trying to kill me." No, no,
no, no, no. And obviously the police
don't know about his channel, right? So
what they do is they come for you. I was
only there for like 1 hour and then
obviously I I explained that like the
guy's got a channel on me. He won't
leave me alone. He keeps stalking me.
Bear in mind the police don't know any
of this [ __ ] because he's the he doesn't
show the police his channel. and where
I've saved all of these things. I said
to him like cuz they had other phone. I
was like go on the phone. I'll tell you
the pin if you want. Well, there's no
pin on the phone. Go down it and you'll
see everything he's been doing. Soon soon NFA
me, you know, because the police don't
know this stuff until they actually look
at it. You see, he's trying to be a
victim because he's a narcissist.
Meanwhile, he is harassing people on
YouTube every day that he's jealous of.
It's a He's a weirdo. It's autism, bro. It is
autism. It is autism. Bad jealousy and bad
autism. It stinks, bro. It really does stink, you
know. It's sad, isn't it?
He's such a [ __ ] little virgin. I'm
sick of talking about it as well, bro.
I'm gone after this anyways for a little
while. I don't even like wasting my time
or epic like even talking about these
people, bro. They're not even worth the
time of day. They're not even worth
[ __ ] on if there was no toilet.
Like, I don't like talking about them,
bro. Let's move on now. Anyways, different
subject. Uh, Monty doesn't speak to me
anymore. I wonder what Monty's problem
really is. I wonder what his problem
is. Trying to play me for get he him
getting his kids strip searched. [ __ ] off.
Yeah, he's weird,
man. He doesn't let me in, but he lets
John West in. It's a madness, isn't it?
Sean wishes he could shag that Morgan in
it, Gary. Oh, he's so jealous. Why does
he get jealous when other people meet
women as well? I'm trying to understand
it. He says that he's got this
girlfriend that he [ __ ] right? So why
does he get jealous when you meet new
women? Doesn't add up, does it?
You're a minute. Is it because you're
actually getting laid and he can't get
laid because the flaccid penis don't go in?
Yeah. Doesn't make sense, does
it? Be nice to understand. E.
Yeah, but Chase is a coward,
lad. He gets triggered when you meet new
women, but yet he's got this girlfriend
that he never [ __ ] because he doesn't
have time to [ __ ] her. It's crazy, isn't
it? Yeah. Crazy, ain't [Music]
it? He would love to have kissed Morgan.
He would have loved to [ __ ] her. He
would have loved to suck her tits.
That's where the jealousy comes from.
You see, it's a horrible, horrible
disease. Like, even my mom knows it's
jealousy. Like, even my mom knows it's
jealousy and we don't even talk anymore.
You know, she'll be the first one to
tell you this [ __ ] you know?
Like, oh yeah, it's St. Patrick's Day in
two days, isn't it? [ __ ] Oh
yeah. Yeah. He mate, listen. He No, not
even a date. He could only dream of
speaking to somebody in real life and
actually getting their
number, you know. He could only dream
about actually approaching somebody and
actually getting their number, let alone
going on a [ __ ] date. [ __ ] virgin.
Yeah. Yeah, lad.
Yeah, it's a madness, bro. What's this
[ __ ] percent on now?
That must suck though, bro. It being 30
in still virgin. I couldn't imagine it,
mate. Could not imagine it. Especially
the way my sex drive used to be.
Oh, it's the madness, bro. [Music]
What is that?
You don't want to [ __ ] die a virgin. D
virgin. Where's Timmy anyways?
Tim Slots for years, bro. I've seen that
Tim Slots account for years. Yeah.
Remember Gary, if you don't find Sher Co attractive, you're gay. [ __ ]
hell. If you don't find You can't deny
that Sher Co is attractive or you're
gay. You can't
deny Cheryl Car was
attractive or you are gay.
Yeah, that's what he
says. That's what he says. Um,
Gary, he picked up the trend.
He picked up a
trend. Exactly. Did he did? He did. He
did. Cuz it's all it's all to the name.
You see, years ago, there was a trend
with that Cheryl Cole thing. There used
to be one with Beyonce as well. If you
don't like Beyonce, you're gay. It's
just a trend. And because people in
college used to think he was gay, he
started to and he doesn't like the fact
that he's gay, he um was going on about
Chev Co because obviously people
wouldn't think he was he thought that
people wouldn't think he was gay if he
kept going on about
her. [ __ ] even Morgan's better than
her. I'd pick [ __ ] Morgan over
[ __ ] Cheryl Car any [ __ ] day.
[ __ ] hell. There's nothing special. I
don't see what's special about
her. He says that makes you gay, but
I've had more women than him. How can I be
gay? You know what I mean, bro?
Crazy. How can I be gay, bro, when I've
had more women than
him? I don't see what is so special
about her. I mean, if I was seven
Guinnesses in, yeah, I probably would
[ __ ] her if I was seven Guinnesses in,
but she's nowhere near as attractive as
people make her out to
be. She is nowhere near attractive as
people make her out to be, you know.
Bro, to be honest with you, I don't even
think I would cold approach
her. To be honest with you, I don't even
think I would cold approach her. To be
fair, I I actually don't think I would.
No, I wouldn't cold approach
her. I wouldn't cold approach her.
That bit, bro. Hold on.
If you don't like shower or car, you're
gay. What a little
copycat. Yeah, we've only ever done it
raw. She ain't even got no tits either,
so she wouldn't even be for me even if
she was attractive.
Does he understand that people have got different
types? He literally only said that Sher
Cole was attractive just to fit in.
That's [ __ ] sad, man. What a loser
having to say things to fit in.
having to say things to fit in. It's
mad. Yeah, she does do it wrong. She
only ever does it
wrong. Just like Stig does it raw. Stig
done it raw as well.
Yeah, Sig done it
raw. She was going to [ __ ] at first,
Sig. Then she just went on top of me. Remember?
Yeah. Yeah, I remember
that was a crazy cat.
You know what Antman
said? He couldn't
know. He probably misses how my dick
tastes as well. To be
fair, you probably
uh This is how it [Music] tastes.
Yeah. Yeah. Came back. They always come back in
it. Or is this Peter Betty's money
either? Yeah, I got a Mother's Day uh
thing to send to someone, but I might
not send it to Lady. I might not send it
to Laney. I might send it to my other
mama, Gary. A mama that will appreciate it.
Gary, send it to another mama. Gary.
Yeah. No, I'm not going to keep paying for
it. I'll never forget that, bro. She was
like, I'm not going to get with you.
She was like, "I'm not going to get with
you until you stop gambling." I said,
"Nah, like if you try to touch me, I'm
I'm going to go away and that until you
change." And I said, "Oh, well, what if
I give you money?" She's like, "I'm not
a prostitute, but how much? I'll never
forget it." Well, I said, "How much do
you want?" And I had £50 on the side,
and she just sucked my dick and I came
in her mouth. So, that was a good deal.
£50 [ __ ] without a condom. And I came
in her mouth. Deal.
My god, look at this self projector. I
replied to him. Yeah, he said skin tick,
disabled tick, mont a tick, socially
awkward tick, incel tick, gambling
problem tick, jobless tick. I said, stop
talking about yourself like that. It's
not good for your mental health. I'm not
skinn, not disabled, not a ma, not
socially awkward, not an incel. Yeah, I
probably gamble more than I should do,
but I never am skinned and I always pay
my bills and I don't need a job cuz I
get enough money. Stop talking about
yourself. It's no good for the mental
health. Hey bro, that that actually is a
good uh Listen, why don't you come on
here and actually um and actually talk
and actually talk so we can hear what
you people sound
like coming from coming from a base
coming from a basement. Do I
Yeah, that's definitely definitely
self-p projectioning. Look, these these
people can't even go out to the
pub. Socially awkward mint disabled.
That's all of these people. They
self-reflect. They literally talk about their own
lives. They literally are the biggest
skint monters on YouTube. Listen, bro.
Let me let me tell you this, right?
Every single time LJ goes live, they're
there. We never see these people with
friends. We never see these people out
and about. We never see these people on
holiday. They put no content on their
channel. They literally are talking about
themselves. They literally self-project.
Like these people get about they
probably get about three400 pound a
month benefits, right? And then as soon
as they get their benefits, they gamble
it. Do you not understand, Gary? That
these people think that everybody has
the same life as them. Skin, fat, ugly,
anxiety. They think people have the same
life as them. So that's why they call
you what they are because they think
that you are the same as
them. Think of it. They're talking about
people being skinned. They're talking
about people being jobless. Yet
literally they're sat on YouTube all day
and there's literally no content on their
channel. You know what I'm saying? Like
think of it right these people coming
here right calling me trying to call me
a m. The same people that won't dare show their
face due to how ugly they are. They
won't dare show their face because they
know they're ugly. That's why they come
and talk about other people every
day because they're sad little [ __ ]
ugly mongos that ain't got nothing in
their lives. They're losers, bro.
Losers. And it's not even that. It's
like even when you block a million
accounts, they'll just make other
accounts. You know what I'm saying? It's actually a
madness. They literally talk about
themselves for a living. That's that's that's their
job. Stop talking about
yourself. Let me see if I can get that. Stop
talking. One second.
Like these people sit on YouTube every
day putting themselves down, calling
themselves skinn, calling themselves
disabled, calling themselves a ma,
calling themselves socially awkward.
Like, why would you come on YouTube
every day putting yourself down? Like I
would say that everyone's got [ __ ]
mental health problems as it is, but why
would you want to keep putting yourself
down and talking about yourself like
that? It's not nice. And you do talk
about yourselves because you've been on
here for years and you can't get off of
YouTube. And if you was better, you
would do better. But you you don't. It's
literally not nice to talk about
yourself like that.
These are the same people that are in
their late 30s, 40s that can't even
leave their house. They literally have
nothing but a
keyboard and talking about themselves
for a living. Skin, skin, skin, skin,
skin. It's because these people are
skin. They only know their own lives,
their own life that they're living. The
skin life on benefits. Do you not
understand that? These people only know
their own life that they live. You know
what I'm saying? They go on like they
know other people's life, but they don't
know other people's lives. They're
jobless fat retards that can't get off
YouTube. Literally, that's literally what they
are. You know, sad sad with their life
on benefits. That's why they tell people
to get a job because they don't have a
job. They need to tell themselves to get
a job because they've never had a job. They're too
disabled. That's why they they're on
here. You understand? That's that's why
these people are actually on
here. It's sad, bro. It actually is
sad, you know.
Yeah. And that's it, bro. And that's really
it. These people are the all time
monters. You understand, bro? Like these
people are the alltime mters. Look at
this account right here. Skimp disabled
m social incel. They are literally
describing their whole life. They are
literally talking about their own
existence which is why they're on
YouTube every day. It's literally all
them. They literally right sit on
benefits waiting for that £300 every
month. No life. Can't leave the house.
All ugly which is why none of these
people can show their faces. Right?
They're all monters which is why they
can't show their face. That's where the
jealousy comes from. This is why they
sit on here every day doing what they do
because they're sad that they're
sadistic, fat, and skin. Do you not
understand? This is why they're on
YouTube every day. Think of it. When do
you ever go a whole day without seeing
these people? Never. Because they're all
fat, ugly, mon, and skin. It's
themselves that they're talking about.
It's all them. Listen, if they put their
cameras on, bro, I would prove it. I
would prove it. They can't get off of
YouTube because they're skint fat and
ugly. Why do you think they're so
they're obsessed with skint people?
Because it's the life they're living.
They're living skin. They have nothing
to show. Think of how many times Yeah.
You show these people money and they can
never show you nothing and they with
jealousy. They have nothing. They literally have
nothing. Literally, they're skinned,
fat, ugly munters, and they're hopeless
because they're in their 40s. They're
too late to change. They've stumbled
across a community where they can
self-reflect their lives onto other
people, their misery onto other people.
Do you not understand? That's the
science behind these fat, ugly people
that can't get off of YouTube. Like,
bro, I would literally, bro, pay any
money right now if these people can show
their face, but they can't because
they're too ugly. That's why they call
other people money is because they're
ugly. Ugly, fat, and skin. That's what
they That's why they keep talking about
people every day because it's themselves
that they're referring to. That's why I
say it's not good to talk about yourself
like that. It's no good for your mental
health. calling yourself socially
awkward, calling yourself skint, calling
yourself jobless. It's not nice to talk
about yourself like that. And you are
talking about yourself like that because
you don't know anyone else's life. You
only know your own
life. It's not nice to put yourself down
like that. It really, really
isn't. You know, you are socially
awkward. You are skinned. You're fat,
ugly, and you can't even leave your
house. Stop talking about your ugly
self. You know what I'm saying? Stop
talking about your fat skinned bun selves.
Yeah. Stop talking about your m self
because all of these people, right, that
tried to call you a ma, you're better
looking than them. You're literally
better looking than him. That's that's
the most funniest thing about these
people, you know? Would you ever go a
day and never see these people on YouTube?
These people can't even go to a pub and
and afford a drink. That's how sad their
lives are. That's why they have to try
to get people chucked out of a pub.
They're basement dwellers. This is what
I've said all along. They are literally
basement dwellers. They've got nothing
in their life. Literally have nothing in
their life. Nothing. Not even a plastic
pot is why they're on YouTube every day.
They're [ __ ] basement dwellers. They
literally are. They literally basement
dwellers, bro. I swear down they're basement
dwellers. They are basement
dwellers. It's sad. It's a sad state of
affair. Never had anxiety in my life.
Never been socially awkward. Never been
skinn. You are literally talking about
your own life. You're talking about your
own selves. that the life that you're living.
Yeah. Talking about their own lives that they're living. Yeah. Yeah,
man. One second. You know, some back at