Yeah, bro. One sec. Some more people join. [snorts]
One sec, brother. Yeah.
I literally asked you yesterday,
not yesterday, earlier
that I would come and meet you so you
can say anything to my face and you're
still talking [ __ ] You've you've
literally proved that you're about
nothing and you will do nothing and
you're still talking [ __ ] on other people's channel.
Like, bro, what is it with are these
people generally disabled or something,
bro? Like, honestly, like, are they are
they actually disabled or am I making
this [ __ ] up?
Am I making it up or something, bro? Like, [ __ ]
Yeah, sorry about that. I was just
listening to But yeah, Joseph Ferrar,
listen you little fat [ __ ] little low
life. Stop talking [ __ ] about people on
L Js when you're never going to say
anything to anyone's face. I literally
gave you the option of me traveling up
there and it is confirmed that you will
say and do absolutely nothing to
anyone's face. Like you already backed
down earlier. So why do you keep coming
on here talking [ __ ] You are the sad
bastard. You're the one that's got a
[ __ ] YouTube channel having to post
up only fake wins and you can all you
can do is talk [ __ ] behind the keyboard,
but you'll never say anything to
anyone's face. You sad bi you sado
biased little nons lover. That's all I
want to call you to your face. I
literally said that's all I want to do
is travel to you and call you a dirty
little nons fat ugly lover to your face
and you will not meet anyone. You will
not any you will not meet anyone. So I
don't understand why you keep coming on
here telling people that they won't do
nothing when it's confirmed that you'll
do nothing. when people have said that
they will come up and tell you about
yourself to your fat nons ugly face and
you will not meet anyone fatty though so
I don't know why you keep doing this
you [ __ ] fat ugly biased nons lover
little low life and I want to say it to
your face you know I don't need to go
but on anyone's channel to say this I
want to say it to your face but you will
not meet me I'm not like you don't have
to go on people's [ __ ] channel. And
the reason I went on it is because I was
on my mom's phone. I thought, let me
just go on my mom's phone and it come
up. It wasn't even on my phone. And
there you are again talking [ __ ] What
presents have you bought? Let's see the
presents that you have bought. You fat,
sad, bastard little keyboard warrior.
You know, you can't even [ __ ] talk on
a panel. You're that scared. You're that
anxietyridden. You can't even talk on a
panel. You know, I've literally said I
will come and tell you about yourself to
your fat nonsloving face. I told you
this earlier, the people that was on it
and you said, "No, no, no. I won't meet
you. Oh, it's embarrassing." But yet you
keep talking [ __ ] and talking [ __ ] and
talking [ __ ] I've slagged off your ugly
misses. I've called you a biased
nonslover. I've said that I will come
and say it to your face and you don't
want to know. What the [ __ ]
[ __ ] clown. You're an absolute clown.
You're all the same on here, man. Red
Star. All the same fat, ugly, skinned,
low-life people. You just the same. All
the same on here, bro. You just said
that you don't want to meet anyone. So
why are you on someone's channel talking [ __ ]
You will never ever say anything to
anyone's face. You're scared of your own
voice. You're scared of talking. You are a loser.
You're you're you're clearly obsessed.
You don't talk about anything else. I've
catch I've caught you talking [ __ ]
behind my back. So, let's let's do it
face to face. Come on. I don't know what
the problem is. Why are you so scared?
You're so confident people will do
nothing. So, let's see it then. [ __ ]
[ __ ] Absolute [ __ ] [ __ ]
I'm I swear most people in this
community are just crippled.
Oh, you think the whole world Yeah, I do
think the whole world's against me.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Let's go with what
you're saying. Yeah. What you going to
do about it, [ __ ] What are you going
to do about it? What you going to do
about it? Nothing. Just shut the [ __ ] up.
I call you a [ __ ] biased dirty
nonslover to your [ __ ] face and walk
off. [ __ ] [ __ ] Absolute [ __ ]
Yeah, it's going good. I've just caught
this Joseph Ferrar talking [ __ ] again. I
literally said to him earlier, Dusty,
that I don't mind traveling up to the
Northeast again and I will say
everything I want to say to your face
cuz you've got a lot to say online. It's
This is what I said to my mom earlier.
These people have got a lot of money to
say on uh I lost £200 earlier on
roulette, but they've got a lot of [ __ ]
to say behind a keyboard.
Dusty, they've got a lot of [ __ ] to say
behind a keyboard. You know, I've caught
you on L J's. And the reason I was on L
JS is because I was on my mom's phone. I
woke up, my phone was dead. I had some
macaroni cheese. And then again, you're
still talking [ __ ]
You're still talking [ __ ] you sad, fat,
ugly bastard. When you have backed down
again and you're still talking [ __ ] fatty,
he's another bomb. He will not meet
anyone. I said to him earlier, bro, I
will come to your area. And he's, oh,
I'm not going to beat you. I'm not going
to beat you. But then the fat ugly [ __ ]
is talking [ __ ] again. This is what I'm
saying. Then the fat ugly nons lover
nons legs lover is talking [ __ ] again.
I'm eating my food, bro. I'm sat there
eating my food, bro. Yeah, literally
eating my food. I've gone on my mom's
phone and this guy is talking [ __ ]
again. You know, let's see your
presents. Don't worry about what
presents I got for people and what what
about the presentation you've got. You
fat dirty sinking nonsubber that will do
nothing. And I've proven it because you
will not even meet anyone. Even when
they've said they're going to come, I'm
not going to meet you. I'm not going to
Why is it with these people on here,
bro? Yeah. Sat there obsessed for years
and years and years, but will never meet
anyone. You bro, don't you? It just
doesn't make sense.
I I won't even fight. I'll just call him
a dirty, stinky little non-sleg bias
[ __ ] to his face and walk off. That's
all I want to do, you know? And see what
you've got to say face to face. And if
you ain't got anything, I'll walk away.
Keyboard warriors, bro. Absolute
keyboard warriors. That's all they
[ __ ] are on here.
Don't [ __ ] come on my chat talking
and I'm seeing you talk [ __ ] on L Js
when you're not going to meet anyone.
You're never going to meet anyone.
[ __ ] [ __ ] Loser. Disabled.
Uglyfingered. Ugly misses. I can say
anything and everything, but you're
never going to meet me. You know,
stick to being a shitty uh uh a low IQ
troll. Do you know what? You're so bad
that you can't even troll anyone. Like,
I I know what his channel's about. He's
so They're so disabled, Dusty. I figured
them out. I know what his channel's about.
Proper proper disabled. Melt with
nothing. Showing a fake pension. showing
a fake pension that and even if it
wasn't real, bro, which it isn't. He
can't even touch it. He's [ __ ]
absolute skin. He's It's He's like Red
Star, bro. I come on here earlier. Yeah.
And I said that I lost 200, bro. And
everyone was laughing. I was like, "Bro,
200 does nothing to me." And I said it
about like 500 times. I like, "Bro, 200
is nothing to me. It is literally
nothing." And they still continue to
laugh even though I told them multiple
times that it means nothing to me
because they're [ __ ] skint.
That's their monthly money, bro. £200 is
their monthly money. It was It's kind of
funny, bro. You know,
you know, you're never going to meet
anyone. You said that you're never going
to meet anyone, but yet you're still
talking [ __ ] behind people's back. What
the [ __ ] bro? Make it make sense. It's almost 2026.
fat little [ __ ] bias lover. Not legs
I'll tell you how he's a virgin to his
face and I tell you how you're a biased
nonch lover to your face and then I walk
off. How about that one? [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] absolute [ __ ] Another one. Yeah, man.
If someone's got something to say, just
say it on this channel. They're not
blocked. just say it on this channel and
then I will offer to meet you. There's
no point not doing that and then doing
it behind someone's back and you're
never going to meet anyone.
Yes, I said the country is designed to
annoy me. And what's your problem? If
you want to discuss it further, I I said
that I will travel to you, but you will
not meet me. You said that you will not
meet me before I've even ended. So, if
you've got a problem with some of the
stuff that I say, I'd rather you do it
on here and to my face. I think it's
better that way to be honest.
[ __ ] dirty. He's another bomb, bro.
He's another little low life. I susted
him from ages, bro. Dusty. I susted this
low life from ages when he started being
biased with the whole nonslegs thing and
the Lord J thing. I susted it, bro. I
sussed it. I sussed this weirdo a long time ago
cuz they're not smart. They're [ __ ]
They're stupid. You know what I mean, bro?
But yeah, if you're not if you want to
actually meet and say something to
someone's face, then yeah, I I don't
mind coming up there again. I've said this.
Yes, the country is literally designed
to annoy you. It literally is. That's
why a lot of people move to Thailand.
Have you got anything to say? Are you
going to come and say to my fa Are you
going to let me come up there and you're
going to say to my face? Are you just
another nods legs? Are you Are you just
another Red Star? Are you just another
little keyboard war with no life
that pretends that he works? Come on
now, bro. Like, what is it? Come on.
[ __ ] absolute [ __ ] on this
community, bro. Absolute [ __ ]
Lucky I didn't do that football bet,
bro. I would have lost. Lucky I didn't do it.
So yeah, bro. Like yeah, if you're not
going to let someone travel to you and
you can say like, but yeah, that the
reason about this 200 pound is because
these, like I said, these people are
skin red star. Like they got nothing to
do all day. They wake up at 700 in the
morning waiting for their little monthly
200 uh their little monthly, what's it
£300 a month? They ain't got nothing.
They're skin. They ain't got nothing on here, bro.
sad, fat, ugly little low lives. Same
with that Provident Loans. Same with a
lot of these people on here.
Same with that Joseph Ferrar.
They're all the same on here, bro.
And that's that. Call me a [ __ ] sad
bastard. [ __ ] come and say it to my
[ __ ] face, you [ __ ] The same thing
as [ __ ] Laney basically told these
people ages ago. If you've got anything
to say, say it to someone's face
or don't say it at all. Especially
[ __ ] on another person's [ __ ] channel.
You're not blocked. This is what I'm
saying. They're not blocked on this
channel. So what? You know,
proper proper disabled community. This
is, bro, really are disabled. It is a
country designed to annoy you.
It literally is a country designed to
annoy you. That's why people leave.
That's why people go to Asia. Yes, it is
a country designed to annoy you. The
women, the people, the system, they're
waiting around for things. Yeah, I said
that. Yeah. And if you've got anything
to say about it, you fat ugly [ __ ] Come
on here. Let's talk and let's arrange a
face to face meet up,
you know? Are you gonna just keep
talking [ __ ] Show fake gambling wins
because we we all know that people do
not win um that much on, you know, on
Fiesel and you're just going to do this
the whole of 2026.
You fat loser. You can't even talk.
You're that you're so [ __ ] disabled.
I've never known it where somebody can't
even come on a panel and talk.
That is mad because at least Bomb used
to talk. You know, Smokey B, I think he
even spoke. This fat [ __ ] is so disabled
that he can't even talk on a panel, bro.
He can't even talk on a panel cuz he's
an absolute [ __ ] You know,
mad. Absolutely mad, bro.
[ __ ] little [ __ ]
And that's that basically. Yeah.
What the [ __ ] bro? Like, seriously.
I don't want to know. Yeah,
I was thinking about ear uh when I woke
up, Dusty, it's kind of mad. You can't
even win money anymore.
It's like what we were saying unless you
do like the both teams to score like you
can't even win money.
That's mad. Like do you remember [ __ ]
like bro 10 years ago you used to
actually be able to win like where the
industry was better you know 20p
roulette and that in the book is you
can't even you can't even win bro.
That's mad. Like, well, unless you do
the football or the horses or something,
you can't even win money. What the [ __ ] bro?
The industry's finished.
Unless you bet on the football.
That's mad, bro. That is actually mad.
That is really That is mad.
Yeah, that online roulette is definitely definitely rigged.
No. 5 8 11 10 when Peter Belly's on that
table, Dusty. You better believe that.
This [ __ ] Joseph Farra. Hey bro, I
lost 200 pound on roulette earlier.
Steven Howard, these people are
laughing. And I've said multiple times,
200 pound is nothing to me. And then
this Joseph Farah come on here earlier
yet. And I said, "If you've got anything
to say, I don't mind traveling up to you
and you can say it to my face cuz I've
got a lot to say to your face." Little
[ __ ] says that he's not going to
meet me. More excuses. More excuses.
More excuses. I woke up. Laneie cooked
me a macaroni cheese. Yeah, she cooked
me a macaroni cheese. I'm on Laney's
phone. I'm on LJ's live stream. This fat
plum Jo is talking [ __ ] again even
though he said that he is not going to meet anyone.
He's literally said that he is not going
to meet anyone. And I've literally said,
I do not mind traveling to the northeast
and he still doesn't want to meet anyone
and say to his face.
But yet you go on L J's channel, Steven
Howard, and this [ __ ] is talking [ __ ]
again. This flat, this fat plump is
talking [ __ ] again. You know,
sad bastard. You got a lots to say
behind the keyboard and I've got a lot I
want to say to your face, but you won't
meet me. This is what I mean with these
people, bro. You know
what presents have you bought, you
little [ __ ] Show everyone on
YouTube what presents you've bought for
people, you sad fat bastard.
You know what I mean, bro? They're
[ __ ] idiots on here, man. Proper
idiots. Steven Howard.
like you're not blocked on this channel.
So why are you slagging people off on
other channels? Slag me off on here to
me and I will come and tell you about
yourself to your face. You're a dirty
little non-slig lover. Dirty little
nonslaving [ __ ] that will do nothing. Simple.
[ __ ] absolute [ __ ]
Yeah, it was online roulette Stephen
Howard. It was earlier, bro. You can't
win money now, bro. You really can't. I
was going to do a football bet, but I
never. Lucky I didn't. It lost. So
yeah, it's very hard to win money now, bro. Industry's finished.
You can't even win money now, bro.
Unless you [ __ ] win on the football.
That's actually mad, bro. The industry
used to be decent
many years back. Many, many years back,
bro. It used to be decent now. You can't
win. [ __ ] all.
You can't win. [ __ ] all, lad.
You're best off just not even doing it.
That's what I mean, bro. Oh, you're right.
What? Legs are not aching me.
Yeah, that's what I was going to do. The same thing.
Yeah. Well, yeah, I was going to do the
same thing, Kitty. like hidden minister
and slow. Yeah, it's exactly the same. I
was going to put 200 pound on it.
Uh but then I was going to do Enfield
and Slow. That would have won, but the
first one was
uh the first one I was going to do Kitty
Minister and Slow to be fair. I was
going to put 200 pound on it. It was
either going to be 200 on that or 200
pound on roulette and I chose that. >> [snorts] >> Yay.
It's not good, bro.
200 pound returned 554. So, I think it
was worth it, you know. But yeah,
roulette. It just kept going on any
number I didn't have. Steven Howard,
that loser number seeker.
It was Spin Dog. Yeah.
Yeah, it was Spin Dog.
I lost 270
70 pound feet. And the reason these
people laugh at it, Stephen Howard, is
you've got to understand that these
people in this community are [ __ ]
skint. They've got nothing. So that's
why 200 is a lot of money to these
people. So they found it funny because
they don't have £200 to their name
because they're skimp, you see.
Yeah. Where these people are [ __ ]
skint [ __ ] skin flints.
Um, they seem to find it funny. Even
Even though I told them multiple times,
£200 is nothing to me, they they still
had it. So, yeah.
Yeah, it was a £17 fee. I know it's a [ __ ] joke.
I withdrew 112, but I was going to just
take that, but um,
yeah, it would have took a while to
process. Yeah, £17 fee.
So yeah, it's all right anyways, bro.
Don't worry, I didn't go back on it. I
won't. I do it like every three or four months.
So yeah, you can't even win money now, bro.
You can't even win [ __ ] money now. Imagine that.
You can't even win money. Imagine that, bro. Imagine that.
Can't even win [ __ ] money.
>> Yeah, literally it's a ripoff, bro. £217.
Oh [ __ ] bro. Miss, miss, miss, miss,
miss miss. I don't think you can win
money anymore, Steven Howard. Can you? Nah,
you can't win money now, bro.
I don't think so, bro.
Them days are over. Yep.
I won't be doing it again, bro. I won't
be doing it again.
Yeah, I won't be doing it again, bro.
Don't worry about that.
I'm not even addicted. I This is my
first time in three or four months.
Yeah, I started talking about kids and
everything, bro. That's why I don't do it anymore.
Yeah, that's why I don't do it anymore.
This was the first time in months, bro.
It's [ __ ] so rigged. It's unbelievable.
Yeah. So, you can't win money anymore,
bro. You can't win money anymore.
I don't think so. No.
Nah, you can't win money anymore, bro. Another
[ __ ] thing. It's a country designed to
annoy you. This country is designed to
annoy you and get under your laugh nerves. Women, people,
and this is another thing to Joseph.
You're saying about how I think the
world is against me. Okay, let me answer
it like this. You will get random ass
people trying to start problems on
trains in nightclubs. So explain that
one you [ __ ] Explain that one you
[ __ ] How you will have random ass people right
try to start a problem
because they're [ __ ] It is a
[ __ ] country full of [ __ ]
I was on the train uh yesterday. I was
on the train two days ago. I was waiting
for someone to start on me, bro. I was
really like waiting, bro. I was waiting
that whole day for someone to start so I
could just do something, bro.
So I could seriously hurt someone badly,
bro. That's That's what I was Yeah. I
hate this country. I hate being out of
this country. It's a [ __ ] hole.
So explain that one then, [ __ ]
[ __ ] fat loser. He's another nonsleg.
They're all the same. These people, bro.
Red star, nonslegs. Those are They're
all the same. These people are all the
same, bro. Fat, ugly, no life, no money,
obsession on YouTube, will never meet
anyone. They're all the same, these
people on here, bro. All the same on here.
Nothing to live for. They'll be the same
in 2026. They'll be the same in 2027 and
they'll be the same in 2028. They got
nothing to live for, bro. This is their
life on here. This is their life on YouTube.
I smash his [ __ ] face in. Ugly [ __ ]
[ __ ] dirty little virgin. Same thing
with that Joseph Ferrar. I'll [ __ ] him
up as well. [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] disabled [ __ ] Yeah.
I'm so happy I don't go out anymore,
though. Steven Howard, I'm so happy.
So happy I don't go out anymore.
It's a good thing, bro.
No more bad experiences. Yay.
Well, the damn new thing was [ __ ] but you know,
yeah, I don't know when I'm doing it,
bro. I can't be asked.
I just want this year to end.
What do you think of Joseph Far even
now? He's a fat nons lover. I want to
call him a dirty I want to call him a
nons lover to his face, bro. A little nonsle lover.
I want to say it to his face. Yeah.
I need to buy this Franklin game on the 26th.
He ain't about nothing, mate. And he
tries to tell other people that they'll
do nothing when I literally said I would
travel to him, but he will not meet me.
He literally said he will not meet me.
So, but so he wants to just be a
keyboard warrior. So, he's another nonslegs.
He's another non-slar
nonsle. They're all the same on here.
Sat on here from 7:00 in the morning to
the time they go bed. It's these
people's lives. Steven Howard.
And yeah, I do think the world the
world's against me. And what are you
going to do about it? And what are you Yeah.
How did you know about How did you start
getting vibes from this nonslover?
I got it. I got it when he started uh
defending Non's legs and he was trying
to get people to gamble and he's clearly
showing win only wins. Oh, by the way,
Stephen Howard, I gambled today cuz I
wanted to gamble cuz I was looking at
the football. I was like, "Oh, it's the
last weekend till Christmas. Oh, I want
to gamble." These people didn't
encourage me to gamble. These little
clowns don't [ __ ] with my head. These
little clowns don't bother me in any
way. They're the ones that have got to
sit on here from the time they wake up
to the time they go to bed being
obsessed. Not me, bro. Not me. And
believe it or not, I'm hardly on it
compared to these people.
I knew it when he started defuh
defending nods legs. Amen.
What's up, bro? >> [sighs]
>> Yeah. Huh? Oh.
Yeah, they are, bro. Definitely.
[ __ ] you up my [ __ ] ass, bro again, dirty [ __ ]
They are all the same, bro. Amen.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, this might be this Instagram thing.
Yeah. This must be this Instagram thing
that they were talking about last year.
Was it last summer? Yeah, it was. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
No, this sh
definitely this sh Yeah.
Oh, nothing, bro. I saw you.
I want to know why these [ __ ] are up my ass again.
Never mind. But yeah, that Joseph
Ferraria is a nonslav.
Not going to you're not going to [ __ ]
start [ __ ] messaging me, mate. Yeah.
Simple as that.
No one, bro.
It's these police officers playing two
sides of a coin again. Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Why do these come up my ass again?
I do one.
Look, Terry's doing this again. I've
been out shopping my misses. Something
you will never have. You don't have a
miss. And she lost £200. £200 is nothing
to me. I don't know how many times I've
said to these people, £200 means
nothing. No matter how many times you
tell these people,
no matter how many times you tell these
people, bro, £200 means nothing to me.
It is something to you. Go and buy your
shitty trainers. 200 is nothing to me.
It's only to you. Look at your traders,
you stupid little [ __ ] See, this is
what I mean. They never stop. This is
what I mean on here. These jealous
people never stop.
and he keeps making accounts. These
people have got nothing
Bro, £200 is nothing to me.
Another [ __ ] Christmas, brother. 200 is
nothing to me. 200 means nothing. I'm
not skintike Terry.
I don't wear shitty trainers.
brother, £200 is nothing to me. It means
nothing because I'm not skint like these
people. That's the only reason why they
keep talking about 200 is because
they're skint. They're sat there with
nothing every day. That's why they think
£200 is a lot of money.
You know, they think £200 a lot of money.
It's because these people ain't got no
money. That's why £200 is a lot of money
to them. It's nothing to me.
My week's better knowing that you're a
[ __ ] with shitty trainers and that
you're a virgin and I went to your area
and you didn't turn up.
You know what I mean, bro?
My area my mine's better. My, you know,
my weekend's good knowing that you got
shitty trainers, you're a [ __ ] and
you got no girlfriend. [laughter]
My weekend's even better. You little nons lover.
My life's better knowing that you're a
skin trapped with shitty traders and I
went to your area. You didn't do anything.
Yeah. You know what I mean?
I didn't run out of my area, mate. When
somebody come to my area, you did.
You know what I'm saying? I mean,
my whole life's been better knowing that
you've got no traders and I ran out of
your area. I ran out of your area.
You're I run you out of your area, you little trap.
And he's making new accounts. These
people are not about it. You know what I mean?
These people Look, he made a new account
as well, bro. The [ __ ] [ __ ] with
the shitty traders who ran away from me
made a new account.
They're all the same, bro. These people
in here are all the same.
They are literally all the same, bro.
They are literally all the [ __ ] same.
They are literally all the same.
[ __ ] Fanny with shitty trainers.
Little [ __ ] fanny. You remember when
he was This is what I mean. It's always
the same with these people. You made a
new account as well. You You [ __ ]
fanny. You [ __ ] fanny with terrible
trainers. And they will never meet you.
They're all the same on here, bro. This
is what I mean. They are literally all
the same on here.
This is what I mean.
All the same on here, bro. Little low
lives. And they've been doing it for
years. They've been doing it for years.
200 means nothing. I'm not skint like
you, Terry. I can afford a new pair of
trainers. You know what I mean? I'm not
skint like you, [ __ ] with shitty
trainers. You little [ __ ] You got run
out of your area. I'm not a skinned
[ __ ] like you. Think outside the box.
200 pound means nothing. To me,
it means something to you. You can't
even afford a new pair of trainers. You
little fanny. Bro, he's made a new
account as well. He's such a loser. This
is what I mean with these people on
here. They're all losers. They're all
[ __ ] losers, bro.
They are [ __ ] absolute losers.
They are absolute [ __ ] losers.
5 hours. He's a [ __ ] loser. And they
say that they're not jealous of people,
bro. These people, they say that they're
not jealous of people, yet they make
fake accounts to try to [ __ ] with people.
It's mad, isn't it, bro? It's actually mad.
Yeah, they got no life on here, bro. 5
hours. What a low life. What an absolute
low life. He made another account,
Steven Howard, 5 hours ago. What a low
life. What a loser.
These people on here are [ __ ] losers.
But then again, it's getting that it's
almost Christmas, bro. In a couple of
days, these people are very lonely, very
skint. So, it's to be expected, bro.
They're sat there on YouTube. No money,
no life, no family. So, it's to be
expected with these people.
It's to be expected with these people, bro.
No family, no life, no Christmas,
no money. So, it's to be expected with
these people, bro.
It's Christmas in a couple of days.
They're lonely. No money, no family. So,
of course, they're going to be like this.
They're sat there living their worst
life. So, of course they're going to be
on here, bro. Of course they're going to do this.
Yeah, they definitely. But don't don't
forget, I'm younger and better looking
than them, bro. I'm younger and better
looking than these people. So, it's to
be expected. These people are going to
be on YouTube Christmas. No life, no
future, no money, no family. All the
knows what they are. [ __ ]
No All right. It Jesus.
Are you going to be happy? They're not
interested when I'm reporting these people.
You don't [ __ ] No. No. No. No. No.
[ __ ] you threatening, bro. Yeah, bro.
about you strongly advise. Are you mad?
You know what I mean? Are you [ __ ] mad?
Yeah, they're all little low lives. Tv
made another account. Tubby made another
account five hours ago. What a loser.
They're all losers on here, bro. All
absolute losers on here. I won't be on
here tomorrow, by the way, bro.
Yeah, I won't be on here tomorrow. So, yeah.
One second. I'm going to come back. I'm
going to come back. Yeah.
Yeah, sorry about that, bro.
Yeah, bro. They're definitely [ __ ]
They're definitely definitely gay on here, bro.
This better not be over this Instagram
thing cuz I'm going to go absolutely
[ __ ] mad. I am.
Yeah, I'm going to go [ __ ] mad. I am
I'm going to go absolutely up the
[ __ ] wall if this is over this Instagram thing. Yeah.
Sorry, bro. Yeah.
[ __ ] message my phone [ __ ]
threatening me 5 days before Christmas.
You silly little [ __ ] You silly dirty
little [ __ ] You know what I mean?
Yeah. Sorry about this, Stephen Howard, bro. Yeah.
Like you strongly advise you don't
[ __ ] threaten me with your bully and
shitty little tactics. You dirty little
pig. You know what I mean? [ __ ]
That Joseph is a [ __ ] dirty little nonslover.
Dirty little nonslover.
Who knows, bro? 2026 might be the year,
bro. These people get a life. What do
you think? Uh, Steven Howard.
These are all bullying tactics, bro. I
know the [ __ ] system and you know
what I mean.
Yeah, it's got to be that Instagram
thing. When was that? Months ago as well.
Got to be. Yeah, it's got to be over
that thing. Yeah, I'll just tell him to [ __ ] off.
That's what I will do. I will just tell
them straight to [ __ ] off.
That's what I would do, bro.
[ __ ] threatening me, mate. you know.
Yeah, that's what it is. It's that
thing, isn't it? With that Instagram thing.
Yeah. I wondered when they were going to
call me. They said that they were going
to call me over some Instagram thing as well. Yeah.
Yeah. That was months ago. But it's got
to be that Instagram thing.
I wonder why they didn't call me.
Yeah, I'm going to sit there and say the
same thing to me. Same say say the same
thing to them as they've said to me. Oh,
well, it's just social media.
You remember months and months ago,
Steven Howard, when I went to the police
and they said, "Oh, yeah, we might
contact you about this Instagram uh
thing months ago. That's what it's got
to be. I'm just going to tell them to
[ __ ] off." I said, "I'll come, but I'm
just going to be an awkward bastard, and
you're not going to like it." So, is
there really any point me coming?
Oh, do you remember when that the the
Instagram uh the police said that
they're going to contact me to talk to
me over this Instagram thing like months
and months and months ago? And yeah,
they basically messaged me trying to
threaten me. So, yeah. Um, so I'm going
to call them and say, "Firstly, don't
threaten me. Do not tell me that you
strongly advise me to do something.
Right. And secondly, right,
take a take a leaf out of your own book.
Yeah, I am not coming. [ __ ] off. If you
want to come and arrest me, you can do
that. [ __ ] off, [ __ ]
You said that you don't do anything over
social media. And I'm going to bring up
all the nons thing as well. It's just
some woman on Instagram, bro. Something
from ages ago, but it's not the point.
Don't message me. Do not message me 5
days before Christmas trying to tell me
what you strongly advise me and then
start thinking that you can try and
threaten me, mate. Your little bully
tactics don't work. Yeah. And I'll be
like, haven't you got you got other
things to be investigating? I can give
you a couple of crime reference numbers. So
yeah, I can give you a couple of crime
reference numbers if you want. You know,
[ __ ] they're really doing like what
the [ __ ] 5 days before Christmas.
Really, bro? You're literally It's like
5 days before Christmas and they're
emailing me. Sorry, they're text they're
texting me. [ __ ] off. How about you [ __ ]
off about that one?
Absolute clowns, bro. These these police
off Oh my god. You would have thought,
bro, if they were actually Yeah. trying
to get someone in for an interview,
they'd [ __ ] try like November or even October.
What the [ __ ] 5 days before Christmas.
Really? Come on now, man.
Nah, it's not fake. It's definitely
definitely them. And it better not be
over social media because they're not
going to like what I say to them. If
this is over social media, what I think
it's over, I'm just going to tell them
to do one and [ __ ] off. That's what I'm
going to do. I don't give a [ __ ] And
and listen to this, Joseph. I don't care
about the police. I hate the police. I
think they're a bunch of pig [ __ ]
eatating [ __ ] Yeah. And you will do
absolutely nothing about it. [ __ ] idiot.
No life. No, it's No, it's not fake,
bro. It's definitely definitely them.
No, it's definitely definitely
definitely definitely them. It's not the
point, bro. Don't [ __ ] text me
telling me what I need to [ __ ] do. Yeah. Simple.
Do you know what I'm saying? You either
get involved with social media or you
don't. Which one is it? Like, are you
going to get do you get invol or you
It's either you get involved or you
don't get involved. Which one is it? You
can't play two sides of a coin, bro.
It's not one law for one. One law for
the other. [ __ ] idiots texting me,
bro. But oh, email us so we can talk to
you. How about [ __ ] off? How about [ __ ]
Cuz anyhow, right, I need to go there.
Anyhow, you get me in that police
station, I'm not leaving until you do
something about these people. Simple.
Like that. That's that that that's it. I
will not leave. Simple. And that's it. I
will not leave until you do something
about these little harassing [ __ ]
You know, even if it's not YouTube
related. I think it's not even YouTube
related, but still, it's not the point.
You want my ass over Instagram. My
solicitor and the court advised me to
report something several times. I
reported it several times and you didn't
do anything about it. So what what you
up my ass for, [ __ ] What you up my
ass for? How how have you even got my
[ __ ] number, you [ __ ] idiots? Madness, bro.
That's what I'm going to say, bro. I
don't even think it is YouTube related,
but even still, bro, you're you can look
my name up on the system about how many
times I've been arrested, right? Yeah.
Yeah, even if it's a woman on Instagram,
it doesn't matter. Anything to do with
social media, I'm not leaving until they
do something about these people. Even I
don't even think it is anything to do
with these people, but it's still social
media, you know,
cuz that could potentially ruin
someone's Christmas kind of because
you're trying to put stress on people.
But obviously, I know the system. I know
what they're like. So, since you're so
interested in social media, I can give
you a couple of channels if you want. I
can give you names. I can give you
evidence cuz you're so interested in social media.
You know, you're so interested in social media.
So, you know what I mean? Idiots.
No, I don't think so, bro.
Nah, I don't think so.
No, it would. It's too soon for that.
And all of them people are in different countries.
Nah, it's that Instagram thing from months ago.
It's that Instagram thing. Yeah. From
months and months ago, bro. I know
exactly what it is cuz they told me when
I was reporting nonslegs.
It's not serious either way, but still,
if it's over social media, which well
obviously is going to be, um, then all
I'm going to be answering, I'm just
going to be talking about me
through the whole thing. So, it's pretty
pointless me going there because I'm
just going to be an awkward [ __ ] and not
leave. So, you know, it's it's
pointless, you know.
No, it's too soon to be that dick thing.
And then people was uh they were from
different countries. They were in
different countries. None of them were
from England. So, I very much doubt it.
Then I'm going to say, "Well, how come
you're letting these people come on here
every day and harass people when they've
been reporting multiple times, but
you're up my ass again?" You know,
so I ain't even going anyways, bro. If
they want to come and arrest me, they
can come and arrest me.
Still ain't got some devices back that
they [ __ ] took. Mad.
They're idiots, bro. These police. What the [ __ ]
about I'm required? I'm not required to
do anything, brother. Are you mad? You
don't [ __ ] message me 5 days before
Christmas telling me what I'm required to do
about what I'm required to do. You don't
message me after the history that I've
got telling me what I'm required to do.
No, bro. That's not how that's
happening. That's not how that's working,
you know? And I would want an update on
all on on these crime reference number
that's still on my phone. [ __ ] like
I'm going to ask them as well as well. I
will ask them straight, are you racist or something?
And I'll ask them like, are you racist
or what is it, bro?
Cuz I like to know where, you know, I
mean, you're messaging someone 5 days
before Christmas over social media
again. You said that report stuff on
social media, you know, and that's why
I'm going to be saying the whole thing.
Why are you up my ass? And I was saying
that way. Why are you up my ass?
You know what I'm saying, bro?
[ __ ] idiots. Absolute idiots. [clears throat]
It's a mad mad um thing,
right? It's bad it bro. bad. It isn't fair.
It's just one of the [ __ ] things about
this country, isn't it?
It's one of many [ __ ] things about this country, bro.
Like I said, a country designed to annoy you.
I have said it multiple multiple
multiple multiple times. Yeah,
I know it isn't fair.
They're racist. The police are racist as well.
[ __ ] you messaging me for, [ __ ]
That's what I'm going to say. Yeah, racist [ __ ] Yeah.
No, it's that Instagram thing from
months ago. It's got to be
Yeah. It's got to be what they were saying before.
So, in that 6 months, what have you done
about any of these people that's been reported? Huh? Huh?
What have you done in them six months?
What have you done about any of these
people that were reported? You're
messaging me 5 days before [ __ ]
Christmas, idiot. Yeah. What What are
you doing, bro?
So, I've just emailed them and I'm going
to when they when I get on the phone,
I'm going to be like, "What are you
doing? What the [ __ ] are you doing?"
That's what That's what I'm going to say to them.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] bro. What the
So you get involved with social media
when it suits yourself. Yeah. When it suits yourself, idiots.
And they proper try to be very
threatening as well with the messages as
well. Like it could be the minorest
thing, but they will really try to like
threaten you. um and
stuff like um to make it seem worse than it is.
And they done it 5 days before Christmas
as well. That's another thing you you
know that needs to be brought up.
You said that you don't get involved
with stuff that social media. So what
which one is it?
[ __ ] absolute clowns, bro. These
police are clowns. [clears throat]
They're idiots, bro. The police are idiots.
Not poor, mate. Got more money than
you'll ever have.
So, yeah, this thing needs bringing up
to them as well, bro. Whether it's over
YouTube or not, that's another thing.
They should have a Merlin on my [ __ ]
address to be honest. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
What the [ __ ]
Madness, isn't it?
I'll give it to them on the phone, bro.
When I get them on the phone, I'm going
to give it to them hard, bro. Watch.
Don't need you texting our [ __ ] phone
5 days before Christmas over social
media. You said you don't get involved
over social media.
And then if it is that thing about the
dick picture, which I don't think it
would be because they were all in
different countries, I'm going to be
like, "Oh, what?" So, it's okay for
people to lead people on then. It's okay
for people to [ __ ] harass people on
YouTube. I don't give a [ __ ] about these
clowns. They don't affect me. But at the
end of the day, in the eyes of in the
eyes of the law, you know that what
these people are doing. I bring up
everything. Everything, bro. I don't
give a [ __ ]
I'm a danger to women. Oo, a s. Ooh, a
s. So, I'm going to um I've emailed them
and I'm going to basically uh say to her
when I get them on the phone, what do
you think you're doing emailing me 5
days before Christmas? I want an update.
Yeah, I want an update on these crime
reference numbers that I've got. Don't
[ __ ] try and threaten me down my
[ __ ] phone in an indirect way about
you strongly advised. Don't [ __ ]
threaten me, mate.
Simple as that.
There's a little contact us. [ __ ] off, man.
And stop being a simp player, though.
Women don't like you and they'll never
sleep with you. And defending women is
not going to make them like you. Um,
remember that when you're in your
deathbed, bro. Women don't like you.
Stop defending them.
I know it wouldn't be the dick pictures
because that's too early.
Um, it's got to be that Instagram thing
from months ago. what they said. They
said they were going to contact me like
when was it? I think it was
I don't know when was that. Was it this
year or last?
Um, no, it was this year. It's got to be that.
I'm trying to think when did I get
arrested? What were December?
Yeah, last year I was at Laney. So,
yeah, it's this year. It's got to be
that. Either [ __ ] way. Whatever the
[ __ ] Yeah, it's got to be that. And I'm
going to I want to know why they're
messaging people over social media.
That's what I'm wanting to know. Why
they're messaging people over social media
when you say to people that they need to
report stuff. It's It's nothing to do with you.
Like you that's what you've said
multiple times, you know? So what are
you heads or tails? You need to make up
your mind, bro.
No, it's that Instagram thing. It might
be USA. It might I think it might be
that USA easy thing or something else.
But even still, bro, whatever it is over
social media, everything's going to get brought up
cuz I've had many, many, many account
encounters with these police, right?
Right. Time and time and time and time
and time and time and time and time
again over the years only because of
social media. If it wasn't for social
media, I would have never been arrested.
Well, maybe once actually in 28 years.
So, at the end of the day, yeah, I'm
just going to [ __ ] just go at these
I'm just going to show them everything
what these people have been doing if
it's anything to do with social media
and I'm just going to start the whole
thing up again. Simple.
Stop being up my ass over social media
telling me what I need to do, you know?
[ __ ] off, man. What the [ __ ] you know?
threatening people on a Saturday, the
last weekend before Christmas. Are you [ __ ] mad?
These people [ __ ] must be, bro. It must be.
[ __ ] them anyways, man.
Oh, either way, bro.
Yeah, if it was serious, they would just
come and arrest you and take your phone and [ __ ]
See, I'm not scared of the police. You
know, as you get older, you know the
system. You know what they're what
they're like, bro. Yeah.
Madness, in it. Absolute madness.
Stupid country in it. The country is a
[ __ ] joke. A country designed to annoy you.
Like they're saying about the world not
being against you. Yeah.
No, it's probably an inv it's probably a
involuntary interview, bro.
No. No. They they can
cuz what they'll probably do is say,
"Oh, you either come to the station or
we're going to arrest you." And they
might not even arrest you. But even
still, I don't care. I want to know why
they're up my ass over social media.
They don't do anything about these people.
And that's what I'm going to say, bro.
And that's what I'm going to plead. It's the truth.
This Joseph Farra says about the world
not being against me, but why is it that
you go on a train and you get people
acting like [ __ ]
Why do you go on a train and have people
acting like complete [ __ ] bro? Maybe.
Maybe, bro. But again, I'll just say to
him, it's social media. It's got nothing
to do with you. Same advice as you gave
to me. Same advice as you gave to me, bro.
Or it could be that Instagram thing that
they said that they were they said they
were going to contact me um in the
summer. They said they were going to contact me
and arrange. So, it could be that.
But yeah, I'll just turn around and say
social media, it doesn't bother you. I'm
giving you the advice that you've gave me.
So, if these people are allowed to be on
YouTube, maybe they're harassing people,
I'll do what I want. Simple.
They come on here harassing people, right?
And no, they don't do anything about it.
What the [ __ ] And then they up my ass.
So, you know what I mean?
I think the police are racist as well.
Deep down, bro.
I think the police are also racist. Yeah.
And then if you don't contact them, they
probably won't even arrest you. But then
they threaten you. Why are they doing
this 5 days before Christmas as well?
What the [ __ ]
All right. Terry made an account 5 hours
ago, Dusty, saying it's made his weekend
better that I lost 200
again. 200 is nothing to me. It's it's
it's a lot to you because of the
trainers that you wear. You made an
account 5 hours ago. I swear these
people are disabled on this community.
How they can sit on here for years and
keep doing this. They are generally
disabled on here, aren't they, Dusty?
They are generally disabled people,
aren't they? I don't even think that
they're jealous. I just think they're
disabled on here.
That's why I think I just think they're disabled.
how they can sit on here for years,
right, doing this
and 200 pound is literally nothing to
me. And I said it about a million times
and they're still laughing. 200 is
nothing to me. Uh, [ __ ] hell, bro. You know?
Yeah, cuz you don't have a family. He's
a little [ __ ] virgin who can't even
afford a new pair of trainers.
He ain't got anything in life, bro. Just
like the rest of the people on here.
They ain't got nothing in life.
Where's Joseph Farah? He's He's He's not
on here, is he? No. Where's he Joseph
Farra? He gone quiet.
Don't [ __ ] slag me off behind my
[ __ ] back, [ __ ]
Don't slag me off behind my [ __ ] back,
you [ __ ] [ __ ]
And then [ __ ] You know what I mean?
Yeah. That's what happens when you call
when you catch these people slagging you
off. They never come back on your channel.
They'll never come back on your channel.
Have you noticed that, Dusty? When you
catch them slag slagging you off behind
your back, it's like that cue. They'll
never come back on your channel. Cowards.
apps don't work.
I've come to realize that. Yeah, Reddit
is just not real life, bro.
>> Yeah, it's just not real life.
I don't think Reddit's real life, bro.
That's the way you got to see it, is it?
Like the stuff that they say like other
stuff like anxiety and stuff, it's it's
solid. But when they talk about dating,
they have got no clue. They really,
really have got no clue. The other stuff
that they talk about is all right.
But we're dating and that. They've got
absolutely no idea. Yeah.
Do you think the Reddit mods spend all
day on Reddit then, Steven Howard, or do
you think they've got a life outside of Reddit?
Load of old Bill.
Do you reckon they've got a life outside of Reddit? Steven Howard.
Oh, do you think they spend all day on Reddit?
Joseph Perau is a little nons dusty.
Are they like jealous or do they want to
[ __ ] me or I'd love to know what it is
why I've got so many middleaged
uh old men obsessed with me? I'd love to
know the answer, bro, without throwing
any accusations. Do they want to [ __ ]
you? Are they jealous that you've got a
mom that loves you? or they jealous over
you. I'd love to know the answer.
H I seem to have a lot of people
obsessed with me, bro. More than Timmy, don't I? Meow.
You all right? Gravesy.
I agree. I was looking at a Cheryl Co
interview yesterday. She's so
attractive. Oh my god. You can't deny it.
No, she's definitely definitely attractive. Uh, Grezy,
any thoughts on that, Grezy? >> [snorts]
>> [ __ ] hell.
will call me out. Little copycat.
Oh, did you watch the boxing?
Can't believe the old bills up my bloody ass.
I'm not happy what I'm seeing on TV. Um,
Grezy, I'm hearing it here. I'm hearing
more and more about this misogyny [ __ ]
I'm going to I'm going to reply to go on TV, bro.
I want to share my thoughts. I really do
Yeah. Are they good for them?
Yeah. I really want to be on TV, bro.
I have a lot to say
about double standards, sexism,
biasness. I've got a lot of stuff to say
that leading people on should be illegal
cuz leading people on is is is causing distress.
Why is none of that illegal? I don't
understand how that's ille not illegal.
I really don't understand how none of that's illegal.
But saying you hate women and stuff
seems to be uh
I'd have a lot to say about this stuff.
I'd be like, why is it right for women
to moan and complain and everyone feels
sorry for her? But when a man says he
struggles, he's labeled every name under the sun.
Oh, do you know what I'm saying, bro? Like,
I strongly feel I feel so strong about this, Dusty.
I generally hate women. Like I generally
do. I feel that strongly about it, bro.
Now, really, really do now, bro.
I [ __ ] do. I'm not even joking.
I'm [ __ ] asexual, I think. Yeah, I'm asexual now.
They turned me asexual, brother.
Yeah, I'm asexual. Me. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm never playing that [ __ ] roulette again.
I'm never playing that roulette again,
mate. [ __ ] that.
Yeah. Macaroni cheese.
Yeah. And that online roulette is
definitely fixed. Definitely fixed.
I lost 200.
Oh, but apparently I'm skint.
These people are [ __ ] hilarious on
there, bro. It
I can't believe Red Star has been doing
this for years. Stephen Howard, waking
up 7 o'clock in the morning, monitoring
me, stalking me. Does anyone have a
brain on here and and realize how weird
this is? Cuz obviously I know a lot of
people on here were slow and disabled,
but surely there's got to be like one
normal person on here to not
to realize how weird what these people do is.
Nope. I've still got money, bro.
I've still got money.
Don't worry about that. A yeah,
he's a loser. That Red Star, they're all
losers on here, bro. 7:00 in the morning
stalking, monitoring. Yeah, like there.
They're [ __ ] losers. Look at that Pat
Mustard. Look what he turned out to look
like, bro. Look what he turned out to
look like. That Pat mustard.
They're all the [ __ ] same on here.
These losers, bro.
Yeah. I've still got a grand and a bit
left, so it's not bad, bro. Yeah.
I was going to stick it on the football, but
I decided roulette instead, not knowing
about the fee, obviously.
I just find it mad how you can't win money anymore.
So, how do you how are you supposed to
get money now? You just Well, you can
win money, but you have to lump on both
teams to score. That's the only way, is
it, Dusty? That's the only way you can
win in it.
That's I think that's the only way you
can actually win money now.
What do you think, Dusty? I don't think
there is any other way unless you save.
You either save, but we're talking about
like I don't think there is. madness.
No, there's no other way, bro.
I lost [ __ ] 200 quid.
I could have gave that 200 pound to Laney,
but I don't play roulette often. It's
very rare I play it. I don't know why I
felt like playing it.
You reckon you can win in the bookie
slots? I don't think so, Dusty. Is it? No.
No, I don't think you can, bro.
You can't win money now. [snorts]
Like, you used to be able to in the good old days.
So, ladies, don't. Why would I do that?
I've got money, bro. I don't need to
[ __ ] sell boots. I've got money, bro.
got over a grand. So, yeah.
Nah, you people not losers, bro. Nah, I
take back what I said, man. I don't
think you're losers. Nah, no. Sorry. I I
take back what I said.
Nah, none of you are losers, bro. [ __ ]
You've got money, you've got a life,
you've got friends, you work. You just
happen to sit on YouTube from the time
you wake up to the time you go to bed.
But you've definitely got all these things.
Makes you wonder, don't it?
Makes you wonder.
Makes me wonder. I don't know about any anyone else.
Yeah, I got my pip. Yeah. You don't know
how much money I get. You don't know
what money I have.
You don't know anything about anyone.
little clowns. That's why I laugh at
you. You know when you sit there and you
laugh at me losing 200 pound, I laugh at
it because you don't know how much money
I have. You don't know how when I'm
getting my next money. You don't know
anything. That's why I just laugh at it. But um yeah, bro,
the roulette is not good.
Never selling lanies, bro.
Your one benefits yourself.
Why are you projecting, lad?
Your one benefits yourself, lad.
So why you why are you talking about that? Yeah.
Do you know what? I might play Frankie
at some point, Stephen, with like a 100
pound or two pound spins or something.
Not for a long time.
Yeah. Disabled, bro. You're disabled yourself.
Again, self projection. Only disabled
people would come on here for over 10
years doing what you do. So you must be
talking about yourselves.
Yeah, you must be talking about
yourself, lad. Only disabled people
would do what you do on here
every [ __ ] day. Every day
for years, time you wake up to the time
you go bed.
Only disabled people will do that.
Don't forget, Stephen, we've got the
whole of January to save as well.
Yeah, we've got the whole of January to
save as well.
So, that's a good thing.
Yeah, they will do.
But the way I saw it was this Stephen
Howard. I've been out once this month.
Yeah. And I think I spent £120. I've
been out once this month and I've just
lost £200. Could you think if I went out every week? week, bro?
I would have been spending more than
that £200 to be fair. So that's the way
you got to look at it. Like you would
have been spending more than 200. So
that's the way you got to look at it,
bro. You have to do something.
So, you know, that's the way you got to
look at it.
And I knew next month I've got a whole
next month to save. So, I mean, I knew
what I was doing, bro.
So, yeah. It's bad. It is. It is [ __ ] though, man.
I would have probably went one spent 150
today if I went out.
I'd rather have gave it to the roulette
to be honest. That's how bad it is.
I used to do that on Saturday, Steven
Howard. I'd spend like 6070 and I'd be
like, "Yeah, but you would have spent 60 70 drinking
getting more bad experiences.
I could never go back to that again.
Steven Howard Roulette, I could never do
it, bro. I can never ever go back to that.
Nah, [ __ ] that, bro.
[ __ ] keeping them clowns in business. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] keeping them bastards in business.
You know what I mean? [ __ ] that.
It's the truth in it. Like I said, every
3, four months, you know,
but I mean like seriously, bro, like
what the [ __ ] And it is around
Christmas as well. So,
are you going to play roulette against Steven Howard?
Beans on toast.
Never had beans on toast in my life. Self-p projection.
That's definitely self- projection.
Beans and toast.
Really? I had macaroni cheese today. Uh
yesterday I had an Indian then a Chinese.
Nope. Definitely definitely definitely
not me. I don't like beans. Definitely
definitely definitely not me.
Beans on toast. That's never been me.
You got the wrong channel.
You've definitely definitely definitely
got the wrong channel.
Definitely definitely got the wrong channel.
That's definitely definitely not me.
Beans on toast. I don't even like beans.
Yeah, it is women's fault. They're
[ __ ] I hate them. Yeah.
Yeah. They're [ __ ] They're [ __ ]
I hate them. Beans on toast. Do you
remember when Timmy had to do that? He
lost all his money and he had to live on
bread. He had to live on bread.
Yeah. He had to live on bread. You remember that?
Yeah, he had to live on bread, do you
remember? For the whole month, was it
like the whole month? [ __ ] hell, bro.
No, [ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that.
That is a madness.
Yeah, everything you're saying is self-
projection, bro. Keep the self-p
projectioning comments coming.
Self projection. Self-p projection.
Self- projection. You must be talking
about your own life. Beans on toast.
Never had beans on toast in my life. I hate beans.
Yeah, you must be talking about
yourselves. Definitely talking about
That's why I don't block the self-p
projecting comments because they're
entertainment. It's nice to know about
your own your lives.
Yeah. Why the Spongebob movies out
today? Um Steven Howard. Yeah.
Am I going out tonight? Um well um
um well considering I said I'm done with
women and they're all evil and I'm sick
of this country. Maybe no.
Just maybe no.
I won't be out New Year's Eve either.
No, we've done this million times before, bro.
No, I'm definitely not going out, bro. I
know it'll be rammed. I don't want any
more bad experiences.
If the weather was nice, yeah, then I
would actually I might I might have
actually gone out.
Maybe if the weather was nicer, but nah.
Going out in the cold, wasting money
just to hear I've got a boyfriend. No
thanks. I'm good.
Brother, you're on benefit yourself,
bro. You're on benefit yourself.
Stop self projecting. Yeah.
No, me. No, I'm fine. Me? No, no, no.
Samuel, I'm all right. Me, bro. Where
I've been out so many times in my life
and I've done this [ __ ] so many times in
my life, I don't even get bored.
I don't even get bored. Me, I don't even
get bored at all.
I generally generally don't get bored.
I'm just chilling watching Franklin
saving up money. Even though I lost 200
pound on roulette, but I don't mind me, bro.
No, I'm I'm good. I'm fine me.
That's what happens when you get to a
point where you're so fed up and sick of
their [ __ ] This is what happens. If it
was a really really hot day, it was a
nice day, then maybe I would go out. If
the weather was really nice, maybe I'd
Yeah, I would go out then. But nah, I'm
not even going out New Year's Eve
either. I don't care
because you know that you're not missing anything.
Yeah, it would be. Yeah, it would be Ram
today. Yeah, just the O'Neils. Do you
know what? If I could get into the
O'Neals, then maybe I would go out today,
but I can't. So then maybe I'd think I
might go out if it was if I could get
into the O'Neals.
I rarely gamble, bro. This was a oneoff.
I don't really gamble, bro. This was the
first time in about three or three or four months.
Yeah, it's not it's not It was actually
217, but yeah. So yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I hate this country. I hate women as well.
£17 [ __ ] fee.
So yeah, nice know you can't even win money anymore.
You can't even win [ __ ] money anymore, bro.
That ain't good.
I'm just on It's just self-reflection.
I'm just on L J's channel. I'm looking
at the comments.
Yeah, it's just self-reflection again,
bro. We've heard all this before. I
think the main problem is that Xmus
benefits have not been paid early this
year. I was waiting for Slug to appear
and playing the BS by now, but Slug is
very quiet, so my guess is they are all
skin to release Monday. This is all self projection, bro.
More self projection. Ranting all day
after 200 pound loss. Alone again. All
day. Christmas. Hated my family.
Yep. Self projection again. I'm not
hated by any members of my family.
Yeah, this is just all self projection.
We've heard all of this before.
So, where's the where's the IQ in this?
Because these people say that they're
intelligent. He's absolutely skinned to
the point where he can't afford to buy
anyone a person. He'll be alone this
Christmas. Self projection again. Yeah,
this is all self projection, bro.
We heard all of this last year as well.
Yeah, we heard all of this self
projection last year on the same channel. Bro,
these people are supposed to be intelligent.
Everyone's skin. Everyone's hated by
their family. Really, bro? Do the Are
these people sure they're not talking about themselves?
Steven Howard, are these people right
sure they're not talking about
themselves? Cuz it seems very much to me
that they're actually talking about
themselves. Skin hated by family. I
mean, people hear my mom all the time.
Are you sure these people are not
talking about themselves?
You know, they're definitely definitely
talking about theirelves, bro. Definitely definitely.
Everyone seems to be skinned every day
to these people.
Every day. Like every day of the year,
everyone seems to be skinned to these
people. How is that even possible?
What the [ __ ]
They They call people skin cuz they're [ __ ] skin.
Because they're skin, bro.
I can't afford to buy anyone a present.
I bought my mom a present.
I can literally buy a present whenever I
want another present. What are you
talking about? How can How can people be
skinned every day of the year, bro?
Are they sure they're not talking about
themselves? Like, seriously, bro?
They've been doing this now for [ __ ]
They've been doing this now for 10
years. And none of these people have
ever been seen with women. None of these
people have ever been seen to have a life. Right?
Listen, bro. They they've never been
seen with a woman. They've never been
seen to have had a life. All that they
have been seen to be is on YouTube 24/7.
Are they sure that they're not the skint ones, bro?
Are they really really sure that they're
not they're not talking about themselves
to be coming on YouTube for 10 years
calling people that they don't know skin
and then being embarrassed for the best
part of [ __ ] six years? Are they
really really sure that they're not
talking about themselves?
And another self-p projection mental to
me that he would rather live like that
than find a job. That's self-p
projection. These people don't have a
job. Everything is just basically self-p
projection with these people.
And we love it. You people are losers
about we love it. You you you and the
law J crew are [ __ ] fat ugly losers.
Why would you love someone that's
younger and better looking than you,
bro? You people are fat, ugly losers. No
one cares what you people love, bro.
reading some of these comments. Yeah. We
don't care what you fat moronic disabled
people love. You don't even count as
people, bro. They don't even count as
like a person.
They're absolute bully victims that just
come on YouTube every day. They're
disabled skin bully victims. No one no
one cares what they love, bro. You know
what I mean? They've been bullied their
whole life. That's why they're on here
skin every day. Why are they on here repeating, bro?
for 10 years. If these people really
aren't skint, ask, you need to ask
yourself this question, bro, for real.
If these people are not skint, right,
and they're not all of the things, why
are they sat on here year in year out,
year in year out with their shitty little comments?
Where's their money? Where's their
girlfriend? Where's their friends?
Where's their where their Where's their
[ __ ] family, bro? Didn't you hear
Laney come on my [ __ ] come in the
room yesterday saying, "Oh, I think it's
a good idea. You should get off of
YouTube. It's for the best. Really, bro?
And they want to talk about people not having family.
Really? These people are going to be
like, shouldn't these people be out
right now drinking with their mates on
having Why? That's another question as
well, Stephen. Shouldn't these people be
out there drinking with their friends
with their work uh the work do you know
Christmas um party? Shouldn't these
people be out there with their mates, be
out there with their friends? They say
that they've got a better life than
everyone. Shouldn't they be out there
today? It's the last weekend before Christmas.
Shouldn't these people be out there like living life?
I'm just wondering, bro, because if
you're sat here saying that, oh, I'm
giving up on life. I'm saving money, and
I'm saying that, and they want more than
me. What does that say about these people?
What does that say about these little clowns?
These little clowns that have been on
here for 12 years. What does that say
about these little clowns, bro? Come on.
How can people be skinned every day of the year?
Every day of the year, someone's skin
even though they get money. How How does
this work, bro?
They're idiots, bro. They're absolute idiots.
All right. They're proper idiots on this
even, bro. I can't, bro. I can't.
My family hates me. There's only one
family member that I don't talk to, and
I could do if I want to, but I just
don't like them. Speak to my mom. Speak
to my sister.
This is all self-p projection, bro. This
is all self projection with these
people, these skint fat, ugly people.
And have you noticed that none of them
come on camera as well? Steven Howard.
Have you also noticed that none none of
them would put their fa they won't put
their face on camera
because they're fat and ugly. It's a bit
like what Monty man says. They're fat,
ugly, life's rejects and they can't
prove you wrong. That's another thing,
bro. And they can't prove you wrong. Life losers.
Should they not be out with their work
workmates having a drink?
Makes you wonder, doesn't it?
No, it makes me [ __ ] wonder.
All they do is call themselves skin and
call themselves muners.
I'm surprised they're not high. They're
putting themselves down. Putting
themselves down every year.
These people put themselves down.
There's no content on this channel either.
Yeah, that's self projection.
saying that I'm alone again Christmas
when I literally live with my mom. Self
projection. Do you know what? I'm going
to do a video on these people, bro. I'm
really really going to do a video on these people.
I'm going to do a video on these people
quick and then I'm going to come back, bro. Yeah,
I'm going to do a quick video and I'm
going to come back, bro. Yeah,
one sec, bro. Give me Give me a couple
minutes. Yeah, I'm going to come back.