Yeah, I couldn't be bothered to do a video, bro.
Yeah. Sorry, bro. I can't even be
bothered to do a video on these little
clowns. You little self reflectors. Skin self-reflectors.
Yeah, just self projection with these
people in it, lad.
Jesus Christ. Are they still going to be
disabled in 2026?
Are they still going to be repeating in 2026?
Are we going to have some new content?
Or is it going to be the same repeating self-reflectors?
Yeah, they're just these people on here
are just fat, ugly little nerds, little
bully victims, and they just bounce off
of everyone else's life. That's what
they do. These little nerds waiting for
their £300 a month benefit money. Um,
that's what they are. That's why they're
on him every day. These people are
skint, bro. They're on that [ __ ]
Universal Credit, bro. I'm telling you.
£350 a month it is. That's why these
people never have any money and they're
sat on here every day calling people
skint cuz they're skin themselves
cuz they probably spend that money like
in within the first day or the second
day. That's why they call other people
skint cuz they are skin. These people
are skinn bro.
Why else would people that age come on
here every day repeating themselves if
they weren't disabled and [ __ ] skinned?
[ __ ] madness, bro. Yeah. Oh, what?
These people are [ __ ] skimp. That's
why they're obsessed with skimp people.
Cuz they're [ __ ] skin for 12 years.
That's why they call people skin. Cuz
they're skin. They're [ __ ] proper
boring mongos. You can tell they're
disabled, bro. Like, imagine these
people actually left the house and they tried socializing.
They're [ __ ] just fat ugly people.
Yeah. repeat, isn't it?
Uh, nothing, bro. It's just the same
repeating people. Triple H, the
Christmas projectors are out.
They come on here every day calling
people skin, but yet they're on here
every day for years.
Are they sure they're not talking about themselves?
I think these people are talking about themselves, bro.
Think about it, bro. If they if these
people have got a job yet brakes, if
these people have got a job, then
wouldn't they wouldn't they be out with
their work dudes today? Saturday, ain't
it? Weekend uh before Christmas. But
nope, they're sat on YouTube again
calling people that they don't know.
H strange, isn't it? Very strange.
sat on YouTube, bro. Again,
calling people that they don't know
every day. Classic, isn't it?
Well, like I said, 2026 hopefully will
be different. If these people have
really got an IQ and they're not disabled,
then it will be different. Triple H. So,
you never know, lad. Maybe.
They say they've got an IQ in it. That's
why they don't show their face.
So, we'll see next year in it.
No skin talk, no repeating. Yeah.
Red Star is a fat ugly [ __ ] who ain't
got no life and he ain't got no family.
He's going to be sat on YouTube
Christmas stalking as usual
like always with these self-reflectors.
Bro, the thing is they're talking about
people's family hating them, bro. Are
they sure they're not talking about themselves?
They must be talking about themselves, you know?
Yeah, bro. They must be really talking about themselves.
These people are going to be all alone
Christmas. No family, no money, no life,
which is what they're what they're
trying to say about you.
My family hate me, but I live with my
mom. Yeah, made that make sense. Okay.
Self projection. They don't know any
members of my family. These skin people,
how can people be skinned every day? How
can people be skinned every day of the year? Projection.
Yeah, they're self-reflectors. Yeah.
Yeah. Bro, that's self-p projection, man. Self projection.
These people are going to be lonely this
Christmas. And I know this cuz I went
live last year and they were all on they
were all on my live stream. So, I've
actually got proof that these people are
going to be alone Christmas.
They were on here Christmas, bro. Harry
Fraud and everything.
But yeah. Nah, they've got I, bro.
They're intelligent. They've got an IQ.
They're not going to be They're not
going to be on here next year. They've
got a life. Everyone's skin. Remember,
everyone's skin. Everyone's family hates them.
No, they're not going to be on here, bro.
They're not going to be on here next
year. Why would they be on here next
year? They've got a life. They've got
all this money, all these friends.
They've got a job. What? They don't need
to be on here, bro. Every day. Don't be silly.
[ __ ] madness, bro.
Yeah. You know it's down bad. Yeah. When
I don't even go out anymore and I save
money and these people are on YouTube
more than me. That's how you know these
people are down bad.
That's how you know they're down bad, bro.
That's how you know that everything that
they say is about themselves
cuz you will see the same people, same
faces, same comments. Hold on, you got
all this money, you've got this life.
How how you having time to hate on
YouTube every day?
Yeah, cuz everything said themselves, bro.
On that on the L J channel, everything
is about their own lives. Fat, ugly, no
money, no life, no nothing, bro.
Everything is them. Everything is their life
projected onto other people, lad. Yeah.
They shouldn't even be on here today.
It's Christmas weekend, bro. They
shouldn't even be on here.
They're not saving for anything. They're
calling other people. I'm not calling
other people. Only the people that call
me. So why are they on YouTube? Think of it, bro.
That Joseph Ferrar's being a [ __ ] talker
again. Triple H.
I caught him on liberies. Triple H. I
caught him on labies.
He's got a lot to say behind the
keyboard. A lot to say. This fat
bastard. We was talking about this earlier.
[ __ ] fat [ __ ] Nons lover.
Don't even think someone like you could
ever try and troll me, bro. No.
Yeah, pretty much.
John, I've got a question. If these
people If these people have got all of
this money and their life and a life,
why are they on it all day every day? I
don't understand it. If they've got all
of this money on their life and and
they're not skin, why are they on here
every day hating?
>> I just don't understand it. Maybe
someone else could answer me.
Cares what you fat, ugly losers love. We
love it. No one cares about what you
fat, ugly rejects love, mate. You know
what I mean?
They ain't got to life these people, bro.
Yeah, they are disabled, bro. To be fair. Mow meow. Show.
You little copycat.
You're a little copycat with no mind of
your own. Meow. meow meow.
No mind of your own.
Um, I had macaroni and cheese.
Yeah, I won't be eating again, bro. Not
bothered. Don't care. Yeah.
>> Yeah, bro. Nothing. I just had I had mac cheese.
You remember when they all copied each
other? Steven Howard,
you don't like Sher Cole. You're gay.
No, you're gay. You're gay. Remember,
they always used to copy each other. Yeah.
Yeah. Waxi will be shocker block.
Yeah. Waxies chocolate block, bro. Little copycat.
A little copycat.
Yeah. Little copycat with no mind of your own.
You little copycat with no mind of your own.
I'm looking forward to next year, bro.
Different [ __ ] on this community.
No more repeating in it, Stephvena. They
won't repeat next year, will they?
Cuz they're intelligent. They've got a
high IQ. That's why they don't show
their face in it.
So many weasels on this community, bro.
Yeah, I won't be going out New Year's
Eve. Stephen Howard is cancelled.
New Year's Eve is cancelled.
It's cancelled you, lad.
Well, I can because I just did.
I can. And I'm going to get stick for it
as well cuz I plan to go out with
someone New Year's Eve.
It's all cancelled.
It's all cancelled, bro.
Everything's cancelled, bro. Everything's canled
in before your skin comments. Nope, not
skin. Got money. Try again.
[ __ ] idiots on here, bro.
I could win the lottery right now and
I'd say the same thing. That's that.
No, I didn't cancel Christmas last year.
It was ruined last year, but this year
I'm actually canceling it.
No, this year I'm actually canceling it.
There's a difference. It was actually
ruined last year.
Yeah, go to Waxies today, lad. I might
go to Waxies today.
I want to go to O'Neal's,
but I can't get into the O'Neals.
What's the plan? Nothing, though. Just
do nothing. Just stay in bed.
I'm not looking forward to it. I hate Christmas.
I don't even like to be out in public. I
hate people. That's why I just chill and
just watch Franklin and that.
I hate people. So,
yeah, I'll be in bed.
It's not money. I've got money, bro.
And I get money after Christmas. And I
have money. I get money every week as
well. Nothing to do with that.
Now, I'll probably have the Christmas
dinner, but that's it.
She doesn't bother me because last
Christmas was ruined. So, I don't really
care about Christmas. So, if I got
chucked out and disowned by my family, I
wouldn't care. I don't really care about
Christmas. It wouldn't be anything to
me. It's just another day. I don't care about Christmas.
I hate Christmas.
It's just another day. The only day I
like is Halloween.
I like Halloween. Me.
Yeah. I don't I don't care about Christmas.
I hate this country. I hate people, bro.
I hate people, Dusty. As I got older, I
started to really start hating people. I
like that Oreo, man. You know? Yeah.
I hate women. I hate [ __ ] [ __ ]
I hate anyone from the West.
The only people I don't hate is like Asian people.
The Red Star's going to be on here
Christmas all alone. It's not about the 200.
It's not about £200. £200. Nothing to me.
It's not about £200. I've got money,
bro. It's not about that.
I'm not even pissed off about that now.
It was just a bit annoying earlier.
Yeah, I do remember him.
Yeah, another year of this [ __ ] [ __ ] that.
It's not about 200 pound, bro.
Even though losing 200 pound annoying,
but it's not about that. So,
I'm not doing anything New Year's Eve either.
I don't love anyone. I love myself.
I only love myself.
I don't care about gifts either. I
wouldn't care if I didn't get any gifts.
I don't really care. I can buy my own
stuff. I'm independent, so I only care
about I only care about myself.
I don't buy presents for people. People
are selfish. People are two-faced. No,
I'm all right.
I hate Christmas.
[ __ ] Christmas. I'm the Grinch. [ __ ]
I'm the Grinch this year.
Yeah, I've got money, bro. I could have
bought 200 I could have bought presents for £200
because I don't care about it.
Because I don't care. I just want this
year to hurry up and end. Hurry up and
get some more money so I can book this
flight and get the [ __ ] out of here.
It's not nice drinking around this time
of year as well. It's too busy, bro. You
have to wait ages to get a drink.
I don't think I'd go central London if I
was going to drink, you know, like
today. I think I'd go like just local.
It would be busy enough. Yeah, central.
No, no, [ __ ] that. Waiting 100 hours to
get a drink. No thanks.
No, I wouldn't do that, bro. I wouldn't
I don't think I would go central. It
would be too busy
unless I can get into O'Neals, but
that's a that's I wouldn't I don't think
I would. I think it's pointless. It
would just be too busy.
It would just be too busy. Yep.
Yep. I'll get money again soon anyways.
So, I'm out of here. I need to buy a
phone though. So that's going to cost me
that £400. I'm going to get a brand new phone.
Save up as well. Oh, and I'm out of
here. [ __ ] this [ __ ] [ __ ] this for a
game of soldiers.
Have you ever heard that saying, Dusty?
[ __ ] this game. The best time to go out
in this country is March or April.
March. March and April. >> [snorts]
>> March and April was the best.
That's when I last got my dates was
March and April.
That was my peak of success. March,
April, and then after that it just went
to [ __ ] It's like my barber. He said,
"I hate November. Everything goes right
from March and April and then it starts
going downwards." And I see what he
means cuz it's happened to me as well.
After April, things go bad.
So I I get I do get what he means. Yeah.
Cuz it happens to me as well. That's
what this barber told me. Yeah.
I was trying to do this thing with
Ant-Man Dusty where you get an extra £50
a week. Basically, you open two bank
accounts and this guy Matt Bets and he
gives Ant-Man £100 and obviously I'd get
50 pound extra a week, but it never
worked. Even though I tried to open the
bank account, it just wasn't doing it,
which was the whole reason why I printed
this thing out.
That's another thing that pissed me off
as well cuz it [ __ ] I had to go to
three shops to print that [ __ ] bank
statement. So, [ __ ] that, bro.
Yeah, it would have been It's like £200
a month, isn't it? You're not going to
say no to 200 a month. He used to do it.
So, but that never worked.
Yeah. 200 pound. Yeah.
Yeah. It never worked. I don't know why,
bro, but never worked.
Yep. You get £700 a month. £800 a month,
which is more than enough money out there.
That's a lot of money out there. £800 a month.
He said when I was subleting, I could
have moved there. No, I couldn't because
if anything went in the house wrong in
the house, then I I wouldn't be able to
do it because I had a responsibility
really. When you're subleting, you're
supposed you're actually supposed to be
living there. So, I couldn't go halfway
across the [ __ ] world and then
something happens and then what am I
going to do? Come all the way back
when they're arguing or something goes
wrong in the house. It wouldn't happen
unless I had someone else looking after.
It's a responsibility. So you wouldn't
be able to go there with a clear head?
No, you couldn't, bro. You couldn't.
Trust me, you couldn't.
Not with four people, five people living
in a house. You and what? Go across the
world half [ __ ] halfway across the
world, bro. No, it wouldn't happen
cuz you got responsibility. Bit like
having a child. So you wouldn't be able
to do it.
and you're not there to see what happens
as well. So, it wouldn't happen cuz if
there was an argument that happened
about putting gas in and you're not
there and you don't know what's going on
and you don't know what you can't do that, bro.
So, when I used to travel, I used to I
was actually living there. So, I saw
everything that was going on. So, no,
you you'd have to really be living there, bro.
I'd still be in that house now. I
wouldn't I would have never come back.
I like that house. I'd never I'd never
be I I would have stayed, bro. Like forever.
Forever, bro. I would never have left, I
don't think. Never.
Yeah. You receive benefits for two months.
If it's one person, then maybe you could
Yeah. like you could rent but not four
or five people living in a house. You
can't, bro. It's a responsibility.
There was times where I used to go out
drinking and they there'd be a problem
and it would just put me off the whole thing. So,
like I said, it's all right if you're
living there. It's all right if you're
living there, bro. And you're going not
too far away. Yeah. But not
You should get nonslegs a little job, Triple H.
I reckon he should get a little job
doing the world of good. Yeah. [snorts]
Yeah. And that Joseph Ferrar, he was
talking [ __ ] about me on on Lavar Triple
H about I'm a sad bastard. Have you
looked at your [ __ ] self? You fat
[ __ ] You fat [ __ ]
Have you looked at your [ __ ] self
for once in a [ __ ] day? You [ __ ] fat [ __ ]
You know what I mean? He said he won't
meet me under any circumstances. Triple
H. So he's just another little keyboard warrior.
Yeah, he's just another little obsessed
keyboard warrior. Joseph Ferrar.
That's what he is. Just another little keyboard warrior. Yeah.
No, he's not all right. He's a little
He's a little prick. No, he's not all
right, mate. Yeah. If [clears throat]
you got anything to say, you can say it
on here and you can say it to my face. I
went on my mom's phone. I went on Lav's
live stream cuz I was eating and my mom,
it just come up on my mom's phone. My
phone was dead. And I see this guy
talking mad [ __ ] about me being a sad bastard.
Rav, I told you I will come up there and
you can say it to my face. And he
weren't interested. So just stop it. If
you're not going to say anything to
anyone's face, just stop it.
You biased nonsel loving [ __ ] [ __ ] off.
Oh my god, bro. The people not know when
to [ __ ] off. Yeah.
No, that that Joe is a he's a sad old
bastard, bro. He's a sad [ __ ] He's a
nonslegs lover. Kieran will tell you it as well.
[ __ ] off, man.
What about you, Steven? Do you like Joseph Ferrar?
Do you think he's all right?
No. I mean, I I might be biased cuz I
don't like biased people. I just don't
like biased people, bro.
I just don't like biased people that
think they're intelligent.
So, you know, that's that's my problem.
Sorry, bro. You know,
never worked a day in his life.
Do you like Joseph for Steven Howard?
Apparently, I've got no money to go out. That's interesting.
I get money every week as well.
I get money every week.
Apparently, I've got £30 to last me till
Christmas, even though I've got over a
grand and I get money every week. You
learn something new every day.
So, say I done my balls in, say I lost
all my money, I'd get money every week.
So the minimum the minimum I could live
off is over £300.
That's the minimum.
You know what I mean, bro?
But yeah, it is scary. You can't win
money anymore. That is very scary,
Steven Howard, bro. It's very scary.
That's scary, bro, that you can't even win money.
What? How can you win money except from
the football now, bro? I don't think you can.
I don't think you can, bro. Rates, I
don't actually think you can. You can't
even win [ __ ] money anymore, bro. No.
Is there any way you can win money
except from the football? I don't think you can. No.
Do you reckon you can or nah?
I reckon you've got I think I think you
got more chance winning on a slot, bro,
in the bookies and online roulette.
What do you think?
Do you know what team you want to do
next week, Stephen Howard? You want to
do Enfield Town and slow?
I've been studying them. They done it.
They done both. It was both scoring them
today and the odds were better.
I should have, but I weren't going to do
them anyways, so there's no point saying
I would have cuz I weren't going to do
them. But I was going to do Darlington.
You need to kind of study this [ __ ] But
it's uh odd, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. But I'm saying after how how can
you get money, bro? How can you win
money nowadays? I don't think you can in it.
I don't think you can win money, bro, anymore.
That's what I'm trying to say. I don't
think you actually can win money anymore
like you used to. No,
cuz online roulette is definitely fixed.
100%. It is fixed.
And the slots don't pay out. I don't
think you can win money anymore, bro.
Unless you get lucky on the FBI or you
do football, I don't think you can win.
You can't win, bro.
The industry is finished. Back when I
was 18, you used to win loads of money.
Now you can't.
I would say that bar roulette. Yeah,
you've got more of a chance of winning
than [ __ ] online.
[ __ ] knows, mate. [ __ ] knows.
So I remember I put 60 pound on the bar
roulette. I took out a grand. I got it instantly. Mad
because and you see a lot of people
don't play them as well. Triple H
because that Joseph Ferrar is full of [ __ ]
The guy's probably playing on demo mode,
bro. Like the thing is you can't win
like that on their machines. I know it
and you know it. And it's not jealousy.
I don't care about anyone else, bro. I
would love for someone Yeah. to go into
every single one of them bookies and and
make them go bust. I would love it. But
that's not how it works. You know it and
I know it. I'd love some [ __ ] to go to
every single bookie and clean them out
for millions, bro. And I'd say fair
play. But unfortunately, that's not how
that works. So he's full of [ __ ]
Yeah, he's full of [ __ ] bro. You can't
win like that. That's what I'm saying.
You trust me. Last Christmas, I got
rinsed, bro. Rinsed with their machines.
Wrenched. Absolutely wrenched. 600, no
bonus. I think it was 650 no bonus,
brother. I got rinsed from them
machines. Absolutely wrenched.
Especially this time of year.
Betting on football is good this time of
year cuz at least they can't rig it.
You used to keep them in business,
didn't you? Uh, Triple H, every week you
used to blow your wages, didn't you?
Bless you. You used to keep them betting
shops in business.
They saw you coming, mate. They saw the
white man coming. >> [laughter]
>> They saw the white man coming, mate.
That's what I used to say. That's what I
used to say when I used to loss.
Bro, I'm not doing Christmas out of
choice. I've got money, brother. I've got money.
Yeah. They saw the white man coming, mate.
That's what I used to say. Yeah. They
saw the white man coming. Yeah. [laughter]
I don't know why I used to say that.
>> Yeah. He hasn't took them to the cleaners though
because he's only showing wins. But
yeah, I don't think you can win on um
online roulette anymore, bro.
I don't think so.
[snorts] I don't know, bro. Who knows?
Yeah, they saw the white man coming.
They saw the white They saw the white
man coming, bro.
You used to keep them in business,
didn't you? Triple H, every week. Bless you.
>> Yeah, they saw the white man coming. [snorts] And uh
I've got about £1,500 to last me a
month. Triple H.
Yeah, I've got about £1,500 to last me a
month. Steven Howard, how's that ever
going to last me a month? I'm so skinn. Yeah.
Yeah. I agree. I agree. Yeah,
I like show
but I'm a little copycat.
It's harder to save money now, brother.
I ain't got a house, but it still comes.
It just comes a lot slower.
Like about not having a house is no
responsibilities. Oh, it's lovely.
No one calling me back to the house.
That's one good thing about it, bro.
Sat there last month, £1,700, getting
money every week, no responsibility. Oh, it's lush. Meow.
You little copycat. Meow.
She will call me out.
I I knew this guy. Yeah. He lost his
wages and his dad had to lend him £300
for the month. I was dead.
I was [ __ ] dead, bro. [laughter]
I was [ __ ] dead. Triple.
No, I was dead, bro. [ __ ] dead.
Yeah, I was dead, bro.
Bless you. They saw the white man coming.
They saw the white man coming, lad.
Yeah. No, I lost 200 pound on roulette.
Yes. uh earlier.
No, I'm not good at all.
You don't like shing gay?
What did you say? Triple H nonslegs was
copying then. Was he copying the crowd? Meow meow
meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow
meow meow meow meow Ow. [screaming] Little copycat. Oh yeah.
Yeah. Even worse. Yeah. He needs to get
a job. He needs to get [ __ ] lied.
T going to [ __ ] die of virgin. Yeah.
I just think he needs to get laid.
I think he just needs to get laid. Hey,
haven't found my other channel and they never will.
These little nerds Ricky Millington.
Oh, do you remember that account? Ricky Mill.
Yeah, I had a back already change. Yeah.
Yeah, I had a macaroni cheese.
It was cooked for me.
Nice, bro. Nice.
Nice mad dress. Lovely.
I could do with a mad address, but I'm
not a little copycat.
Yeah, I won't eat again.
No, not interested in eating me. Yep.
Red Stars got no life. Oh, do you know
how sad this loser is that him and
Nonlegs they uh they message each other
on updates about me? He's such a loser,
bro. They're proper proper losers. You
know that Red Star? Yeah. He emails like
Dodge and Dodge emails him. Imagine
being that obsessed with someone that
you don't even know. What a [ __ ] loser. Loser.
And you've been doing it for years as
well. They're losers, bro.
Yeah, they're proper proper losers. They
ain't got nothing in life. Nope. You
can't handle spicy curry at all. Nope. No.
Well, no, cuz he lives in Thailand.
But I speak to him every day. Yeah.
We usually said that if I had a child to
approach it would get whisked straight
into the care system.
Yeah. the baby would get whisked
straight into the care system.
I could get a takeaway, but I can't be
bothered, bro. I'd rather just save the
money to be honest.
It was Grezy
whisked straight into the care system. [laughter] Baby Peter.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
200 [ __ ] pound on [ __ ] roulette,
man. What the [ __ ] Yeah,
>> I need to go cine more on Tuesday. I
just don't feel like doing anything.
You know what I mean? Um, Dusty, I just
don't feel like doing [ __ ] all.
Just nothing, mate.
Will these people ever leave me alone?
Triple H, will they ever leave me alone?
Just checking my emails.
I found you, Curry.
No, I'm not getting I might get some chicken chips.
No, I'm not getting nothing, bro. Uh,
nice curry. I'm fasting. Peter B is
fasting. Peter Betty will get fat.
Else Peter Betty will get really fat. Hey,
I'll never deposit on that site ever
again. [ __ ] £17, bro.
£17 fee. What the [ __ ]
I lost £200 on roulette. Yeah, I do have
fish and chips, bro. I love fish and chips.
I love fish and chips, bro. But mainly
from the seaside cuz it's less greasy.
Yeah, I do like fish and chips.
Yeah, it's lovely. I like a savoy as
well. I could go to the Chinese and get
a Savlo and chips. I like savoy.
Ben, I'll never forget one of your quotes.
Same people, same story. See you next year.
I'll never forget that.
Same people, same story. See you next
year. Oh my god, that's mad. [laughter]
And I think you come off for a year
after that, didn't you, Ben?
Didn't you, Ben 10?
You come off for a year after that,
didn't it? And you come back. And what
happened after you come back? [laughter]
Oh, I love I love I love Fzilos. I like
the strawberry ones, actually. Yeah.
Yeah. And was it was it a different story?
It's the same repeating people. Ben, [snorts]
your skin. Get a job. Your skin.
Yeah. I lost £200 on roulette. Ben, it's
[ __ ] fixed. I lost £200 earlier on roulette. Bro,
I was going to either put it on the
football or put on roulette. I don't
think you can win money now, Ben.
It's too hard to win money now.
It's too hard to win. Um, filthy Ben.
I It's too hard to win money now, Ben. Bro,
I wish I could have went to O'Neal's today, Dusty.
Oh, O'Neal's Water Street. I bet
everyone's having a laugh there now.
They're having fun.
I bet it's lovely to get into. I bet
it's a lovely place today, ain't it?
Yeah. Water Street. O'Neal's Water
I used to clean them up for money, bro.
the casinos. Then I'd go to the O'Neals
casino. O'Neal's casino. O'Neal's
[ __ ] bro. They got [ __ ]
Seriously, bro. Every week they used to
get [ __ ] by me, bro.
Yeah, it's going to be rammed today,
Dusty. Absolutely rammed. More rammed
than New Year's, I reckon.
Yeah, definitely more rammed than New
Year's. Today's going to be packed at
O'Neals, trust me.
What happen? What happen if I tried to
get into the O'Neal's dusty?
You can't come in. You can't come in.
I'll be like, "You can't come in." Yeah.
Country is a joke, bro. Punchy's a [ __ ] joke. No.
Do you remember that account trip? Peter
Betty can't get attached anymore.
Because he's already found his mama.
Do you remember that comment, Triple H?
Do you remember that account, Dusty?
I've not seen it for a while. It might
be busy with Christmas. There's nothing
Peter Betty can do to change. He's [ __ ] Citro.
Yeah, scumbag. That account, is it?
They've not been around for a while.
You can't quit YouTube and leave
Greavves you without content. Poor [ __ ]
I'll never forget that. Poor [ __ ] [clears throat] Yeah. Don't copycat.
I'm not sure. I know Nenegs is a virgin
though. He needs to get laid. He needs
to get [ __ ] live. He's going to die.
He's going to die one. He's going to die
one. He's going to die one.
Now, I fancy some fish and chips, Dusty.
But the fish and chips around here, it's very um
the fish and chips around here is very um
it's very greasy.
Unless she goes, I might just make some eggs.
I don't know. Yeah.
In before your skin comments, Mr. B.
I like Savoy.
Get Chinese. I've had that before. Um,
no. I just want to eat anything. I had
macaroni cheese. So yeah. >> Yeah.
And I'm not skin either, Dusty. I've got money.
I've got money, bro.
I've got money.
That's the mad thing about it, bro.
believe this red star just sits on
YouTube stalking people all day. Is
anyone like normal enough to understand
how weird this is?
Does not does anyone not understand how
weird this is?
sat on YouTube stalking someone you
don't know for years every day for
years. Do you not think that's a bit weird? Dusty triple
think it's weird, bro.
From the time you wake up to the time
you go to bed.
Do you not think it's weird?
I don't know.
You're banned again.
Uh, Terry's doing this [ __ ] again.
Joined eight hours ago.
Yeah, these people really need to get a
life, bro. I'm not even responding to
that. When are these people going to get a life? 2026.
[ __ ] women despise you as well, Red
Star. You're [ __ ] still a virgin.
You're the one that's sat on YouTube
every day, you little virgin. Hey, bro.
I'm going to unblock this Red Star
account right now. Yeah. And I'm going
to show you how much of a loser he is.
A loser stalker. I'm going to unban him
right now. Yeah. And see how quickly he
comes in the chat. He's a loser.
He is a [ __ ] loser.
One of life's losers, bro. My ugly life
loser. No life.
I've unbanned the [ __ ] so you're going
to see how quickly they uh
they're not my They're not my Reddit
accounts. But yeah, he's a stalker. He's
got no life. He's a fat ugly loser, bro.
Little bully victim.
He's a bully victim. He hasn't got a life
by being sat on YouTube recording
everything. Pat Mustard used to do it. Remember?
Pat Mustard used to do the same thing.
Yeah, Pat Mustard used to do the same thing, bro.
They're fat, ugly, jealous stalkers. I
don't know how they can live like that
though. Every year, every day for years.
Like every days. I don't know how they
can live like it, bro.
like every day for years how they can do
it. Like I don't understand.
Years and years and years they've been
doing this, bro.
Years and years and years and years and
years and years and years they've been
doing this, bro. these people here, you know,
talking about women detesting me. Well,
you're still a virgin. So, what does
that say about you? Yeah.
Here he is.
I can't see any comments. Let me have it.
It's you. No woman. You. No money. You.
That's you. Yes, you. I know you've got
no money, no family, no woman. That's
you. All of those are you people. That's
why you on YouTube every day. Repeat.
That is you. No money, no life. That is
you. You, you, you, you, you. The letter
you. That's you people. We've seen
evidence of this. We've seen evidence of
you people. No family, no girlfriend, no
money. It's you. You. You. You. You.
You've never been seen with money. You
never been seen with women. No family.
That is you. You. You. You. You.
Everybody knows that I've got more
family than anybody on this community.
Bro, you are the ones that are sat here
every day calling people skin cuz you
skate yourselves and you've been doing
it for 12 years cuz you're spastics.
What do you win, bro? You don't win anything.
You're skint ugly, no family people that
can't get off of YouTube and get a life.
What do you win? You can't even go out
in public without being bullied, bro.
You fat, ugly, skinned people don't win
nothing. You got no money, no family, no
future. That's why you're on here every
day. Can you explain to me how you have
anything if you're on here all day,
every day? Can you explain this to me?
You got family, you got you got women,
you got money. Why are you on there
every day typing your life away?
No, that's you, bro. That's you.
That's you people. And what are you
people? Middleage, no job, no money, no
girlfriend. That's you, bro. You are in
your 40s, no family, no job, no
girlfriend, no life. What are you
people, bro? Everything is Everything is
yourselves, brother. I could literally
sit here with no money and I'd still
have more than all of you people. That's
how bad your lives are. I could be sat
here with no money and I'd still have
more than you losers. That's saying
something, bro. I could be homeless and
I'd still have more than you losers.
You YouTube losers that ain't got
Hey, for years same skin. Are they sure
they're not talking about themselves, bro?
What the [ __ ] bro?
Yeah, it's their life.
It's like that red store. A complete
loser. You've seen the moment I unblocked.
The moment I unblocked, he was there
straight away. He's an absolute loser
with no money, no life, fat and ugly.
Disabled. I told you, bro. They're the
same on here. It's just like that red
star. Nobody, no girlfriend, no future.
That's why he's got a channel dedicated
to me and stalking me. We'll never meet
anyone. We'll never say anything to
anyone's face, but that's another story.
But yeah, I told you, bro. In under a
minute, I told you
these people are going to be lonely this
Christmas, bro. They're going to be
alone. They're going to have no family.
They're going to have no family. And
they keep trying to deflect.
No family Christmas.
It's mad, isn't it? They do get worse
because they realize that, bro, it's
Think about it, right? They're lonely
every day. Every year, every day of
every year, they're sat on here calling
people what they are themselves. It's a
normal day. So, obviously Christmas is
going to get worse because they're going
to be alone Christmas. They're going to
be they're going to spend Christmas
alone. Lord J's going to be on here Christmas.
Bro, do you want me to go live on
Christmas and prove it? Do you want me
do you want me to put the live stream
on? Yeah. And walk to the shop and then
walk back and quickly end it. I'll prove
it, bro. I can prove that these people
will be on their Christmas.
I'll go live for like 20 minutes on
Christmas day and I'll leave it up. I'll
walk and I'll come back and then I I
want to know why they're on [ __ ] YouTube.
These little [ __ ] clowns. Hello. >> Yo,
>> they're [ __ ] idiots in it, man.
>> That's off at that like within within
under a minute he's coming that red.
>> He's a stalker. He's a stalker. He's got
no life, bro. He's been doing it for years.
What you said is quite right though cuz
you said it's the same [ __ ] It's been
the same [ __ ] for the past [ __ ] six
years. Skin, lonely, virgin. It's just the same.
>> Yeah, but they say that they've got an IQ,
but how can they be if they're
intelligent, right, when they think of
new things to say?
>> Not lying. Hey, that red star doesn't
miss a trick, man. Does he?
>> Nah, he's a proper proper loser. A
proper loser in it. Proper loser, bro.
But I don't understand how they can do
this for years though, bro. Like they do
they've been doing it years. Like
>> Yeah, it has been going on a while. Like
you'd think they get bored, wouldn't
you? But it just they seem to get worse.
>> I think they're disabled. They must be
disabled, isn't it? Like they must be
>> some misses, isn't it? >> Huh?
>> They're not happy in life. She They can't be.
>> So do you think LJ will be um on here Christmas then?
I don't know about Christmas Day, but
he'll be on it'll be on over Christmas period.
>> A lot of these people will be on here
Christmas. Do you know what they're
going to do? This is what they'll do.
Yeah. They're going to pretend that
they're not on here Christmas, right? In
hopes that I or someone else go live,
right? And then when we go live, they
will come on saying, "Oh, you're on here
Christmas." When in reality, they're on here Christmas.
>> That's what they'll do. You know that
>> they'll turn it on to you. That's
exactly what they'll do.
>> That's what they'll do. But we because I
was live last Christmas. They were on
here. They were on here, bro. Yeah, you
were saying that lad. I looked mental that man.
>> You was there last year yourself? I'm
sure you was there.
>> No, I don't think I was on Christmas lad.
>> I'm sure you was or the day before or after you.
>> Yeah, it might have been the No, been
boxing night. I was going to boxing it.
It might have been your Christmas Eve.
>> You know what I mean?
>> But these people are mad lad.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
seems on Peter staying in for a whole
month so he can save his benefit money
for New Year night. [laughter]
>> That's self That's self projection.
That's self projection. I've got more
than enough money to go out now and
>> that's self projection. Must be talking about yourself,
>> brother. But I had a I had an account
earlier say that I've been living off
beans on and toast. What the [ __ ]
[laughter] Yeah, that these people
definitely are talking about themselves,
bro. Definitely definitely talking about
themselves. I do not think that why are
these people right not on a work sto
because if they work chair they'd be out
today in it a lot of them
the custard man
>> no but a lot of them would be wouldn't they
>> you would think like yeah you'd think
they'd have yeah
I've been on quite a lot recently like
but I've keeping off the ring for a bit
me so it was a loser loser
>> you must get the same comment
D and D out.
>> Yeah, they are proper proper boring, bro.
>> It's just the same [ __ ] in it.
>> Yeah, but they say that they're not disabled.
>> There's something not right with them in there.
>> Yeah, 100%.
I just think they're just fat, ugly, old
people. That's what I think about a lot of them.
>> Got they can't have
>> No, they can't. It's not like they've
done it for a month.
>> It's not like they've done it for a
month for over co or during the winter.
They've been doing it years, bro. And
they will continue.
>> It's been going on a while. I know. >> Yeah.
>> Yes, man.
>> I don't know why they keep Bro, I lost
£200, but £200 nothing to me, bro. I
still have money. Why? What the [ __ ]
>> But the reason these people are saying
that Christmas is canceled because
they're saying that you only have 200
quid and then you've gambled it and now
your Christmas is canled.
>> But I said, "No, but it's not that
though because I've got money, bro. I
told them see they're disabled on here.
You explain something to them and then
you have to keep explaining it, bro. 200
pound is nothing to me.
>> Yeah, exactly, lad. But you know what
these people get? Like
>> Yeah. Like it's something to them cuz
they're skint. That's why they're saying
it, bro. Because they don't have 200
pound to their name. You've just lost
200 pound. You just lost 90% of their
[ __ ] monthly benefits, isn't it?
>> [ __ ] I'm mad at it. Um
within within within under the minute
that a [ __ ] Red Star account was
coming, man. [laughter]
But but yeah, why is he not out with his mates? [snorts]
>> I don't think they have any on here. Do
I lad? [laughter]
>> No way. Is it?
>> Do you know when you said that today?
>> No, I'm off. I'm keeping off.
>> You know if you know if you went to
Newcastle. Yeah. It was going to be
Choco. Is it?
>> It'll be Ram. Yeah, it'll be Ram Black
Friday. Yeah, it'll be it'll be more Ram
today than it was than it will be New
Year's I reckon. Defer.
>> Oh, I don't know.
>> New Year's.
>> Maybe the same.
>> Yeah, maybe the same. Maybe the same to
be fair. Maybe.
>> I like boxing. DM me.
>> Yeah. I was going to put 200 pound on
two teams, but it would have lost
anyways. 200 would have returned 554.
It's good return, isn't it?
>> It is good return, but like you said,
you lost 200 quid on the roulette, but
then if you put on a bet, you'd have
lost. It's just the same sad song.
Everything you do gambling wise.
>> Yeah. Yeah, but at least with with that
roulette, you Bro, I'm telling you it's
rigged. That roulette online, bro. I'm
telling you, it's rigged.
>> I was I was betting 19. It misses everything. [laughter]
>> I've been telling you this for years.
It's rigged. Of course, it's rigged.
>> So, what like So, how could like So, how
would can you win gambling then now?
Like, except from like football,
>> match betting.
>> No, but except from that like
>> nothing. You can't make money gambling nowadays. Impossible.
>> You could before though, is it? Yeah,
you could. Yeah, I made a feel good back
in the day. Yeah, [ __ ]
>> But that horse racing now.
>> It's not Hey, did you you did you bet on
the box then?
>> No, BJ was 1 to 12 on
>> Oh, you know, you know, for that um Jake
Paul to win. The odds was only 12 to
one, you know, when it should have been
100 to one. Have you noticed that
[laughter] they've caught on to [ __ ] now
as well? They've made the odd [ __ ] on on
>> woke up and put the alarm on and watched
it, man. He was just [ __ ] he was just
running around the ring and that and his leg.
>> A lot of people would have lumped on um
a lumped on that. What's your name?
Anthony Joshua. Joshua.
>> Yeah. He's about to have 12 grand on
>> a lot of people a lot of people would
have lumped on that and they would have
lost as well. You know that because they
would have done it for like over certain
rounds and that in it like evens and
they would have lost and they would have lost.
>> The book is cleaned up again. I didn't
think it was going to go past two
rounds. Me personally. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. They did. Antman said as well he
was going to put money and he said oh
[ __ ] like would have lost it.
>> Yeah I had lost as well. I thought it
wouldn't run past 10
>> you know good things to bet yeah they
they it's hard to bro the only way you
can really beat the bookies. Yeah is I
think like with the double both teams to
score bro or like singles you it's hard
to beat a single haven't you a double
probably a double max I think the
trebles are me as well.
>> Yeah I never do I never do trebles. No,
>> I seen that Joseph Ferrar comment saying
um when you are playing on the roulette
wheel, Peter, I don't want you back to
the left hand side of the zero because
then it will go on to air.
>> Exactly like
>> Yeah, that but that was the first time
playing roulette in like Yeah. months,
bro. Three months.
>> Did you just I just I just f the bash, you know.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's not worth man. Nah,
it's [ __ ] in here. [ __ ] [ __ ]
[snorts] Yeah, it is [ __ ] bro.
>> Do you reckon you can win? Do you reckon
you could win in the bookies now on the slots?
>> No, man.
>> No, at all.
>> I tell you something. I tell you what
[ __ ] annoys me. That honor booket
Manny. Not that step, man. Puss always
winning videos. He's full of [ __ ]
>> Yeah, it's like Joseph Ferdo. He does the same.
>> I've been in bookies before and I've
lost [ __ ] 300 quid without even You
go into these bookies now, you barely
even see anyone on them.
>> That's how bad it is.
>> That's it. I one made no one no one's
ever on them. It' be [ __ ] empty all.
>> Yeah. The worst
Sundays Sundays they always used to be
on their machine Sundays, bro.
>> And you remember when they used to be 50
quid, 100 pound spins, you couldn't get
a [ __ ] a terminal, could you? At one point.
>> No. No. No. No. You couldn't. No, I
remember that. Yeah. [laughter]
I used to stand at me. Yeah. Yeah.
But I reckon you got more chance of
winning on that bar roulette than [ __ ]
>> No, that's a scam. It
>> is a scam. But the online's a scam as
well, is it? >> Yeah.
>> What did Monty say about this community?
He says that they're all fat, ugly
repeaters, isn't it? I
>> Monty said that, lad. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Did you watch his last live stream in it? Um,
>> yeah, I seen this last one. Yeah.
>> So, how do you know when he goes live?
Does it just pop up when you're not seeing it?
>> Say that again, lad.
>> So, how do you know when he goes live?
Does it just pop up?
>> No, I don't have notifications on me for people.
>> So, okay. So, what's his what's his
account name then?
>> Mad Man Campman. >> Huh? [laughter]
So what? You just typed it.
>> You just So what? You just typed his
name and it come up. [laughter]
>> You're in it too deep. You are >> mazala
to go on one of the vetting terminals like Peter.
>> Yeah. You should be annoying in it, bro.
>> Yeah. I've waited for half an hour 45
minutes before me.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Really? [laughter] Yeah.
Patty power. Have you ever been in a Patty Power?
>> Yeah, man.
>> Have you ever been in a Patty Power?
>> No. There's no Patty Power near. No.
>> Yeah. So, you've never been in one ever?
>> No. I've been in one of Middlesbr like
years and years.
Is there a lot of gambling places in
Middlesbr, bro? [ __ ] a few. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I can't remember seeing any to be fair.
>> What roulette do you like the best? The
global draw or the 20 bench roulette?
>> Um I like the I like both of them, but
with a with a global one, it could just
go on [ __ ] 10 to one. That's the thing.
>> Yeah, that's true. Yeah. Yeah, we can
one can as well. And it seems to be
harder to get the [ __ ] um the on the
green is it the pie gamble? It seems
harder on that one.
You know what I mean?
So you're going to be on here first of January? Yeah.
You're going to be on here first of January? Yeah.
Triple H is gone fire. Triple H. Yeah.
Look, my [ __ ] cover's gone undone,
bro. Look, my cover's gone undone. Look, bro.
It's gone undone. Look
what the [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah, man. I like
I like several. Franklin.
She's good looking.
Steven Howard. And if you don't like her, gay.
You're gay. No, you're gay. No, you're
gay. No, you're gay. No, you're gay. No,
you're gay. They all used to copy each
other. [ __ ] mind of your [ __ ] own.
No mind of your [ __ ] own.
He wanted [clears throat] to follow the crowd. Should
I get some food or not?
I don't know, bro.
Maybe to get some food.
All right. Hey, did you get your uh Did
you get your curry, Dusty?
Did you get your curry, bro? See,
why won't this red star leave me alone, Dusty? Oh.
Oh, no. What a weirdo trying to be
someone else. These people Why? These
people are proper disabled on here. They
need to grow up coming on here trying to
put up nudes.
Yeah, these people are [ __ ] proper
disabled on here, bro. Yep. >> Get
>> I might get I'm going to get a curry. Um
Dusty, but it's not going to be in
Madress. It's got to be a vindaloo. So
you can't call me a little copycat, can you?
You can't call me a little copycat, can
you? Are you going to call me a little
copycat? A little copycat? Meow.
You're going to call me a little copycat?
I don't know whe to get a tandoori. I
don't know, bro.
Mommy made me Oh,
I don't want a mad address. I want him
in the loot.
I'm a big strong Turkish man. Maybe I
won't bother. I don't know. >> [snorts]
>> Will this red store ever leave me alone? Uh, Dusty,
would this [ __ ] ever leave me alone,
bro? Like maybe next year or something.
It's getting weird now. His obsession.
Leave me alone.
What do you think?
He was there in under a minute.
What's your opinion on it, Dusty?
Leave me alone.
Come on. Did you just get curry and
rice? Sir Dusty,
did you just get curry and rice? [clears throat]
I'm going to get a takeaway, bro.
Yeah, I'm going to get this take, I think.
Thanks a lot, Dusty. [ __ ]
So, you know how I said about these eggs, right?
You know I said about these eggs and
people think I'm skin right
now. I've just ordered a takeaway. No, I
didn't get any. No, I just got thicker
curry and rice. Yeah.
Yeah. Chicken curry and rice, bro.
I didn't get any papa dums.
I don't really get none, bro. It's too filling.
So, how about I just afford how did I
just spend £21 on a takeaway then?
If I'm skint right, how have I just been
able to afford a takeaway
or just bought a takeaway, lads?
One second, bro. Hey,
if I can't afford if I can't afford
if I can't afford food, how have I just
bought a takeaway, bro?
So, how you how can you make money
nowadays, Dusty? You can't do it in it.
I don't think you said. Nah.
No way, bro. Nah.
Where is it, bro? I've just It's just
gone off again.
No pending orders. Why has it gone off again, brother,
when I've just ordered it? Hold on.
Oh god, I just ordered this and it's not coming up.
Brother, I've just ordered this. Where was it?
You don't have any orders in progress?
Well, I definitely definitely do.
Because I've just
Why isn't it coming up, bro?
Why is it not coming up again? Hold on.
One second, please.
I guess it was just going
I guess I'll just get a notification
when it's on its way.
It needs to [ __ ] off and get laid.
You're going to die a virgin.
I always said he was going to die a [ __ ] virgin.
[ __ ] virgin, mate.
That's why he always used to call me a
virgin because he's the biggest one going
because he was the alltime virgin. The
virgin of Hall of Fame.
because he is a big virgin with a little
dick that's never bit up my say it to
your face. You're nothing but a [ __ ]
virgin. Ugly rat face. Skinny little
nasty grand a month boy virgin.
That's on £1,000 a month. That's what
I'd say, mate.
That's what I'd say, mate. You're
nothing but a dirty little virgin. A
smelly little vulgar virgin. Yeah.
Why does the delivery not come up, bro?
There must be a glitch in this cuz I've ordered it
orders, but it's not coming up, man.
I've just ordered it, bro. One second.
Oh, don't worry. It's all in safe hands.
Yeah. Just like him. Lonely on YouTube stalking.
Like I said with these people, it's all
self-p projection of their own lives.
As you see, under a minute, he was
there. He's a fat, ugly slob that just
lies around on YouTube stalking.
He hates the fact that I'm younger and
better looking than him. This is where
all of this [ __ ] comes from. Dusty, am I
right or am I right, lad?
He hates that you're younger and better
looking. That's why he does all these
YouTubers lava for years. They've been
doing it for years.
They've been doing it for years.
He hates that you're younger and better
looking. And it's hard to accept the
fact. So that's why he does all of this YouTube [ __ ]
because he's a [ __ ] loser. Only a
loser could sit on YouTube all day every day stalking.
Only someone that's fat, ugly, and their
lives are over would do that. No person
does it, mate.
Do you know mate?
These people are lonely.
Yeah, these people are lonely. They know
all about being lonely. They're the
biggest loners of all time.
Lonely people sell YouTube and it's
going to be the same in 2026.
Do you reckon Red Star will come off of
YouTube next year? Do you think he's
going to be a loser for another year? Or
do you reckon he's still going to be
that YouTube fat ugly loser that can't
get off? Put your bets on, bro. Put your bets on. Yeah, man.
I've ordered food. Yeah, Mike. Oh, but
how did I order food? I'm skinn
apparently. How did I order food when
I'm skin? Triple R.
How could you order food when you're
skinned? Apparent apparently you're
skin. Well, by you, I mean me. How can I
order food if I'm skinn?
How can I order food if I'm skinn, bro? Answer it.
They said that I'm skin.
How can you order food if you're [ __ ]
skin? Cost me over 20 [ __ ] quid.
Because they're skin.
>> Because Red Star skin. Cuz LJ skin. Cuz
they're all skin. That's why they call
people skin, cuz they're skit themselves.
Yeah, that's their lives, is it, bro?
Yeah, use colana. Oh, yeah. You can do
that for food.
Yeah, [ __ ] losers.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, they do that now, don't they?
But bro, we all know the truth of it is
that these people are actually skint.
That's why they sit on YouTube every day
doing what they do because they are
actually the skint ones.
Like these people are really the skint
ones because think about it, bro. I'm
I'm I'm saving Yeah. and I don't really
go out much anymore, bro. And they're on
YouTube more than me. How can you explain that?
How can you explain that when they
they're on YouTube more than me? They
are literally on YouTube more than me
and I'm saving and I and I don't go out
and I don't really do much anymore.
So, it must be that these people are
skinned. That's why they're sat on
YouTube every day cuz they're skinned.
They're skinned themselves.
Where's my basketball shorts?
Oh, I just wear my dressing down. [ __ ] it. >> Yeah.
So, it must be that these people are skinn.
It must be that they're skin, isn't it?
If they're sat on YouTube every day, right,
from the time they wake up to the time
they go to bed, then they must be the
skin ones, in it. It must be them.
It must be them that are skin. It must
be these people. It must be their lives. No,
it is their lives, bro. They are [ __ ]
skinned as [ __ ]
That's why they call other people skid
to take the heat off the fact that
they're skinned on YouTube all day, every day.
Am I right or am I right? They want to
try and take the heat of themselves
because these people are skin. So that's
why they call other people skin. And
listen, Redshaw, you can show your 800
pound benefits, your [ __ ] skin, just
like Virgin Boy, your pair of skin
[ __ ] Pair of skin [ __ ] And you
showing your daddy's life savings
doesn't change the fact that you're
skinnier than a [ __ ] skin clinch.
Skint than a [ __ ] skin, mate.
Yeah, cuz they ain't got a life.
You tell me. Answer the question then.
If these people have got a life and
they've got money, why are they on here
all day every day?
I'm asking this question, bro. I want
someone to seriously answer it. If
they've got money and they've got a
life, right, and they've got friends and
family, why are they on it all day every
without taking a day off? I think that's
like a that's a normal that's a good
question to ask. Why are they on YouTube
all day every day?
I I I want to know, bro. I want to know
the answer to this.
Got to be something I'm missing, mate.
If they've got all of this money, right,
and everyone else's skin. Yeah. And
they're calling people. Why are they on
YouTube every day? Yeah.
There was a glitch with that, bro.
A fy skin flinch. Your skin
[ __ ] skin flinch. Skin fing.
So yeah, if they've got all this life,
all their money, why are they on here
every day? Doesn't add up.
Doesn't add up, bro.
Why are they on YouTube every day?
Can someone answer me? They got all this
life, all in this money.
Cuz they're skin. That's why. Cuz
I'm trying to understand it, bro.
Please, can someone help me understand it?
Oh, yeah. I paid I paid colana for my
food. These people are such mongos, bro.
They need to [ __ ] get alive. I'm off
of it um after today. Anyways,
it's the same atmosphere. It's the same [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, I'm off here after today for a
little bit, bro. But I'll be back first
of January. I'm coming back, bro. Don't
Don't miss that, bro. I'm coming back.
It's the same atmosphere, dusty.
Yeah, the same [ __ ] Same atmosphere, lad.
Nope. I'm waiting for my takeaway and
I'm eating it and that's it.
No waxies for me, lad. Nah, bro.
No axes for me, lad.
I've got a chicken curry tomorrow.
Ladies making me a chicken curry
tomorrow. I wonder if any of these
mothers any of these people's mothers
making them through food tomorrow.
Oh, it's a pub. It's a pub in central
London where loads of people go.
No, I'm having this food. I'm going to
chill out, watch some GTA stuff from
Yeah. Just go to sleep.
Yeah. All the women have got boyfriends
there. That's where I met Finnish Izzy.
That's where I met I met a lot of people in waxes.
It's £8 a pint there, Dusty. £8 a pint.
Yeah. Waxies £8 a pint. Yeah,
a trendy spot.
Yeah, it's all right to be fair, bro.
Yeah, it's all right to be fair.
Yeah, I just don't care about Christmas,
bro. I've got money, Dusty. I do have
money. I just don't care about Christmas this year.
I want to be back at the old house
with the tenants and [ __ ] I don't like it here.
It wears off, you know. It gets quite
boring. Not boring. No, isolated. Not
boring. Isolated is the worst is the word.
Who the [ __ ] is this?
>> Who's this? Whoa.
>> Are you disabled or something?
Yeah, they're definitely disabled on here, bro.
What the [ __ ] lad?
Yeah. No, it's that indigo.
It's that weirdo. Why is there so many
disabled weirdos in this community?
You know why you get um like you get if
you stay on here, you become like brain
damage? because you're hanging around
with spastics that create the same atmosphere.
So when you're off it for like 2 days,
you feel fine again and then you come
back on you're fine and by the second
day because they're mongos. And when you
sur surround yourself with these
disabled people, you become like them.
Like you've seen that Red Star, he's
been doing the same thing for years.
It's the same atmosphere. I'm surprised
they don't get bored of it. What lives
do these people actually have to be
doing this? None. No life.
They've got no life, bro.
And that's that.
Fat ugly people that ain't got no life. It
going to be lonely Christmas. These
people, bro. They're going to be [ __ ] lonely Christmas. Lonely Christmas.
That Joseph's another one that's
obsessed with me, bro. Another one that
wants my ass.
Your little non lover. Joseph Farra.
The reason I call him a non lover,
Dusty, is cuz whenever I go out used to
go out non legs,
um, he'd be straight to his rescue. So,
I just nickname nicknamed him the na lover.
It's always been his name, the notch
lover. But unlike him, I'll say
everything to his face. He will never
say anything to my face. I will say
everything to his face.
Christmas dinner. Bro, these people will
not be having a Christmas dinner.
They're skinned. They got no family.
How? They're not going to be having a Christmas dinner.
Christmas dinner, bro.
Christmas [ __ ] dinner. How they
getting Christmas dinner? The [ __ ] skin, you know.
Like I said, pray for 2026.
I pray for 2026 that there's a change in
this community, bro. I'm I'm feeling
positive about it.
Yeah. Then there's not going to be no
downfall, bro. I'm not failing. I'm up
as I ever can be. More up than these
fat, ugly, disabled losers. Anyways, yo.
>> Yes, lad. So, one needs to be having I'm
just waiting. I'm just waiting for my
I'm just waiting for my scr.
>> Yeah, lad.
>> You know what that means?
>> Food, lad. I How do you know what it means? Scram. Do
>> you ever get fish and chips?
Yeah, sometimes. But not a lot. Not
>> It's spot on though, isn't it?
>> If you got annoys me,
>> have you Wait, wait. Where's your
nearest sea slide? Black, it
>> probably red car. >> What?
>> Probably red car.
What's it called?
>> Red car.
>> Where's that? That's um isn't that where
they film that [ __ ] um two pints of
log I think?
>> Um no I'm still wondering it.
>> Oh okay. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. But if you
get it from the seaside and fish and
chips it's nice bro from the seaside. If
you get it from anywhere else it's always greasy. >> Yeah.
What was I going to say there? You said
these people won't be having Christmas dinner.
>> Oh that's one corn I was thinking about
dusty. You know two pints of logo packet
of crisp run corn I think. Yeah, they
won't have Christmas dinner. [laughter] >> Why?
>> Because they're skint
Why do these Why do these people come on
here every day calling people skin then?
>> That's a good question. I can't answer
that question cuz I don't know myself, lad.
>> Because surely it's good. Like if
everyone else is skint Yeah. then
they'll have a life in it.
>> You'd think they got bored of it,
wouldn't you? It's been going on for 8 years.
>> How long? about eight. Yeah.
>> Yeah. More than that, I think.
>> Yeah. Some of these accounts, if you
click on it, it would have it's been
made 13 years ago.
Some of these accounts.
That's [ __ ] mad.
>> I don't know why they do it. I don't
know why they do it, bro.
>> Huh? [ __ ] mad. Yes. So, do you reckon
there'll be a few people on here on that
Christmas day then? >> Definitely.
If you could name three who will be on
who do you think the three guarantees?
>> They're all going to be on.
>> I'd say Red Star
and I'd probably go for
>> LJ will be pretend he won't be but he
will be on it. He'll pretend he won't.
But he will be.
>> Yeah, he'll be on. He's always on.
>> I'm going to go live Christmas. I'm
going to I'm going to go live. Yeah.
Walk to the shop 10 minutes and come
back and hopefully there'll be no one on
the live stream, right? >> [laughter]
>> You'll have to let us know lad neck like
on Boxing Day.
>> Yeah. Do you reckon there'll be on on there?
>> There'll be stuff. I think there will be.
>> Do you know what I always pray for? That
I'll go live and no one joins. But they always join.
>> Yeah, there's normally a few in as well in there.
>> No, I want to go live one day and have
no one join for like an hour, but it
never happens. People always come in.
>> I think people have a notifications done.
>> You know, have you ever went on Timmy's
yet? They're in there within 2 seconds.
Is it? Have you ever clicked on it
straight away one time and you seen them in it?
>> Yeah, I've done that before. Like I
think I've I've been on YouTube looking
and come up to me live. So I press what accounts?
>> Uh the account who says skinned that
king Mr. B. They're always in on on his case.
>> Is it anyone ever is it anyone different ever?
>> Just the same people just the same names.
>> No, seriously.
>> So what do you want it to be? What do
you want it to be like? Different people
every day or >> um
Yeah, you've got to have a mixed up bit
of a mixup, haven't you?
>> It's not. It's the same people.
>> Same sad accident. I
>> They're like robots. I don't even think
they're people because how can they do
it for years? And are they actual people
behind these accounts?
>> They could be bots, couldn't they? When
you think about it, like if they've been
doing it this long.
>> Yeah. [laughter] Could be. It's true.
It's got to be bots, is it? Cuz it's weird.
>> Have you seen that channel um archive of
Peter F or something? He records a full stream. >> Yep.
>> I think that's a bot like.
>> Yeah, but you like it though.
>> Some of it's good laugh, but some of it
gets boring sometimes cuz it's just the
same [ __ ] in it.
What did you say? It is the same repeating [ __ ]
>> Yeah. [laughter]
>> So why did you say nonslegs was going on
about shovel cole then?
>> Say that again lad.
>> So why did you say nonslegs was going on
about shovel cole?
>> To fit in.
>> What? Like at school that
>> I just tried to be with the cold kids
but he's not cool kids is he?
>> Yeah but it's like you never done that.
Have you copied? >> No.
>> What do you get out of it? It
>> [ __ ] mad. Hey, he's one for your um
>> You had Chinese though, didn't you?
>> I had [ __ ] salt and pepp.
Yeah, it was
>> Yeah, my food's coming now.
>> Can you tell us that story with Sean
when he first had that spicy curry? You
warned him not who, didn't you?
>> Yeah, I warned him. So, you went
>> What did you say?
>> Went into this went into this Indian
place, right? And obviously I've always
had binderoo and he said, "Oh, I I want to
>> I want to try it." And I said, "Oh, I
don't think it's a good idea obviously
because people like him can't take spice."
>> And [ __ ] I warned him not to. I said,
"Oh, have like a chicken ka instead."
And then he had it. I said, "Oh,
whatever." And he was like,
>> he was struggling with it. And then the
next day he called me saying, "I've got
the shits. I've got the shits." I said,
"It's not [laughter] my fault. I [ __ ]
warned you. I've ordered you not to have
a vindaloo, but you wouldn't listen. You
wouldn't You wouldn't take advice that kid.
>> Yeah. You might have done it to try and fit in.
>> Yeah. The crowd, didn't it?
>> Yeah. So, what what is he? So, you're
basically saying that he's a copycat.
>> He just wanted to do to try and be cool,
but it backfired, didn't it? [laughter]
>> Oh, do you think you think Do you think
it was funny that I lost 200 pound? Ah,
>> I don't think it's funny anyone losing
200 pound though. [laughter] >> Huh?
>> Say that again.
>> Yeah, it's not funny losing, is it?
>> The [ __ ] depressing, is it?
>> Yeah, it is. I'm surprised you never
like used to kick off and smash machines and that.
>> I used to go off my [ __ ] didn't smash
machines up, but I used to [ __ ]
ever say anything to you.
>> It's like they're laughing at you, isn't
it? Yeah. Did you stop and ever say anything cheered?
>> The only thing I probably probably I'd
say I've done shop was like there's a
bloke was wet and then he just just
stabbed me. My name was to go and I
think I lost this one day. I said, "What
the [ __ ] you looking at?" Something like that
>> and I had a bit of an argument.
>> I had a bit of an argument with him.
>> Mad mad,
>> but like have the staff ever said stoping that?
>> Yeah, I know. There was this one mom who
I used to talk to in there, man. She was
a candy actually. She used to put a
block on the machine for me as well cuz
I used to go and I said I'm only having
50 quid or something in and then what
did you what did you call her? What did
you call her? A caddy last.
>> Yeah. Yeah. [laughter]
>> I said to her I said just I'm going to
put 50 on me card and that's it. Don't
point out she wouldn't like I blew me 50
and then she said no. I said nice one. I thank
>> you said you lost a grand in the bookies
once in it. I've done balls in bad lot.
No, I told you that story before. I was
[ __ ] I had about 1,500 quid in me and
then I went to the book a bit further
down because he would let me put no more
money on me car.
>> He said he stopped it. He said no more.
Did you laugh at you?
>> So how much how much did you lose and
all that there?
>> Got it all back. I clawed it all back,
didn't I? Cuz I put 200 quid in down the
coral down the road and I [ __ ] clawed every penny.
>> So when you when you when you used to
lose your wages, what did like what did
your parents say?
same the same old he said me that what
said to me he said you'll never change
you you'll always be better than that
but then then one day >> really
>> I used to ask him for I used to ask a
guy borrow off from that through the
week and that man
>> used to do what
>> I used to ask him for a borrow to get me
through a week cuz he used to do balls in
>> yeah really used to rely on that weekly
payment didn't you say that again you
used to like that weekly payment didn't Yeah. Yeah. And
>> you used to Yeah. lose it all, didn't you?
>> Then he used to get it and then blow it all.
>> Mad. Mad.
Crazy [ __ ] You are.
>> It's at zero section as well. I've noticed.
>> No, you're taking a piss.
>> No, it actually is. It's
>> No, it isn't cuz you used it.
>> No, cuz you used to bet zero.
>> Never ever bet zero on the roulette.
I make years ago.
>> I did about I did about 9 years ago. I
turned 10 into 500.
>> Nice lad. You watch
>> you watch the people on them roulets or
don't you like a lot of people like name
up everyone put that zero on that? I
don't back zero on it. >> Never.
>> [ __ ] that. I don't back never had back zero.
>> So do you know what I was trying to do
with Ant-Man? Did you get what I meant?
Like for the extra money you did you get
it or not? What what I meant?
>> Yeah. Yeah. So you open up new bank
account then they give you Yeah. I know
what you mean. Yeah. Yeah.
>> So someone else does it but they
obviously give you money in it.
>> You get money from making account.
>> How do you know? Have you done it?
>> No. I've seen it now advertisement but no.
>> Would you do it?
>> Not really. I don't need 50.
>> No. You wouldn't get 50. You'd get 100.
>> Oh yeah.
>> So it be it would be £400 a month. I'd
get 50 cuz it's split in it.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> So that's still that's still £400 a
month, isn't it? like, >> "Yeah,
>> but obviously Adman couldn't do it
anymore because of um uh they closed his
account, so he couldn't do it anymore."
>> You get me?
>> After Yeah, they cutting on off. The
only thing with that though, bro, the
only thing with that is they keep
sending you cards and you have to keep
like putting in the bin. I >> reg.
Yeah. The only thing with that is they
keep sending you cards and you have to
chuck him in the bin. send.
>> They keep canceling cards and sending
it. Yeah. To do it. So they send it to
your address. You have to keep chucking
the cards out. You know what I mean?
>> Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> So Ant-Man Yeah. He went Thailand. He
come back with like 200 cards. He
chucked them all in the bin. [laughter]
>> Imagine that.
>> Antman over there.
>> He loves it. Yeah. Yeah. Loves it.
No, but um Yeah. So it used to be 150 a
week but a lot of the sites cotton on.
Do you know what that means?
>> Clicked on. Yeah.
>> No. Like cotton on. You know what I
mean? What people are doing is it
>> on means click on what you scam you doing.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
It's funny you know all these saying is it
post the link and see if that um see if
anyone wants to come.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
I just find it depressing how you can't
win money anymore really on them
machines and that
>> the gamble industry is dead now mate
>> it is it is it is
>> you used to put you used to play the
slots when you used to go out drinking is it
>> yes I still do have a go now >> 20
>> 20 bar or something I couldn't think
where shot [ __ ] under bars and under
100 pound in them um under pots [snorts]
>> 20 quid if you win Oh, happy days. I
play the premiums, me I know what I like
on them in the uh pubs. I like that
[ __ ] catch of the day, me.
>> Oh, I ain't play that one. Yeah, I see
it. I see it though.
>> If you was to go bookies yet, what would
you say on the machine you got the most
chance of winning on?
>> That is it?
>> No, cuz you have to put the green bar
before you even get a [ __ ] spin
before you eat your numbers.
>> So, what then? What would you say then?
A slot in it. Obviously,
>> it's like that. I just play that
rainbow. He's po like that m premiums.
>> Did you used to like Did you used to
like my Frankie videos?
>> Yeah. I used to like that fishing
friends back in the day m loads of new
ones and all.
>> Yeah, but then it become they changed
the machines bro like last December they
they updated it. They upgraded the
machines the way they looked and since
they done that bro you can't win nothing
on the [ __ ]
>> They're going to upgrade them. The
amount of money the gambling industry
makes a year man's mental.
>> Yeah. The only thing they the only way
you can beat them is the football in it.
But even that's harder. But I'm I'm up
on the football. I'm up on the football
100%. I'm up on the football. [snorts]
>> Yeah, it's like I had a B. I did feel
better. We fell asleep. But uh I
wouldn't have had both teams go on their
um spares game. Both teams score on the
New York game. Both teams score
Southampton. I'd have done that as a
travel. That would have been me travel.
I said that Joe earlier but I didn't.
Imagine you what how much money would
you have if you put a six both score no
draw and you what you put 500 pound on
it you'd be rich in it for
>> would you ever have to work again do you think nah >> um
what you got for about 6 to 400
something like that 30 or
>> well two of them two of it seven to one
two seven to one so yeah you'll be rich
[ __ ] hell yeah my food's One second.
>> Something wedged.
>> Thank you.
>> Yeah, my food's gone, bro.
>> What you got, M? I mean, the little >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, um, yeah, it would be a
lot of money, wouldn't it?
>> It would. Yeah. Yeah. Hi.
>> Would you if you How much money would
you win? Yeah. before for you to quit work, >> right?
>> Um, [ __ ] >> 300k.
>> Not really. No, I don't care. Won't be
nothing. No, I million me. I [ __ ]
>> And you just And you'll just pack up work.
>> I'd never work again. Yeah.
The average expectancy of life like 60
60 to 65 like 60 well 60 to 70 just say
I'll just say just say good after hard
days go up and you know you got money
coming in it
>> yeah but when you used to put in the
betting chops or I was working all
working me off I like to put the lot in
>> you say you working your off I put the
lot in the fra [laughter]
go to nightclub I used to go nightclubs. Yeah.
>> Oh, look at that.
>> Is that ticker starter? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, that's why I get that.
>> I got some curry. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Not bad. I've got something else
to I've got something to say. Actually,
someone comment I seen someone comment
on your Indian curry before you loo.
Someone said you put um you put loads of
rice around your curry so it's not that hot.
>> Oh, really? Is that what I said? So
instead of eating like instead of
tipping it all on, you just you get a
little bit out and putting been eating the rice.
>> Okay, I'll do it now then. Sorry.
>> I never saw that problem. Oh [ __ ] >> Me.
Try it, lad. Try it. H.
>> What'd you get, Lamb? Vindelo. Oh, yeah. [ __ ] yummy.
>> Yeah, it looks all right. Like I
>> like a masala, mate. [sighs]
>> A what?
>> Take a masala.
>> I never had that.
>> You what?
>> I said I've never had that.
>> What? You never take a massage? >> No.
What you trolling?
>> I don't. No, I never. I've never had it, bro.
>> It's mild or belly. >> Mhm.
>> It's mild.
>> Have you Have you ever had a mad dress?
>> No. Don't bother. Not me. I'm not a spice person.
>> You're a bit like nonsense. >> Yeah.
I like karma.
Samuel Samuel Jackson said he likes karma.
>> My mom My mom likes karma.
>> Is your mom a work? >> No. [snorts] >> Sometimes you what?
>> We call her.
>> Does your mom sometimes watch that John Ly's live?
>> Yes. Yes. [laughter]
What did he say about her? [laughter]
>> She's right leg, lad. Yeah. [snorts]
>> So she she's sub to that lav. >> Mhm. [laughter]
>> Yeah. So does she get the notifications
when he goes live? >> Yeah.
But you don't just click on it. [laughter]
Be off if she commented on [snorts] what
>> funny if she commented on her.
>> You know what though? Yeah. I don't
really like Indian in the summer, you
know. It's too I don't know.
>> Say that again.
>> I said I don't really like eating um
Indian in the summer. I don't know why. >> Yeah.
You look good on your live stream. You
haven't brushed your teeth for two
weeks. Is that true? >> No.
>> I lied.
>> I mean, you used to piss in the bottles and that
>> when I wake up when I wake up, I piss in the teeth. >> Yeah.
>> No. [ __ ] Why do you do that?
>> Do you not understand? You don't
understand the point of it.
>> No, lad.
>> Well, you wake up with a boner.
>> I don't know.
Yes, you [ __ ] do.
You don't wake up with a boat. >> Nah.
>> [ __ ] off.
>> I don't know. car it.
>> Oh, Sean.
>> Yeah. And you? Yeah.
>> Huh? She's not my She's not from She's
all right, but she's not from the airline. >> Why?
>> He'd watch He'd watch Ed Matthews.
>> Yeah, I was watching. He was in New
York. I watched him on kick.
>> Yeah, I watched it. Yeah, he's he's
[ __ ] good. Good crack. He gets some bad.
>> Yeah, he gets He deals with a lot of
[ __ ] as well though, ain't it?
>> Yeah, he does, lad. Yeah.
>> He's women, bro. I've seen it. But yeah, he does.
>> It's funny, is it? Funny, bro.
>> How do you know about him? How did you
find out about him?
>> Big [snorts] Tik Tocker. Well, a big
Yeah, he's a big [ __ ] dream one. You
know what I mean?
>> How do you know about Jake Paul and Logan Paul? >> YouTube. >> Really?
>> [ __ ] got what? What? I watched a
fight yesterday, man. It was [ __ ] mazing.
>> You watched the side, man. That's funny,
isn't it? [snorts]
>> I've never watched that me, lad.
>> You don't know them?
>> No. Why is this charger not working? One second. What?
>> Did you see that guy knocking your
chest? That's funny. No, I'm not. Didn't
see that lad.
>> I only watch a little bit cuz like I get
bored of him sometimes when he just
[ __ ] talk [ __ ] That them
>> you watch you watch you watch KSI.
>> I watched him fight that [ __ ] Tommy F.
KSI is famous, isn't it?
>> Yeah. You like them prime drinks?
>> Yeah, they're all right. I've had them.
>> I like I like the orange one.
>> I like the blue raspberry one, mate.
>> I've had that one as well. I used Bro, I
used to have the blue raspberry one.
Yeah, brother. I used to have it with
>> with white Captain Morgans. It used to get you, bro.
>> Yeah, you used to like your room, didn't you?
>> Yeah, but bro, I think it' kill me now.
I used to drink the white Captain
Morgan. You know how strong that is?
>> Yeah, it's strong.
>> Have you ever had it?
>> Oh my m the white one though.
>> It's hard to get. You can't just get it.
I used to get ordered in from me or you
can get online. You can't just get it.
>> Didn't you used to drink on your live streams before? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, I can remember them. Yeah. Yeah. >> Yeah. Remember Izzy? Who? >> Isabelle.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Did she drive her?
>> She wasn't for me. Yeah, but she might
have been for you.
>> You need to You need to tell Nex that uh
you need to tell Nex that Britney has moved on.
>> Yeah. Huh?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Did um what' you get with
Sean's girlfriend? Yeah. No.
Bro, he always used to go on about this
Britney in Canada. Do you remember?
>> No, it must have been before my time.
>> He said that he's to kill himself over
someone from Canada.
>> Actually, [ __ ] hell.
>> He needs to I think you need to tell him
that she's moved on, you know.
>> That's it, lad. How do you think [ __ ]
reckon most of these people got on here
through Tim Eldridge?
Probably a lot of people. Yeah, I did.
>> I wonder I wonder Red Star got on
through Shawn Ma probably.
>> Yeah. What do you think of that Red Star
loser in it? >> Yeah.
>> I think some of his content is quite
funny to be fair. Like
>> I don't think it's funny, but I think
it's sad. Don't forget this is their
whole life. I don't think you
understand, bro, that it's their whole life.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> You don't think that it's it's mad?
There's mad lad. But
>> that's all I've got in life. Clearly
>> they text each other. Nonstop text about
me when they're out in that when
nonsense is out. You don't feel that sad. [laughter]
>> What do you mean? Like proper properly
text each other.
>> Yeah. They let each other know if
there's any new stuff, [laughter]
>> but they say they've got a lie.
>> That's [ __ ] mad that lie.
>> Tim went downhill recently. I think he's
been on drugs. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. He's lost a bit of weight, Samuel,
hasn't he? Tim's lost a bit of weight.
Yeah, I think he's been on that Buzz.
>> Always on that Tim Eldridge's case. That Mask Miller.
>> I don't know his channel, but I've heard about him.
>> Yeah, he's be always on his case. >> Yeah.
>> Do you remember that Bruce Millington song? Yeah. Yeah.
>> What? Do you see it?
>> You are.
>> Do you see that account?
>> Oh, Ricky.
>> Ricky Mill. Do you see it?
>> I've seen him about floating about your head.
>> I thought at first that was you.
>> Why would that be me?
>> I don't [clears throat] know.
>> She don't want you.
>> Remember to braid. Be Be realistic. Yeah.
>> Then what? What? Cuz I told you to meet
up with it. [laughter]
>> Did you? Uh,
>> so what do you do on a night now? When
you wide awake, you go on that Reddit
and do you
watch I just watch GTA videos?
>> Oh dear.
>> Like you see, have you seen the shorts
where it comes up? What happens in this
GTA and that GTA? It's addicting. You've
seen it, I'm sure. I know.
>> Nah, don't [ __ ] bother a GTA.
>> Basically, it says like what if you do
this, this happens in this GTA and they
list all the GTA and what happens in
them ones to get it. Like
>> I know what you mean. Yeah.
>> Yeah, it's addictive as [ __ ] They're
only shorts, but it's addictive, bro. It is addictive.
>> Why don't you go back to doing your live
streams on the PlayStation when you used
to play GTA? There were the there were
the bad days when that were at the peak there.
>> You can't do it on Xbox.
Oh, can't you?
>> No. You've got a game of console.
>> Nah, not now, lad. >> Really?
>> I've got one. I don't play on it.
[ __ ] in the for me.
>> Do you remember when they were going on
about your um the burger on your floor?
>> N it still goes onto this.
>> I don't see anymore. I don't see
anymore. Does it?
>> Yeah, [snorts] it was going on in leases earlier. >> What?
They was saying it in leases earlier.
>> Who? Which one?
>> JX Real Face or someone
>> cuz that's you don't understand. That's
all they've got on you. So they will use
that until they find something new. You
know what I mean?
>> The sad man, aren't they?
>> And because they don't have anything
new. You understand?
>> Losers like what you need to do. Just
ignore them. P.
>> You just need to ignore them. So if I
ignore them, right, and I just do
videos, come back in two years, they
won't still be doing it.
>> No, yeah, they won't be. No, they'll
they'll call it a day cuz you know,
you're not they're not getting the
reaction out of you, but it go for
months and months after you leave. But
>> no, I think they will still do it. I
think they still Yeah,
>> because you could even when I haven't
reacted for Bobs, they they still do it.
Like you go on the channel and there's
been it's it says uploaded an hour ago.
You get it? >> Yeah.
>> I don't I don't think they do it for a
reaction. I think they want to [ __ ] me,
bro. I think they want my ass or
something. That's what I think. I think
they're gay, bro. I don't want these people here.
>> It's that Red Star, man. He's even fine. You count.
>> He's a loser, is it?
>> So, what do you what would you guess he
looks like in real life? This Red Star.
>> Not a [ __ ] clue, lad. Would
you say he's young or if you was to guess like that again?
>> But I said, would you say that he's young?
>> I'm going to go No, I think that could
be that red. I think could be that
chase, mate. That's my guess. >> Yeah,
>> why don't they go for Monty? Why does
none of these people go for Monty again?
They do go for Monty man, but Monty
man's not on as much as you.
>> Yeah, Red Star doesn't go for Monty.
>> I know. He Sean's mate. That's why I
think it's I think it's Chase that Red Star me.
>> Yeah, that chase is another little [ __ ] It
>> You remember You remember him?
>> You and him, my mate. >> No,
>> you were at one point.
>> Hopefully he loses his Valentine's card
next year, would it? >> [laughter]
>> That doza for a little snake. I see him
talking [ __ ] about me on meies earlier. Triple [laughter]
>> yours. All right. I don't mind.
>> No, but yeah, but I thought talking [ __ ]
about me, bro.
>> Did you pull him up on it?
>> Yeah. Yeah, but I said you you're saying
I'm a sad bastard and that. Say it to my
face. If you got anything to say, just
say it to my face. Don't You're not
blocked on this channel. They're not
blocked on this channel. Do you let me, bro?
Yeah. Where's that from? Newcastle.
>> Uh, Yorkshire. North Eastern. Same same
[ __ ] And I said to him, I don't mind
going Newcastle game and stopping off
Yorkshire if you want to say anything to
my face. And then he says, bro. Then he
says, oh um, I'll never meet you. I'll
never meet you. But then he continues to
talk [ __ ] So he's no better than non, is he?
>> You got on well with that at one point, didn't you?
>> Yeah. They started being biased.
>> I don't think you I don't think you
understand what he's doing, bro. Do you?
Are you Are you intelligent enough to
know what he's doing?
>> He's just making him jealous by winning, isn't he?
>> His channel is dedicated to trying to
troll me indirectly. Do you understand it?
>> What? By putting loads of wins up in there
>> by showing wins. That is not like you
don't win all the time like and what
he's doing indirectly. And if you go on
if you go on if you go on um if you go on right
one second if you go on elabor and you
see him type it's always about me you're
not seeing what he's indirectly doing bro [laughter] I don't
>> he's trying to troll but he thinks he's
smart but he's not I know what he's
doing bro I'm not I wasn't born
yesterday bro you know
>> yeah I don't know They're sados. That
Joe is a sad, bro. He was on here
earlier. I was talking to him normally
earlier and he said, "Have you got any
presents?" I said, "No." And we was
having a normal conversation. I woke up,
bro. My mom cooked me food. I went my
mom's phone. I went on and he's talking [ __ ] What?
He said that he's not going to meet me
and he's still talking [ __ ] and he's
telling people that they will do nothing.
>> [ __ ] mental. I don't know.
>> But yeah, he definitely definitely only
shows wins. What do you like more
YouTube already? I know you got some
[ __ ] on. And like I told you, but I
wouldn't be jealous if if somebody
cleaned out all of them bookies for
millions. I'd be happy. I'm not jealous,
bro. I don't get jealous of people.
>> That's it. And
>> I'm telling you I'm just telling you
facts that someone can't keep winning
like that. That's it's facts, bro.
People are allowed to have like an
opinion and not not be jealous. You know
what I mean?
>> Yeah. But he has had a few wins, Joe,
but like you said, he doesn't tell you
his losses, does he? But um >> yeah,
>> he has been on a [ __ ] has been on a
winning streak lately and like I've
never seen the B shop out like like that. Like
>> Listen, listen. Go to the bookie
tomorrow and you will lose. I guarantee
you you will lose.
>> 100%. Yeah. Well, 99% you'll lose. Yeah,
>> you're going to lose. So, how does this
guy keep winning and then what and what
he's trying to do is when you're
questioning it, he's trying to make it
seem like it's jealousy when it's not.
is making valid points
cuz think about it, bro. Say someone
someone my channel when I was only put
up wins yet and they said, "Oh, you does
that mean they're jealous?" No, it doesn't.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Exactly. Yeah.
>> You need to be realistic about what you said. >> Yeah.
>> Eventually, you will lose a lot of money
if not all of your money when you're
playing [ __ ] like that.
I've seen one of your I've seen one of
Joe's videos where he was [ __ ] Was he
[ __ ] 86 or 800 pounding? >> Yeah.
>> You would never do that again.
>> No, I'd never go. I wouldn't play them
again. Like I never ever play a property
again in my life. Like doesn't interest me. [snorts]
That's not He's another one. He's
another one that's obsessed at Joe. He's
another one obsessed.
>> Yeah, he's another one. Here's
your mate in it.
>> And you'll remember that Zing Zings.
>> Uh yeah. But yeah, actually the one
the one about is it
>> Zing Zing. Yeah.
>> The one from Liverpool with a blue
picture in it.
>> Yeah, that's him.
>> I remember it.
>> He was all right. That's
>> I don't remember him. I wasn't here to
>> I remember him. [laughter]
>> I want I want Mr. James Spoon back.
>> I wonder what happened here. Yeah.
Haven't seen him for ages, man.
>> Maybe just got stick of it in it.
>> He said he's on the field a month ago, didn't you?
>> Yeah. Yeah. He comes on very very very rarely.
>> Very rare you'll see that come. Remember Pat Mustard? >> Yeah.
>> You liked him, didn't you?
>> I thought he was some of the things he
was funny, but he was a sick puppy, man.
Sick sick man.
>> You like London Taylor, is it?
>> I don't. I've never had a problem with
Taylor. I think he's all right. London
>> Yeah. Yeah.
Me used to hate that. Yeah. Taylor him as well. >> Yeah.
>> When he went to Scotland to meet Shadow,
>> did he? I don't know. I didn't see that.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Did you show up? >> No.
>> Give it to like he's g him. >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Oh, man. Stop. You know what that means?
>> He better be your roast, didn't he? Yeah.
>> Yeah. Is it funny? [laughter]
>> Yeah, but the neighbor the neighbors the
neighbors didn't know, did they?
>> I don't know. What What time about was that? Like, >> huh?
>> What time about was it? Early. I was at [laughter]
>> You ran out the back door. Someone said,
"No, that day I wasn't even there. I was
in Nottingham. Remember
there was two. Was your mom was your mom in
You know, she moved out one of the times.
>> So, do you reckon I could I would have
died then if I was in need to give you a good
>> Yeah, but not not death in it. Yeah,
I've had an actual break. Listen,
listen, bro. Listen. Imagine. Yeah.
You've gone to bed yet and you woke up.
You woke up to violence over YouTube. Imagine.
I know what you're saying, but [laughter]
you're on the phone. You fall asleep and
you woke up to be beaten up. [laughter]
>> What did they do? Put the windows in.
>> It's not funny, is it?
>> Well, you think it's funny cuz you're laughing.
>> No, I'm not laughing. You're laughing. [laughter]
You're not because how could that be over YouTube?
>> No, it wasn't over YouTube. You were
[ __ ] being racist to run, weren't you?
>> Yeah, but it was over you. Yeah, but
that was on YouTube though.
>> I think he had enough Taylor and he [ __ ] this.
>> Yeah, it was it was over. He's calmed
down a lot since since having the bum
[ __ ] in it.
>> I've not seen him about actually. I
think he's off there now, isn't he? >> Yeah.
But then I I went I lived back in the
house there for a while, but then it all
calmed down. Nothing happened, is it? It
all It all went over, is it? It's mad to
think that, is it?
Yeah. Yeah, lad.
>> You have to come back in six months and
it would die down in it. Yeah.
>> Yeah. But why do you think it's funny?
You wouldn't laugh after that happened
to your parents house.
>> I wouldn't let that happen in your
parents house. Peter,
>> what did you say you would do again?
>> That's where me and you were different. You are
>> What did you say you would do again?
>> [ __ ] [ __ ] stab or something if it was me.
>> What? You'd run out with a knife? Well,
[ __ ] [ __ ] someone's trying to do
your [ __ ] house. You [ __ ] Yeah, you
[ __ ] You don't let people do that. Yeah, you
But here's the thing. Yeah. You said
people have been killed over YouTube in
it. They have. In America, they have
>> I'm not sure. Well, [ __ ] I'm not too
far into this YouTube, mate.
>> No, I meant like a different community.
Like any community?
>> Probably someone. Yeah, more than likely. [laughter]
>> Imagine that though. Your funeral. Yeah.
And look who was left over YouTube.
>> See that? Yeah.
>> Didn't my didn't bo you'll end up
[ __ ] dying over this. It's funny.
>> Remember that. That be all right, man.
Didn't he remember when he used to go in your live?
>> Yeah. But you saw it. You saw it when
they were in it. Timmy, Mike, and Monty.
You saw it in it.
>> I seen it. Yeah. You said you want to go
for a drink or we do it dirty.
>> You said that Mikey. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I seen that.
>> That was YouTube. It
>> was YouTube. I tell you what was funny
when [laughter] Tim Eldidge when Tim
Eldrich like Tim Eldidge said I'm going
to knock him out. It [laughter]
>> did you hear that bit?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Jaden was saying and Jaden was
like put the put the camera on. And I
had to put the camera on in it.
Yeah, I mean that do you like the five great guys?
>> Yeah, I don't even know what it is, man. >> Huh?
>> Who are them?
>> The five great guys.
>> I don't know who they are.
>> Jaden. Um, what's it? Jaden, Shagger.
Jaden and all them.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. The five. And they've
got a channel called The Great Guys.
>> I'll have to have a look.
>> Is it funny?
A lot of these people are unwell on here, man.
>> Is it funny though?
>> That J that Jamie Egg has had a few
fights on this YouTube, hasn't he?
>> Yeah. I shouldn't have brought him on, is it?
>> He shouldn't have like that.
>> But he had the chance to get off, didn't he?
>> He lost KK over it.
>> You think it's funny, is it?
I think that's [ __ ] sad. You know,
>> he lost a lot. So what? So if he didn't
come on his YouTube, he'd still be with
Kay and that and the kids.
>> 100%. Yeah.
>> With the kids,
>> he would. Yeah. To have his kids. Yeah.
>> Or not even that. If if he didn't come
on it, if he did meet Pat Mustard,
maybe. Even if he didn't meet Pat
Mustard, you know what I mean?
>> That's it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. True.
>> It's Pat M. Remember he said, "Who call
who's who calls all of this?" And he
said Pat must master the call was all this
pack cars at all. Did he? >> Yeah.
>> Do you remember when the window when
KK's windows got done that in?
>> Yeah man. [ __ ]
>> you thought it was funny. [laughter]
>> I wouldn't say it was funny like [ __ ]
off man. [laughter]
You thought you thought it was funny, is it?
>> No, that's not funny. Stuff like that, man.
>> Me and you've been speaking years, is
it? Do you remember we was talking when
it was CO? >> Yeah.
But what makes me laugh is these people
said that they were affected by CO, but
CO was just normal to them because they
don't go out anyway, isn't it? >> Yeah.
So, where you where you going to drink
on New Year's? Uh, as we not boxing there, >> Darham,
>> go Newcastle. >> Maybe
on the ground.
>> Newcastle's a bit long, isn't it?
>> The slugging letters.
>> Yeah, that's what Yeah, there's a slug
letter here, too. There's a few of them.
>> Is there one in Newcastle? Yeah,
>> I heard middle was a good night out.
I only been to B once many years ago.
>> What night out? >> Yeah.
>> Was it nice? It
>> was all right. Sunderland's a good night out.
>> Yeah, but it's it's dangerous there, ain't it?
>> Dangerous anywhere really, lad.
>> They sound funny in Sunderland. Do you
remember that Ryan Hansen? He was from
uh Sunderland. Do you remember when he
used to come on here?
>> Yeah, I can remember him. Yeah. Yeah.
>> He was from Sunderland. He had a mad accent, bro.
>> What do they call people from Sunderland? >> Um,
what they call [ __ ] Yakers. [laughter]
>> Yakers. [clears throat]
Is it Yakers?
>> I don't know. I'm not from the Northeast.
>> You need You need to go You should go
Leeds, bro. You should go to Leeds.
night out. We like it there.
>> Right. How long did it take you to get
up to Newcastle from on the train from London?
>> Uh about 3 hours and 30 minutes
>> is all it was on the train.
>> Yeah. But obviously I had to get to the
train station. So all in all probably 4
hours and a bit.
>> But driving driving's a lot longer.
Driving's long. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Driving's about 5 hours in.
>> It's long, bro. Is it?
>> Yeah. But Newcastle is like the
outskirts of London, isn't it? >> North.
>> Be realistic. P is it? >> Yeah.
>> What? Be realistic P in it.
>> You know what the outskirts means? [laughter] >> Yeah.
>> So, so Middles Middles was the outskirts
of Newcastle, wasn't it?
>> Yeah. so far away. But
>> yeah, that's what I was saying. Like
within 40 miles, 50 mi, that's the
outskirts. Yeah, pretty much. >> Yeah.
Right. Well, I'm going to jump off, lad.
I'm going to take some neuropen.
>> Some some [laughter] what?
>> Neuropen tablets. I've got an edit. [laughter] >> Really?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I put I'll speak in chat, lad.
>> Take some on paracetamol. Not paracetamon.
>> We'll do peace.
>> Okay, bye.
>> All right, this triple H is trolling me, man.
Be realistic, P. [laughter]
Be realistic, Peter. I might take some
tablets. I want to fit in. I want to fit
in with the crowd. >> [laughter]
>> in the crowd.
I might take some tablets. Yeah.
Not for a very very very long time, bro. Maybe March.
Yeah, maybe March.
Yeah, probably March, bro. Yeah.
cuz there's no reason to go out.
There's no reason to go out, lad. I've
got [snorts] no reason to go out.
I think Triple H is trolling me, man.
There's no reason to go out. Uh, Bob.
Yeah, maybe March. Maybe. Yeah.
What's the reason to go out?
Is there a reason to go out, bro?
What's the point of going out? You can't
get laid. You can't pull. So, what's the point?
You know, I'd rather give up with life
instead. It's easier.
How much money you got, Bob? Did you get
paid? How much money do you have?
Yeah, but you can't pull. So there's no
bike going out because you can't pull here.
You can't pull anything.
Yeah. How much money do you have? Uh Bob
Yeah, I spent 200 today.
I spent [ __ ] 200 today [ __ ]
gambling, bro. So,
yeah. So, how much?
Yeah, I spent £200 on roulette.
So, what you got like 200 left?
Yeah, I've got like over a thousand.
I can't be bothered going out, bro. Yeah.
Online. Yeah. £217.
So, how much did you how much do you have now?
I don't get no money till next not next
week, the week after.
So, what you got now, Bob? Like £100?
You get paid Tuesday. Yeah. Nice, man.
I get money every I get money every
week, but it's not much.
You got £100 left.
Yeah. At least January, you can save
money, bro. Cuz no one goes out January.
So, you got the whole month to save.
That's why I'm buying my phone next
month. I'm just going to buy a 400 pound
phone cuz I know I'll be saving next
month cuz I won't be going out anyways
cuz no one goes out January. So, yeah.
But every year I stay in for like six
weeks. I was going to go out New Year's
Eve, but I can't be asked, bro. There's no point.
Yeah. and no one do does anything
January. So you got you got until
midFebruary to save which is why I done
this £200 because I knew I weren't going
to be going out. So I don't mind losing
200 pound. Well, no I don't mind it but
it's annoying bro. Um
yeah, I'm coming off here.
I don't even need to say stop gambling
because I don't gamble anyways. That was
the first time in months. Um,
basically and just be selfish.
Get off here and be selfish. That's my
New Year's resolution. Yeah, pretty much.
Yeah, I don't go out much anymore,
little Dave, cuz I don't feel the reason
why I should have to go out and try. I
should be with someone already. I should
have a sex life. I should be settled
down with someone. I shouldn't have to
happen to still be going out at 28
every week. I used to go out twice a week, bro.
I shouldn't have to keep going out, you know? >> [snorts]
>> I used to love it, bro.
When I was like 24, 25.
Used to go to the O'Neals Thursday, Saturday
cuz I used to love it when I was
younger, bro. Um, but now I'm just like
I'm happy just to stay in,
you know, and just chill. I don't even get bored.
I generally don't even get bored
in the winter. Yeah.
Yeah. I just It's just I can't be bothered, bro.
Someone was like to someone else, oh,
maybe you're an introvert. And I was
thinking, bro, just cuz somebody doesn't
want to go out, it doesn't mean that
they're an introvert. I'm not an
introvert and I and I don't go out
because it's just the same [ __ ] with
women every time. So, I decided to give up.
It was the best thing to do was to give up.
I thought I was the best. Um, yeah. Nothing.
Yeah, I'm not an introvert. I'm not an
introvert. I'm an extrovert.
But I just can't be bothered anymore. Bro,
did you used to go out when you was
younger? I used to. 24, 25, I used to go
out twice a week. I had loads and loads
of money as well. So, I could I could
have easily done that, bro. You know
what I mean?
I don't know how I would have done it
without the house. I'm sure I would have
found a way, but
I lived a good life, bro. So, that's why
I just I've done it all. Been there done
that. [ __ ] that, bro. You know what I mean?
Yeah. I done it up until about 206.
24 25 was my peak, I think. Yeah. 24 25.
I used to go casino every Thursday. Go
drinking then Saturday. Every week, bro. Every week. Yeah. Yeah. Nice.
Yeah, I didn't have to work, bro. I was
sublet for three years. I got a one in a lifetime opportunity.
So, that's why I was able to uh not work.
That's how I was able to not work, lad.
I just subleted.
Used to win money, so I never had to uh
never had to work.
Three grand a month for doing nothing. Lovely.
So yeah, obviously I had all the lava.
Well, I don't have the house anymore.
They got the house back eventually.
They were trying to get back for years.
I made a lot of money, bro. I used to
gamble, travel, prostitutes, going out
drinking, [ __ ] everything, bro. Used
to go to restaurants.
No, they don't do anything about it. No,
it's a civil matter. But still, that Yeah.
No, I'm not going back. [ __ ] that.
I won't be out now. I need a long long
break, bro. I need a really really long break.
A long long long long break.
I don't need I should have to go out trying again.
Yeah, it was pretty nice day and it's
not nice now cuz I don't have the [ __ ] anymore.
It took them three years to get the
house back, bro. Three [ __ ] years. Yeah.
Do I have any regrets? Hell no, bro. I
won't going to sit there and stack money
for [ __ ] three years. I won't going
to sit there and stack money for 3
years. I'm not I'm not like [ __ ] non legs.
Uh [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah, man. So, obviously I've never had to work.
I've done I've done Uber and that
just as something to do. I've done a
delivery job just as something to do. But yeah,
it's not the best paying, but that's that. Yeah.
Yeah. It wasn't even my idea, bro. It's
like a My mom's friend said one day,
"Oh, you know, you can rent them rooms
out and get some money." Like, I was
living there by myself the whole year
without renting them [ __ ] rooms out.
So, I missed out on a lot of money, bro.
Yeah, they were like, "Yeah, you know,
you can like rent them rooms out and that." [laughter]
Like they gave me the idea, was it? So I
was like, "Oh, [ __ ] it." Yeah.
Yeah. It was lush, bro. Lush.
These people tried stopping my income
multiple times. It never worked.
years they've been doing this. These
people have been doing this for [ __ ]
years, come to think of it now, bro.
Yeah, they really are. Sadax. I'm off
after today anyways, bro, for a little
bit. Don't miss me too much, Dusty.
Yeah, if they try to get your money
stopped, they'll basically try two times
and then any more reports, they just
don't investigate it.
They just don't investigate it.
It's sad when you think about it though,
Dusty, that like these people will
like try to um ruin people that they
don't know, like seieve of jealousy and
try to ruin people that they don't know
just cuz they're fat ugly people that
ain't got nothing. I.e. Red Star, i.e. a
lot of these people. It's kind of mad
that you know, bro,
think thinking about it now.
And then after the second time, they'll
just stop investigating it.
I wasn't stupid, bro. I knew what I was
doing. So, could you imagine you had a
job on here, Dusty? Say you you get a
job, right? These people tell you to get
a job. So, say you you get a job, right?
And you tell these people that you're
working, they'll make you lose your job.
So, just they're idiots, bro. They They're just Yeah.
They don't like it that people have got
a better life than them and they're
younger than them and they're better
looking. That's why these people on here
do this, lad.
That's why these people on here do it.
You know, it's the truth, Dusty, as well.
They tried stopping people's money multiple times,
you know. So, how is it just YouTube, bro?
They tried stopping my money multiple
times, bro. never worked. I had a
separate bank. I had a separate bank account.
So they can never, you know, >> yeah.
So what are you doing on Tuesday
anyways, Dave? You having a little
drink? I'm going to the cinema on Tuesday.
Yeah, I'm going cinema Tuesday.
In the morning.
What are you up to, Captain?
Oh, bro. We have to get rid of that
triple eight. Dusty,
he's been caught being too faced.
Oh, that's not good, man.
Oh no, bro.
Well, it doesn't bother me anyways, bro,
cuz I'm not going to be on here anyways
for a little bit.
What the [ __ ]
These people just like all too faced on
here or something. What the [ __ ] man?
Bro, these people are so two-faced on
here, Mr. B. Man, I don't have the
energy for argue with them. I'm off here
after tomorrow anyways.
I'm sure like Charlie is the only normal
one on here, Mr. B. Charlie and [ __ ]
How hard can it be, bro? What the [ __ ]
am I reading, bro? to these people. Madness.
Yeah, I'm off him anyways, bro.
Yeah, we've seen all of this before.
Skint, skin, skin.
Some highlights from a little online
casino session last night. 100 pound
star and lots of bonuses on fish and
Frankie. Then a nice one to finish a few
spins on the wheel and a tasty blackjack
session. Didn't want to push my luck, so
cast out. Booking a nice holiday for the
new year. Red Storons Joe Wrong Media.
Remember when Poverty PE could gamble
like this? I can gamble like that right
now. You don't know how much money I
have. You don't know anything about anyone.
But you keep thinking you know how much
money people have.
Yeah, I remember it as well. And I I
remember that I can still do it because
you don't know how much money people have. So yeah,
just self projection as usual with these
people. I mean, it's YouTube in it, bro.
YouTube would always be the same YouTube.
Yeah. Sad people, bro. Sad people.
[ __ ] three hours.
Yeah, I'm off anyways, bro. After today. Anyways,
they're [ __ ] idiots on here, bro. Yeah.
And he didn't win two and a half grand
for 100 pound. He's full of [ __ ]
So that's another thing.
Yeah, that's [ __ ]
Yeah, these people are proper spastics
on here, lad.
Yeah, they're proper proper spastics on here. Mr. be. Yeah, bro.
yeah yeah yeah
proper skin weirdos on air
But yeah, that Triple H is too faced as
well. But bro, I can't be bothered with
these calling these idiots on here.
Calling them, bro. People I don't know.
It's just just weirdos on here.
They're just weirdos that are just
jealous of people that they don't know.
Just little low lives. That's all they are, bro.
That's all they are and always will be shadows. No life.
No, no, no, no. Yeah, bro.
Uh, why are you laughing on Laur's
channel? Are you another one that's too faced?
I saw you laughing on Laur's channel
with all the self projectors
with these little self-reflectors. Lad,
you're not too faced like them, are you?
Please say you're not.
Yeah, there's a lot of two-faced people
in this community. I do you know what? I
just I just think this whole thing is
weird because these people don't even
know you, bro.
I I I Bro, this is what I find so weird
is that like you don't even know these people
on here. That's what makes this whole
thing so weird.
But I'm off anyways cuz this is repeating. So
because it's just self rejection. It's just boring.
It's just the same self-p projecting uh comments, bro.
Skin skin. We've heard it all before,
bro. It's just self-p projection.
It's the same [ __ ] with these people,
bro. Like, it's not funny. It's just boring.
No, it's just boring, lad. That's why
you don't see me on it for days at a time.
No, it's not about being thicker skin.
It's just boring.
It doesn't affect me. It's just boring.
It's like watching the same film over
and over again. It's just boring. It's
just the same repeating people.
They ain't got a life.
I'm not I'm not bothered.
They're just repeaters.
I've seen all of this for years. I've
seen this I've been seeing this same
thing for years, lad.
It's just the same repeating.
I've seen all of this for years, lad.
Same repeating people for eight years.
Same repeating people, mate.
Same repeating people.
So, when are you people going to get off
of YouTube and get a life anyways?
When are you people going to get off of
YouTube and get a life
instead of talking about people that you
don't know every day?
Just just, you know, throwing it out there, bro.
How much was that piano? Yeah.
So, I really wish that was true, you
know, 100 pound to 2.5K.
But that Smokeoky B is full of [ __ ]
just like that Joseph Ferrar because we
all know it's facts that people don't
win like that anymore.
We know it's facts that people don't win
like that anymore. And I'm not jealous.
I'm not jealous of anyone. I don't care
about money. It's just facts. Stating
facts is not jealousy.
Yeah, bro. Like, stating facts is not
being jealous, lad. It's the truth.
And that's that.
People don't win like that gambling anymore, bro. Trust.
Women are [ __ ] evil [ __ ] That's why
I don't go out anymore, bro. They are
evil scum of the earth [ __ ]
Yeah, they're evil scum of the earth.
Little [ __ ] I hate them here.
Yeah, I hate them, lad.
That's why I don't bother with them
anymore. They're all the [ __ ] same,
bro. All the [ __ ] same.
Yeah, they're just [ __ ] [ __ ]
So, you gamble or what?
I wish I had a nice win on roulette,
bro. I wouldn't go back for a very long time.
I wouldn't go back for a very long time,
lad. If I um gambled,
I won. Wouldn't be back for a very long time.
I tried £200 earlier. It went nothing. Yeah,
it's hard to win money nowadays, bro.
Very hard to win money nowadays. Very hard.
Yeah, I think I've got over a grand.
But I just don't spend anything, bro. I
just don't I just don't I just don't
spend anything. Me?
Yeah. I don't spend nothing. Me, lad.
I could easily go out and drink, but I
just don't want to, bro.
I just don't want to.
Yeah, it's hard to make money nowadays, bro.
It is hard to make money nowadays. It's
hard to win money. It's hard to win Yeah.
Yeah. It's hard to win money, bro.
It's [ __ ] so hard to win money now,
bro. It never used to be like this. I
lost [ __ ] 200 pound today.
I've caught you being too faced, bro.
But I don't give a [ __ ] anyways.
You can be too faced all you want,
Triple H. I don't have energy, bro. I
don't know you. You don't know me. So, I
don't give a [ __ ] I'm coming off soon anyways
and I'll be back after Christmas. So
yeah, I lost 200 pound of roulette
earlier. Well, 217 actually cuz the fee. Yeah,
Trip H is too faced as well. Yeah, I've
seen your comments. Yeah,
I don't give a [ __ ] anyways, bro. I
don't have the energy.
Yeah, he's too faced, bro. I've seen
these comments. I don't really give a
[ __ ] anyways, bro. You're all the same
on here. I don't have energy for it
because it doesn't bother me, bro.
Because I know that no one will ever say
anything to my face. So, I don't really
give a [ __ ]
I really don't care, lad.
I don't really care. It doesn't bother
me because I know that no one will ever
say anything to my face. Joseph will
never say anything to my face. So, I
don't really care, bro.
severely depressed. Nope. I'm not
depressed at all, bro. I'm not even depressed.
I'm not depressed, bro. Why am I depressed? Nah.
Fed up, but not depressed.
Definitely. Definitely. You're
definitely not depressed, bro.
Definitely not depressed. There's a
difference, bro, between being fed up.
If you was depressed, you would even get
out of bed, mate. That's what happens
whenever I go out drinking. No.
And these people's words don't hurt me
because it's just self-p projection.
All of this like Christmas thing, you're
going to be alone Christmas,
it doesn't bother me because it's all self-p projection.
That's why I don't react to these little
clowns because it's just the same
self-reflecting people, bro.
But last week, uh, two weeks ago, I
didn't get out of bed for like three days
because I don't care about Christmas.
Because I don't care about Christmas.
I don't care. Yeah.
[ __ ] Christmas, bro.
Yeah. In his head. The guy's skin, mate.
Skint and a [ __ ] skin flint.
I don't believe that Smokeoky Bees is a
win either. I don't believe it, bro.
because of I mean what's the chances
that you you've turned £100 into 22 half
grand online? It doesn't seem very
likely, does it? I just went on that by the way.
Yeah, that's another [ __ ] That's
another load of [ __ ]
Yeah, she can have Christmas. I don't
care about Christmas.
I saw that. Yeah. Yeah, that's [ __ ] bro.
That is bollocks. I did see that. Yeah,
that two and a half grand. Yeah, bro.
What's the chances, eh? Online. That's
[ __ ] Absolute bollocks.
I don't care about Christmas, bro. I
only care about leaving this country next year.
I'll be in paradise slabs. Yeah. Laney,
I'm not Christmas. I didn't. Sorry. I'm
not I didn't know I was Muslim.
I didn't know I was Muslim, bro.
I didn't know I was Muslim. That's news to me.
And King doesn't live here.
I just don't care about Christmas.
I preferred being in the old house than
this house. It's very isolated here.
I preferred I would actually prefer
being in the old house lonely, bro.
Eating. I'd rather be in in the old house
than be here to be honest.
I don't give a [ __ ] about family, bro. I
don't give a [ __ ] about any of that
[ __ ] [ __ ] that.
I'd rather be back at the old house alone. Yeah.
You know, I don't care about family.
I only care about myself.
Yeah, [ __ ] Christmas.
[ __ ] Valentine's Day as well.
A country designed to annoy you. Laney.
Yeah, I'm Muslim, bro. I drink alcohol.
I eat pork, but I'm Muslim. Yeah.
Yeah. Valentine's. When is Valentine's?
25th of February, isn't it?
be another boring lonely Valentine's.
Boring, isn't it? Bors me. This country.
A country designed to annoy you.
You like my little sayings?
No, it literally is designed to annoy
you. I had to go to three different
shops to print something the other day
and I'm thinking, "What the [ __ ]
Yeah. Playing Franklin.
Yeah. I hate Christmas. No,
I just drive around in circles. Nice.
I'm mental. Why am I mental? [snorts]
No, no, no. Yeah.
Get a [ __ ] job.
I can't believe these sados are still on
YouTube years later.
I can't believe it. These sad bastards
are still on YouTube. There's literally
people making money on kick. Yeah,
there's actual people making mad amounts
of money. And then you get this
community, dusty, you literally see
people making money on kick. Yeah,
people out living life. And then you go
on this community, bro. And you think,
"What the [ __ ]
You think what the [ __ ] bro? They're
[ __ ] It's a loser community. Proper
proper loser community, bro.
Proper loser community, man. There
people making money like streamers and that.
I'm not in it. But that's the thing. I'm
not in it. But I'm not in it. [laughter]
I haven't been on for days.
Ah, someone said to Triple H that Moldi
cheeseburger needs to be surgically
removed from your carpet, lad. [laughter]
That made me laugh. Yeah,
Triple H is a Mong. Why?
No. Bless Triple H with his little his little dialect.
Nope. But these people in this community
have got autism.
Called out for what, bro? None of these
people are ever going to meet you.
It's just like that Joseph Ferrar. He'll
never meet anyone.
I didn't say anything. All I said was
these kids being brought up by another man.
I bet you I can. I stay
I bet you I [ __ ] come.
What's the best GTA?
I think San Andreas is the goat, bro.
San Andreas is the best game ever. Oh,
you're still on YouTube.
Still on YouTube. Say
>> Mont skin boring.
I just can't believe these people repeat
themselves every day.
It's the same repeating people.
Have you ever played NBA, Dusty?
It's my birthday soon, Dusty.
It's my birthday soon.
What do you think of that, Dusty? Is my
birthday soon, lad? Got me any presents?
>> Oh gosh. Yeah. [snorts]
I'm having a little sneeze. Dusty. Huh? Oh, sorry. Yeah.
Oh gosh, Dusty. Oh gosh.
>> [clears throat]
>> Anyways, I'm gone. Yeah.