Oh my god,
they're on YouTube. Christmas. I knew
it. Oh my god. I knew it. I've just
walked up the stairs. THEY GOT NO LIFE.
OH [ __ ] [ __ ] hell. One second.
They fell into my trap. They're on YouTube.
Oh, they're on YouTube. They're on
YouTube. They're on YouTube.
My god. There we go. YouTube Christmas
[ __ ] day. Fell into my trap. There
you go. You got 11 people on here
watching. Look, they're on [ __ ]
YouTube. They got no life. They got no
[ __ ] life. They fell into my [ __ ]
trap. I knew it. I knew these people had
no family. I [ __ ] knew it, boys. I
told my mom I was going to do this as
well. 17 people [ __ ] watching.
They're on [ __ ] YouTube Christmas
Day. They talk about other [ __ ]
people. I planned this since I've woke
up. Yeah. I w to come back until New
Year's. And look, they're on YouTube
typing away. It's so clear. It's them
that they're talking about. I told my
mom I was doing this, by the way. I'd
literally told my mom that before I do
my sister's day, I'm going to go live.
See, look. 17 people and they're on
YouTube. They got no family. I [ __ ]
knew it, boys. I knew it. I [ __ ] knew
it. You know, they can't help themselves
even on Christmas [ __ ] day. [ __ ]
comment. Yeah. telling other people that
they got no [ __ ] family and they
don't have this. And look, look at this
idiot. Look at this idiot. You got 17
people. 18 people watching. Yeah. Yeah.
These people are supposed to have
families. They're supposed to have
money. They're supposed to have a
[ __ ] life. Yeah, mate. It's bollocks.
It's absolutely [ __ ] bollocks. 18
[ __ ] people. What the [ __ ] bro? You
don't even get that on a [ __ ] weekend,
mad, bro. These people are going to be
lonely Christmas. I [ __ ] knew it. I
knew it. I [ __ ] knew it.
Self projection. Self projection. Look,
I told you they fell right into my trap.
They fell right into Peter Belly's trap.
That's all I basically come on here to
say. See if it was the same people on
YouTube. And it is. Same people Christmas Day.
Oh, thank you, man. Thank [snorts] you so much.
Yeah, bro. Thank you, man. Thank you. It
just shows that you people ain't got a
life and you ain't got no family. That's
all I basically come on here to [ __ ]
prove to be honest with you. Um, yeah.
You ain't got no life. You ain't got no
family. You ain't got no money. Bunch of
[ __ ] fat, ugly people that ain't got
no life. That's all all I basically come
on here to say really. And look, look at
all them now. They're not They're not
trying to type because they know.
Yeah. Because they know. Yeah, bro.
I'm gone now cuz some of us has got a
life and got family. So, I'm going to
put this video up and prove that it was
you people all along. Sados, sad
bastards. Ain't got no life. Trying to
talk about other people when you're
[ __ ] on here Christmas Day. Yeah, I
went live for five five minutes to prove
that you people on here. See you later now. Anyways,