Oh, try to battle, bro. [ __ ] me.
to a lawyer.
Literally was went to Weather Spoons to
get breakfast. Oh, let me let me put a
[ __ ] football bet on today cuz loads
of teams are playing. They don't open
until [ __ ] 10:00. Is this country
trying to [ __ ] annoy you or
something? I'm not going back out to put
a football bet on. I went out for a
[ __ ] reason, mate. You know, I was
hanging around for an hour. I'm I'm not
going back out. Simple. Simple as that.
And then both of the [ __ ] cash
machines weren't [ __ ] working.
One open at 9:30, then one open at 9:00,
and then the cash machines weren't
working. [ __ ] off, silly little [ __ ]
Like, I'm going to go back out. I'm not
going back out. No, I can't do it online.
So, I just want to do a football bet.
Simple as that. I was like, "Oh, let me
get a train into um town. Trains are not
running, but the buses are running. [ __ ]
off, mate." Literally, a country
designed to annoy you. I stick by what I say.
Yeah. Never mind. I just won't do it.
literally all playing tonight
because I feel like if if it is a
holiday. Don't open at all. Don't open
at all. Then
there's teams that are play. Every
single league is playing. All the teams are playing.
The test machines are not working. The
trains are not working, but the bus is not working.
Why are the buses working if the trains
are not working? This doesn't make any
sense. Anyways, never mind. Just weren't
meant to have a bet today.
I wanted to chill with the roast dinner,
have a bet and chill.
>> Yeah, I I won't be going back out.
Sorry about that, bro. Yeah, I just
wanted to do a football bet today cuz
all loads of teams are playing.
>> Yeah, I I'm sick. You always waiting
around for everything in this country. I
feel like in this country, you're always
waiting around for everything.
Waiting around. Waiting around. Waiting
around. Waiting around. Waiting around.
Waiting around. That's what it feels
like in this country, bro.
But it's not worth going back out for.
You see, it's not worth it. I'm not
going back out for that. [ __ ] that. You know,
that's why I went back that that's why I
come back home. I was I was going to go
to town cuz there would have been one
open in town, but uh the trains weren't
running cuz I weren't going to go all
the way back home to then go back out.
I'm not doing that. So, but the trades
weren't running, so I'm back home now anyways. Yeah.
Yeah, cuz I went to get breakfast.
Yeah. Well, I'm not going back out. So,
you can get [ __ ] I am definitely
definitely not going back out.
I should have to go back out, bro. It's
[ __ ] like this that annoys me in this
country, bro. It's not even like, you
know, just the women and stuff. It's
different things that annoys me. Yeah. Yeah,
annoying as [ __ ]
No, I just wanted to put a football bat on today.
and it hasn't um
don't open till 10:00
and the cash machines weren't working. I
went to get Weather Spoons breakfast.
[ __ ] bors me it does. I'm not going
back out. Then I tried to go into town
but then the trains not running so I
just come back home and I'm not going
back out. I just wanted to do a little
football bet today. It was boxing day
but I'm not going back out. So you
didn't get [ __ ] Bors me.
[ __ ] bors me. This country bors me.
Here they come. Who comes?
Oh, you still on YouTube. You get life,
bro. [ __ ] hell.
Well, you literally just sit on YouTube
waiting for me to go live. What a loser.
Yeah, I need to ban you. So, I just have
to go my other account to see that. What a loser.
Um, they do it because they don't want
to be exposed for what they are. People
that's got no family, lonely skin.
That's why I proved they were on YouTube
yesterday. I proved they were on YouTube
yesterday, but I was live for 5 minutes
uh before I went to my sisters and then
there were 18 people watching and two
people commenting with in less than 5 minutes. >> [laughter]
>> Yeah, they pretend that they're not on
YouTube Christmas. It's funny, but it's
cuz they got no family and they don't
want to be exposed for what they are. You see? Yeah.
What a loser, bro.
What a loser. That red star is a proper
proper loser. You would have thought
these people would have got bored. You
would have thought these pe these
spastics would have got bored, but
clearly not. They've been doing it for eight years.
Proper disabled in it.
Literally sat on YouTube waiting for
content. What a loser.
But like I said, you can you can tell
them about themselves all day long, but
uh you know, they're not bothered
because they're so disabled. They You
probably can't even understand what you're saying.
Yeah, bro. I got my coat on. Look, I
just went out.
Yeah, it bothers me, bro. [ __ ] bored me.
Yeah, I'm not doing another I'm not I'm
not going back out.
One second. Someone sent me a voicemail.
Yeah, sorry, bro. Um, yeah, what a loser. Anyways,
yeah, it was all you little [ __ ]
Right. in the new year. I'm going to let
you um have, you know, your Christmas
and your new year, but I'll be coming to
Yorkshire anyways um in January. So,
make sure you little fat [ __ ] fake
pension, fake wins, you come and say
this [ __ ] to my face, what you were
saying on L's, you sad, fat, ugly
bastard. Yeah, make sure you say all
this [ __ ] to my face when I come. Yeah,
you [ __ ] chubby fat pension skint
ugly fat misses. I'd rather have no
misses than have your fat ugly misses
who lives in the bookies. And make sure
you say this to my face or are you going
to do nothing? Are you going to show
everybody on YouTube how you do nothing?
Huh? Are you going to show everyone? You
[ __ ] sad fat bastard. You got a lot
of [ __ ] to say. You got a lot of [ __ ] to
say behind people's back. And how I know
this because I was on um I was on my
mama's phone and she subbed to Laura J
last week. I clicked on it as I as I
woke up and I see you commenting typing
[ __ ] you fat pathetic sad old bastard
and I'm going to say it in Yorkshire as
well to make sure you come out then.
Yeah, you [ __ ] fat sad biased little
nods lover. And I'm just going to say
all this stuff to your face. No
fighting, no [ __ ] I just want to
say everything to your face. You dirty
fat ugly Mrs. Nods lover. And I'm going
to walk away. That's all I'm going to say.
and that's all I'm saying anyways.
So, make sure Yeah.
Make sure you don't run away. Yeah. Personality
and mindset. Yeah. Maybe you should you
should come to London and you should
stop showing fake wins and a fake
pension cuz you're fooling nobody, mate.
You're like the most lowest IQ troll
that I've ever ever come across.
You can't even talk on a panel. You
don't know how embarrassing that is.
I've literally seen somebody comment on
your thing, right? Saying about how
scared you are. You can't even talk on a panel. [laughter]
You're an embarrassment, mate. Stop it.
Literally just stop it. You know, you
should come to London. You might it
might stop you showing fake wins and you
might actually gain an IQ level. [ __ ]
hell. Trust me, no one's jealous of a
fat ugly loser like you, mate. Showing
fake wins. Showing fake wins off horse
sale by date. Truck me, mate. No one's
jealous of you.
Never has has been, never will be. Why
do I know this, bro? Cuz I've got more
money than you. I'm younger than you.
I'm better looking than you. I've never
had anything as ugly as what you're
with. I don't have to show fake wins on
YouTube to try to impress people. What a [ __ ] loser,
you know? And that's that. You sad fat
bastard. He'll do nothing. I can't wait
to say that when I'm actually in
Yorkshire, you know. I can't wait to say
it. I'm in your city. You'll do nothing.
Fat though. That's what I'm going to
say. You keyboard warrior, mate. Mate,
listen. You're not constantly winning.
Me and everybody else knows that you're
full of [ __ ] Yeah. And like I said,
yeah, I sound so jealous. Okay,
whatever. Well, you can say this to my
face, can't you? When I'm in Yorkshire
next year, can't you, bro? Yeah, bro. No
one's jealous of you, you fat, ugly
bastard. You're the one that's obsessed
with me. You are the one that's so
jealous of me. You won't shut up about
me, you [ __ ] fat [ __ ] I see you on L
J's. I see you on this person's. I see
you on this person's. You won't shut up
about me, mate. All I'm stating is that
you show fake wins. I don't keep going
on about you. You're the one keep going
on about me. Mr. Scared to talk on a
panel. Pathetic, mate. But that's
probably cuz you're in a wheelchair when
you're an absolute [ __ ] like most of
these people on here to be fair. Not
even being triggered. It's basing facts
what you people are. I know the truth
hurts, but that's just the way it is.
And I told you I don't even want to
fight. I don't want to hit. I don't want
to throw hands. I just want to tell you
what you are to your face. Not behind
the keyboard. to your face. You know, I
even said I'd come on your front door
and tell you about yourself to your face
and then you kept saying I'll do
nothing. So, I I mean I I I don't know, you know.
Yeah. You have nothing. Yeah. You're
you're the one that's got nothing,
matey. You're the one that's got
nothing. You're the one that's showing
fake wins, fake pension, living under poverty,£40
jeans, 200lb phone. Everything points to
you, not me. Literally everything points
to you and not me.
You're the one that's poverty. You're
the one with the fat ugly misses. You're
the one that's skint. You're the one
showing a fake pension. It's not me, bro.
Simple. So, yeah.
Yeah. You right.
I know they are scum. You're right. I'm
just telling them what they are cuz they
are pretty much all the same, you know,
like fat, ugly, jealous, low lives. And
I love how they how these people try to
say that they laugh, mate. They're the
biggest laughing stocks ever.
They're fat. They're old. They're ugly.
They're skint. If they looked in the
mirror, mate, they literally if they
looked in the mirror, bro, they'd get
the biggest laugh at themselves. They
would They wouldn't even need to pay,
bro, a broadband bill every month. All
they would need to do is look in the
mirror and laugh at themselves.
Skint, fat, ugly, losers, low life. They
were on it Christmas as well. We proved it.
fat, ugly, skint, down and out wasters.
So, yeah. So, like I said, bro, just
don't um in future accuse people that
they'll do nothing when you're the one
that can't even talk on a panel, scaredy-cats.
Oh, I remember you players know. You was
on YouTube yesterday. I was live for 5 minutes.
I don't know why, but they always do it,
bro. And like I said, I think this guy's
Rocky Ride, by the way. And here's the
thing, DH10. Even if you show them, they
will still like just call you the same.
It's they're just disabled basically,
bro. Like, end of They do it because
they're disabled. Laugh at you, Joe. You
don't laugh at anyone. You can't even
talk on a panel. You're the laughingtock.
You are the laughingtock. Fat, ugly,
can't talk. Can't meet anyone. Trust me,
you are the one that's being laughed at,
not me. You know, you're the one that's
being laughed at. Can't talk, fake
pension, fake wins, no money, 200 pound
phone. Trust me, brother. Someone like
you is not laughing at me.
Someone that's scared to talk on a
panel. Let that sink in. Someone that's
so disabled and so shy that they can't
even talk. But apparently, they'll laugh
for that people. Get away with yourself.
Anyways, I'll be more than happy to
travel to you. So, you can say anything
you want to say to my face and I'll
leave it there. And if you don't want to
do it, then you have proven that you'll
do nothing and you will never do
nothing. I mean, I said this to you,
where was it? Last week. I said, I'll
come today and and I'll give you the
chance to say it to my face. Excuses.
You're another nonslegs. That's why you
get on cuz you're all the same.
Disabled, coward, skinn, you all have
the same resemblance. That's why you get
on so well. That's why you get on so
well with nonslects because you're all
the same. You're all the [ __ ] same.
I know. It's bad, bro. Is it? And and
you know the thing is UK signing Sunday
they open at the same time.
Sunday they open at the same time. Would
you believe it?
Yeah. Sunday they opened at the same
time. I was I'm not going and then I'm
not going home and going back out. I'm
not doing that. So I just want I just
want to do a football bet. Simple, bro.
The trains weren't running, but the
buses were running.
Yeah. Well, then stop talking [ __ ]
behind people's back, then you coward.
Well, then stop talking [ __ ] then, you coward.
Stop being a coward then. If that's what
you really think. Yeah. Stop being a
coward. And trust me, bro, you're going
to be embarrassed. You're the one that's
old, ugly, and disabled. You're the biggest embarrassment.
You're the biggest embarrassment ever,
mate. Ugly fat old fake pension 200lb
phone brother. It's all about you.
Everything that you're saying is all
about you. Poverty is you. Skin is you.
Fake pension is you. Everything is you.
I don't know how many times I have to
say this to you and you don't get it in
your thick head. You are the one that's
showing signs of poverty. Not me.
Definitely. Definitely not me. 200 pound
phone, 40 jeans, multi holiday.
Everything is pointing to poverty.
Nothing is pointing to poverty with me, bro.
Someone sent me something. Yeah. [snorts]
And that's that.
Brother, I'm living in my prime. I'm
younger than you. I'm better looking
than you. I've had more of a life than
you. I don't show fake wins. I don't
show fake pensions. And I've been with
more women than you. And guess what,
mate? I'd rather have no woman than have
what you're with. That fat ugly thing.
That's not a flex, bro. I used to say
the same to nonsleleds. I would rather
have no woman than have that ugly thing.
That fat sausage finger thing that
you're with. Never in my life. I can
safely say this, brother. My word means
nothing. I have literally said to you
that I will meet you and you're you're
running away. What are you talking,
brother? I've just said to you for the
past 10 minutes. I will meet you and
tell you about yourself to your face and
all you keep doing is running back to
nods legs every time I'm telling you I'm
telling you this. But mate, listen.
You've got a [ __ ] 200 phone, 40
jeans, a fat ugly misses, a fake
pension, and a shitty holiday. Do not
try to talk about someone like me, mate.
Yeah, simple. You know what I'm saying,
brother? You are the one that's living
under clear poverty. You see yourselves
when you're talking about other people.
That's what it is with you, bro. Yeah.
With you [ __ ] people. You're nothing
but a fat, ugly, wrinkled waster. And
you know what I'm saying about you is
the truth. Like I said, if you're not
going to grow a pair of balls and meet
someone, bore off. You'll do nothing.
Look, this is projection. Like this,
that word you're saying right now means
nothing. I've said that I will come to
you and tell you that you're a dirty
biased fat nonslover to your face and
you won't meet me. So what you're saying
is you will do nothing because you won't
even meet just like you won't talk. You
can't join a panel cuz you're scared cuz
you'll do nothing. That's why you won't
join a panel. But people even people on
your channel know that I've got you
scared. You will never ever ever show me
what bookies you go to. That's how bad
it is. You know where I live. You know
the area that I live in. Do you think
you would ever ever let me know where
you are? No. Cuz you know better. You
know what's good for you. Fatty. Fatty
waster in his 40s. You know what's good
for you. You know what's good for you.
That's the only bit where you know you
know you are a bit intelligent.
You know you're nothing but a fat ugly
waster slob. Yeah. We can tell you're
fat as well. Have you seen your [ __ ]
hands? You [ __ ] fat chubby hands. You
fat [ __ ] And you're coming trying to
[ __ ] talk about me. You [ __ ] fat
northern ugly bastard that won't meet no
one. Ugly little waster with a 200lb
phone. [ __ ] out of here, boy. You know.
Get the [ __ ] out of here, you [ __ ]
loser. Go suck your boyfriend Nons legs
off. You've got You've got You literally
have something you you and him have got
something in common. You both will never
meet anyone. You're both big behind the
keyboard, but you both will never meet
anyone. That's that's what you've got in
common. Like even Timmy Yeah. Let me
tell you something, right? Even Timmy,
as bad as Timmy is. Yeah. Mr. B trolls
Timmy. At least Timmy's At least Timmy,
right? At least Timmy actually meets
people. At least Timmy actually meets
people, brother. Yeah. This Joe will
never meet anyone cuz he's a fat ugly
waster. He can't even talk. He's a
waster. Just like nonsakes. I mean, at
least nonsex sto.
But you know, even Tibby goes and meets
people. Oh, nothing, Ben. I was going to
do a football bet, but the bookies don't
open till [ __ ] 10:00, bro. So, I just
came back. I went to the pub to get a
breakfast, but I'm not going to go back
out just to do a football bet. Catch
machines weren't working and everything.
So, I thought, [ __ ] that. Yeah, okay,
whatever. Like I said, come back to me
when you'll meet me anyways, little
waster. You fat wrinkly slob with a fake
pension. Fake pension. [clears throat]
They are such a loser. Wait, bro. They
are actually so disabled, bro.
>> It's so I know. It's boring, isn't it?
>> It's boring, isn't it? It's so boring.
That's Do you know what they are? They
are They are literally just fat, ugly
waster slobs. They literally are.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Listen.
Anyways, I'll be coming anyways in
January. So, make sure you show up. I'll
let you have your little holiday and
that and we'll see what the fat slob
will do nothing's all about.
We'll see what this fatty is all about
when you in his city. We'll see what
your fatty is all about. Listen,
brother. You can't even talk on a panel.
Shut up. Go and show some more fake
wins. Go and show some more fake wins.
We want to see some more fake wins,
mate. Listen, you listen to me. You
can't talk on a panel. I'm a lion. You
can't even talk on a panel. You can't
even tell me where you are. Stop
projecting, you little [ __ ] I've
slagged your misses off. I've slagged
you off. I've slagged your poverty life
off. And you still won't beat me. And
you're still typing behind the keyboard.
Give it up, kid. It's embarrassing now.
I've slagged your misses off. I've
slagged your poverty life off. I've
slagged your low IQ off. And you still
won't meet me. You're all the same. No
wonder you love nonsleg so much because
you're all the same. You're the same
[snorts] as him.
You fat hovery ugly fat misses, you
know. And and you know another thing is
right. Yeah. I can literally say that
I'm single right now and I've never had
to resort to anything as ugly as you and
Nodle Legs. Never in my life have I ever
had to resort to anything like that. And
bear in mind I'm 28. Yeah. And I've got
more life experiences than both of you
combined, which means I've met a lot of
people. Never in my life have I been
with anything as ugly as any of you two.
Said it all about your lives, bro. Yeah,
you fat ugly slob. Go and show some fake
wins. You low IQ little muppet. You
scared to talk. Go and show some more
fake wins, bro. Everyone loves seeing them.
Fake wins from a fake man living under
poverty. Living under poverty. That's
you. I've got more money than you would ever have.
Yeah, whatever. Like I said, bro, when
you'll meet me and you've got stuff to
say to my face, you fake pension, man.
Then come back to me. Yeah. Yeah. I'd
rather be lonely than me with that fat
ugly whale that you're with. You fat
ugly waist. Now go and [ __ ] off. Yeah. Go on.
God, how mate I'm I'm having dinner
today. I'm having company today. I don't
know what you're talking about, mate.
Lonely. I've literally got people coming
over today. I'm having a roast dinner
again. Mate, [ __ ] off, you fat, ugly
waster. Like I said, I've offered to
come and meet you several times and
you're not having any of it. You chubby
bastard. £200 on the phone. Chubby
bastard. £200 phone. [ __ ] [ __ ] You
[ __ ] absolute [ __ ] You can't even
talk on a panel. You're that disabled.
You're scared of your own voice. That's
how disabled you are. Probably in a
[ __ ] You know what though? But
actually, no, bro.
I actually think, you know what? I
actually think I'd be meeting someone in
a [ __ ] wheelchair, bro. I think if I
met you, I'd be meeting someone in a wheelchair.
You know, you and Lunches are the same.
You're both cowards. We were talking
about this the other day. You and your
ugly boyfriend. You know what I mean?
Showing your little fake wins, thinking
that you're a good troll. You're
probably in a [ __ ] wheelchair to be
honest with you.
And yeah, bro. I mean, my mom doesn't
want me shouting on YouTube. Where's
your mom? Where's your mom, Joe? Oh,
your mom don't love you. You was alone
Christmas, wasn't you? [ __ ] talking
about people being a sad bastard when
you're showing fake pensions and fake
gambling money. You sad bastard. And you
want to talk about other people,
I'll be coming to leave soon anyways, mate.
That's not a problem.
Sean, that's near you. and she said,
"I'm gonna go live and I'm going to be
like, "This fat, ugly, fake pet bug
would do nothing." And you're going to
have to sit there and watch me do it as
well. You know what I mean?
Yeah. Yeah. I'd rather live with my mom
than live with that [ __ ] fat ugly
[ __ ] that you're with. I'd rather have
no [ __ ] woman. I'd rather have no
woman than be with what you're with. So
Joe, you're going to let me come to your
city and you're going to do nothing?
Is that is that what you're So you're
telling me you're going to allow me to
come and you'll do nothing? Is that what
you're saying? Cuz we're trying to
understand the projection here. We're
trying to really understand it. You know,
you're going to let me come there and
you'll do nothing. Not you. Surely not
you. Not you, Joseph Farah. You little
[ __ ] You're just like your dog's
legs boyfriend. You're just like your
boyfriend. No, he can't be a baby. He's
got a girlfriend. You're just like your
boyfriend. Both ugly. Both got ugly fat
misses. Both won't meet anyone. You're
just like your boyfriend. Have you? Have
you Have you considered getting married,
lad? You know,
mate, it doesn't matter what I've tried.
I've had more women than you will ever
have, and I've never had to resort to
anything as fat and ugly as you. So, I
mean, yeah. So you're going to let me
come and you'll do absolutely nothing
like your boyfriend? Really? You [ __ ]
loser? Do you know what? You You nonsar,
you should be named the free musketeer
losers. The three losers that would
never beat anyone that's only got energy
behind the keyboard. You know what I mean?
Nah, I must be talking to someone else.
There's no way you're going to allow me
to come to where you live.
and you'll do nothing cuz we know that's
our favorite word, bro. You know,
brother, so you're going to let me come
and you'll do nothing, you sad bastard.
You're already scared to talk. You're
already scared of talking and then
you're going to let somebody come and
you'll do nothing.
Yeah, simp women, brother. Listen, I've
had more free sex than you will ever
have. Why don't you show everybody your
misses? Why don't you show everyone her face?
because she's [ __ ] ugly like you.
That's why you can't show your face cuz
you're ugly. Just like nonsades. Just
like Red Star. Three ugly people that
ain't got no life. Anyways, bro, I want
to see some more fake wins on your
channel today, matey. Maybe 50 to2,000.
I want to see some more fake wins. Come
on, let's see some more fake wins.
You've got to be the only person that
can beat the bookies, you know. You've
got to be the only one. I'm surprised
they've not shut down because of you,
you know. You literally you literally
must be the only one that can beat the
that can beat the bloody bookies, you
know. Yeah. Like, [ __ ] mate.
I need to say this to you one more time,
bro. I'm not Monty Man or Timmy. So, I'm
not even sub to your channel anymore,
but brother, you're you're trying to
troll me. Someone that's more
intelligent than you will ever be. I've
clocked I clocked on to what you was
doing ages ago when you was defending
your boyfriend non legs. Oh, he's not a
bird. I got a girlfriend and then you
started like showing fake wins. I knew
what you was about. You sad fat [ __ ]
from a long time ago, bro. You're fat
ugly waster. 200 lb phone ass a long time ago.
It can't go and then he started he
started showing fake wins. You fat ugly
waster. Anyways, I'll be in lead soon.
Anyways, bro, I'll let you have your
little holiday. I won't stress you out
too much. Um, and we'll see who's the
one that will do nothing. Yeah, Joseph.
We'll see who's the one that will do nothing.
Let's show everyone on YouTube who's the
real one that will do nothing. Yeah.
See what I'm saying? Yeah. That's good, bro. Yeah.
I'll [ __ ] get my dick out and piss
all over your face.
No, that's not what happened. Anyways,
Joe, I'm going to be in your city and
I'm going to be owning you
and I'll be in leads only you and you'll
do nothing and I'm going to show
everyone that the fat ugly waster on the
200 phone will do nothing.
Sorry mate. My mom keeps coming in.
That's what happens when you've got a
mom that loves you. You would know cuz
your mom hates you like Dolex's mom. So,
you know, it's normal for for someone's
mother to try to help them, you know.
You know, so what? So, you're you're not
going to beat me, Joe? So, then you
can't sit there and tell people they'll
do nothing when you're going to hide,
you little [ __ ] So, you're going to
let me come up there and you're going to
run away like a little [ __ ] and and
tell other people that they won't do nothing?
Do you mean that you'll do nothing? So,
have you have you both agreed? Have you
both bro Lane has owned you people
multiple multiple times? She's
embarrassed me. She's literally owned
you people multiple times. You're fat.
You're ugly. You're moronic. You're
skint. I mean, Laney has owned you
people multiple multiple multiple times,
mate. You know, someone's going to be
embarrassed by you. You fat ugly
nonslegs lover. Shouldn't you be on your
boyfriend's channel nonslegs? your gay
boyfriend. Shouldn't you be in your gay
boyfriend's channel? You're both scared
of eating people. You're both keyboard
warriors. You're both do nothing.
Isn't it? You've got so many
similarities of your boyfriend, Joe. Why
have you got so many similarities as
your boyfriend? You're going to be
another one that lets me come to your
area and you'll do nothing. And I'm
going to show everyone that the fatty
will do nothing. And I'm gonna get so
file with my words. I'm going to call
you a fat, dirty nodslugger. Ugly
northern dirty little bastard. I'm going
to draw attention and you'll do nothing.
Don't [ __ ] come on here thinking that
you control me with your gay nonslegs
boyfriend with your gay l with your gay
self, with your ugly face, fatty misses,
[ __ ] ugly [ __ ] You know what I'm
saying? Don't dare think you can try and
troll me. you fat waster on a 200lb
phone and then and then and then we will
see who's the one that will do nothing.
You know, you've already told us that
you're in between Newcastle and Leeds,
but I'm going to go to Leeds cuz I
haven't been to Leeds for ages. And I'm
going to show you up. I was thinking
about it today, bro. Like when I was
pissed off when the bookies weren't
open. I'm going to show you up. Yeah, my
word doesn't mean anything. Okay,
brother. Like if that was the truth,
then you would come on the panel and you
talk. You know, listen, my word don't
mean nothing, brother. You're scared to
talk. Why are you talking about words?
You are scared of talking. Why are you
talking about people's words, bro? Why
are you talking about people's words
when you're scared of talking? That's
why there's an account on your that goes
on your um that goes on your channel and
he says that you're scared of me.
Because it's embarrassing, brother.
Very, very, very embarrassing.
There we go. I enjoy my fake holidays.
Okay. Yeah. Come back to me when you can
talk, you sad bastard.
Nons legs lover.
Yeah. You [ __ ] nons legs lover.
in 10 minutes. I'm not going back out.
Yeah, I won't be going back out. No,
[ __ ] that, bro. It's a shame because
there was some football playing. I'm not
going back out.
Yeah, like I said, Joseph, come back to
me when you can talk on a panel.
and we'll arrange a meet up. Then we'll
take you serious.
When you can grow a pair of balls and
talk on a panel, I'll take you serious.
Until then, go back to your non-slegs
boyfriend and suck his dick. That's the
only action that you're going to get.
What did I get for Christmas? None of your business.
I got six presents.
Yeah, none of your business. You're
another one that talk [ __ ] behind
people's back. None of your business.
But I got six presents.
Yeah, I'm not going back out, bro. [ __ ]
that. [ __ ] that. I was out earlier. I'm
not going back out.
Mate, I've had sex more times than you
will ever have. Joe, go suck your
boyfriend's dick. Oh, he got a
girlfriend. He got a girlfriend. Are you
sure you don't want to suck his dick
some more? You fat bastard. You scared
to talk? Scared to talk on my panels?
How does it feel that you're scared to
talk on my panels? Yeah, skin brother,
you're the one on the 200lb phone, not
me. You're the one with the 40 jeans,
not me. That's facts. That ain't me.
That's you. You're the one that's living
under poverty. Not me. That's your life.
Not me, Skip boy. You're the one with a
200 pound phone and a 40 jeans. That
ain't me. All of my shit's designer.
Nope. That's definitely you. 40 lb jeans
living under poverty. And I think that's
why you're so um obsessed with people
living under poverty cuz you're living
under poverty yourself. And the way
you're trying to like deflect is by
trying to tell me that I'm living under
poverty when the one that's living under
poverty is yourself. Poverty Joe.
Poverty Joe, lad.
Oh, he is broke as a [ __ ] joke, mate.
All of these all of these wins that he's
putting up is they're all fake. All he's
doing is putting his own money in. Yeah.
And taking it uh and then and and taking
it back out, pretending he's won. He he
shows fake wins. Do you not understand
this? Joseph Ferrar, he's very very low
IQ. All his channel was trying to do is
trying to annoy me, but I I'm smarter
than the fat waster, so he can't do it
to a guy like me, bro.
Yeah. Prove me wrong with facts. You've
never proved me wrong ever. All that
you've shown is you're a two-faced low
life that's scared to talk. That's the
only thing that you've proved.
The only thing that you you've proved is
that you're a scared waster who's scared
of talking and scared of meeting anyone.
That's the only thing that you've ever proved.
[ __ ] poverty ridden [ __ ] mug
showing fake wins. That's why you're so
obsessed with poverty because you're
living under poverty. You are the one.
Because you not understand that most of
the people in this community, brother,
it's just it's just self projection.
You know what I mean?
Bro, listen. Tell him to come on a panel
and talk. That would put it to bed, but
he can't. He's scared of talking.
Imagine being scared of talking.
Madness. [ __ ] madness.
But listen, like I said, Joseph Ferrar,
I'm not sub to your channel. All your
channel is is trying to troll me and you
suck at it. Like manto man, you really
suck. Your wins are fake. You're living
under poverty. You're [ __ ] skint. And
that's that. Skint, poverty ridden, low
life nonslegs lover that ain't got no
life. I am not sub to your channel. You
know your little fake wins and your fake
pension. Brother, I sussed you out ages
ago. It's too obvious. It's too obvious,
brother. Listen, you've already been
shown money and I'm not showing you
money ever again. Go self-reflect on
another channel. Yeah, you come on a
panel and you talk and you arrange to
meet me, then come back to me. You've
been shown money. You've been beating at
the money game. You've been shown money.
It's been repeating with you for years
now. You're boring, mate. You're boring.
And this is part of your disability.
This is part of your disability. You
have been shown money multiple times.
Nonss lover. The same thing as I'll say
to nonslegs. You have both been shown
money and you have run away multiple times.
Ah god. Listen. My word means nothing.
Okay. Come on the panel and talk and
tell me my word means nothing. Okay. Let
me put the link up for you. Right. Let
me put the link up. You come on here.
Right. You Joseph, listen. You come on
the panel, right, and tell me where to
meet you and tell me that I'll do
nothing and see what happens today.
Let's Let's put this to rest, right? You
come on the panel, you tell me where you
are and I'll do nothing and see what
happens today. Come on, big man. Let's
put this to rest. Come on. I've got all
the time in the world, right? And let's
see what happens. Tell me where you are
and tell me I'll do nothing and see what
happens next on a panel. On a panel. So,
it's actually arranged.
>> So, let's see. Yeah.
Yeah. Right. Let me put this link up. One sec. Come on.
Put this link up. Anyways, brother.
Yeah, that's self projection. No one
cares about saying your skin. That's
self projecting, bro. We all know you
people are skin. Man, brother,
come on, you fat nonsubber. Come on,
nonsle's boyfriend. come on the panel
and tell me where to meet you and try
and tell me I'll do nothing and see what
happens, bro. Right now. Do it right
now. I'm I'm free today, bro. I'm free
today. So, at the end of the day, I I
don't mind traveling anywhere. How about
your little dodge legs lover, your
boyfriend and I's rooting for you. Come
on. The panel's there. I'll let you in.
Just talk. Tell me where to meet you.
I'll be there today. No [ __ ] Come on.
Come on, Joseph Fra. Come on,
brother. No one cares about the skin
comments, brother. It's all projection
with you people. Oh my god, brother.
It's almost 2026. No one cares about the
self projection from you skin people.
It's boring now. It is boring now. The
skin self projection is boring now.
That's why no one reacts to it. Brother,
listen. We have proven you people to be
skinned multiple times. It's boring. You
can come on here every day and and still
calling people skin. It's not going to
prove that you people are the skint
ones. It's not going to change that.
It's not going to change. Listen,
Joseph, join the panel. Tell me where to
meet you and I'll be there today. I'll
get my coat on right now and I'll make moves
covered. You dodge legs lover. I'm
rooting for you. Your boyfriend's
rooting for you as well. What? What you
scared of? What are you scared of?
You're telling people that they'll do
nothing. Come on. Listen, bro. My coach. Listen. Listen.
Right. I'll put my car up.
Put my charger. I've got a backpack. I
don't mind. Come on the panel and try
and tell me where you are and tell me
I'll do nothing.
And see what happens in the next in the
four or five hours. Come on.
Come on. Do the fro.
Yeah. Anyways, no one cares about this
these self-p projecting comments. No one
cares about this. Anyways, Joseph
Ferrar, come on, bro.
Come on. I've got my little coat on, my
little evidence pack. The link's up
there. I'm ready when you are. Come on.
I'm free all day today, bro. I don't mind. Come on.
Come on. No self projection. Just come
on. Tell me where to meet you with your
voice and I'm coming.
I'll bring my little evidence pack if
you want. So you're not going to meet
me? No. So you're not going to meet me,
brother. I'm deadly serious. I said this
to you last week as well. I'm deadly deadly serious.
Yeah. No one cares about these boring
self-reflectors. Go away. Self-reflector
self projection. Anyways, that's all
these little melts do on here, bro.
Listen. Yeah. DH10. This is all these
people do on here, bro.
This is a fake Jo, but okay. Damn on
anyways. Just he's going to try and put
he's he's going to try porn bomb the whole thing.
Yeah. Okay. Good for you, bro. I showed
more money than that. Okay.
But good for you, bro. No one cares
about money. I'm showing more money than
that. All I want you to do is talk and
tell me where to meet you.
No, I didn't get it for Christmas. I
bought it myself. Anyways, all I want
you to do is talk and tell me where to meet you.
No one cares about that money, bro.
You've been shown more money than that
multiple times in 50s. Anyways, come on.
Tell me where to meet you. I'll meet
you. Simple. Not a problem. I'm free all day, bro. Idiot.
Same repeating bastards on here in it.
No, no, no, no, no. Joseph, Joseph,
Joseph, Joseph, Joseph, you've already
lost the money game. Listen, listen,
listen, brother. We're not playing the
money game anymore. We're playing the
meeting game. You have told me multiple
times that I will do nothing. Yeah,
that's what you've said multiple times.
Talk on a panel. Tell me I'll do nothing
and see what happens. Stop running away.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. You have
been shown more money than that, right?
Stop deflecting. Stop trying to turn
this into the money game again. You have
been shown money and I beat you at the
money game. End of. Come on here. Tell
me that I will do nothing. Tell me where
to meet you and see what happens in 4
hours, big man. Simple. Yeah. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
I I've gone up into lose. Are we Are we
meeting or what?
Come on, you little nonslegs lover.
Come on. Your boyfriend's rooting for
you, Joe. You're not going to let your
boyfriend out, are you? And you can tell
me face to face. Oh, he's got a
girlfriend. You can't be a virgin. You
can suck his dick. I'll bring him along with you.
Just show Cologne alone receipts.
Brother, listen. You pathetic
self-reflectors are not getting a
reaction. You can keep self-reflecting
your skimmness. It doesn't bother me.
I'm only interested in meeting this [ __ ] Yeah. Simple.
That's it, bro. That's that.
Come like your nonss lover [ __ ] It will
do nothing. You're You're still not
meeting anyone. You you you're talking
[ __ ] behind the keyboard all the [ __ ]
time and you still won't meet anyone.
What the [ __ ]
Joseph, you've already been beaten at
the money game for over a year. You got
shown 50s and I made you run away. I've
already made you run away. I don't need
to participate in that game again. That
little self-p projection game of yours
again. I want to meet you. You told me
numerous times I'll do nothing. Right. I
want to come to you today and laugh in
your face. I want to laugh in your face.
To your face. Simple. Come on.
So, you're not meeting? You're not going to? No.
I'll just disclose it for being a
[ __ ] nonslegs lover again. I told him
I'll meet him today, Dusty, but he won't meet me.
Well, he told he told me that I would do
nothing. So, I told him I want to tell
him about himself to his face. So yeah,
I mean I want to uh
Yeah, Boxing Day, Sunday Boxing Day. No,
actually Sunday opening hours is the
same in London. Again, that's lack of
life experience from you cuz Sundays in
London the bookies open at the same
time. So I think I've got more life
experience than you, [ __ ] In
London, they open the same time on
Sundays. Yeah. You know what I mean?
So actually yeah, Sunday opening hours
is actually the same as weekday opening hours. Idiots.
What? They are idiots though, isn't it?
I would just love to get my hands on one
of the mom. I would just give me 5
seconds with these fat, ugly, disabled
skinned people. Bro, you don't you know
what I mean, bro? Like, you know when I
was pissed off earlier down the road.
Yeah. Like, before I get on the bus,
just give me 5 seconds with these ugly
people. With these fat, ugly. I would
knock the [ __ ] out of them.
I would literally knock the [ __ ] [ __ ]
out of these ugly people, bro. Yeah.
You know what I mean?
They think they literally think that
you're on their side, you know.
>> No, don't don't don't counel over these
fat ugly people. They've got no family.
They got no one.
>> I understand.
>> Yeah, true.
Well, it pissed me off early with the
bookies because there's no reason why
they should be closed until 10:00 in the morning. >> Yeah.
>> 3 hours,
>> you know? It's annoying. That's what wow
me up cuz there's no reason for it. It's
like you're always waiting around, you know?