that [ __ ] account made 18 years ago.
You [ __ ] bum. And you're trying to
[ __ ] talk about me, bro.
Bro, I really hope this guy accepts me
to me, bro. I I'll go today, bro, if he
agrees to it. I don't mind, bro. I
really want to hurt one of these people.
I hate these people in this community,
bro. I [ __ ] hate these people. You
don't understand these fat ugly nerds.
Like, when I get my hands on one of
these people, bro, you're going to see
what will happen, bro. You will see what
will happen. I just want my hands on one
of these fat ugly skin [ __ ] bro.
Like, you know what I mean? With these
people on here, bro. Your account was
made 18 years ago. You sad bastard. I
just seen it, bro. 19th of February,
2007. You [ __ ] old dimwit. And you're
trying to [ __ ] talk about other
people, you sad [ __ ]
A lot of sad people on this community, bro. you know,
telling people to get off YouTube. You
people on YouTube from the time you wake
up to the time you go to bed, you sad
bastards. You might want to [ __ ] take
a leaf off your out your own book, you wasters.
[ __ ] 18 years ago your account was
created, you sad disabled bastards.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
18 years ago, you sad bastards. You was
on [ __ ] YouTube Christmas, you sad
bastards. How sad is that? Madness,
you know. Sad, sad, sad, pathetic,
jealous wasters. You know what I'm going
to do, bro? I'm going to put a link up.
You know, I'm going to put a link up in
a bit and I want you people to join and
show what you look like.
It'll explain a lot. Put your cameras on
and show your fat, ugly faces. You know
what? It will explain a lot,
you know. It will explain a lot
as to why you jealous people come on
here every day from the time you wake up
to the time you go to bed, you know. It
will explain a lot. It really will. Yeah.
[ __ ] 18 years ago. [ __ ] fat ugly mongos. Jesus Christ. Online harasses.
Ain't got no life, nothing.
Just like Joseph Fro. Another sad
bastard. It will be proven today that he
will do nothing for the second day again.
sad, ugly, low lives. Like, people don't
even like their [ __ ] comments, bro.
That's how unliked these people are.
Sad, ugly stalkers.
It's true, ain't it? It's true.
I hate these people on here, bro.
I [ __ ] do.
Is everyone going to join, bro? I'm
putting the link up. Yeah. Why don't one
of you people join? Show your faces.
Come on. You talk about other people
every day. Yeah. Why don't you come in
and show your faces?
Come on. I'll put the link up for you.
Nah, cuz you're fat and ugly, you know.
Not to show your ugly faces cuz you're
all old, you're all wrinkly, you're all
ugly. I'm not crying, bro. I'm just I'm
just saying what you people are like.
Oh, sad little bastards that can't get
off of YouTube. Disabled fat ugly
bastards. I'm not crying. I'm telling
you is what you are. Sad acts on YouTube
for eight years. Yeah. Calling people
every day that you don't know. You sad,
pathetic little bastards that get
bullied every day. That's why you're on
here talking to each other. You ain't
got no friends. I proved that you people
have been on here Christmas as well. You
people was on here Christmas cuz you got
no mates. You got no friends. You got no
mother. You got no money. People telling
you about yourselves, bro. Cuz it's the truth.
No friends, no girlfriend, no mates. No.
Is everything you, bro? Everything is
you. Human. No. I'm completely calm,
bro. I'm not fuming. I'm just telling
you sad acts about your lives. I'm I'm
all good, bro. Just telling you about
you disabled people
who can't get off of YouTube cuz you
ain't got a life,
you know, about you little ugly single
people. Anyways, what what's what's
what's your New Year's resolution?
Tell me what your New Year's resolution is.
uh YouTube being a low life for another eight years.
Are you going to be on YouTube being a
[ __ ] low life for another 8 years?
Are you going to get a life? Tell us,
bro. Tell us. We want to know. We want
to know, bro. I'm asking you a question.
Are you going to be a [ __ ] sad
[ __ ] low life for another eight years
calling people everything you think you
are? Bro, you people are triggered. You
are the ones that have to come on the
internet every day repeating yourselves.
You're majorly triggered. If I literally
if I had to wake up yet every day from
the time I go to the bed to from the
time I wake up to the time I go to bed
and hate on people, brother, that's
ultra triggered. Like that's where you
probably got the word from because
you're triggered yourselves every day,
you know, on here on YouTube hating on
people younger and better looking than
you. I mean, that takes some being
triggered, bro. Like it's not even I'm
not even being angry. I'm just stating
facts. I know the truth hurts, but it is
it is the truth.
Fat ugly people with no life. Pathetic.
That's what you people are. No friends,
no girlfriend. Yet you try to talk about
other people. You ain't got no money.
Brother, I'm calm as as a cucumber. I'm
just telling you people what you are.
I'm I'm addicted to YouTube. I was off
of YouTube for a week.
Yeah. Bro, only you would think of that,
bro. Listen. It's not my fault that you
ain't got a mother. Yeah. It's not my
fault that you got no bub. Because I'm
hitting a nerve what I'm saying about
you people. That's why you're writing
this stuff, bro. Cuz I'm hitting a
nerve. You people are low lives. You
can't take a day off of YouTube because
it's all you got. I've already proved
that you people was on YouTube
Christmas. You sad, depressed [ __ ]
idiots. That's what you are. Yeah,
bro. You don't have a bub. Your mom
doesn't want you. That's why you talk
about my mom, bro. Because you ain't got
a bub. Hit a nerve. I've hit a nerve of
you people. You people was on YouTube
[ __ ] Christmas. I hit a nerve of you
skid triggered people. I hit the nerve.
I can hit the nerve more than anyone
else can. No, no, no. That's That's you
people. Okay. Okay. Let's Let's go by
evidence. Okay. So, we go by evidence
now, right? We have proven that you
people can't take a day off of YouTube.
I can. I've been seen with women, you
people haven't. I've been seen with
money. You people haven't. All the
evidence is pointing to you being them
things. Not me. Not me, bro. Not Not me,
bro. Listen, join the panel and put and
show your camera. Put your camera on, brother.
put your camera on. It will explain a
lot. I'll put the link out again because
I think it's it's very rude if I don't
put the link up. Join the link and put
your camera on. It will explain a hell
of a lot, you know, and all of the
people right, you know, they will come
on and they'll see this. It will prove
that you people are fat, that you are
ugly, that you are nobodyies, that you
can't get off of YouTube, that you are
low lives, that you was on YouTube
Christmas because you got nothing.
Yeah, I'm a disabled bud. Okay, come in
the hangouts and put your camera on.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Bing b.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Join the link
and put your camera on.
Put your camera on. You're laughing
because you know that I'm right. Okay,
bro. Whatever. Come on. Come on the live
um join the link and put your camera on.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro. So, join
the hangouts, put your camera on. Let's
see your face and let's see your money.
Okay. Whatever. The link's there, bro.
Show your face. Show us your money.
What are you waiting for, bro? Jesus
Christ. We're both on YouTube. I want to
see your face and I want to see your
money. And this is where I'm going to
catch you people out again. So there's
there's no point of all of this. The
link's there. Come on.
Everything that you say is about
yourselves. I was actually giving you
advice earlier, but you didn't take it.
Like, okay, how long have you people
been doing this? Yeah. 2012. Since I was 15, right,
brother? You've already been shown
£5,000 and you ran away, brother. You
have been shown thousands and you ran
away. It's your turn. Anyways, listen.
What I was saying earlier is you people
have been doing this since 2012, right?
And you're still skinn, you're still
fat, you're still ugly, but you think by
doing it another [ __ ] 15, 16 years
it's going to change anything. But it's
not. You haters on here will always be
fat. You will always be ugly. No matter
how many times you try to say that I'm
ugly. Yeah, I've got nothing. Whatever
you keep saying, brother, listen. You
people have proven that you've got nothing.
You're You've proven more times that
you've got nothing. I've shown more
money, more women, more mates, better
looks. You can't even come on camera cuz
you're fat and ugly. So no matter how
many times you want to write stuff, bro,
it doesn't it doesn't bother us because
we know that you are the fat ugly ones.
Think about it, Michael. Yeah. All of
these people that have done this [ __ ] in
the past. Yeah. I can name you four
people that's done this for quite a long
time. Yeah. Saying that you're this,
you're that, you're this, you're that.
They were prolific at it. And then their
camera got put on and they were fat and
ugly. So when you think of it like that,
bro, we know what these people are like.
We know what these sad YouTube dependent
ugly people are. So it that's why it
does not bother us. I was pissed off
earlier because of something else.
I've told I've asked you to come on the
camera. M No, just these ugly people in
this community, bro. I'm just sick of
these people in this community. These
little low lives to be honest with you,
bro. That's that's all, man.
You know, these low life fat, ugly
people that ain't got nothing. You know,
bro, that's you, depression riddle.
That's you, bro. That's you fat, ugly
people. You're only talking about
yourselves. Mister can't take a day off of YouTube.
You can't even take a day off of
YouTube. Stop talking about yourself.
You've been doing it for 12 years and
you're still all of them things. You're
still You won't come. You won't come and
show your face cuz you're ugly. Because
you know your skin. Everything is about
you little imbeciles. Listen, bro. You
don't even have any mates. You're lonely
ugly people. I done this Christmas. I
done this on Christmas, brother. We've
shown what you people already are. Fat
and ugly. Disabled. can't get off of
YouTube. Why do you think Yeah. these
people that go on LS, they talk to each
other? Because they ain't got no mates.
They got no friends. Why do you think
they they they listen, bro? Why do you
think they come here and talk about
people having no friends? Because it's a
reflection of their own life when they
look in the mirror. They're skint.
They're ugly. They're boring. They got
no woman. And the only way they can cope
is by trying to tell you that you ain't
got these things. You know what I mean?
You've been shown £6,000 multiple times.
You showed me nothing. I've shown you
more women, better looks. You ran away
again. I mean, the evidence is there.
The evidence is literally in black and
white. You Listen, why don't you come on
camera now and show your face
cuz you're an ugly bastard. And that's
one you will always have on these
muners. These little muners on the
internet, you will always have on them,
bro. They can't show their face cuz
they're ugly and that's what kills them,
bro. Why do you think these people go
for me? Michael Barry M. I'm younger
than them. I'm better looking than them.
They're ugly old skint. Listen, I've
seen one of these accounts that
commented on my thing. Yeah, just a
minute ago. The account was made 18
years ago. So, could you imagine how old
that person is? 18 years ago, bro. 18
years ago. So read into that what you
will. An account made 18 [ __ ] years
ago. That's more than half of my life.
So that's already proven that they're
old, right? We've already proved that
they were on YouTube Christmas with no
family. I mean, we we're getting there.
You know what I mean? We're getting
there with these people.
18 years. I would have been [ __ ] 10.
What the [ __ ]
These people ain't got no family, no
life. I knew it all along, bro. I knew
it all along.
These s pathetic people, these monsters,
all all their life is is trying to bring
other people down to their level. That's
their life. That is their life on here.
They're at a level and they're trying to
bring other people down to their level
cuz they know they [ __ ] it. They
[ __ ] their life up. They're old.
They're ugly. They got no family. They
got no one to turn to. And that's why
they come on here. And that is why they
come on here doing this.
That's why they come on here doing this
because they don't have anything
in their shitty lives.
Yeah. Yeah. Skid, bro. Like I said,
you're only talking about yourself. All
you're doing is putting yourself down.
All you're doing is putting yourself
down, bro. When you're when you're
saying all of these things, you're only
talking about yourself.
You're only talking about yourself.
You're only putting yourself down. So
when you So when you write these things,
all you're doing is putting yourself
more down than you already are. You're
not affecting me. I know I'm younger
than you. I know I'm better looking than
you. I know I've got more body than you.
You can't come on a camera and have a
debate with me. You can't join the
hangouts, turn your camera on, and prove
me wrong because, bro, I know I'm
younger. I know I'm better looking. And
your shitty little self-p projecting
comments don't bother me.
Your shitty little self-reflecting
comments do not bother me, which is why
I don't block you. We've seen you fat
ugly people multiple times. We've seen
Graycat. We've seen Bomb. We've seen Pat
and they were all fat and ugly. And
funny enough, all of these people also
spoke about other people's looks,
you know, asking people to show you
£150. Brother, you've been shown
thousands of pounds and you run away.
Evidence again that you're skint.
Yeah, it was good, bro. It was good.
Yeah, man. These people's on YouTube
Christmas, by the way. Despite saying
that other people ain't got no family
and how my family hate me, these
people's on YouTube Christmas, lad.
But I did expect it to be honest, you know.
Everything they say on here is just about themselves.
It's just a reverse onto themselves.
Yeah, they were on Christmas.
It was good. These people's on YouTube Christmas.
These people's on YouTube Christmas, bro. Yeah.
When are you people going to actually
get off of YouTube and get a life?
You should make that your New Year's resolution.
You haters need to like just get a life.
What is it with these people on here,
Jensen? They're [ __ ] weirdos, aren't they?
What is it with these people, bro?
They're [ __ ] [ __ ] in the head. What
do you think? [ __ ] idiots.
Sat on the internet for [ __ ] how many
years calling people that they don't
know. Jesus [ __ ] Christ, man. Sad losers.
No looks, no money, no life. Sad
bastards. Real sad bastards. Madness, bro.
M. I've already got money.
Listen, [ __ ] if you want to ask me
something, try the hangouts and put your camera on.
Why do you reckon these people are there
harassing me all the time, Jensen? I
think they're jealous of me, bro. These
people are there. I generally think
they're they're jealous of me, even
though they won't um admit it to themselves.
These people are proper harassers on here, bro.
I think it's cuz I'm younger and better
looking than them and that's why they
look for me, bro. I honestly think that.
But I'm not even joking, but I'm not
even trying to like blow smoke up my
ass. It seems very very strange how
individuals that don't know anyone can
be obsessed every day. You know,
I think they're jealous of something in
life, bro. I'm not even I'm not even
joking, man. I'm not even just saying that.
And they don't do a full reaction before
you say that because even if you don't
give them a reaction, they still do it.
Just in case you was going to say that.
Weirdo, isn't it? Absolute weirdos.
Yeah, I haven't been out for ages.
Jensen approaching or drinking, man.
Well, I drunk on Christmas two beers,
but that was it. Yeah, bro. I I ain't
tried for ages, man.
I was just sick of it all. I just gave up.
Yeah, I just gave up, bro.
Nah, it's just always the same [ __ ] is it, bro?
I have a boyfriend, the same leading on,
and it's just um it's just toxic, bro.
That's why I gave up. I gave up with it
because it's too toxic. But I went I saw
a horror film the other day. Yeah. Have
you heard of The House made Jensen? It
was a good horror film, but the sex
scenes were so depressing, bro. It was
like it was a [ __ ] porno. I'm
thinking, "What the fuck?"
No, I'm thinking I'm going to try and
join the pool industry, bro.
Um, on the 1 of January, I'm going to
like sign up and see if I can join the porn industry. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
That's what I'm going to try. What I'm
going to try doing. I need to go to the dentist, bro.
I think I need another filling, man.
[ __ ] it's bad a bad it.
>> Yeah, I need to go to dentist, bro. For real.
I had a feeling um a month ago. Sorry. Yeah.
It's like right in your [ __ ] jaw as
well. It's horrible. [laughter]
Oh man, he's my dentist, bro. I to get an appointment.
Why do you think it's not fun doing it here, Jensen?
Is it because it's the same [ __ ]
I have a boyfriend and that is that why? [ __ ]
[ __ ] hell, bro.
I' say [ __ ] cable [ __ ] god knows
how many times a day. Painful, bro.
[ __ ] man. It is [ __ ]
Yeah, Joseph Flex's boyfriend if you
didn't know. Jensen,
they're so similar.
Very, very similar, bro.
I'm off if no one's typing. So, yeah. Yeah.