There we go. So, he's not meeting people.
He's a [ __ ] house.
Yeah, he's a [ __ ] house. [snorts]
Yeah, just as I expected. Well, you're
done anyways. You [ __ ] house.
[ __ ] absolute [ __ ] house, bro. Knew it.
[ __ ] knew it, bro. Here's the
[ __ ] house. Absolute [ __ ] house. Will
never meet anyone. I knew it, bro. I
[ __ ] knew it. [ __ ] knew it. Oh, man. Madness. Madness. What's up?
Yeah, another [ __ ] house.
Knew it. I [ __ ] knew it, bro.
>> [clears throat]
>> No, no, no, no.
What makes me laugh is how he says that
people laugh at me. How can anybody on
this community laugh at anyone, bro? The
state of these people, these wasters,
yeah, that have got nothing in life but
YouTube can laugh at another person. Are
you really sure about that? I don't
think so, man. I really, really, really
don't think so. Uh, no.
I really, really don't think so.
I think deep down you're laughing at
yourselves cuz you know you're
embarrassing just like this community
and then you're trying to say that you
laugh at me. Are you Are you for real?
No. You laugh at yourselves.
You don't laugh at someone that's
younger and better looking than you,
mate. Trust me, you you really really
don't. You laugh at yourselves. I'm so
ugly skinned people that ain't got no
life is laughing at
someone that's younger and better looking.
Make it make sense cuz I know that's
like your favorite word. So yeah, make
it make sense.
laugh at me
when I'm younger and better looking than
you, but you laugh at me. Fat, ugly, low
lives laugh at me.
People that don't ain't got no friends.
People that spent fat that spent uh
Christmas on YouTube laugh at me.
Really? Really? No, I don't think so.
You're [snorts] using exactly the same
excuse as Bomb Bomb used as well. All
you want to do is take a picture
of video run off or to say I told you so
fat disabled. Bro, you're using the
exact same. This is what I mean with
these people on here. They are literally
all the [ __ ] same.
They're all literally the same on here,
bro. These fat, ugly weasels with no
life. They are literally the same. Same
excuses, same [ __ ]
No life. They're all the same on here.
They've got exactly the same excuses as
well, come to think of it. Yeah.
Who's people? People from [ __ ]
large A's, bunch of fat, ugly virgins
that ain't got no life, ain't got no
money, ain't got no future. Laugh at me,
bro. What's to laugh at? Look at your
own lives. Yeah. Look at your own lives
before talking about other people.
[ __ ] 18 people on [ __ ] Christmas Day.
Look at yourselves before talking about
others laughing at others. [ __ ] pathetic, bro. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
That started it.
Sad sad people in this community, bro.
What's there to laugh at?
To be honest,
someone that's younger, someone that's
better looking than you. You You can't
even deny it. And And you're saying that
you're laughing at me? What the [ __ ]
What I'm laughing at is how most people
in this community ain't got a life
sat on here from the time they wake up
to the time they go to bed. No friends.
That's what I laugh at to be honest.
You know, they've got the same excuses.
I swear they're just all disabled on
this community, bro. This This is why
you rarely catch me on air. They're just disabled.
They're just disabled keyboard warriors,
fat, ugly people. Bit like Reddit
moderators in a in a way.
Brother, listen. I laugh at you people.
You was on YouTube Christmas,
sat on YouTube every day. Brother, I get
more laughs out of you pathetic people.
You You literally remind me what I don't
want to be like when I'm your age. fat,
ugly, no money, no family. I'm laughing
at you. I'm laughing at you fat, ugly
people every day on YouTube. I get more
laughs out of you than you would ever
have out of me. I've traveled all over
the UK. Not one of you people have come
out once. Not once. We all know that
your you are housebound. We all knows
that you're [ __ ] anxietyridden,
brother. You don't laugh at no one but yourselves.
fat ugly people that [ __ ] lie around
on YouTube every day. Seriously, bro,
bro, it is true. How can a bunch of
skint Yeah, listen. Listen. How can a
bunch of skint ugly people laugh at
someone like me, younger and better
looking? Make it make sense. Someone
younger, better looking, that's got a
better life than them. When was the last
time you people left your [ __ ] house?
You don't even leave your [ __ ] house.
You just come on here hating on
strangers every day. What could you
laugh at? Your life is no laughing matter.
Your lives are no laughing matter. It's
very, very serious, you know.
Yeah. I'm just reading what you wrote.
And it doesn't matter if someone's been
in a relationship for 3 years. He is an
absolute virgin because disabled women can't consent.
So, yes. Uh, he is an absolute virgin
and he will die a virgin just like
Timmy, just like the bomb.
There's a couple of virgins on this community, mate.
But yeah, you two have definitely
definitely got similarities.
Both jealous of Peterbelly, both
obsessed, both keyboard warriors. Oh, I
love your excuse as well. Uh, I love
your excuse for not meeting me, by the
way. That's a typical bomb excuse. Yeah,
because I'm going to do a video on
Runaway. [laughter] Oh, I had to laugh
at that one. Oh, bro. You really think
someone's going to travel all that way
to do a video on Runaway? It's pathetic.
It's literally pathetic.
You really think someone's going to
travel all that way to do that? [laughter]
You people are pathetic. Ah,
you are pathetic. You really, really are
pathetic. Just carry on showing your
fake pensions and your fake wins, [laughter]
mate. I would slap you up with one hand.
It's not even a joke.
You know, with with one [ __ ] hand.
It's really, really, really funny.
You know what I'm saying? It's really
funny. But we know why you people do
this. Fat, ugly, and disabled. We know
why you people do this on on the
internet. It's not like we don't know.
Every single person that's done this and
been exposed have been fat and ugly and
jealous. So, we know why you people do
it. So, that's why we can't get annoyed.
In a way, we feel sorry for you people.
I was pissed off at something else
yesterday. It wasn't you people whining
me up. I was pissed off because you
people are fat and ugly and that's the
root core of it. So, at the end of the
day, you don't bother no one. You're
just a bunch of fat, ugly people that
failed at everything in life that you've
tried. You're past your prime. You're
fat. You're old. You're ugly. You're
skint. And you're boring.
You know, we all know you about you
people. We all We all know what you
people are like now, you know. We all We
all know it. We all know you people.
What you do, you know?
Sad, obsessed little weirdos.
And that's that. I ain't got a life.
Simple. Is it?
I done a football bet yesterday. I only
put 20 on it
for both teams to score. I got two out
of four. Was an ass to be fair. I I I I
didn't really seem bothered, you know.
Yeah, my sister has a gambling account.
so I just put 20 pound on the football.
Well, I can't get a win because I rarely
gamble. If I wanted to get a win, I
would. I don't need to win. I've got enough money.
You said they ask for proof of income if
you win online in it. So yeah, I'm not
going to I'm not going to play online
ever again. I don't think
I don't need a win, mate. I've got
enough money. Your joys of you not
knowing what other people have. Yeah. So
that's why I'm not doing it. My my
sister's got a bookie account. I'm not
going to say which one. And I [snorts]
was thinking, okay, maybe one time I'll
put like I'll put some money on roulette
like whenever I want to play it rarely.
But then if they're just going to ask
for that, then there's no point.
There's no point. I'm not doing that. So,
when I deposited £200 on Roulette, bro,
it was a £17 fee. You know, they charged
me £17 to deposit.
So, I actually lost £217 when I played
the other day. £17.
So, I can't even use that site anymore.
the industry is pretty [ __ ] dead, isn't it?
I mean, unless unless you bet in the
bookies, I I wouldn't trust getting paid
out to be honest.
Yeah, £17. It weren't even like it was
two or£3 pound. It was And then I was
going to put it on the football, but
then it would have lost anyways. I'm not
[ __ ] That is mental, man. I'm not
Yeah. So, I don't I I think unless you
bet in the bookies, you're you're not
ever guaranteed, you know, it's not
going to ever be fair,
you know? I don't think cuz the bookies
there's no fee and you obviously you get
paid there and then
arcades. Yeah. So even casinos are dodgy.
So obviously you can use a dodgy site
online but obviously the fees and even
if there was no fees they could just
easily just not pay you. So you're
pretty much [ __ ] really unless you
there like you said the bookies or or the arcade.
Pretty much. Yeah.
I remember before I put 60 and I won a
grand. They paid within seconds. It went
straight into my account.
Why do they ask you for proof of uh
proof of um income
and obviously it's a UK regulated
regulated site so
they will do it if I win. That's the thing.
Yeah, that's a new thing. That is
though. They never used to do that.
I don't know why they do that, bro. What
the [ __ ] I bet a lot of people don't
play now cuz of that it
was you playing that 100 to one
roulette. I think I've only played that
a couple of times. Yeah,
[ __ ] £17 [ __ ] fee. But what makes
you laugh is that when you withdraw that
there's no um there's no fee when you
withdraw. That's the that's the funny
thing about it.
Well, you can if you use PayPal.
You can if you use PayPal.
There's a way around it. PayPal. Thank me later.
Yeah, you can if you use PayPal. That
was a problem with a lot of people. Just use PayPal. Simple.
Are you sure? Oh, well, I heard people
using PayPal, so
but it's not even just that. Anyways,
you need to make sure obviously you're
going to get your money, you know, and
obviously Yeah. So, they charge a fee,
but then when you withdraw, there's no fee.
See, with the um golden bet, it used to
be a fee to withdraw, but it wasn't
obviously much. So, I didn't mind it. But
industry's finished. It is literally
[ __ ] finished, mate. [ __ ] me. [clears throat]
Making myself a lovely cup of [ __ ] I
feel so much better. You know, Joseph,
giving up on the dating scene. Oh my
god, I feel so much better. I had a good
Christmas. No mood swings.
Did that not tell you how toxic the old thing was?
I don't want to go back to it ever
again. I think it's been over a month
now. It feels so good having that out
your life. Oh, mate. [ __ ] hell. Yeah. Feels good.
Never again, bro. Never again.
Yeah, maybe March.
Maybe March or something, but I won't be
because I'm applying for the pawn thing
in the new year. Well, here's what I
said I was going to do. I said that I'm
going to every um single option I can
before I try it again. I'm going to try
the pawn thing and I'm going to look at
other things to see. And if there's
literally no other way, then I'll try
again in maybe 3 months. I
[clears throat] mean, I'm going to do
everything I can to not go around in
circles again. But if I have to, then I will. Simple.
But I'm going to try my best not to cuz
I don't want to deal with that [ __ ] ever
again. It's not normal. It's toxic. And
you know it's not normal because when
you give up, you will know when you give
up for two weeks, you feel so good. Oh
my god, you have no problems. That's how
you know it's just [ __ ] up in the
first place. I'll try the ball thing
and that's it.
So I'll try and if if there is no other
way then I will have to try again in
March or something. I don't know. But
I don't want to I really don't want to.
I'm a grown ass man and I don't want to
be playing people's stupid games anymore. You know
there was this woman Joe. Yeah. Yeah.
And this black guy approached her on
Instagram, but he deleted it. I've
actually got it recorded. He's gone up
to talk to her. She was on the phone.
She's like, "I'm on the phone. Move away
from me." And I'm thinking, "Bro, what
what the what, bro?
Their [ __ ] attitude. Who the [ __ ] do
they think they're talking to?" That
annoyed me even just watching that. And
they weren't even talking to me. And I'm
thinking, I'm so glad I don't have to
deal with that [ __ ] anymore. It's just
annoying even watching it.
But I don't have to I don't have to deal
with it anymore. You know,
I just made myself a tea. I need to cut
back on the sugar. I don't have sugar in
my tea anymore cuz my teeth. So, yeah.
But I would do everything I possibly can
um to to to not want to go around in circles again
because obviously he was approaching
her, but you don't have to be [ __ ] rude.
And you shouldn't be rude because if
that man stands up to you, you're not
going to like it. If someone tells you
about if he told her about herself,
you're not going to like it. So what's
the [ __ ] point of it, bro? What's the
point of being toxic and rude? Because
if that guy stands up for himself,
you're not going to like it. You ain't
So I just don't understand. It just what
what why people need to be like that.
It's it's mad.
But rather than the me dealing with it,
I'm not dealing with that again, mate.
I'll be you'll be damned if you think
I'm [ __ ] dealing with that again.
[ __ ] that, mate. Yeah.
Oh, by the way, when I done that 200 on
roulette last week, I just thought if I
had went out drinking every week, I
would have been spending more than 200.
So, to be honest, it wasn't even that bad. >> Yeah.
but yeah, I'll give it until like March,
midFeb, March. If nothing's happened,
then then I'll have to go out again.
Hopefully not, though. Hopefully, we'll
sort something out. Yeah,
it ain't it. It's It's bad, bro.
You know, it is bad,
but it doesn't annoy me anymore. I'm
fine cuz obviously I've I've given up. So,
it's only the sex scenes in the horror
films that um that bothered me the other day.
That bothered me a lot.
I bit [ __ ] paid to watch Paul and I
went to [ __ ] see a horror film. But yeah,
I saw some guy approaching in
Switzerland earlier. It seems like it's
the same there as well.
Same there as well, matey.
Yeah, I need to cut back on sugar for a
couple of weeks and Yeah. Yeah, man.
So, like if it was if it wasn't that
Morgan's thing, would you still be
playing online then or now?
I used to gamble mostly
in real life in it. I only played online sometimes,
but I don't know, man. It's just
[ __ ] is it? It's [ __ ]
All is [ __ ]
He's trying to get your money off the bastards
and and the fees and [ __ ] So, how how much
How much can you withdraw before they
start asking for like proof of um income and that
cuz to be honest when I done golden bet
yeah they asked me for proof of
transaction which was fair enough though
cuz I had enough money out of them
before they started asking like that was
after like the 10th [ __ ] withdrawal
and they just said oh can you show this
and it was bit by bit and to be fair but
proof of income [ __ ] at you know
you that's none of their business to be
honest. You should have to show them
proof of income. That's nothing to do.
That's not their business mate to be
fair. Why are they asking for that? Um
and obviously the dodgy sites are
[ __ ] they they charge ridiculous fees.
[ __ ] knows, bro. [ __ ] You can't win
nowadays, bro. It's just can't win.
It's [ __ ] isn't it?
I was thinking a go on that global draw roulette
in Lab Brooks, that global draw one.
I probably won't though, to be honest. [ __ ] knows.
[ __ ] knows, man.
I don't want to go back to in the new
year. This whole approaching thing. It's
[ __ ] boring, mate. Really, really boring.
It's really [ __ ] It's really boring. I
just chill nowadays and eat good food.
I'm not asked about sex and women. I
don't think about it
to be fair.
It's not worth it, you know.
>> [clears throat]
>> Oh, Joe. This woman was complaining. She
said, "Oh, she she gets dates and sex,
but she can't she can't find someone to
settle down with." Oh, poor you
being able to get dates and get sex. Oh,
poor you. I almost cried.
So hard done by, is it? Someone that's
able to get dates and sex. Wow. So hard
done by, aren't you?
Yeah. So hard done by.
That just goes to show that they would
never ever be able to walk a mile in any
man's shoes, bro. If they're moaning
about getting [ __ ] dates and getting
getting sex. That is insane, bro.
And quite frankly, it's just a mug's
game. And that's why I gave up because
it honestly is just a mugs game.
Think of it. It's what I said the other
day. It's like you g if you gamble
sometimes you win. Yeah. People tell you
don't gamble because you're going to
lose in the end with the dating thing.
You'll never win. You'll always go
around in circles. You always have the
same problems. So I'm surprised people
don't tell men to give up on dating, you
know, a long time ago or people that
struggling. They tell people to give up
on [ __ ] gambling.
It's just strange. It is strange because
gambling's got better odds than dating. So
very very strange.
A bit hungry. [snorts] Yeah.
Monty man makes me laugh.
Monty man makes me laugh. He said that's
five people that's got no family. [laughter] I'm dead.
>> You all right, Laney? Oh.
I feel peckish. I don't know what to get.
Oh, that's so annoying.
I can't have corn flakes.
No, I can't have corn flakes
cuz the old toothies. Oh, [snorts] [ __ ] hell.
Should I eat a Anybody
can come on the internet. Even a child
can come on the internet um and you know
do what uh do what you do basically. So
you know when you actually grow a pair
of balls and you can actually meet
someone then come back and talk about
how you bully this person and bully that person.
Like my life's the worst on here, bro.
You people literally come on here from
the time you wake up to the time you go
to bed typing shitty comments. It was
only a Christmas day. I proved you was
So what are you on about?
Like you're an idiot. Like I would say
my life is probably better than most
people's on here and I don't even have a
perfect life. It's not even about me
having a perfect life. It's what these
people do on here every day.
Yo, what are you saying, bro? Yeah, I
just went on your channel bullying me.
Smokey B. I would knock you out with one
hand, bro. It's not even a joke. One
punch, I'd knock you out. Just because
you're a keyboard warrior, it doesn't
mean you bully anyone. It's like what uh
the quote Mike Tyson said about keyboard warriors.
Stop it. It's embarrassing now.
And yeah, I'm glad you're finished
bullying cuz you never bullied in the
first place. You little [ __ ] house. All
you done was showed yourself up
and we know. Why don't you we join
Hangouts and put your camera on and show
us what you've got. You ain't got nothing, bro.
All you people live to do is hate on the
internet for years. That's what you live
to do. That's your lives. You know,
so much self projection on this
community, Jeremy Kyle. It's unbelievable.
I'm younger than these people. I'm
better looking than these people. I can
do what I want when I want. Why is my
life bad, bro?
What? Because I'm simply what? Chilling
in the winter and not going out drinking
in the winter. I mean, what? I mean, I
was busy yesterday. I was busy the day
before that. What makes my life bad?
Because I don't go out drinking every
week in the winter. Like, you need you,
if you're going to say something, bro,
you need to back up what you're saying.
I think I know that you people have got
a [ __ ] life because what you come on
here and you do every day. You was on
here Christmas. I mean it's it's facts.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
I don't know what they want you to be
doing. What the [ __ ]
Just self projection with these people.
You know, you don't bully people just
cuz you talk [ __ ] behind a keyboard.
Anyone can do that. Anyone can be a keyboard warrior
and that's that.
You know what I mean?
We know. So all of these we Why don't
you join Why don't you join the link?
But you won't join the link and you
won't show what you look like because
you people on here are fat and ugly. And
I'm talking about the haters. I'm not
talking about like people. Fat, ugly
people with no life.
What's it matter what I do, bro? I don't
understand. What the [ __ ]
Look at all of the people that go and L
J is typing away. They got no family.
They got no life. They have nothing.
They literally have got nothing. not
even their youth and they're trying to
talk about [ __ ] other people,
you know? It's mad.
Don't forget, I've done a lot of [ __ ] in
the past four or five years. These
people ain't ain't done nothing. If I
want to chill out for a couple of
months, that's that's on me, bro.
You know what I mean?
I don't go out drinking anymore for a
reason. I don't deal with women anymore
for a reason. if that's what you're
referring to. There's a reason why I
stopped doing it and money wasn't the
reason and it isn't the reason. So, you know, mate, like
any of these people joining and put
their camera on, it would explain a lot.
I've said it from day one and I'm saying
it now again.
Fat, ugly, stinky people probably don't
even leave the house. these people, man. You know, sad bastards.
Well, then they just join the hangouts,
put their camera on, show them what they
look like, show them what they've got.
But they can't do that cuz they're
embarrassed by the way they look.
They're embarrassed by their life. And
they come and talk about other people, you know,
and that's that.
That Smokey B ain't got no life. He
ain't got no life at all.
He has got no life at all, mate.
Coming on there trolling at his age when
he's older than me. You ain't got no
life. You ain't got [ __ ] all.
idiot as [ __ ]
could get that, but no.
If you had come when you said you was
going to come, you would have knew what
time it was. You little fanny. You never
bullied anyone in your life. You little fanny, mate.
You would have known what time it is,
mate. If you come and you said you was
going to come, you would have you would
have got slapped the [ __ ] up and
everyone would have saw it as well. Let
me reply to that.
You've never believed anyone in your
life. You little Milton Kees funny.
W Ke's funny. You're nothing but a keyboard warrior.
And if you had come
that day, you stood. [snorts]
You know what? If I was if I was fat and
ugly like these people, they'd have no
problem with you.
You'd fit in well on this community. If
you if you was fat and ugly like these
people, you would you would fit in well.
You'd fit in well, bro. You'd fit in
very very well.
You'd fit in very well.
Ke's funny, mate. Never bullied anyone
in your life. If you come on the door
that day, you would got slapped up and
you know it. You [ __ ] idiot about you
bullying me. Get out of here, you
[ __ ] monk. You bully yourselves, you embarrassment.
Your whole channel is a [ __ ] embarrassment.
I can't believe they these people just
hate the fact that you're younger and
better looking than them. It's madness,
isn't it? It really, really, really is
madness. They turn It's as if they turn
their nose up,
you know, uh to people that aren't like them.
I'm going to try this uh thingy again.
Yeah. Why are these people so obsessed
with me? DH10.
They're so bloody obsessed with me, these people.
I wish I was fat and ugly. Then I'd be more accepted.
Yeah, I think these people are really
jealous, bro, of me. I'm not even going
I'm not even saying that to make myself
look good. I I generally think it is
jealousy with these people, bro. Yeah, definitely. that bro.
Um, I had to uh
I had to book a dentist appointment. My
bad. I was on the phone.
I don't know. Why are they so obsessed
with me? BH10.
They say that they're not jealous of me,
but I think they are.
Yeah, sorry. I had to book a [ __ ]
dentist Boy, man.
quite long for an appointment, but is
what it is.
Yeah, they always gone about my looks,
bro. I think those kids deep down they
know I'm better looking than them.
Ah, you little copycat. Meow.
What the [ __ ] can I eat, bro?
You're nothing but a stinking copycat. DH10 little copycat.
I love these people to put their cameras
on and show their faces. DH10 no.
I'm surprised that Smokey B ain't
deleted his account. The [ __ ] house.
I'm only joking, bro.
I love these people. Yeah, I was only joking.
I wish these people would come and come
on and put their cameras on, bro. Like
join and put their cameras on.
It would explain a lot, wouldn't it, DH?
Then it would explain a lot.
Oh, you were like that. [snorts] Weirdos, bro. Huh? >> Definitely. >> Yeah.
>> Why do you think they do it? DH10. Huh?
I might go watch that Spongebob thingy though. Maybe
I'm hungry. M.
Yeah. I'm just thinking what? Nah,
I'll just eat later.
Cooking that long.
No, [ __ ] that.
It's quite far away now.
Christmas just ruins everything, can it?
Why do you think they do it? DH10, why
Now, if you was to guess, it's very
strange, isn't it?
I think it's just because they're fat
and ugly and jealous to be honest, bro.
Yeah, that's what I think.
See, I can show my face, bro. I need to
get a haircut.
I need to get a haircut, brother. Jesus,
it's not bad. I need to shave. See, I
can show my face, but I'm not scared
like these people.
I [snorts] can do something these people
could never do.
I don't know what's so uh
they can't show their face, bro. Cuz if
they show their face,
they don't have a life. They ain't got
no, bro. I was on a um
on Christmas, bro. I was live for 5
minutes. I walked downstairs, made a
tea. I come back up and there was people
watching and a couple of people typing.
So this goes to show that everything
that they say is all about them. Skin,
lonely, fat, ugly, everything is about
them, bro. This is what I mean. Family
hate you. They say your family hate you.
And that that's projection, bro.
Everything is about these people that
they're basically with these people.
They're they're um
at a certain level in life and they want
to bring other people down to their
level. That's basically what it is with these people.
They ain't got no life. [sighs]
They've got no life whatsoever. Did you
just realize that?
Yeah. Because they're low lives. They
ain't got nothing. They're nobodyies.
Like I'm only on here DH because I've
took a break from like the dating and
the going out and drinking and [ __ ] So
I mean I was off of YouTube for a week.
Now I'm just back for a little bit.
But cuz obviously I don't really go out
much anymore cuz of how toxic it is.
But yeah. Yeah. Red Star does it as
well. He he messages people about me. They're sados.
They're in denial. If they if they don't
think that they're they're jealous or
something, bro, they're they're lying to
themselves. They're not even lying to
me. They're lying to themselves.
Yeah, they're they're lying to
themselves, bro. [sighs]
And they'll never come on camera and
show what they look like.
They ain't got no life.
They can't even take one day off of
YouTube. They can't say the same about me. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
Did you just hear what I said?
Did you just hear what I just told you a
minute ago, brother? It would have
answered that question that you just asked me
considering I've given up because of how
toxic it is. Uh, no.
And it won't be for a very, very, very,
very long time.
I'm happy being like this, bro. I I No,
I gave up basically. I I've given up, bro,
because of how toxic it is and
depressing it is. That's why I gave up.
And boy, does your mood change when you
give up. You feel so much better. That's
how you know how toxic it was in the first place.
So now I've completely given up with it,
bro. It's depressing, annoying. I just gave up
and I won't be back doing it for a very
long time. If I can help it forever, if
I can find if I can find something else
like joining the, you know, porn
industry or whatever. You know what I'm
saying, bro? Cuz I I don't want to go
back to that, man.
And I should have to go back to it.
So, that's that.
[snorts] Nah, once you you get to a
certain point, you get to a certain age,
bro, that you realize that they're all
the same. And once you realize they're
all the same and they'll never change, brother, you
you're wasting your time.
Generally are, bro.
You got nothing to do with [ __ ]
It's like, nah, I'm good, bro.
I'd rather not,
you know? I'd rather not.
Yeah. Yeah, I went to watch that new
horror film DH10
and there was like um sex scenes in
there and it was um yeah, kind of depression depressing.
I don't know if you watched the new
horror film, but other than that, it
doesn't bother me. I don't care. I don't
I don't want to try again, bro.
Yeah, I went to watch that housemmaid.
Yeah, that housemaid was sexy, bro. Oh my god,
I was crushing hard the whole way
through. There was like sex scenes and
that. But um see that and I didn't even
know she was famous. I didn't know she
was really big until um I I looked up
the film and then saw the actors. I
didn't know anything about her. And I've
got a very specific type. I'm not like
[ __ ] legs [ __ ] saying Shevil Cole
is attractive to fit in. I don't go by
names. I don't know people's names. I
don't I don't copy people. I didn't even
know who the [ __ ] she was. But it turns
out she's really famous. Yeah.
I don't um I don't copy the crowd.
say people are attractive to fit in.
That's just boring, bro. I'm not a copycat.
I've got a mind of my own.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah, I watch and I and I still need to
watch the Spongebob movie.
I need to watch the Spongebob movie, bro.
The Spongebob movie. And yeah,
that's it. I think I just seen him. So yeah. Yeah, bro.
No. Did you watch a new horror film? It
was a good one to be honest.
Yeah, it was good, bro. Like I said, I
can show my face. I'm not scared of what
I look like. These people are. They can
say you're this.
Yeah. The new horror film called The
Housemaid, bro. It's It's trending. It's
got pretty big.
But you There's always sex sex scenes in
these horror films. And it's like it's
trying to mock you.
It's like it's trying to mock you cuz
obviously you won't be able to just go
out and meet someone. It's never going
to happen. It's already been established
in this country. It's never going to
happen. So when you happen to see [ __ ] like that. Yeah.
It's kind of depressing, you know.
Because you're not going to meet anyone.
You're not going to meet anyone. That's
normal. And that's that. So
yeah, I've got money. I've got enough
money to go out. I got plenty of money,
bro. It's not about money.
You know, I make money. I've got ways to
make money. I've got money. Simple as
that. And it is definitely definitely
not that. You know, you get to a certain
age and you think, "Bro, what the [ __ ] man?"
Just people that don't play games.
Uh women that don't act act toxic, have
attitude, and play games. And there's no
one in the world that exists like that.
So, I mean, they are all the same.
They're rude, they're stuck up, they
play mind games, they leave people on. I
don't need that tox toxicness around me, bro.
Simple as that. So, it's better giving
up. It was for the best, to be honest. Yeah.
Bad really. And then you get to a point
where like I I was saying before, I
don't know if you was on it, is that I
shouldn't have to keep trying. I
shouldn't have to. I've tried enough. I
should be with someone. And if I don't,
then I don't. Simple. I'm not trying
again. [ __ ] that, bro. You get [ __ ]
I'm not doing that again.
Why should I have to,
you know, at this age? Why should I have
to keep trying? I've tried more than
enough. Get [ __ ] It's a mug's game,
you know? So, that's that.
We know what they're like.
And that's it. Yeah,
I don't have four both teams to score. I
got two out of four. I just needed Hford
and um Enfield Town to score and then never
put 20 on four teams.
Sorry, normal. I should rephrase the
word normal. Uh decent. There's no
decent women in the world. Sorry.
Yeah, they're not decent. So yeah,
they're all just [ __ ] and play
games with people. [snorts]
The last time I went out was with my sister. Yeah,
cuz at 28 is not the age where you go
out drinking as much as you did when you was younger.
So why should I have to keep doing it? I
shouldn't have to keep doing it, bro.
And I will not keep doing that. I refuse.
So that's that. [sighs and gasps]
It's all good, bro. Yeah. [clears throat]
But yeah, you go on large days, you
always see it's the same people in it.
DH then same repeated people.
They've got all this money, all this
life, but they were on YouTube typing
away all day. Doesn't add up, does it,
bro? Doesn't add up.
I should be able to put out New Year's Eve. Really? Says who?
What is it? Suddenly got to be different
this New Year's Eve than the last one
and the last one and the last one.
I don't think so.
Definitely definitely don't think so. I
mean, it wasn't different last New
Year's Eve. It wasn't different the New
Year's before that and the New Year's
before that and the bank holiday before
that. So, I don't know. I don't think
so, bro. I don't fancy my chances.
I don't fancy my chances,
bro. It doesn't matter what party you go
to. It doesn't matter what day it is.
Women are the same. So
I refuse, lad. I don't know. But when I was
Yeah. Of course she was, bro. Of course she was.
At 28. That's a bit old to be doing
that. You should have been doing that at
like 24, 25.
28. Every week. At 28. Really? I stopped
that [ __ ] at like 26. Going out every week. H strange.
Every week at 28. I ain't got out every
week for the past 15 months. Probably
more than that. Wow. That's mad. You
must have had a lot of energy. >> Yeah. Jesus Christ.
>> And that's that's for you, bro. But
guess what? I I can I can assure you
I've been with more women than you and
I've been out more times drinking than
you. And it's not a competition. I'm
just telling you facts. I have, mate. I
used to go out two, three times a week.
Why the [ __ ] would I be going out
drinking every week,
you know? No, you should be settled down
now at 28. No, you should be settled
down now. And by you, I mean me. You
shouldn't you shouldn't go out drinking
every week at 28. You should be settled
down now. Now.
You know, you're closer to 30 than
[ __ ] 20. You should be settled down now.
I'm not [ __ ] going out drinking every
week, bro. [ __ ] that. I ain't been out in ages. So, yeah.
Because it's impossible to date in this
country, as you know. So, I don't know
why you're asking I don't know why
you're asking the questions, you know,
the answers to
because women are [ __ ] in this
country and they're stuck up and they've
got unrealistic standards. I'm not going
to have a debate about it.
So yeah, and I'm not going to get into
it either. So, but there you go. You
answer the question and that's that.
Drinking every week at 28. You must have
got some weird [ __ ] looks.
Must have got some weird looks. [ __ ] that.
Okay, bro. Whatever. Well, you have your
experiences. I have mine. End the story.
Yeah, just leave it there. I have my
experiences. I know what they're like.
I've been out millions of times. I know
what they're like. I've got evidence to
support what I'm saying and that's it.
Just agree to disagree.
Whatever, bro. I'm not here to argue. I gain nothing.
You know, I watched the uh Instagram thing, bro.
Oh, bro. Of course he is. But that's
normal. I mean, every everyone will just
dismiss your struggles.
Bro, that's that's uh that's um that's
what they do. Dismiss your struggles.
But if you're a woman, they feel sorry
for you. And that's another thing, bro.
If you know that it's a gender thing,
it's a waste of time arguing because we
all know that women that date and get
sex that have been dumped by a man,
everyone feels sorry for them. And but
yet, if a man tells people his
experiences, they all blame him. Once
you know it's a gender thing,
especially, it's a waste of time
arguing. It's a waste. It's a waste of
time arguing. Anyways, I watched an
Instagram thing um the other day and
it's like it's just a waste of time
arguing. Arguing you just never get
anywhere in life arguing. It's the
truth. And with this thing, it's a
gender thing as well.
They're biased based on gender. So, you
know, that's that that makes it even more um worse. So, [gasps]
and I'd say it's pretty impossible for
80% of people. It's more impossible for
people than it's not. So, yeah.
And I'm not comparing myself to other
people either. So, Oh.
Yeah. You've been married for 12 13
years. And how long have you been with that person?
Listen, mate. I'm not comparing myself
to other people, so you're wasting your time.
Bomb. Who's under that account?
Yeah. Good luck trying to date now,
mate. If you ever get divorced, you know.
So, yeah. You've known your life your
wife for 15 years. Well, if you ever
break up with your wife, bro, try and
date in this day and age and see how far
you get. That's all I'm saying.
You 15 years ago. Do you mean before
Instagram and before Tik Tok? Sounds
about right. Yeah. Yeah. Back in back in
the house party days. Yeah. Yeah.
Sounds about right to be fair. 15 years
ago sounds about right. Probably a lot
easier two years ago for [ __ ] sake.
15 years ago was even easier then.
Mate, I see people doing this [ __ ]
Multiple guys approaching women on
Instagram and they get the same [ __ ]
They all get the same [ __ ] Black,
[ __ ] white, no matter what color they
are. I've been watching them, bro. It
comes up on my Instagram thing. Yeah.
Yeah. See you.
>> Yeah. All right.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I will. No.
>> No. It's definitely a female problem.
Definitely. Definitely a female problem.
I've watched guys on Instagram. Yeah.
Black, white, different colors, and they
get the same thing. No, it's definitely
women. Even Even when I'm not even when
I'm not approaching DH10, I'm watching
these other guys do it. It's definitely
definitely women. Like, I'm I'm not in
the I'm not on the dating I'm not in the
dating game anymore, bro. I ain't
approached for ages. And I see these
guys, England and America, and that
tells you that it's the women because
all of all of these different guys that
go to approach these women, they all get
the same thing. I was watching it in
Switzerland, America, Manchester, it's
definitely definitely these women. And
if you tune into like Ed Matthews, have
you ever watched Ed Matthews? And this
guy actually gets like women sometimes
and he gets the same [ __ ] That's how
you know it's definitely definitely
women. When you're seeing it happen to
other people, white, black, [ __ ]
Swiss people, it's definitely definitely women.
And then when you go to Thailand, you'll
get none of these problems. I mean I
mean the proof is that it is women. But
with people like this Anna account,
right, they will never admit it because
where they've never had a woman, their
way is defending women, thinking that
they will get a woman, you know?
like these and look no job. This is
self- projection. Clean your teeth. See
where this guy's never had a woman. He
what what is with a lot of these white
knights. Yeah. They think by defending
women it will get them women. But women
don't like them. But because they've got
autism, you know, like these white
knights, because women have never liked
them, they think by sucking up to them
um it will get them women. This Anna is
probably a virgin.
Never had a girlfriend, never been laid.
And I've had more women than him. A lot
of these people that are defending
women, you will find that you've had
more women than them. And yeah, you are
speaking facts about yourself. No job.
Why are you not at work now? Okay, one
second. You You want to talk about
working? Yeah. Why you Why are you not
at work now?
It's self projection. That's why no one
gets Bro, this is why no one gets mad at
you people because you're self
projecting. You're trying to bring other
people down to your level. It's what?
This is all you fat, ugly people do is
try to bring people down to your ugly
virgin level and it's not going to work.
You ugly people are never going to bring
anyone down. You tried at Christmas.
Yeah, you tried it a couple of days. You
No, you actually tried it a couple of
days before Christmas try to bring
people down to your ugly level coming on
YouTube every day trying to tell me my
family hates me this and then I go live
on YouTube for 5 minutes with evidence
that it was you people that had no
family. You people that ain't got any of
these things, all you're doing is trying
to bring people down to your level.
Ugly, jobless, no woman, failed at
everything in life, no hope. Like we've
seen, brother, you've done it weeks before Christmas,
trying to ruin people's Christmas cuz
you losers have got no one. Am I lying?
I'm not blocking anyone because I'm
lying. I'm not lying, am I? Yeah. My mom
hates me, brother. Again, this is self projection,
brother. This is self-p projection.
You people was on YouTube with no family
on Christmas. This is self projection.
I don't know how many times I have to
get through to you people. You ugly
people was on YouTube on Christmas.
Evidence does not lie, bro.
Yeah. Evidence don't lie. You was on
YouTube Christmas. Let that sink in. Yeah.
Yeah. I was at my sister's Christmas.
had some nice food with my sister, with
her friend, with my the [ __ ] is this?
With my mom. Who's this?
People was on YouTube Christmas. The
evidence is there, bro. The evidence was
there and is there. All you people do is
self-reflect. Anyways, why are you not
at work today?
Why are you not at work today?
Why are you not getting on with your
life today? Is it cuz you're fat, ugly,
straight on to YouTube? It doesn't
matter if it's Saturday, mate. It
doesn't matter if it's Saturday. Why are
you not at work? Good for you that it's Saturday
because you ain't got a job. You're a
fat bum. Like I said, bro, if any of you
people come on camera and show your
faces, it would explain a hell of a lot.
It would explain a hell of a lot
is you're fat ugly
people. I've already played the money
game and I beat you. I made you run away
over six grand. Yeah, I've already
played it and I've already beat you.
Have you got anything new or just the same repeating?
Yeah, I played the money game, bro. And
I beat you at it. I made you run away. A
wise man learns from his mistakes. We
all saw you people when you got shown
six grand. You ran away. You ran away. A
wise man learns from his mistakes. But
yeah. Okay. I guess I can play it with
you if you want. If you really really
want, show me 12 grand and then come
back to me.
Show me £12,000 and then come back to me
and I'll happily entertain you.
come back with 12 grand
and come back to me.
But listen, brother, like, you can keep
defending women. Women don't like you.
They'll never like you. Please listen to
me. Like, I don't want you to be 80, 90
years of age, bro, lying on your
deathbed or whatever the [ __ ] condition
you've got, right? Yeah. At the end of
the day, thinking that women liked you,
you defended them, but they don't like
you. Women will never like you. you're
still a virgin defending them. Please,
bro. I want you to sit there and
actually listen. Women don't like you.
Females don't like you. They've never
been with you because they don't like
you. And no matter how many times you
defend them, it's not going to it's not
going to uh do it. Um Yeah. Yeah. If you
show me 13 grand, come back to me. You
You show me You show me 12 grand and
come back to me. You show me 12 grand
now and then come back to me. Else I'm blocking you.
Yeah, you show me that 12 grand now, not
daddy's life savings and then come back
to me. Yeah, show the money now. I'll
put the link in.
One second, bro.
You show me your 12 grand today and then
come back to me or I'm blocking you.
Yeah, there you go. Put the link up. No
one's blocked. Anyways, show me that 12
grand with the money game and then come
back to me.
Right. Come back and show me that 12 grand.
You started something. Now finish it.
You [ __ ] Come on. Let's see the 12 grand.
Show me the 12 grand. I'm not going to
ask you again or I'm going to block you.
Simple. If you're not going to come and
show me the 12 grand,
I'm blocking you.
There you go.
>> And you're bad. You know,
I don't ask multiple times. And this is
anyone who's watching this. This is what
these sad acts have been doing for the
past 8 years. Sorry, man. Just had a hiccup. DH10.
This is what these sad acts have been
doing. Like I said, Smokeoky B, you were
supposed to come on my door. If you had
come on my door, I would have slapped
the [ __ ] out of you. You were supposed
to come on my door and you didn't cuz
you knew what's good for you, bro. Like,
you come on the door, I would have
smacked your teeth down your throat. The
only one that's a bully victim is you.
You didn't show up. No one cares about
your poverty lifestyle. No one cares
about your shitty £1,700, bro. If you
had come on the door, you would have
knew what time it was. You would have
known what time it was, but you didn't.
You said that you was going to come on
my door. You edited the community post,
brother. I would have bullied you in
real life. I would have bullied you face
to face if you had come on that door
when you were supposed to. And you can
come today if you want.
You can come today if you want. I mean,
come today, come tomorrow. Like, you're
a Milton Kees little spaz. You're not
about it, bro. Yeah. You're not about
it. You're from Milton Kees. keyboard
warriors, right? This this this internet
[ __ ] has gave people like you power,
bro. You don't bully no one. If you come
on the door, I would have broke your
jaw. I would have slapped you like a
little [ __ ] and shown everyone what you
are. Like my my [ __ ] nephew, bro,
could come on YouTube and be a keyboard warrior.
You know, you're a Milton Ke waste man
that bottled it. Where does this where
does this bullying come from? You come
on the door and I'll smack your face in
and then you can try and tell me that
you bullied me. Simple. Yeah, you can
have a timeout now. Sad, pathetic low
life. Another low life with no family.
Yeah. So, Nah, no one's going to get
hurt on here, bro. No one's ever going
to get hurt. This has been going on for
years with these people, lad.
No one's going to get hot hurt by these little morons.
You know what I mean? >> Hello. Sorry. Sorry.
Boring. It's boring now, kid. You got
anything new to say? It's almost It's
almost 2026, man.
>> Sorry. Sorry.
Sorry. Uh, that's that's boring now. That's boring.
>> Yeah, you said that about 10 times now.
>> Yeah, you said it you said it 10 times. >> Sorry.
>> Yeah, bro. You said you said that about
10 times now. Anything new?
>> Yeah. Good for you, man.
>> Good for you.
>> Any anything new? Anything new? Anything >> Sorry.
>> Why do you Why do you Why do you put
your camera on? Show your face.
>> Sorry. Sorry.
>> Is it because you're ugly? Is it because >> [laughter]
>> Bro, come on. Put your camera on and
show what you look like. Show everyone
what you look like, bro. Come on.
>> You You and this Jamie Hey or a B Listen
with you ugly people. You don't even
sleep. You've been on it all night. I
You know what? I feel sorry for you
people. You know, like you have got to
be proper disabled to do what you do for
eight years. I feel sorry for you. No
family, lonely at Christmas. Like you're
not even anything to be annoyed about,
brother. You're actually like complete
bully victims. Like I actually feel bad
for you, man. I really really do. Coming
on YouTube, no friends, no girlfriend,
no I feel bad for them. I feel bad. Like
literally yesterday, bro, I wasn't even
getting annoyed at these people. I was
pissed off about something else. But you
actually have to pity these people, bro.
You you know there's 17 people watching
which is not even as many as that was on
on [ __ ] Christmas day. I feel sorry
for these people
skin at home, no girlfriend, no life,
projecting. I feel bad for them. Don't
have no money to go out and do anything.
I feel I really feel for these people.
I really really feel bad for them. I
don't know if like it's just me or you
feel bad for him. I can't lie.
Maybe that's just me, bro, but I feel
bad for these people. Yeah.
I feel bad for him, bro. These people
are really, really special needs on
here. Proper proper special needs.
Anyways, DH and I was saying that like I
see a lot of these people approach women
like so is everyone wrong then? So all
are all of these men wrong? So all of
these men that approach women and they
have to deal with the same [ __ ] Is
everyone the problem and not women then?
So obviously I get you're married and
that's fine bro. you know, you've been
married 15 that 13 years, you've known
the person 15 years, whatever. You know,
I get that. Whatever. But so all of
these guys that approach women, are they
all wrong then?
Like I'm just I'm just curious because
to me it seems like a lot of men that
are dealing with uh the same [ __ ]
Mary skin. Yeah, you ask. Stop repeating
you boring bastard.
So, like is it um
is it every is it every man and not the woman?
Now, I see a lot of these men get the
same thing. Is it you sure it's not
women, bro? It seems to me that it's
definitely definitely these women
because I'd be very very concerned, lad.
I see a lot of these people.
Uh you're not coming in. Go away. Self
projector. Um, [snorts] I see a lot of
these people approach women and they get
exactly the same thing.
But it's not women
really, bro. Come on.
It is definitely definitely definitely
definitely women. And if I thought for a
second it wasn't, bro, then I'd be out
today. Saturday. Yeah. [ __ ] hell.
>> I'll be out today, lad.
But I I know it is definitely definitely
these women which is why I gave up
and then then she's put stories up. I'm
going to spam that [ __ ] bro. What the
[ __ ] I got her [ __ ] uh Snapchat,
bro, two months ago and she never replied
and she putting stories up. Oh, she's
definitely getting spammed.
Oh, bro. She's definitely getting
spammed, man. What the [ __ ]
This was from a couple of months ago.
And now you see why I've given up the H10.
This is one of the reasons I don't [ __ ]
with it. [ __ ] with the uh what's this?
[ __ ] with the dating scene and that,
bro. You know what I mean?
That's why I don't really [ __ ] with it.
You know how it is, man.
Yeah. So I see a lot of these people um
get the same thing
which that in itself gets dismissed.
No, it's definitely definitely
definitely women, bro. Definitely women.
It 100% is women. And you'll see from
other people's experiences as well.
You'll see, bro. You'll see approaching
videos. You'll see [ __ ] streamers
approaching women and that they get the same thing.
So why do these people get the same
thing then if it's not women? Because
it's obviously the women in this country
stuck up. It's obvious, bro. What the [ __ ]
bro? It's definitely definitely women. Bro,
this is real life, bro. This isn't
Reddit. This is real life. What I say is
real life, bro. I don't I don't lie
about anything, you know.
100% it is these women, bro.
Look at that. Don't even reply and then
you're putting [ __ ] on your Snapchat.
This is why I don't bother with him, bro.
Yeah, I got this Indian number from two
months ago. DH message them. No reply.
I've just seen them put a [ __ ] story up.
I just don't like people ignoring, bro.
I don't even like them. I just don't
like people ignoring me.
>> Like I said, very toxic.
very very toxic.
[ __ ] I'm hungry, bro. Yeah,
I'll be offer anyways in the new year,
lad. I'm coming off this um community, bro.
To be fair,
Don't [snorts] know. Don't care
to be honest, bro. Don't know. Don't care.
Any more, bro?
Don't [ __ ] ignore me and put stories
up. What the [ __ ] bro? I just clock that.
You know what makes me laugh is how
people can sit there and say they're not
all the same.
When you literally
will will see women do and act the same
way to multiple different men.
How people can sit and say they're not
all the same is is is quite um
quite concerning to be fair.
How they can say they're not all the
same when they clearly are.
I think they're lying to themselves when
they're saying that they're not all the
same. They are definitely definitely all the same.
I don't know how people can say that
they're not. They generally are all the same.
lie to himself. Bro,
I think a lot of people they lie to themselves.
>> Is there any cheese? Oh, I got some
cheese. I can nibble on some cheese.
The only problem with this is I can't
really drink Coke. I'm not supposed to
be drinking Coke cuz my teeth.
My teeth is [ __ ] bro.
I need to go dentist and get another feeling.
Can't really be drinking to be fair. I
might need to get a straw. I'm just
nibbling on some cheese, but I'm not
going out. I'm too tired. Got some cheese.
That Oh, he's another sad bastard.
he's another sad bastard at Viper.
Yeah, mother bosses.
Yeah, he's a sab bastard that
another self projector. I remember a lot
of self protectors of this community
though to be fair.
>> [clears throat]
>> I need to reduce my sugar intake.
Yeah. I need to reduce my sugar intake, lad.
Hey, I had a lovely Christmas dinner, bro.
You want me to put it up? I I actually
recorded it. It was banging.
I found myself much happier quitting dating. You know,
you put all them years into trying to
meet someone, bro,
and you wake up one day and you think, "Fuck that.
[ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that.
This woman on Reddit was like, "Oh, you
should go out, maybe bars, restaurants,
events, stop documenting your bad
experiences, hit the gym again."
See, it's never women's fault. You see,
this is one of the reasons I Another
reason why I gave up is because of the
double standards as well.
No, I'm not.
I just had some cheese, bro. I'm a bit hungry, but
I can't be bothered to go out. I'm tired as [ __ ]
It's also the double standards.
You already know the answer to that.
And you know the answer.
Don't know why you're asking questions.
You know the answer to it.
But that's okay, lad. I don't judge.
You know, women are all the same. You
know, I gave up.
Yeah. I want a breakfast. But
no, thank you. I've given up, lad.
What? The one on uh Snapchat, the the
ignor. Yeah, I might do to be fair.
And this was someone from two months
ago. This was someone from ages ago,
bro. A couple of months ago when I done
that video approaching, you remember?
This isn't recent. I gave up a I gave up
ages ago, bro. But yeah. Nah, bro. I'm
not sending it. I give up.
I give up. I feel so much better when I
gave up. Kentucky. Like I said, I went
to see that horror film the other day, The Housemaid
and the maid was sexy and the sex scenes
kind of triggered me slightly. But other
than that, bro, I was I'm fine. I can
live without sex. I can live without a
woman because I know what they're like.
I know they're all the same. I know
they're no good. I don't like the double standards.
So, I'm fine. I'm completely fine by
myself, bro. Trust me.
You know, all hope is lost. I don't want
anyone, bro. I'm good. You know,
people clearly show they can't be mature
and they can't be decent. So, I'm not
wasting my time. Simple.
Why would I lose more hope when there is no hope?
Cuz all you're doing by going out is
you're losing more hope. But there is no
hope to begin with. My lounge, huh?
Oh yeah, that [ __ ] [ __ ] But yeah,
Sprouty know I gave up, bro.
I gave up.
These people been on YouTube all night.
You know these sados.
They have been on YouTube all day.
I feel bad for him, bro.
Just people that have got nothing in life. Excuse me.
See, like I said, these people don't
bother me, bro. I was pissed off
yesterday. I was pissed off at the
bookies and that cuz they weren't open.
These people don't bother me. These self
projectors don't bother me.
I don't react to these self self projectors, brother.
>> [clears throat]
>> Like they're just all self- affected
little low lives. I don't care about them. So yeah,
my sleep in uh as [ __ ]
These stupid idiots.
They're idiots on there, bro. What life
do these people actually have? Oh no.
What do you think? Kentucky fried Pete.
Yeah, that's rude ignoring someone when
you're doing a um story post. I'm just
going to send them my dick just like I
done with the finished one. I sent a lot
of them my dick, bro.
That's how I got my WhatsApp banned.
Yeah, I sent them my dick ages ago, bro. Yeah.
On Snapchat. I could do. Yeah.
or make like another Snapchat and just
like doing it. Yeah. Madness
Christmas is over. See you next year.
really skinn and oppressed. That's
that's repeating, bro.
That's self projecting and that's repeating.
Come on now, bro. It's almost 2026.
Let's think of some new comebacks.
That's boring as [ __ ]
Nothing skint about me, mate. I've got
plenty of money and I'm definitely
definitely not depressed. I'm tired, but
definitely definitely not depressed.
No, definitely nothing skin about me.
And that's projecting and that's repeating.
We don't want this on this channel, bro.
You need to think of some new comebacks.
cuz it's very boring. Same people, same comments. Yeah.
Anyways, I'm off in a bit. Anyways, Look
at that beard, brother.
Look at that [ __ ] beard.
Anything new? Uh, no, bro. Just the same
old repeating people.
Anything new with this community? Nah,
it will never it will never be new on
this community, mate. Just the same old
repeating people. You should know this by now. No, same repeaters.
I'd go for a meal today, but my tooth obviously
got a problem with that. Um,
I don't know. I don't know what I'm
doing. I'm just looking to chill, bro.
My pattern super [ __ ] up.
Think about it. What's two months of of
your life taking a break and saving?
What's two months of your life? You
know, when these people sit there and
say, "Oh, you ain't got a life." When
you're saving for a month or two months
or you're taking a break, two months of
someone's life is nothing, bro. These
people have been on here eight years
every day hating. You think two or three
months is anything? Not even a year or
your life is nothing. Say you went to
prison for a year. Yeah. And you come
out after a year. That's that's no time
at all of your life. If you think about
it, a year is nothing. Let alone [ __ ]
2 months, you know?
Yeah. But yeah, there's nothing new on
here, bro. There will never be anything
new on here.
Just the same repeating people.
So, Joseph Fra doesn't want to meet me.
troll people on his channel, bro.
Like showing fake wins and stuff. He He
really really needs to stop it, bro.
Like, cuz he needs to understand that
I'm not Monty, man, or Timmy.
That's [clears throat] what he's failing to realize.
He needs to stop putting these these
silly [ __ ] things up, man. Because you know
Yeah. There'll never be anything new there.
Yeah. They ain't got no life. I just got
my other account, Red Star, an hour ago.
These people live to do this. The madness. Yeah.
I can't believe these people live to do
this. It's madness.
Clearly ain't got no life, no money, no
nothing. They live to do this, bro. They
really live to do this from the time
they wake up to the time they go to bed.
And it's like I've said before where a
lot of these people here are disabled,
they don't understand the severity of it
because they don't understand things
like how sad this red star is.
Sad ugly bastards with nothing in life.
They don't understand the severity. So
they don't understand a lot of things on here.
Just sad losers
just [ __ ] lying around on YouTube
every day from the time they wake up to
the time they go to bed. What life could
they possibly have?
That's a good question. What life could
I'm just saying I'm I'm jealous of
Joseph Far's wins. I've got more money
than him. I don't know how many times
I've stated that I've got more money
than this guy. And because I've called
him out on his [ __ ] apparently I'm jealous.
What the actual [ __ ] You know,
you would need to be winning a lot of
money, bro. In order for me to even
entertain the idea of being jealous, you
would need to win loads and loads and
loads and loads and loads and loads of
money in order for me to to to even envy
you in the slightest. Put it that way, you know?
One air out the other lad.
>> What's the day today? 27.
Yeah, basically There.
But yeah, it is clear as day that these
people ain't got no life. Sat on the
internet hating on people they don't
know every day. But because these people
are not normal, they don't understand it.
That's why they make up an excuse
saying, "Oh, like they do it for a
reaction because they don't understand
what they're doing.
because they're slow in their head. It's
like when you tell them about women, a
lot of these people are not all there in
this community, so they don't understand it.
Cuz anyone that does understand it will
know that they're just
jealous ass people.
Jealous ass people that ain't got no life. Yeah.
So, what life do you people actually have anyways?
Coming on YouTube, stalking people that
you don't know every day. Can you
explain to me and tell me what life you have?
For the record. Oh [ __ ] What life could
you possibly have?
cuz we know that more than one of you
people come here every day recording
everything from the time you wake up to
the time you go to bed. So what life
could you possibly have?
Like I'm I'm intrigued to know. I I
actually am. What could you possibly
have in your life?
Cuz there must be something that I'm missing.
Come on here for 12 years calling people skin.
Uh hating on people that you don't know
every day. What life could you possibly
have? Cuz I'm not I'm not calling you,
bro. I'm I'm asking you.
I'm actually asking what life you could possibly have.
Year in year out, you don't get no money
for it. You don't get paid. So
very strange. Very strange.
Sat on YouTube stalking people.
Is it because they're younger than you?
Is it because they're better looking
than you? Is it because
you people uh are disabled?
What is it? Are you jealous? Or are you
in a wheelchair? Like, what is it, man?
I'm I I really want to know
without calling anyone. I'm I'm actually
really wanting to know.
If you are smart and you've got an IQ,
why do you come on the internet every
day repeating the same [ __ ]
I'm I'm willing to know.
I just want the answers to be honest.
Why you do what you do every day?
If everyone else's skin and your life is
perfect, why do you do it?
I really want to know.
Come on, man. I want to know, man. Come on.
So bad [ __ ] DC him. So yeah,
why do you do what you do every day?
block some more people. Uh,
I've just unblocked some more people so
someone can give an answer as to why um
you do what you do every day.
Cuz you don't bother no one. You just embarrass yourselves.
That's all you do.
Yeah. I've just unblocked some more people. So
it doesn't bother me. I'm asking you why
you do it.
Yeah, I'm blocked.
Like what is it? What are you trying to
get out of it? You don't bully no one.
You don't annoy anyone.
There we go. Look, Red Star. Look, he's
straight on it. I told you, bro. This is
exactly why I done this. These people
have got no life. It's been proven, bro.
You know, over the past couple of days,
right? It's proven that these people
ain't got nobody. They got no family, no
girlfriend. Look, he's straight on the
channel again. He's straight on the
channel. They got nothing. No job, no
girlfriend. I knew it. No, I told you
with these people.
They've got no one. Why don't people
listen to me when I say this stuff? It's
like this red star. Look, he's sat
online every day hating on me cuz I'm
younger and better looking. He's been
doing it for years. He's been doing it
for years. Lonely, no girlfriend,
no family, no money, no future. I told
you. He's literally sat on my live streams 24/7.
He is literally a loser. I told you. I
told you. Just like I told you about the
Christmas thing as well.
Told you about the Christmas thing as well, bro.
Sat on YouTube, no money, no life, no
girlfriend. It was always these people.
It was never any of the people that they were calling.
It was always these people with no
girlfriend, no money, no woman. It was
always these people. I told you it was
always these people. Just like when they
were saying about people's family hating
them, it was always them. Why do you
think that they don't come on camera?
Cuz they're ugly. They're fat and ugly.
Why do you think this red star talks
about my looks? Cuz I'm a million times
better looking than him. If he did not
[ __ ] assume in my pictures every day,
he'd be lost. He'd be looking at his
ugly self. Fat, ugly, no girlfriend. And
he's right what I'm saying. That's why
you can't even say anything back because
what I'm saying is the truth.
Fat, ugly looks, no girlfriend, can't
come on camera. You're all the same.
I've been seen with women. I've been
seen with money. I've been seen with
more than you will ever have. Millions
of times. Millions and millions of countless times.
You people really are pathetic. Every
day stalking people that you don't [ __ ] know.
What life do you people have?
Sad, lonely people on YouTube. What life
have you really got? And you're blocked
again. Prove my point. Under 10 seconds,
you're on my live stream. You ain't got
nothing. You ain't got no life. And
you're blocked again.
Do it. There you go. Proved again that
you ain't got a life.
You're banned, buddy. See you later.
Straight on YouTube. You're banned. Self projector.
I'm I'm nearly 30 and I've got more
money than you and I've been with more
women than you and I've got more family
than you would ever have. Mate, listen.
Think about this. No, do you know what?
Yeah, I'm not I'm not going to block
you. Actually, I'm going to unblock you.
[ __ ] this. Right. Think about you.
You're in your 40s and you've never been
with a woman. You just call someone
every day on YouTube that's younger and
better looking than you, bro. You're
past 30. You're broke. You got no hair.
You've got no girlfriend. All you're
doing on the internet every day is
stalking people because you ain't got a
life. Yeah. Actually, you're not. Yeah,
there you go, bro. Yeah, you're not
blocked. Yeah, you're sat on YouTube, no
money, no girlfriend showing £800 cuz
you are broke. You're broke ass. I've
got more money than you would ever have.
You're past 30 and you got no
girlfriend. You might want to look at
yourself before talking about other
people. I'm 28. I'm younger. I'm better
looking. I got more money. I've been
with more women than you will ever have.
You listen, I will put the link out
right now and I'll prove that you will
never show your ugly face. Baldy
bastard. I will prove to everyone again
that you are literally the baldy bastard
that won't show his face cuz he's ugly
and you know it. It's the truth. You're
a loser, bro. If anyone I know ever gets
to your age on YouTube stalking someone,
I'd slap them for being a loser. If I
ever knew someone that was a loser like
you, bro, I'd give them tough love. I'd
give them tough love. I'm not I can't
even lie. I give them tough love. I
would. Some ugly 40year-old on the
internet talking about a 28-year-old
that's better looking than you. Come on
the hangouts. Look, the hangout, bro. I
put the link right there. Yeah, you're
talking about a 28-year-old that's
better looking than you. Look closer to
home, you sad.
You absolute bully victim. Why do you
think I blocked you, bro? Cuz I love
this [ __ ] Cuz everything I say about
you people is the truth. That's why you
can't even write anything back. Because
it's the truth. You know it's the truth.
You're ugly. You're a baldy bastard.
Already bald. There's no balding cuz
you're already bored. You're in your
40s. You got no girlfriend. And you're
trying to talk about a 28-year-old
that's better looking than you, younger
than you, and got more money than you.
Please stop it, man. It's embarrassing.
[ __ ] embarrassing. Come on, bro.
Nothing I'm saying is is is not the
truth. You're not blocked.
You sad little bastard.
You and nonslegs are the [ __ ] most
ugliest people I've ever come across in
my life. And you're talking about a
28-year-old that's better looking than
you. Come on, bro. If you're if you want
to talk about someone, you should at
least come on here and show your face.
But you can't
cuz you're a baldy bastard [ __ ]
I'm not triggered, bro. I'm telling you
what you are, bro. I'm trying I'm trying
to get through to you.
You people are just fat, ugly
self-reflectors. You're wasters. That's
what you are in this community. You're
wasters. You're ugly. You've been
bullied your whole life. This is why you
come on it. Tell me I'm lying. Tell me
what I'm saying right now is is is
lying. Tell me that I'm lying. I'm not
[ __ ] lying. Everything I'm saying is
the truth about you ugly people sat on
YouTube lounging around cuz you got no
one. Think about it, bro. Shouldn't you
be out there living your life? Come on.
But no, you're sat on YouTube as usual.
Yeah. Sat on YouTube recording
everything. You stalking ugly bastard.
That's what you are, bro.
Yeah. You ain't got no money though,
Redar. You ain't got no money. You don't
even leave your house. You ain't got no
money. What are you spending? You're on
YouTube talking to me. You little loser.
You little loser. You and your
boyfriend. You're skinned than a pair of
skin flints. You and your [ __ ] gay
boyfriend are the skinniest of the all time skint
on YouTube again. Nobody, no woman. Do
not ever think that you're talking about
yourself when you're doing these videos,
mate. Bro, listen. Count out the money.
Count the money to 13 grand. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, not 13 grand. 12
grand. Yeah. Do it, bro. Count the money
that Yeah. Count it. Count the wad that
you've got. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Bro,
you're not going to upset me. I've got
more money than you'll ever have. Trust
me, you're not going to upset me, mate.
You're not going to upset me. I've got
more money than you. I've got more money
than you will ever have. You're not
going to upset me. So, yeah. Put the
Yeah, you are skinned. You are skinned.
That's why you're on YouTube right now
typing to me. You are skint
definitely. Definitely. Definitely. You
are on benefits. Keep talking about
yourself. Yep. That's you. That is you,
brother. Skin benefits. Keep talking
about yourself. Keep it coming. You know
yourself more than anyone else. Yeah.
So, anyways, count the wad, brother.
Listen, the money that you have shown
before is about £700 maximum. You've got
nothing. You are skint like your
boyfriend in the bedset. You and your
boyfriend are skint. That money that you
shown before was fucking£700.
[ __ ] wad. You [ __ ] skint [ __ ]
And then you got your boyfriend showing
daddy's life savings peanuts. Thinking
that you got money and you ain't got nothing.
I rely on the state. Bro,
listen. You're another one. Flash.
You're another self projector. Let me
get again. And I'm going to put the link
up for you. You join and I'll show you
the link set. Are you Are you talking
about the link set that my uh my mom
bought me? Something that you don't
have. You don't have a mum, do you? Flash
your bun. Your family hate you. So you
didn't have a family Christmas, did you?
Bunt with no family. You are the bunt.
Come on right now and show us your face.
You are the bunt. Ugly buna. That's why
you and Red Star can't come and show
your face cuz you're butt ugly and
you're letting me say this because you
know it's the truth. Yeah, bro. I got
bought a leg set by my mom. Something
that you don't have. You don't have
family. You ain't got no family. You
people was on YouTube Christmas. I'm not
lying. When the [ __ ] am I going to sit
here and say I didn't get a link set? I
got a link set for my mom. Something you
don't have. You and Red Star got no
presents Christmas cuz you got no family.
Cuz you and Red Star have got no family.
Your family hate you ugly people.
Bunters. Pair of bunters. Anyways, are
you going to join the hangouts? Are you
going to join the hangouts and show us
your face? Flash.
Nah, you wouldn't do that, would you?
Cuz you got something to hide. Do I need
to tell everyone? Listen. Do I need to
tell every what you people have got to hide?
Is it perhaps maybe because you're very
ugly? I don't see you people at work
today. I don't see you people with a
woman today. Come on, brother. You're
saying that you bully me. I'm on here
talking to both of you. I'm not blocking
anyone. You're both ugly. You're both
skin. You both got no family. You both
can't join the hangouts. Rob, you're
supposed to be bullying me. Come on. I'm
supposed to be being bullied
and all I'm doing is spewing facts about
you and you can't join the hangouts. So,
who's the one that's really getting
bullied? You are.
You dirty dirty muners. You're supposed
to be bullying me, bro. Come on.
Yeah, you don't have a girlfriend, Red Star.
Neither does this Flash. This is what I
mean. And that's another thing with you,
Flash. You've never even seen a woman naked.
You [ __ ] bunter. And you're trying to
talk about someone that's had more women
than you. Younger than you, better
looking than you. I know you're looking
down when I'm saying this stuff, bro.
Cuz it's the it's facts what I'm saying.
It is facts what I'm saying. Listen, can
you you can't you know, you can't you
can't prove otherwise. You know what I'm
saying? I got a link set. I got six,
seven presents. Yeah. Yeah. By my
family. Family. something that you don't
have. Just like player's number, he's
got no family. He was on YouTube
Christmas cuz he had no family. I
literally went live 5 minutes, went down
the stairs, left my phone upstairs,
walked up the stairs, and this [ __ ] with
no girlfriend and no family was on there
in seconds. Sorry about that, bro. I
just had to throw that out there. You
was on YouTube with no girlfriend and no
family talking about other people. Get
the [ __ ] out of here, bro. Jesus Christ.
Like, listen, bro. You're all unblocked
chair. You're supposed to be owning me.
You're supposed to be owning me, bro.
You're supposed to be owning me.
Do I see him owned? Do I seem angry? I
put the link up. None of you can join
because the reason I don't need to block
you people is because everything that
you do is just self-p projection. So,
when you're typing all of these things,
you're just showing yourself up. That's
all you're doing. You're talking about
yourselves. You're writing nasty
comments about yourself, putting
yourself down. You're not You're not
aiming at me, bro. You're not aiming at
me because you aim at me when you can
join the hangouts.
Yeah, you are a sad virgin. Yep. We know
you are. Like I said, if when you can
actually join the hangout, you can
actually show your face and try and tell
me what I look like. Come back to me.
You people are middle-aged, ugly,
bitter, no life. I hit the nerve more
than anyone else ever could with you
people. You're sad, you're fat, you're
stinking, you're ugly, and guess what?
Another 8 years, you doing this is not
going to change the fact that you are
what you will always be. Yeah. Another
eight years, you will still be on here.
No money, no girlfriend, still virgin,
still repeating the same [ __ ] and nothing's changed.
My life couldn't get any worse. Okay, bro. Really?
I'll put the link up. Any of you want to
join, let's have a chat. Come on.
Let's Let's have a chat. Come on.
Come on, join the hangout. Let's see how
many of you people can join and show
your face. Let's see how many of you
people can join and show your face.
Unless you got something to hide. I
don't have anything to hide. I've got
nothing to hide at all, mate. Cuz I know
that I'm better looking than all of you
people. None of you people can show your
face. Not one of you people. I'm not
hiding my face. I'm not hiding nothing,
mate. So, at the end of the day, I'm not
sc I'm not I'm not insecure with the way
that I look. Me, I've got hair. I'm not
balding. Nothing wrong with me. Got a
bit of bed there, mate. But you people,
you can't show your faces.
You literally can't show your faces.
Woody fringe. Really, mate? Really?
Well, well, here's the thing, right?
Okay, put it this way. How comes you're
sat there saying all of these things?
You're sat there saying all of these
things. Yeah, I'm the one showing my
face and none of you can. I'll put the
link up again. One second. So why is it
then I'm the only one showing my face
and none of you people can show your face?
Listen, players number, red star, all of
you people on here, come on here and
show your faces. What you got to hide,
bro? You're saying what you're saying
about me. I don't give a [ __ ] I know
I'm better looking than all of you. I'm
showing my face. I'm not triggered. I'm
not angry. I'm showing my face. Hood up,
hood down. I'm not scared to show my
face. You people won't come on here
because you people are fat and ugly.
Yeah, I can say it more than anyone. I
can say it as clear as anyone. You are
the ones that have got something to
hide. Not me, bro. That's my beard.
That's my face.
Come on. Why don't you come on here and
show your faces? Come on.
You said that you you you cry about
being blocked. You're not blocked. No
one's blocked. You're all commenting. So
why don't you come on here and show your face.
Come on, bro. I've got all day. I've got
all day. Come on. Listen, players.
Drinking. What? Hold on. Players. Wait.
You want to You're drinking today? You
want to drink today?
Yeah, I got no teeth really. Okay, bro.
Like I said, people come on here, join,
and show your faces. Come on,
let's see your face. Come on. Come on.
What you got to hide? What you got to
hide? So, it proves right that all these
years when you're trying to project your
ugliness onto me, I'm showing my face.
You fat ugly people can't show your
face. That's that's literally the thing. You people
can't show your fat, ugly, depressed
faces. Me, I can show my face. I look
like I've got Down syndrome. Do I?
Really, bro? So, why don't you come on
and show your face?
Okay. So, why don't you come in and show
your face? Cuz you're fat and ugly. My
point. Every time I'm saying this and
I'm showing my face, I'm proving it. You
people are fat and ugly. No one cares
about what you people say about other
people's looks. I'm better looking than
you. I'm not scared to show my face. I'm
not ugly like you ugly people that can't
show your face. You got to be cool to be
kind, bro. But it's the truth. You are
talking about me, but you can't even
show your faces cuz you're butt ugly.
You're butt ugly. So, no one cares about
you people on here. Yeah. When you're
supposed to be at work. You're supposed
to be at work, but you're not at work. You know,
you don't show your faces cuz you're
ugly men. what it is with you people.
Yeah, let me tell you what it is with
you people again. You're in your 40s.
You've got ugly looks. You've got no
misses. And all you're trying to do is
bring people down to your level. Ugly,
fat, no girlfriend. You know your lives
are over, bro. No, no, no. Hold it down,
bro. Yeah, you people know your lives are over.
40s, no girlfriend. Plays was on YouTube
Christmas Day. Was you not on YouTube
Christmas? Was you not on YouTube
Christmas Day? You got no girlfriend, no
family, no looks. And what you're doing
is you're trying to bring people down to
your level. But guess guess what, bro?
Yeah. No one can ever ever ever right be
like you people. Fat, baldy, ugly on
YouTube. No one can ever be as ugly as
you people. Ugly as [ __ ] That's why you
can't show your faces cuz you're ugly.
You got something to hide, bro. Why is
it that the man that you're talking
about can show his face, but none of you
can? Because you're [ __ ] ugly. Ugly
people. It's the truth. You people are
[ __ ] ugly. Ugly. You are fat and
ugly. We've never seen you with a woman.
We have never seen you people with a
woman cuz you're ugly. You're trying to
bring people down to your level,
brother. And it's never going to work.
We have seen Okay. Okay. Let me hold it
back. Okay. Okay. Well,
let's let's let's talk facts here. Yeah.
About you people. You remember when Bomb
used to come on here and talk [ __ ] He
turned out to be fat and ugly. Gray cat
fat and ugly. Fat. Fat and ugly. Do you
not think it's a bit mad? Yeah. How all
of you people that come on here, you
always be proven to be fat and ugly.
Brother, you can't own me behind the
keyboard. Yeah. You people, brother,
listen. You own yourself. Life owns you.
You don't need to own me, bro. You a
little clown like you can't own me. You
can't even show your face. How can
someone that can't even show their ugly
face own a man like me? You can't.
You're a fat little nerd. None of you
Yeah. fat nerdy low lives own no one.
And that's why I'm coming on and that's
why I'm coming on here to say. That is
why I'm coming on here to say this. You
fat skint nerds don't own no one. You've
been doing this now since 2012. Yeah.
And you've never owned no one. And you
will never own no one. No, you did not
get my subleting stopped. No, you did
not. And if that's the case, why have I
got more money than you? No, you did
not, Red Star. You got none of my
buddies stopped. You keep telling
yourself that, but I've still got more
money than you. Nope. You never got any
of my buddies stopped. You keep telling
yourself that, though. But I'll still be
h I'll still be sat here with more money
than you. You can keep pretending that
you got my money stopped, but you did
not. And I've still got more money than
you. So, you keep telling yourself that, bro.
You keep telling yourself that you got
my money stopped, but you did not get
any of my money stopped. And I'm still
sat with more money than you. Why am I
sat with more money than you? If you got
my income stopped, bro, how have I got
more money than you? You need to make
the [ __ ] make sense. Like seriously,
bro. You did not get any of my money
stopped if you got if you got my
subleting stopped. Okay. Okay. How did I
have that house for 4 years? Make it
make sense. Listen, I already told the
story multiple times and you made up a
story. Yeah, you sound triggered. That's
all you do, bro. You're repeaters.
You're boring repeaters.
You're boring disabled repeating people.
Come up with something different. It's
boring and repeating now, bro. Of course
it's got to be, bro. It's the same
older. Of course it's the same old.
They're [ __ ] disabled. They're
[ __ ] bongos. What? What? What else do
you think, bro?
But guess what, Red Star?
I'm younger than you and I'm better
looking than you and you can't show your
face. Am I lying? I know. I'm a bit
cheeky, mate. Is it? Yeah, you have got
no girlfriend. Yep. You are small and
angry with no girlfriend. Yep. Talking about yourself,
chatting about yourself again doesn't
get you anywhere in life, bro. Listen,
all you little nerds, yeah, I put the
link out for you. Not one of you can
join and show your face because you're
all fat and ugly. You're all ugly people
with no life. It's the truth. You can
keep writing stuff. I'm close to tears.
Am I really? Players. Players, you was
on YouTube Christmas Day. You was the
first person on YouTube Christmas Day,
bro. You was on YouTube on Christmas.
Let that sink in. Brother, do you want
me to explain exactly what I done again?
Yeah. I clicked the live stream. I went
downstairs. I made a cup of tea. I
didn't even look at my life. Went back
up and you was typing self projecting
the fact that you ain't got a girlfriend
on Christmas Day. Let that sink in.
There's evidence of this, bro.
Literally, I went to my sisters at 10:00
in the morning, brother. 10:00 in the
morning. And I went to my sisters and I
went live at 9:00 for 5 minutes.
Brother, sort yourself out. You was on
YouTube Christmas Day. Stop trying to
self- project, Lona. Like, listen, bro.
You're not blocked. None of you are
blocked. And I'm owning all of you.
They're all self-p projectors, Samuel.
They're all self-reflectors.
They're all There will always be
self-reflectors, man. That's what it is.
It's it's just what it's just it's just
one of them things, brother. When you're
younger and better looking than these
people, they don't like you. I don't
need to block any of these people,
brother. I don't need to block any of
these people at all. Cuz I know when
you're younger and better looking than
them, that's why they go for you. None
of these people will come in the
hangouts. None of these people will show
their face. None of these people at work.
None of these people are blocked and
they're not they're not affecting me.
All they're doing is talking about
themselves. I'm not triggered. No one's
woke up. No one's nothing, brother. You
know what I mean?
Because I know these people better than
they know their [ __ ] selves.
I'm the only one that's been seen with
money. I'm the one that's been seen with
women, girls. None of these people have
anything. Been on here since 2012
talking a load of [ __ ] They've been
talking a load of [ __ ] for 2012. Since
all sat on here alone.
Nobody, no job. Which makes me laugh cuz
they all the first thing they say is
tell, "Listen, you had sex four times,
brother. Your hand don't count.
Your hand doesn't count as a girlfriend,
bro. I know you like to draw a woman on
your hand, but sorry. Uh, your hand
doesn't count as a girlfriend. Sorry, brother.
You people do not work on here. You're
sat on YouTube. You should be at [ __ ] work.
You should be at Why are none of you
people at work? Nope. It sounds like
you. It sounds like Well, I'm If I'm
projecting, come on here and show your
face then. Okay, brother. If I'm If I'm
projecting, come on here and prove me
wrong. It's simple.
You know, you live to hate on someone
younger and better looking than you. You
not realize how pathetic you are. Like
I'm actually trying to like get through
to you. Like you're hating on someone
who's younger and better looking than
you. Look at your life. You don't know
me. You've never met me. Yeah. You of
course you're not going to show your
face cuz you're [ __ ] ugly.
Just like Red Star. Ugly. You ugly
people have been doing this for many,
many, many years. You ugly people have
sat on here for years doing this. You
ain't got no money. You ain't You ain't
gained anything out of it. Think about
it. Look, look in the mirror right now,
bro. Yeah, you've been doing this since
2012, brother. These people have been
doing this since go in the bathroom
right now and slap yourself across the
head. The fact that you've been doing
this for many, many years, you ain't got
no money. You ain't got no girlfriend
out of it. You're still life's losers
and you ain't achieved nothing. And you
know I'm I'm right. That's why like you
know what I'm saying is the truth. You
ain't got no money for doing this. You
haven't got anything. All you've done is
put yourselves down. Calling yourself a
m calling yourself skin. Putting Bro,
you fat ugly people could never troll a
guy like me, mate. Mate, listen. I' I've
let every single person on here. Yeah,
he's getting under my skin, bro. None of
you are blocked,
brother. None of you are blocked because
you're so disabled. All you do is repeat
the same [ __ ] You're just a bunch of
bully victims that repeat the same [ __ ]
You're not blocked. No one's blocked
because you're just a bunch of bully
victims. That That's what I'm saying,
bro. No girlfriend, no life, sat on
YouTube. You're not blocked because
you're just a bunch of bully victims.
You don't wind anyone up.
You're literally You don't bother no
one. You don't trigger no one. You're
Everyone is unblocked. Everyone is
And you're still not owning me. You're
just a bunch of repeaters. You can't
show your faces cuz you're butt ugly.
You ain't got paid since [ __ ] doing
this since 2012. You're just life's losers.
All you are is just life jealous losers
sat at home boring skint no money. And
the more you type, the more Bro, I'm I'm
angry. I'm not the one writing in capital letters.
Yeah, you'll be coming to see me,
brother. How are you going to come to
see me? You can't even leave your house.
You you can't even leave your bedsit.
How How are you going to come and see me?
Listen players, you don't have a
girlfriend. You're in your 40s and you
don't have a woman. I was saying this to
you earlier, bro, like when you was
talking to Timmy. Brother, you don't
have a girlfriend.
You've never been with a woman. Again,
the mirror. It's a good investment,
brother. You need to. You and Red Star
have never had a girlfriend. You've
never been with a woman. You're both virgins.
You're both absolute virgins. You've
never been with a woman. You was lonely
Christmas day. Okay. Okay. Okay. So,
you're saying Okay. Right. Okay. Let's
go by your logic. I'm angry. I'm not
angry. I'm completely calm. You're all
unblocked. I'm completely calm. Okay.
So, if I've got no if I've got if I've
got no um women, why was you on YouTube
Christmas? Okay. Okay. Okay. So,
players, let me scroll up again. So, if
I've got no women, I've got no
girlfriend. Okay. So, why was you on
YouTube Christmas Day?
It's a It's a simple question. So, why
was you on YouTube Christmas Day? Come on.
Come on. Yeah. You people don't bully no
one. Listen, we've all seen you people
when the cameras are on. You are the
munters. You are the ugly munters. And
that's why I'm not blocking any of you
people. Yeah, I'm not blocking any of
you little virgin projectors cuz you're
just putting yourselves down. So, I'm
not blocking any of you cuz all you're
doing is putting yourselves down behind
a keyboard. So, anyways, players, why
was you on YouTube Christmas Day?
You didn't answer my question.
I haven't blocked you. I've asked you a
question. Why was you on YouTube? Do you
think it's maybe because you ain't got
no girlfriend and you ain't got no family?
Do you think maybe it's yourself you're
talking about? Just like Red Star. No
girlfriend, no family. I know. 14 years
of you bullying yourself. I know. You
bullying yourself and you're still doing
it. I know, brother. You clown. Still no
girlfriend, still no money, still
bullying yourselves. I know. I would
have thought you people would have got bored.
same repeating low lives that don't
leave the house. I know 14 years. But
again, these people, a normal person
would have got bored. Normal people
would get bored. But obviously because
these people have got disabilities
and they're disabled, they don't get
bored of bullying themselves. You would
have thought though, you generally would
have thought that these people would
have stopped being triggered, stop
bullying themselves. But because they
ain't got an IQ,
you know, they will continuously just
keep bullying themselves every day. They
don't bully me. I've unblocked everyone.
I'm loving this because they don't affect me.
These ugly people don't bully no one.
They don't bother no one. Only they
think that they do because that's their
disabilities. You understand,
bro? You don't troll anyone. Players,
you was on YouTube Christmas Day. You're
not You can't troll. You're fat, ugly
people. You don't troll no one. None of
you fat, ugly people have got an IQ to
troll. All you do is self project and
repeat the same [ __ ] You was on YouTube
Christmas Day because you're a loner.
You can't troll no one, bro. You
literally was on YouTube on Christmas,
you [ __ ] loner. Lonely on Christmas
YouTube. 5 minutes I was live. Five
[ __ ] minutes. And this loser was on
YouTube. Come on now, bro.
You ugly people could troll to troll
yourself out of a wet paper bag. Bro,
none of you will meet anyone. You're
just fat, ugly, old people. And I can
hit the nerve more than anybody ever can
and everyone ever will. Repeating. Look
how triggered Redstone is. Repeating,
repeating cuz he knows I'm right. I can
hit that nerve more than anyone else.
Fat, old, ugly, skint, boring people. I
can keep hitting the nerve, bro. The
only ones that seem triggered is yourselves.
Bunter. A bun that's better looking than
you. That's had women. Please, brother.
Please. Please. Please. Like, I'm a m
when I've had more women than you. When
you was on YouTube Christmas. Make it
make sense, bro. You was on YouTube
Christmas players. You had no family.
You had no girlfriend. No Christmas
dinner. I'm hitting the nerve, bro. I'm
hitting the nerve.
It proves what these people are. Look,
I'm not blocking them. I'm not blocking
them, bro. I'm not blocking these
people. I'm not blocking these people
cuz it's showing what they are. Jobless,
no girlfriends. I'm letting them carry
on, bro. I'm letting them carry on. They
can keep Yeah, you are the bunt player.
No, no, no, no. Bunt, you are the bunt.
You was on YouTube Christmas.
You was on YouTube Christmas, Mr.
lonely. One second. Let me put your
thing up, bro. Do you want me to put the
video back up when you was on YouTube Christmas?
There we go, bro. Do you want me to put
the video back when you was on YouTube Christmas?
YouTube no family. And then Monty Man
copied my idea. Do you want me to put
the video back up? Do you want me to put
Do you want me to put the video back up
when you was on YouTube Christmas? Woo!
You was on YouTube Christmas Day because
you got no girlfriend and no family.
£1,100 a month. I don't know what you're
talking about, bro. £1,100 a month. What
are you on about,
mate? Redstar, you can keep pretending
that you got my sublet money stopped.
You're not going to get a reaction
because you're talking [ __ ] You did not
get any of my money stopped.
You did not get any of my money stopped.
I've got more money than you. I got more
money than all of you. Why do you think,
bro? Why do you think I'm not getting
I'm not getting mad? Because I'm sat
here with more money than you. So,
whatever you're saying, bro, it doesn't
make any sense.
I have got more money than you. I've
said this to you multiple times. I've
got more money than Lord Jay. I've never
had to beg for money. I've never had to
beg for money cuz I'm skint like Lord
Jay. Never had to beg. Be a beggar. I've
never had to pretend that I've got properties.
I never had to pretend that I've got
properties cuz I'm [ __ ] skint begging
for money. Is that right, LJ? Begging
for money cuz you ain't got £50 to your
name. Oh, what was that the other day?
You lost £40
on on a FBI. You [ __ ] bun. Begging
for money. Oh, I've got five properties.
Let's let's let's go by your logic.
Actually, let me just let me just focus
on this gun. You got five properties,
brother. You've got five properties.
What in Belfast? Make it make sense.
Four eyes. You got five properties.
Yeah. Five properties.
Really, bro? Make it make sense. You
don't own no property. One second, LJ.
One second, LJ. Yeah. One second. Just
me and you. Yeah. No one else. No one
else. Yeah. So, you got five properties
really in Belfast. When What does it How
much does it cost? About £1, LJ? You
ain't got no money. You're skint. Stop
the lies. You was crying over £40 on a
[ __ ] property. You do not have no
money. I don't know why you come on
here. Oh, I own property. I own
property. You're [ __ ] skint. Today
that I've got a beg for money on
YouTube. Happened to beg money on
YouTube cuz I'm that skint. Brother, you
ain't got no money. Yeah. How did you,
brother? Lj, you don't win. You don't
win. I spoke about your kids and I got
away with it. I spoke about your kids
and and I got away with it. But in
London, that would never happen, bro. To
be honest, we win. I spoke about your
kids and you done nothing about it.
Don't run away from me and LT. Get out
of here, please. I'm I spoke about your
kids, your children, your little ones,
and you done nothing. I spoke about your
little ones, and you've done nothing.
You fat Irish skin [ __ ]
I spoke about your kids. What did I say
that I was going to do to your kids?
What did I say that I was going to do to your kids?
I'm not going to say it. RJ, what did I
say that I was going to do to your kids?
Yeah, exactly. So, shut up, kid. What
did I say I was going to do to your kids
and you done absolutely nothing about it
when you're two me? Shut up now.
Shut up now, bro. Bro, please stop it. Stop it.
What did I say
that I was going to do to your kids?
Another man's kids. And what did you do?
You done nothing but stood behind the
game. Stop it. You're not about that
life. Stop it. Stop it. And what did LT
talk about? What did LT do? Yeah.
Listen, listen, listen. RJ, you had
several chances to kick the door in my
face. I was in front of my mom. I'm the
man that spoke about your kids. None of
your follow none of your followers. None
rattled. You people that listen, you are
the one that's typing. You're the people
that are triggered, not me. You're the
people that are triggered typing away.
Not me, mate. I'm laughing at you all.
I'm laughing at you.
I'm laughing at you, bro. You're the
ones that are triggered on YouTube and
you should be at work. So, all I'm doing
is exposing you people. I'm exposing you
jobless skid people. I'm not triggered,
bro. That's why no one's blocked.
I'm exposing the skint lot on YouTube.
Ain't got no life. I'm exposing you all
when you should be at work. You should
be out living life, but you're on
YouTube. I'm exposing you all, bro.
I'm exposing you people. You ain't got
no life. I'm exposing you skinned
people. You're not bothering me. I'm not blocking anyone.
I'm not blocking anyone at all.
No one's getting blocked for me, bro. No
one's getting blocked because you people
don't bother no one. Your ugly
self-reflectors. This is what I'm
saying. Your ugly self-reflectors. I
remade unbothered. That's why you're not
blocked. That's why you're not blocked.
See, like you, L. You've got to ban me.
You've got to ban me. Why don't you join
the hangouts? Come on. Why don't you
join the hangouts? Come on.
I'll put the link up, man. See, I don't
need to ban you. I don't need to ban you, bro.
Because I'm not a bully victim like you
and your followers.
Player's number was on YouTube Christmas
people. He was on YouTube lonely
Christmas. And I've got a video by the
way. Do you want me to put the video
back up? Listen. Players number. Do you
want me to put the video back up when
you was when you was on YouTube Christmas?
No girlfriend. Do you want me to put the
video back up? Do you want me to put the
video back up when you was on YouTube?
Your little low life. No family. No
girlfriend. What was the first thing
that you said to me? What was the first
thing that you said to me, bro? Come on.
Come on, bro. Come on. Come on. What was
the first thing you had to say? You was
on YouTube Christmas, no family, no
girlfriend. Uh, Red Star, you never
stopped any of my money. That's why I'm
not That's why I'm ignoring you. You
never stopped any of my income. But
guess what I done? Guess what I done,
brother? Listen. Listen. If you stocked
my money, okay, let's talk facts, right?
Let's talk facts.
Why did I have that house for four
years? If you got my money stopped, you
never got my money stopped. But guess
what I done? I stopped your boyfriend
from going to events. I stopped your
boyfriend from going to events. I had
your boyfriend run into the police over
me. You didn't stop any of my money. Why
do you think I didn't get anyone back?
You didn't stop any of my money. I had
that house for years. You never stopped
any of my money. But I stopped your
boyfriend from going to events because
of me and the posters. I stopped your
boyfriend going to the events that he
loves with the posters. You never
stopped any of my money. You I had your
boyfriend run into the police over me
stopping going to events would leave his
house. You never stopped my money, bro.
You definitely definitely did not stop
my money. Definitely definitely
definitely definitely not. Definitely
definitely definitely definitely
definitely not. You didn't get any of my
money stopped. I had your boyfriend
running to the police stopping going to
events. You must, you literally must
have us, you must have us confused. I
had your boyfriend not leaving the house
because of posters. Because of me. You
never got my money stopped. I had your
boyfriend scared running to the police.
He was running to the police station.
Not me, brother. You never got any of my
money stopped. I've still got more money than you.
I've got more money than you. And I get
more money than you. More than you will
ever have. All you done was ear dropped
the story and tried to turn it into
yourself. You have never got any of my
buddy stopped. And I can swear on my
dead dad that I can swear on my dead I
can swear on anyone. I can swear on my
mom. I had your boyfriend run into the
police over me and you can't even I had
your boyfriend [ __ ] scared crying and I
ran him off of YouTube for two weeks.
Think about it, bro. Your boyfriend
stopped going to you on YouTube for two
weeks because of me. Because I'm the man
that done it. I'm the man that stopped
your boyfriend going to the events that
he loved. I stopped it. I put a stop to
it. Red Star, I stopped your boyfriend
going to events. I'm the man that done
it. The man with a beard. You never
stopped any of my money. I've got more
money than you. I've got thousands. You
don't know how much money I have. You
never got any money stopped that I've
got. I had your boyfriend stop going to
events because of me. Because of this
mug. Not cuz of me, bro. I I went on a
sale. That was what Bro, listen. I don't
care about going going in a police cell.
I never stopped going to my event.
Something that I loved. I know he never
got my money stopped, LJ. No, he did
not. And I've got more money than all of
you. So, try again. Nope. You never got
any of my money stopped. None of my
money stopped. You can keep telling
yourself that. No, you did not. Cuz if
you got any of my money stopped, why was
I why did I have that house for four years?
You never got any of my income stopped.
Nope. I stopped your boyfriend going to
events. You never got any of my income
stopped. I've still got more money than
all of you. I'm not the one claiming
that I've got five properties and
begging for £50 like L J. Oh, trust me.
You never got any of my money stopped.
Oh, trust me, you never got any of my
money stopped. Oh, you never got any of
my money stopped. Trust me, I've got
thousands. I've got more than you will
ever have. Oh, you never got any of my money stopped.
Oh, Redstone, you never got any of my
money stopped. I promise you that. The
landlord was trying to get the money
back for years,
right? You never got anyone's money
stopped. You never got anyone's money
stopped. I've still got more money than
you. I've got thousands more than you.
And the only reason I don't play the
money game anymore is because every time
I play the money game, you run away.
I've got more money than you will ever
have. I make money. I've got more money
than you. You did not affect my
lifestyle. You never got any of my money
stopped. Never got any of my money
stopped. No, you did not. No, you did
not. You never got any of my money
stopped. You never got a penny of my
money stopped. Nope. Nope. You never got
any of my money stopped cuz I'm sat here
with more money than you. So that does
not make any sense. Nope. Nope. You
never ever got any of my money stopped
because if I got if you got any of my
money stopped, I would have been beating
someone. I would have been beating
someone. Trust me, if you got any of my
money stopped, somebody on here would
have been getting beat up. You wrote to
yourself and you made up a story.
Listen, listen, listen. You made up a
story because I told everyone what
happened. I've got more money than you.
So, it does not make any sense how you
have got my money stopped when I' when
I'm sat here with more money than you.
It doesn't make any sense, Redstone,
you're on benefits. You're on £300 a
month. I stopped your boyfriend going to events.
I stopped him going to events cuz of me.
He ran off of YouTube for two weeks. He
ran away cuz of me. You never got any of
my money stopped. No, you did not. You
didn't get a penny of my money. Stopped.
Not one penny of it. You tried though.
It was a good try. But guess what? I'll
always have more money than you. I'll
always be better looking than you and
your ugly boyfriend who I stopped going
to events for 2 weeks. I love it. You
have all of the conversations, brother.
You didn't get anyone's money stopped.
You literally did not get anyone's money
stopped. Why do you think I'm so calm?
Because it's [ __ ]
You didn't get any of my income stopped.
Why do you think I'm so Okay. Okay, let
me Right. Let me let me explain the
story again. All right, Steven Howard,
are you listening? Let me explain the
story one more time because um this
guy's going to keep making up story how
he's got buddy people's money stopped.
He didn't get anyone's money stopped.
I'll explain the story again. L doesn't
even have any money. He's skinn he's
begging for donations. Begging for
donations cuz he skinted. I'll explain
it to you again, bro. Any genuine person
that wants to listen to this, I'll
explain it all over again. Yeah. Simple.
This red store never got a penny of my
buddy stopped. Not a single penny. If
anyone on here ever got my money
stopped, I would have done what I done
to Noddle Legs. You literally didn't get
anyone's money stopped. That landlord
was trying to get the was trying to get
the house back for years. Brother, you
people don't bully no one. Listen,
Flash, listen. You people don't bully no
one. You're fat, ugly losers. You're
ugly people that Why do you think I'm
not banning any of you people? You bully
victims. Bully yourselves. That's why
I've unblocked you, bro. I've unblocked
all of you people cuz you ugly people
are the bully victims.
Uh no, Red Star, you didn't get any of
my money stopped. You wrote to yourself.
Listen, you wrote to yourself. You
didn't get anyone's money stopped. If
you would have got my money stopped, it
would have took four years. It wouldn't
have took four years. Make it make sense.
You got none of my money stopped. I've
got more money than you. You've never
got any of my money stopped. I had your
boyfriend stopping going to events for
[ __ ] a month. Your boyfriend stopped
going to the to events because of me,
brother. I got your boyfriend running to
the police because of me. Yeah, Lord.
You are lonely. You and your ugly
[ __ ] kids. Yeah. Your [ __ ]
disabled kids. Yeah. Simple, bro.
Listen. Listen. Listen, Smokey. Weren't
you supposed to come on my door two
weeks ago, brother?
Weren't you supposed to come on my door
two weeks ago? You [ __ ] Milton
Keane's little bully victim. You skinned
bastard. When you supposed to come my
door two weeks ago, brother. Oh, I'm
going to come on my door. I'm going to
come on my door. You [ __ ] Milton Kees
bully victim. I slagged off your misses.
I slagged off you. You didn't even COME
ON MY DOOR. You [ __ ] Milton Keane
skin [ __ ] Shove him, 1700 like he's got money,
bro. I was hoping brother do you know
what I was actually hoping you did come
on the door you know but then again
you're from Milton Kees you're a soft
boy you're a little soft farmer boy I'm
saying all of this stuff to you and you
aren't you weren't going to come on my
door you're not going to come on my door
you soft Milton Kees little wanker bully
victim Milton Ke [ __ ] ugly little
wanker he had to go back on his post and
edit it you know what I mean you didn't
get anything taken I've got more money
than you I've got more money than you
and your boyfriend. So, how how does
that make sense, brother? How you've got
it taken when I've got more money than
you and your boyfriend? That doesn't
make any sense. Why have I got more
money than you and your gay boyfriend?
You stopped going to events because of
me. I had him stopping going to events.
I've got more money than both of you.
So, how can you say about how you've had
this took and that took? I've got more
money than both of you combined. And L.
So, how does it make sense?
You know what I mean, brother?
And do you know what I done? Yeah, they
were all on here Christmas. They were
all on here Christmas. Yeah, that's you,
LJ. No women, no just ugly kids. All
you've got, LJ, is ugly kids. All you've
got is a bunch of special needs kids.
And you're not going to come on my door
and I'll give you the money and you're
not going to come on my door, bro.
Listen, listen, LJ. All you've got is a
bunch of ugly kids. I'm spoke about your
kids, but you're not ever going to do
nothing. Yeah. And you know what? I've
took from you, Red Door, your life. I've
took your life. You're on here every day
obsessed with me. You're obsessed with
me, brother. I was going to do something
about it, Smokeoky, but you're too
scared to leave the house. So,
obviously, Bro, you think I always think
I'm right, bro? No. Do I always think
I'm right? I don't always think I'm
right, brother. I'm agreeing with you. I
did. I will do. absolutely nothing
because you people are scared to leave
your house. So of course I'm going to do
nothing cuz you're scared to leave your
house. So how can anyone do anything,
brother? Yeah, that's that's that.
Listen, Lord J, you don't even get 1k a
month. You're dressing in true religion.
You got nothing but a couple of ugly
kids. That's all you've got, brother.
All you've got is a couple of ugly kids.
You don't even have a grand to your
name, let alone a grand a month. 1K a
month, brother. You don't even have
£1,000. You're skint. Who the [ __ ] puts
£40 in a in a FBOT, brother. You don't
even have £1,000 to your name.
All you got is a couple of ugly kids and
begging for money. And I'm talking about
your kids. Listen, Lord J. I'm talking
about your kids. Your kids, they're
[ __ ] ugly. You're not going to come
on my door like you did, Timmy. Your
kids are [ __ ] ugly. And what did they
say? You should never talk about a man's
kids. Well, I've just spoke about your
kids and you're not going to come for
me. Yeah. Simple as that. I'm talking
about your kids. I'm talking about your ugly kids,
you know? I'm talking about your stinking kids.
Your [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] ugly m kids.
I've just spoke about a man's kids and
he ain't going to do nothing. I've just
spoke about a man's kids. What the [ __ ]
brother? I've just spoke about a man's
kids. That's something that you should never do,
LJ. Yeah, LJ, why are you talking about
£1,000? You ain't even got £1,000.
You ain't even got £1,000. You're in red
store or skin, bro. You're on that £300
a month [ __ ] That's why you you got all
this spare time on YouTube cuz you're
skinn. You got nothing going for
yourselves. Why do you think you got all
this spare time on YouTube, brother?
You've got all this spare time on
YouTube because you're [ __ ] skinned.
Red Star's on £300 a month like his
boyfriend. They're both skint.
You know what I mean?
I just spoke about your ugly kids. I
would love Hey, listen. Do you have any
plans of coming to London, bro?
You should come to London, bro. I'll
tell you about your kids to your [ __ ]
face. You come on my door and you done
nothing. You literally done nothing.
Yeah. None of you people stop my money.
None of you people stop my money and
I've got more money than you. I know
it's next level bullying. Do you know
what's Do you know what's even worse
bullying? That I'm on here and I'm
wasting your lives. You're typing about
me. You've been typing to me for the
past 2 hours. You got nobody. You ain't
got paid for it. I'm living in your
head. I'm living in your head. You ain't
got nobody. I'm wasting your life. I got
more money than you. So I'm the I'm the
winner, brother. Listen, Spokey B. You
were supposed to cover my door. Why
didn't you come, you little [ __ ] You
skinned little milky teens [ __ ] I
slagged off your ugly bes as well. I
told you that your wife is [ __ ] ugly
and you've done nothing. And you let me
bully you and your wife and you done
nothing. I spoke about you, your ugly
wife. She's a scat. Yeah.
Yeah. She probably touches up kids and
you'll do nothing. I don't need to worry
about you, bro. I don't need to worry
about you, man. Cuz I can speak about
your wife. I can speak about kids and
you will do nothing because you're for
Milton kids cuz you're from Milton kids.
So you're not to be worried about. I
slagged off your wife. I slagged off
your fat hands, your ugly life and you
done nothing to me. I'm safe. I'm safe.
Safe as hell.
You listen, Lord J. You're the one
that's begging money on YouTube every
day. You're the one that's begging.
You're the one begging for donations.
You don't even have £1,000. You're
skint. You don't even have a,000 pounds.
Oh, I've got property. I've got
property. O Steven Owen, have you heard
this guy saying about saying saying
about how he has property, bro? He
doesn't have no property. Property in
Belfast is not worth anything. The guy's
got no money. He's broke as a joke. You
think anyone that's got money Yeah. sits
on the internet begging for money? Bro,
this guy is broke as a joke. He is broke
as a joke. Do you think anyone that's
got money sits and shops at Iceland begs
for money? Bro, the guy is skint is his
middle name. WHY DO YOU THINK EVERY TIME
you go on lavies, bro, you see the word
skin? Because he's skin is [ __ ] going
ice. AND THAT'S ANOTHER THING. WHY ARE
YOU WHY ARE YOU buying ready meals at Iceland?
You [ __ ] skint bastard. You ain't
even got a grand to your name. You ain't
even got 100 quid to your name, you
[ __ ] skid flint.
These people on here have got nothing.
They proved it. Christmas. Oen. Yeah. I
haven't caught you since I last. Bro, I
went live on Christmas for 5 minutes. I
went down the stairs. I walked up and it
was the same people. Same people
watching me, bro. Same people watching
me. Because these skinn people ain't got
no life. I'm right about him, bro.
I'm right about them. These people have
got no life.
I'm younger than them. I'm better
looking than them. These people are old,
ugly people. They've got no family. Just
remember that, bro. Just remember that.
They're ugly. They got no family. They
were on YouTube Christmas.
It's the truth, man. Yeah. You missed it
cuz you weren't on here, but Yeah.
Yeah. You don't bully. Listen, why do
you bully me, Red Star? Why do you bully
me? You didn't stop me going to my
events for one month like I did your boyfriend.
If you bully me, why did I stop your
boyfriend going to events for one month?
Why was I the cause of that? I stopped
your mate going to events cuz of me.
Sitting sitting in the cell was worth
it. Sitting on the set in the cell was
worth it. It was worth it, bro. To have
your mate stop going to events for one
month. It was worth it. And I didn't
even go in the police cell. Uh, no you
didn't. No, you did not stop my money.
No, you did not stop any of my money.
No, you did not. You did not stop any of
my cash. I've still got plenty of cash.
More than you. More sublet money than
you. I've got savings. No, you did not.
That was the landlord that done that.
You did not stop any of my money. Not a
penny of it. I've got savings. I've got
thousands. More than you. No, you do
not. You did not get any of my money
stopped. You did not get any of my cash.
I've got more cash than you and I've
shown more cash than you. No, you did
not. You did not get any of my money
stopped. I was let in that place for 4
years and I've got more money than you.
And I've got more money than you. You
did not get any of my money stopped. No,
you did not. No, you did not.
You did not get a penny off my cash
stock. I've still got more money than
you. More money than you will ever have.
No, you did not. No, you did not get any
of my money stopped. Listen, Steven
Alvadette, this guy did not get any of
my money stopped. He literally did not
get a penny stopped to my buddy. Right.
If you add me on Snapchat or Instagram,
I'll show you all the money I've got. I
will show you all the money I've got,
bro. I don't mind.
If you are if you are better looking,
tell us all. Brother, you people don't
have a girlfriend. You people have never
had a girlfriend. I've had more women
than all of you. Listen, ask yourself
why you don't have a girlfriend. Ask
yourself why you're the one on YouTube
every day self-projected. Yeah.
Why are you Why do you not have a
girlfriend? Tell us why you people was
on YouTube Christmas. Why was you people
on YouTube Christmas? If you've got a
family and you've got a girlfriend. So
shut the [ __ ] up you self-reflecting
gun. Yeah. So shut the [ __ ] up you selfreflecting.
No family, no girlfriend. Don't even
dare try to ask me questions.
I can't believe that though, Red Star. I
stopped your friend going to events.
I stopped him going to events for a
month. He stopped going cuz of me. I
didn't even get put in a piece.
Actually, I didn't even get put in a
piece, brother. Uh, no. Red Star didn't
stop any of my money. No, he did not.
And that's why I'm extremely calm
because you never got any of my money
stopped. You got my money stopped. No,
you did not. I've still got more money
than all of you. That's why you're not
That's why you're not getting a
reaction. Because I've got more money
than all of you.
I've got more money than all of you.
That's why it doesn't bother me,
brother. Cuz it's just self projection.
They got not one penny of my money
stopped. They got not one penny of my
money stopped. So, I'm going to let them
keep talking, bro. Listen, listen.
Steven Albert, why do you think I'm not
blocking them, bro? Why do you think I'm
not blocking them, brother? You don't
have any mates. You don't have a
girlfriend. Stop self-reflecting.
You know what I mean? Yeah. Why do you
think I'm not blocking any of these
people? Cuz I've got nothing to hide.
I I stopped this Red Star's friend going
to events for a month. Yeah, he didn't
stop any of my money. You can keep
telling yourself that, buddy. He didn't
stop it. He did stop a penny of my
money. So, you must be talking about
someone else. Yeah, you're a legend. You
didn't get any of my money stopped. It
must be a different PJ cuz it definitely
definitely ain't me because in that
case, why am I sat there with more money
than you? That doesn't make any sense.
I've got more money. Listen, Stephen
Hour, the only reason I'm not playing
the money game with these people is
because every single time you show these
people money, they run away, brother.
They run away. I could go right now and
take out money in 50s on my bank. The
thing is with these people, Yeah. is
that they're ugly people that ain't got
nobody. They just want to keep self-reflecting.
Yeah. They just want to keep
self-reflecting their skintess every
day. And no matter what money you show
them, they're going to do the same
thing, brother. They're going to do
exactly the same thing. Yeah. Simple.
That's what they do, bro. Like, they'll
ask you the same thing like two days later.
They did not stop any of my buddy. They
did stop a penny of my buddy. I've got
more buddy than them. Like all of these
people that are typing right now, bro,
they're fat and ugly. They got no g
girlfriend. They got no family. So I'm
letting them type all they want, bro.
It's not It's not a problem. You got L J
on £300 a month pretending that he owns
property, talking about a grand, £1,000
that he don't even have that will never
that he will never have. Coming on here
talking about property when he's
skinned. Think of it, right? You think
someone that's got all of this money on
their life would sit on here every day
sleeping outward? No, they wouldn't,
bro. No, they wouldn't. No, they
Do you really think these people would
be doing that? So, anyways, Lee, why
don't you have a girlfriend? Same
question to you people, huh?
Why don't you have a girlfriend, Mr.
Projector? And if you if you see these
people streaming around, it's the same
three people doing this.
It's the same three low lives that have
been doing this for eight years. It's
the same people. The same lonely people,
disabled lonely people. That's why it
doesn't bother me. It's the same lonely
people that's been doing this for 8
years. It is for real, brother. Someone
these accounts mo. It's the same, bro.
It's the same person. It's like It's
like three, four person people maximum, brother.
It's the same skinned people that ain't
got no life.
Yeah, that's good, man. Like I said, you
never stopped any of my money. So, I'm
I'm I'm good, bro. You never ever ever
stopped any of my money. You definitely
definitely didn't stop any of my money.
You definitely definitely didn't stop
none of my money. So, I'm very very very
very very What happened, Stephen? I
I'll explain this house thing to you
just so this little [ __ ] doesn't try
making up stuff. The landlord was trying
to get the money back was trying to get
the house. Basically, my mom moved.
Basically, my mom moved um years ago and
I was living in that house for a year.
Yeah. I subleted the house. They were
trying to get the money back. They were
trying to get the house back for years
and years and years. They kept coming on
the door before anyone knew about it on
YouTube. These people didn't get any of
my money stopped. And then eventually
the landlord took it to court. It had
nothing to do with Red Star. Nothing at
all. He made up a story when I told
everybody what happened. Yeah. He made
up a story. He literally made up a
story. Yeah, he made it up a story. The
the landlord was trying to get that
house back. Okay. Okay. One second. One
second. One second. Hold it down. Hold
it down. Hold it down. Hold it down.
Right. Okay. So, why didn't I get done
for subleting then? Okay. Okay. One sec.
One sec. One second. One second. One
second. One second. This is how stupid
you people are. Okay. If you gave the
evidence, if you gave the evidence, one
second. One second. Why didn't anything
happen then? I didn't go to court. I
didn't have to pay a fine because you
did not stop anyone's money. You made up
that story. If you prove that somebody
was subleting and you proved it,
brother, I would have got done for it. I
would have got a fin because you never
stopped anyone's money. You're an idiot.
You're a [ __ ] You didn't stop
anyone's money. You never stopped no
one's money. If you showed evidence,
then I would be in court for subleting
or my mom would have been in court. But
that never happened because you never
stopped no one's money because you did
not stop anyone's money. You made up a
story. You made up a story because I
told everybody what really happened and
you made your own story. You did not
stop anyone's money because if you
proved if you literally proved that I
subleted, I would have got done for it.
I would have got done for it. But it
never because you never stopped no one's
buddy. There you go. You just made
yourself look an idiot again. Oh, my mom
would have. or my mom would have to be honest.
Yeah, I know. You people are the
Monties. You can't even come on here and
show your face. You can't even come on
here and show your faces. You are the
monties. Listen to you monties on
YouTube. Jobless, no girlfriend.
Look at you monties on YouTube and you
should be at work,
you know. Simple, simple, mate. Simple,
mate. If you prove that I was subleted,
I would have got done for it. You just
[ __ ] yourself up. You never stopped no
one's money. You did not stop nobody's
money. You stopped no one's money at
all. Not a penny of it. None of my
money. You stopped. No, you did not. No,
you did not. You never stopped my money.
Never stopped by, buddy. You just [ __ ] yourself up.
You know what I'm saying? Listen. And
what are you, LJ? 42 and you've never
been to Asia. No girlfriend, never
traveled anywhere. Look at you, brother.
sat on YouTube begging in your 40s. You
can't even afford a decent curry. You
can't even afford a decent curry in your
40s. [ __ ] 40year-old, no girlfriend,
barely traveled anywhere in his life.
All you've got to show in your life,
bro, is a couple of ugly kids and a bad
back. No driving license. Oh [ __ ] Oh
[ __ ] I forgot to say that. You got no
driving license, no girlfriend, just a
couple of ugly kids. And yeah, I'm
talking about your kids.
Just uh just a couple of ugly kids to
show in your 40s. Nothing but a couple
of ugly kids. Ugly stinking kids. And
I'm speaking about your kids. Are you
going to come for me? Are you going to
come for me, big man? No, you're not.
Cuz I'm not Timmy Eldridge. Just like
you wouldn't meet LT, would you? Cuz you
pick your targets. You pick your
targets. Yeah. A couple of ugly kids.
Couple of them. Couple of ugly kids. I
think there were a couple. What are you
going to do, man? Are you going to come
to London? Are you going to come to
London, big man, with a buyback? Try it.
Try it. Try it, bro. Yeah, you've done
it. You've done it to Timmy three times.
Listen, I will pay for you to come here.
I will generally pay for you to come here. Yeah,
brother. You come on the door and you
done nothing. You done nothing.
Listen, Red Star, you never got anyone's
money stopped. You keep telling yourself
that. You keep telling yourself that.
You keep convincing yourself that you
got my money stopped. You keep telling
yourself that. I'm not going to block
you if it makes you feel better. You
keep telling yourself that.
You keep telling yourself that, brother.
You keep telling yourself that you've
got my money stock whilst I'm sat here
with more money than you. You keep
telling yourself that.
You keep telling yourself that, bro. You
keep convincing yourself that. If that
makes you feel better about the fact
that you're skint, keep telling yourself
that. I'm not blocking you, bro.
You know, I'm not I'm not blocking you.
I'm not blocking you. Lj sat there with
a couple of ugly kids. That's what he's
got to show at 42. A couple of ugly kids.
Never traveled, no driving license,
begging for money. You really think if
this guy had money, he'd be begging on YouTube?
You really really think that he'd be
begging on YouTube if he had money?
You can't even keep up with your own
lies. You really think that you'd be
begging for money if you had you would
be begging for money if you had money?
Really? You'd be begging for money on
YouTube if you've got money.
Really? Really, bro? Come on now. Let's
Let's talk facts cuz it doesn't really
make sense. Come on. No shouting, no
[ __ ] Rob, you got nothing.
You got nothing. My time.
Isn't even allowed her kids because
she's banging. Yeah. Yeah. You keep
telling yourself that. Yeah, ma'am. You
keep telling yourself that. When you
I'll send you the money. You come in.
I'll give you the money. How much money
do you want? How much money do you want?
Oh, Red Star has gone quiet.
You What, bro? You need to tell You need
to literally keep saying about how you
got my money stopped, bro. Cuz you never
got any of my money stopped. It's just
lovely seeing it. It's just lovely
seeing that you think that you got my
money stopped when you didn't. So like
if I generally Steven Allen, if that was
the truth, do you not think I'd be
blocking these comments the same as
someone getting [ __ ] doxed?
I haven't seen him a crisis over 200
pound list. Again, I'll repeat myself.
Yeah, he stopped my money. Oh, did he
really? That's nice of you, man. If you
stopped my buddy, why have I still got
more money than you? You still ain't
answer the question, lad.
You know. Yeah, you said that 2 hours
ago. You ain't got a bird bun. You're
too ugly. You can't get women like Peter
Belly Red Star. You ain't got a girl.
You're too ugly. You're an ugly bun. You
can't get girls. Whereas me, I've shown
me with multiple women. But you can't
get a girl cuz you're too ugly. You've
never been with a girl. You're still a virgin.
You know, you can't have a girl. You're
too ugly. You're an ugly [ __ ] who's
bald. YOU AIN'T GOT NO GIRLFRIEND. You
ain't got no girlfriend. You were
supposed to do this 2 hours ago. You're
still sat here talking to me. Don't
forget I got You definitely definitely
did not get my money stopped. But again,
if that makes you feel better about the
fact that you're skinn Keep saying it.
You keep saying it, brother. You keep saying it.
You keep saying that you got my money
stopped. It's not going to change the
fact that you didn't. That I still have
more money than you. So, at the end of
the day, you keep saying it, brother.
Keep saying it. It's not going to change
the fact that I'm sat here with more
money than you as opposed to being sat
here with [ __ ] all. You're girl. You
don't have a girl. You've never had a
girlfriend. You're virgin in your 40s.
You baldy bastard. Sat on YouTube
stalking people every day. Sat here with
nobody. You baldy bastard. Never got no
words, buddy. Stopped. I I I stopped
your boyfriend going to events, though.
You remember that one, Steven Howard? I
stopped his boyfriend going to events
for a month. You remember? He couldn't
go to events cuz of me and the posters.
He must be getting himself confused. He
must be really getting himself confused,
bro. He must be really, really, really
getting himself confused because I'm
pretty sure that I put posters up and
his boyfriend didn't go out the door
because of me. So he must he must he
must be uh
yeah PJ is a broke bum relies on col bro
you're talking about yourself takes one
to no one none of my stuff is colana it
takes one to no one brother the only
reason you people are going on about
colana is cuz you people are skint that
use kana takes one to no one takes one
to no one brother you know all about
colana cuz you people ain't got nobody
you know all about it the tricks and the
trades being skit like you people
You know. Yeah, brother. You know all
about that. Sat there with no money. You
know all about colona loans. You're the
one that uses them, not me. Look at me,
bro. Best pair of trainers.
Should we Should we show each other
clothes? Should we show the clothes that
we've all got? Brand spanking new
trainers, but apparently got my money
stocked. Uh, let's show some new things
that we got here.
Let's see who wins at the clothing game.
Right. There we go. 100 pound coat. This
is new. Apparently that's collard as
well when you got more money than these people.
200 pound jeans. There you go. Another
thing that these people can't afford.
Should we get the stonies out as well?
Yeah, let's get the stonies out. Look,
I'm beating you at the clothing game.
There you go, mate. I'm beating you at
the clothing game, you [ __ ] idiots.
Oh, but apparently it's it's Claude,
isn't it? Oh, yeah. Really, mate. Yeah,
these people are really funny, mate.
Really, really, really, really funny.
Really, really, really, really funny,
mate. Get the receipts out. I'm not
proving anything to you ugly people.
Listen, listen, listen. One second. I'll
do you a deal. No, no. I'll do you a
deal. I'll do you a deal. No, no. One
second. Everyone, chill, chill, chill,
chill. So, you want to see the receipts?
Yeah, I've got the receipts from the
mainline wear and foot asylum on my
emails cuz I bought them online. I will
show you the receipts on one condition.
I'll show you the receipts. I can put
them up right now. No, no, no. Okay,
we'll do this. We'll do this. Yeah.
Yeah. We'll do this. We'll do this.
We'll do this. We'll do this. We'll do
this. I'll show you the receipts when
you show me your face. You join the hangouts
and you show me your face and I'll put
and I'll and I'll put the I'll put the
receipts up. You show me your face. I'm
going to put the link up and I swear to
God on my mom's life, my dead dad, I
will put the receipts up. Yeah. Never
talk to me again if I don't put the
receipts up. Never never talk to me
again, Stephen Howard, if I don't put
the receipts up. Yeah. I promise. Yeah.
And and and Steven Howard's my boy. You
come on here and you show me your face.
I'll put the receipts up.
I've got him on my email.
You You come on here and you show us
your face and I and uh and I and I and I
and I'll do that, mate. Yeah. You show
that you're not ugly and fat like you
people all are and I'll show you the receipts.
You know what makes me laugh with these
people, brother? You know what makes me
laugh with these people is how they
think that you need to prove yourselves to them.
Bunch of fat, ugly life losers, Steven
Howard, that think that you need to
prove yourselves to these ugly people.
Yeah, Kana loans. Not me, mate. I've got
more money than you. You must be talking
about yourself. Takes one to no one,
bro. Yeah, that's you. Poverty Kana
takes one to no one. Talking about yourself.
So, second, so firstly, you say that
I've got bad credit and then you're
saying that I use colana loans. Which
one is it? Make it make sense,
right? Make it make sense. So, have I
got good credit or bad credit? Make it
make sense because one minute you're
saying that I use Colana loans. Brother,
why would I lose colana loans? It only
comes to £400 just because we're not
skint like you people. We can afford
£400, bro. Think outside the box. It
cost me £400 and something pound for a
pair of jeans and trainers.
I'm not skint like you people. Think
outside the box.
[ __ ] hell, matey.
Yeah, you still there, Steven Howard?
You still there, Steven Howard?
Bro, I want to come on here and own them
at the money game again. But, bro, I
don't want to prove myself to these
people, bro. I don't want to prove
myself to these fat, ugly projectors,
you know? I don't want to prove myself
to these fat, ugly people with no family
that can't get off of YouTube. Like I
want to I want to easily get these 50
pound notes out, bro. But I don't want
to prove myself to these fat, ugly bums
that's got nothing in life. You get my
point, bro. These fat, ugly, projecting,
boring bastards. That's why I don't want
to do it, bro. You know what I mean? You
already saw my trades. You already saw my dreams.
Yeah, to be fair, I do need to stop
banning people now. They're [ __ ]
boring, bro. To be fair, I'm going to
ban these people again.
And it shows that these people have got
no life, bro. They really, really ain't
got no life. I proven it today, bro.
I've proven it today that these people
ain't got no life.
I proven it, the lad. I proven it, man.
Yeah, these people ain't got no life. I
proved it, bro. These people should be
at work, [ __ ]
See you later, you virgin. Bye-bye.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] broke. It shows
that they've got no life, brother. But
listen, Steven Howard. Yeah.
Listen, the landlord, the landlord was
trying to get the house back for 4
years. These people didn't get any of my
money stopped. I can swear to you on my
dead dad, my [ __ ] mom's life. If if
it happened, I would tell you it
happened. I would generally tell you,
brother, these people did not get any of
my money stopped. Not one bit of it.
Not one bit of my money. Not a penny of
it, bro. Yeah, we all saw what happened
to [ __ ] nonss.
Yeah, these people ain't got no life,
bro. For real. For real.
They did not get a penny of my money
stopped. Not one single penny of it. [snorts]
The landlord was trying to get the money
back, the house back for years. He kept
coming on the door, bro. He kept coming
on the door. Yeah. He come on the door
when I was in Amsterdam and the tenants
told me years ago and he was trying to
get that for years, bro.
I mean, these people did not get any of
my money stopped. I've still got more
money than them.
More money than they'll ever have, bro. Yeah,
these people are sad.
ain't got no family, brother.
They ain't got no life, no family. These people,
These people should be at work today. Um,
Steven Howard, they should be at work.
They should be at work today.
You didn't get anyone's money stopped.
Not a single penny of it.
Not a [ __ ] single penny of it.
Grieves has been quiet, Steven.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
These people were supposed to be at work
today, but they were on YouTube typing
away the sad acts.
Sad acts, brother. This is why I don't
come on here much anymore. Steven Hourwood, lad.
That's why I don't really come on here anymore.
Oh, bro, did you watch the new horror film, Stephen?
Banger, bro. Banger. Just I'm sure
you've heard about it in it. You've
heard about it, isn't it? Yeah.
You heard about the new horror film. It
was [ __ ] It was a banger, bro. Uh, The Housemaid.
It's getting uh really big, bro.
[ __ ] there was sex scenes in it, bro.
It was bad. Sex scenes. Sex scenes.
Yeah, the housemmaid. It was good, bro.
[ __ ] sex scenes and [ __ ] bro. It was
mad. I started crushing on the [ __ ] maid.
Yeah, I started crushing on the maid, bro.
Oh, man. I got toothach, bro. I need to go [ __ ]
Yeah, go on it, guys. The housemade is a
good good uh horror film.
All right. Plan B. Do you remember the
chevel co trend?
Do you remember the shovel co trend?
Plan B when they all used to say Chev
was attractive to copy each other.
Do you remember that lad? You seem like
an old school kind of guy. Yeah. The housemaid. Yeah.
They all used to copy each other. The
boys at school. Do you remember? Hey,
you remember that, don't you? When they
all used to copy each other, copy the crowd.
Hi, Timmy. Do you want to join the box, bro?
They all used to copy each other. You remember
they all used to copy each other
calling each other gay and [ __ ] It was
quite funny to be fair. You're gay. No,
you're gay. No, you're gay. They all
used to call each other gay. The little copycat.
Do you remember? Yeah.
Yeah, bro. The House Made, man.
A good It's a good horror film. Stephen Howard,
I recommend it. I [ __ ] recommend it, bro.
Yeah, the M's [ __ ] sexy, bro. Oh,
I hate seeing these sex scenes in uh in
this whole film of Steven Howard. It was
making me want to go out and approach again,
but obviously I given up with it for a
very long time, bro. At least 6 months.
Yeah. At least 6 months.
But yeah, that the housemaid, bro.
It was proper [ __ ] up. Stephen Allo
It's kind of scaring, bro. The sex seems
kind of scaring, you know, bro. Bad.
It just stays with you, you know. Some
things, Stephen, how it stays with you, you know.
stays with you. You know what I mean? But
uh that's that, brother.
Yeah, you must be uh No, the other one.
There's two of them.
If you're not going to watch it, I'll
basically tell you what happened.
If you don't want to watch it, uh, no,
the other one, bro, there's two of them.
Hey, bro. There's a lot there's there is
lots of skittness here. Yeah, you need
to stop being skinn.
You need to leave, bro. The skis is bad
cuz of you. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
Yeah. No, it's not the blonde one. It's
the brunette one, bro. Oh my god, bro.
So, basically, you want me to tell you what happened?
I can tell you it, bro. You'll probably
watch it anyways. Yeah, the brunette.
And she's the same age as me.
She's the same age as me, bro.
Apparently, she's really famous. I I
didn't know, bro. I didn't know about um
Is there football tonight? I didn't know about um
I didn't know about her until I looked
her up. Like I was like, "Oh [ __ ] she's really famous."
I didn't know about that, bro. Until
like The thing is, Stephen, I wasn't
like nons. I didn't start saying, "Oh, I
like Sho. I like Sho. She's attracted."
I didn't even know the cunt's name. I
didn't even know they were that big.
I was like, "What the fuck?" Whereas
nonsex, he just went by the name the little copycat.
Little copycat with no mind of his own.
You know, there's there's a big
difference. [ __ ] copycat. No.
Yeah, bro. She's the brunette one.
[ __ ] me, bro.
Yeah. And they done it about three or
four times as well, them sex scenes.
Yeah, bro. They done it multiple times.
And I was like, "Oh [ __ ] I really need
to try to join the porn industry.
No, it was good, bro. So, basically what
happened was Steven Howard. Yeah. Is
basically this this married man and this
married woman hired a housemmaid, right?
So then a housemmaid come and lived with
them. Yeah. Um
Yeah. So the house the housemmaid
um went to live with them and the woman
was crazy. So the the the husband was um
like they all thought it was the woman
that was crazy. But it turns out that
the woman was crazy because the husband
was crazy and it was a madness, bro. And
then he slept with a housemmaid and
Yeah. mad. Mad. It was mad, bro. There
shouldn't be these sex scenes in these horror films.
No, I like that brunette one, bro.
She had [ __ ] she had a she had a
perfect figure. I told my I told Laney
about it as well.
No, I like that one, bro. I like that
one. But I didn't know who she was until
I looked her up. But I didn't know she
was really famous and that. I didn't
know that, bro. Like, I'm not a copycat.
Never been a copycat.
I'm not like [ __ ] nons.
I don't care. You're okay. You know what
I mean? I like I'm not [ __ ] I'm not
him. I'm not a copycat.
You know, I don't I don't like most people.
That's what he That's what he started
saying the next day in college. Um
Steven Howard about that. You kept
talking about her little copycat.
You're [ __ ] copying. Yeah,
they all used to copy each other, didn't they?
But no, man, it's um
Yeah, it's [ __ ] now. Anyway, Stephen,
cuz I've given up with the dating,
haven't I? I've given up with women and
[ __ ] So, I haven't been out for um
ages. Maybe I'll try again in March. Maybe March.
Um maybe. I don't know.
I just don't want to go through it
again, bro. To be fair,
you know that woman that I got on
Snapchat two months ago, the Indian
woman, she hasn't replied and then she's
put a story up.
Another ignorer. Ignoring [ __ ]
Another [ __ ] ignor, bro.
Was from a couple of months ago. Yeah.
I done a football bet yesterday, bro. I
done a fourfold both teams to score. I
put 20 pound on it and I got two out of
four. I just needed Heraford and Enfield
Enfield Town to score. I never Yeah.
They always call people skin.
It's weird, isn't it?
They always call people skint on this community, bro.
So what? You don't like the them women
in the house made Steven Howard? You
don't like them? No.
I like him. They're [ __ ] uh all
right. They are
>> Did you go >> Captain?
>> Did you go and watch The Maid?
>> Yeah. Did you?
>> I I bet you any money, right? You was in
the cinema going, "I'm going to WhatsApp
that woman." And I am I'm going to do
the No. Did you like it?
>> Yeah, it was good, man. Did you watch it?
>> I didn't. I think it's a load of [ __ ]
>> No, it's a good horror film to be fair,
bro. It's actually good to be honest.
It's got like a twist to it. You know,
>> well, I know the story. I know the story
line and I watched it.
>> Because you what? Cuz you read the book in it.
>> No, it's about a woman. She killed a
person at 15 years in prison and she did
uh she did 10 years and she was five
years out on parole and then she went
and did the babysitting made sorry
husband was in the house abusing a woman
and she killed her husband and said that
he fell from a a certain story. Is that right? >> Yeah.
>> Well, I just saved money, didn't I? I
don't need to [laughter] go and watch.
>> How did you know that?
>> It's called reading.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, you must have read the
book then, didn't it?
>> No, it must be a second one coming out.
K's a bacon. Bacon. Kay's a fatty bacon.
>> Yeah. Kay's a fatty bacon. Kay's a fatty
bacon. Kay's a fatty bacon. Nons.
You're going to No. Senior miners in the
New York. You
bastard. Anyway, he's finished.
>> You're not going on the birth certificate.
>> You know what happens?
>> You're not going on the birth certificate, dude.
>> What you want about on a birth
certificate? [laughter] What are you
talking about? What you want about She's
not going on a birth certificate.
>> [ __ ] to the live stream.
>> No, [ __ ] No, listen. Mongo's not on
the birth certificate. [laughter] Katie
is she's the mother. You dig? She She's
on it. He ain't >> Timmy gamble yesterday.
>> No PJ, it's Christmas.
>> Why Timmy? I lost 200 pound on the online roulette.
>> Why do you keep doing Why do you keep
doing that PJ? I
>> I didn't. That was the first time in
three months. I don't I don't do it much. Timmy, you >> [ __ ]
>> Timmy. Timmy, I've got a question. Is it
true? All right, Timmy. Can I ask you a question?
>> Go on.
>> Is it true? Yeah. If you gamble on like
William Hill online and you win, they
ask you for like source of income before
paying you your money.
>> You know that's true, PJ. You know that's true.
>> I I don't know it's true. I don't know
it's true. That's why I'm asking you.
>> Yes, PJ. That is true.
>> I've heard it. I've heard about it, but
I didn't know if it was true.
>> Let me get my earphones in.
>> All right, Timmy.
>> Can you hear me?
>> Yeah, I can hear you.
>> Yeah, just let me get my earphones in right there.
There. Can you hear me now? >> Gone. >> Yeah.
>> Right there. [ __ ] hands for his [ __ ]
Right there. Right there. Right there.
One minute, mate. One minute.
>> Yeah, I can hear you. I can hear you.
>> All right, PJ. Right. Just a quick one
cuz I'm I'm with family, mate. I ain't
got time for this.
>> Right. Just a quick one. You know, if
you win so much that I ask you for your
ID, proof of income, what job you got.
It's in the terms and conditions, mate.
It's the new gambling act law.
>> But they don't do it in bookies if you
win on the machines, in it.
>> No, PJ, cuz the gambling laws are bent.
You should know. I mean, [ __ ] hell.
You're that autistic and you gone about
being autistic. You should know all this, PJ.
>> Yeah, but you still gamble.
>> Of course I still gamble. I [ __ ] love
it. I'm Irish. [laughter]
>> What did you say? You love it. You're Irish.
>> I'm more bloody Irish than bloody Lord
Jay. Put it that way.
>> Yeah. Yeah, RJ's got nothing to show at
42. He's only got a couple beat up last
night. I think you're disabled.
>> All he's got all All he's got to All
RJ's got to his name is a couple of ugly kids.
>> Yeah, he's disabled like you, PJ.
>> Yeah. Are you disabled?
>> Yeah, I own it, but I'm I'm a maniac disabled man.
>> Can you Can you Can you um can you help
me win money gambling?
Maybe in the new year, PJ,
>> but can you tell me? No. Can you help
>> Merry Christmas, Katie. Merry Christmas.
But you still
>> Timmy, I hope you lose your virginity
next year. [clears throat]
Next year is going to be the year for
you to lose your V card. Timmy,
>> what was that?
>> Next year will be the year that you use
your you um you lose your Valentine's card.
>> I'm going to owe all you [ __ ] What a
st even hide your money behind the beds.
What? Even nonsp
coming to save the taxpayer.
>> What about nonslegs?
>> Sean, you taxpayers nightmare. Get a job. >> PJ,
>> well, you're telling Well, you're
telling nonslegs to get a job.
>> Yes, I'm telling you to get a job as well.
>> I've got a job.
>> My job is get off YouTube, you [ __ ] [laughter]
>> I just Timmy, I've got a job.
>> No, you haven't. Your job is being a [ __ ] bum.
>> I work I work in the casino.
>> You don't work, PJ. You're the biggest
bum on the planet.
>> How do you know I don't work?
>> It's a bit obvious, dude.
>> No, but seriously. Seriously, Timmy,
have you won money lately? Be honest.
>> Yes, I've won lots of money, PJ. I've
got more money than you've had hot cross bonds.
>> I've got three grand.
>> No, you haven't.
>> Yes, I have.
>> Show me some money then. I already
showed you, buddy, before you ran away.
>> Show it again. Why can't you show it again?
>> Because I shouldn't have to. I already
showed you, buddy, and you ran away.
>> Oh, PJ, I've got it in the bank and I
don't explain myself to that. I don't
take this cable seriously like you, lad.
You take the cable serious.
>> Why Timmy? You know these people was on YouTube Christmas?
>> Yeah. And you was to watch.
>> No, no, no, no. I was live for 5 minutes
to see if they were. Yeah. To see if
they were on Christmas, too.
>> Yeah. For 5 minutes. Yeah. Yeah. I was
on YouTube for 5 minutes before going to
my sisters. And what? Yeah. So what?
>> Yeah. Anyway, I've heard some rumors
that your sister's got a new black
boyfriend called Steve.
>> No. No.
>> That's what I
>> I heard I heard a rumor that I heard a
rumor that you're a Red Star friend. [snorts]
>> I'm what?
You're a Red Star's friend.
>> What the [ __ ] are you on about?
>> You like Red Star, ain't it? >> No. Well,
>> I thought he was your friend, huh? Red Star. >> Yeah,
>> I love Red Star. He's a legend.
>> No, he's an obsessed freak. Do you know
Do you know who it is?
>> Don't you dare talk about Money Mike that way.
>> Do you know who it is?
>> Yes, it's Money Mike.
>> No, it's not Money Mike. No, it isn't.
>> It is Money Mike. It's me and Money Mike
running that account.
>> Nah, no way. The spelling the spelling's
too good. The spelling's too good.
>> PJ Money Mike can spell. [laughter]
>> No, the spelling's too good.
>> It's me and Money Mike.
>> Really? Yeah,
>> you're an idiot, Timmy. You are [laughter]
>> Timmy, I think you need to Timmy, I
think you need a trip to the dentist, isn't it? >> Huh? Oh, Timmy.
>> Yeah. Are Are you going to go to the dentist?
>> I go [clears throat] every I go every 12 months, PJ.
>> Yeah, but you're scared of the dentist. >> No.
>> Yeah, you are. [laughter] Yeah, you are.
Yeah. What do you go there for to me?
I've heard women buy your new boyfriend
by your new What do you go to the dentist for?
>> Scared the bogey, man.
>> What do you go to the dentist for?
>> I've heard you're scared the boke.
>> No, but what do you go to the dentist for?
>> A checkup, you dick.
>> What? To get a filling.
>> Well, sometimes. Yeah.
>> It hurts, isn't it? You've never Timmy,
have you ever had a toothache? It hurts.
>> PJ, I love pain. Just remember,
>> you've never had a toothache, have you?
Oh, [ __ ] hell, PJ. Every every
person's had a tooth ache. [laughter]
>> What did you call it? A tooth.
>> Whatever you want me to call it, I can
call it a [ __ ] bell and tough if you want.
>> Bless you in life then to be the 26th of August.
>> Oh, yeah. I'm just going to I'm just
going to get pissed on Peru dog all year.
>> Yeah, your birthday is the 26th of August.
>> Yes, I know that. So, where are we going
from on this? Why you getting excited
over my birthday? Should be excited.
>> Do you remember my birthday?
>> Yeah. the 11th of the 11th, 1986. [laughter]
>> No, my birthday's April.
>> Which day?
>> Uh, [snorts] the first.
>> Your birthday is the 1st of April. So, I
know now your date of birth.
>> Yeah. My date of birth. Yeah.
>> Anyway, I'm off, PJ. Anyway, I've got
some good news for you. >> Mhm.
You're going to die a virgin.
>> You already are a virgin. [laughter]
That's you, Timmy. You are the virgin.
You and Nex are the biggest virgins. The Virgin Mary.
>> Is that giving you Is that made you Is
that made your dick up?
>> How can I be a virgin when I put a porno up there? >> Huh?
>> He can't prove you've had sex on YouTube
for [ __ ] sake. It's against [ __ ] Google.
>> Okay. So, okay. So, nonsex is a virgin
then cuz he calls you a virgin.
I don't really give a [ __ ] if he calls
me a virgin. At least I have a life, PJ.
I go on holidays, go and see people. My
life is not going down the social club
dancing with pensioners. [laughter]
>> Yeah, he's a virgin, is he to me?
>> Yes, he's definitely a virgin. And he
loves And he loves to have it out with pensioners.
>> So what? He's definitely a virgin. Yeah. >> Yeah,
>> he's definitely
jeez. Now he can go on about.
>> So if you see him on the street, will
you hit if you So if you see him on the
street, Timmy, will you hit him?
>> Yeah. And Robbie's money.
>> Yeah. He doesn't have money. That's his daddy's savings.
>> No, it's his money. PJ, he's got money.
He's never had a life.
>> No, it isn't.
>> Okay. So, okay. What if you saw me on
the street? You would just take my hand in it.
>> No, I'd give you a pump. I'll thump you,
hit you, put in the back of an
ambulance, and put on your forehead bacon. >> [laughter]
>> You're just like Monty man. >> Yes,
>> you are. Yeah,
>> but literally I would put on your
forehead, you've been done in bacon. Oh, Timmy. >> Yes.
>> You You said you used to like shovel
cole as well, was it? You used to have a
wank that is it.
>> PJ, I wank over the most beautiful
birds. There's nothing wrong with that.
It's called the nature of life.
>> You know who Shville Cole is?
Yes, PJ. I have ranked over lots of
women, especially when you're on Exc going.
>> Yeah, but you know, you know, nonslegs.
Yeah. He was saying that she's
attractive to fit into me. He wanted to
like fit in with the crowd, you know?
>> Can I just P I've got to go. But can I
just say one thing? Why do you [ __ ]
care what this Shauny says about you?
Why does it affect your life?
>> Because he's just a little copycat. So
what? They're all copycats. I mean, Mr.
B. Ding. They all [ __ ] say the same
[ __ ] but it doesn't affect my day.
>> So why do these people on here call people skin?
>> Because PJ, they do it to get a
reaction. How many [ __ ] times do I
got to tell you?
>> No, but Timmy, that's [ __ ] Because
even if you ignore them, they'll still
do it. So that's [ __ ] [ __ ] now.
So the loving it
>> and I've and I've done it before where
I've not reacted, they've still done it
after six months.
>> PJ, they want to get a reaction out of
you. That's why they keep doing it.
>> Nah, they would still Timmy. Timmy, but
they would still do it. They would still
do it even if they didn't get a reaction. >> Huh?
>> And they still haven't got a reaction
out of me after three years. They think
they've got one, but they haven't.
>> You got a reaction now?
>> I'm not reacting and making a point.
There's two different things. I'm not I
haven't got an anxiety voice getting
excited over [ __ ] people calling me skins.
>> Yeah, but Timmy, you um you you react to nonslegs.
>> I don't react to nonslegs. I [ __ ]
wind him up as like he winds you up and that's it.
>> He doesn't wind me up. I wind him up. He
does wind you up.
>> I wind him up, mate. He's the one that's
obsessed with me.
>> He's the one that's obsessed with
>> Why are you letting some bedsit monk get
in get in your skin?
>> He doesn't. He's just an ugly little
skin rat. I know he's a skin.
>> PJ is He's is not skin because he's skin
and then a skin.
>> Oh god. You got to look it like this.
He's been in his bed in prison for four
years trolling me cuz he's had
>> No, he doesn't troll me. He trolls
himself. So the reason why he's got 15
grand, but if the DWP investigating PJ,
how many times 13 grand is [ __ ] in
prison and four years his [laughter] bed
in a wheelrison being bumped by a Polish gay man,
>> bro? 13 grand is nothing.
>> PJ, you're not very smart because Hey,
Timmy, let me tell you something. You
know the most money into the DWP and
make sure he eats make sure he eats pip porridge.
Timmy, Joe. The most money I've ever had
was eight grand. Like, that's the most
I've ever had. What about you?
>> A lot more than that. PJ,
>> yeah, I had eight grand. The most money
I ever had in my lifetime was double the
amount than Sean's bedside um table money.
>> So, what did you spend it on? >> Everything.
>> Like what?
>> Uh everything. Holidays, house
[clears throat] living
more of a high life than you've had. Hot cross buns.
>> I've been to more cities than you,
>> PJ. It's not about that. It's about
>> No, I haven't interviewed, haven't it? I
have been to more cities than you.
>> So [snorts] what? You've been to more
cities, but you're still a virgin.
>> Yeah, I'm a virgin. Even though I proved
Even though I proved about sex. Yeah,
I'm a virgin.
>> Yeah, [snorts] I know. I'm a virgin. [laughter]
>> Yeah, nonsex is a virgin, is it? Okay.
So, how do you know Nex is a virgin?
>> Because he's never left his bed sit. The
only place he's ever been to is a social
club in Western Super Mayor to go to
Super Club. Um,
pensioners [ __ ] rock and roll.
>> So, so he's never had sex. >> No.
>> Has [snorts] L.
>> Everybody knows Bank's not a virgin. Get
Get a grip, PJ.
>> Okay. What about Tiger? He's a virgin.
>> Yeah, Tiger's a virgin. Yeah.
>> Okay. Mr. B.
>> Oh, he's definitely a virgin. that one.
The first thing he dreams about is Slo's lips.
>> Oh, you know Nons. He's the new one.
He's the skint one. He's the skin [ __ ]
in the beds. Show. And I say to I say to
him, Timmy, show me the 13 grand now.
And he can't show it cuz he don't have it.
>> Probably. No, he's probably he's
probably scared to get it confiscated by the DWP.
>> But why it's such a small amount of
money? Why do we scared?
>> PJ because I'll explain PJ, you're only
allowed to have £6,000. That's all
you're allowed. If
>> you have that, you got to declare it. And no,
>> he's definitely he's definitely skinn
he's definitely skinn he's definitely
skinned that one.
>> Okay, PJ, who cares if the [ __ ] long
not long legs he's got money. Why are
you [ __ ] so triggered about it?
>> I'm not. He's the one posting about me.
He's triggered over me.
>> Yes, because PJ, we've gone through
this. He's a skimp virgin. Apparently
said what you told me is true that his
parents don't like him. He's bit out.
He's all alone in his bed. Sitting there
jacking himself off. So he's gonna talk
[ __ ] about you, PJ. True. That's why
they do it to you. That's why
>> he's got nothing in life. So he wants a
reaction out of you.
>> That's why these people do it to you in it,
>> PJ. I love
>> Mr. B gets a reaction out of you. Mr. B
gets one out of you.
>> No, he doesn't get a reaction out of me.
PJ. I PJ, there's a difference between
getting a reaction and being, you know,
and an opinion. Why? I have an opinion
on Mr. B. Everybody knows Mr. B has
never lived a real life. He thinks this
is bullying. He thinks it's his own
because he's lived a cotton ball lifestyle.
>> I'm just hoping um Timmy in the new year
it will be different the it will be
different comments and different people.
>> That's not going to happen PJ. That's
not going to happen.
>> Yeah, but I'm hoping you can pray in it
>> because people on this community are too autistic [laughter]
>> or like Smokey Be that is it. [snorts]
>> I like Smokey Bee. I'm not going to
slack Smokey Bee off.
>> Yeah, but you've argued with him before
is it? Yeah.
>> Yes, but it was my own fault, PJ.
There's a difference between you and me.
I take responsibility. What I did that day, I
>> Okay. Have you seen Have Okay, Timmy,
have you seen that Joe Town only putting wins?
>> I like I spoke to
>> Yeah, but you know them You know them
wins. He can't be winning all the time
in it. You know that. Timmy Timmy,
listen. Listen, listen listen, Timmy,
you can have Listen, you can have an
opinion of someone not winning all the
time and not be jealous. Of course, I'm
not jealous. I'm just saying because I
gamble. I know.
>> You do get jealous, PJ. You do get jealous.
>> But I've got more money than him. WHY
WOULD I BE JEALOUS? So you've got more
than 15 grand.
>> DF don't have 15 grand.
>> Yes, he does.
>> Okay. But what is he? He only puts wins
up though, isn't it?
>> PJ, me and Joe get on very well. He
showed me his bank account on WhatsApp
yesterday. You know he's a millionaire.
>> No, you've never spoke to Joseph Ferrar.
>> Yes, I do. I speak to Joseph all the time.
>> You sure?
>> He's got his own house, PJ. Paid off mortgage.
>> No, you're a troll. No,
>> I'm No, I'm being serious. He has got
his house paid off.
>> Yeah, he gambles all the time in it,
>> DJ. He's got a lovely gaff.
>> Can you tell me what I what machine to
go on to win money from gambling
nowadays? Can you just tell me like the bookies?
>> I can tell you what to do. You got to go
to Blackpool and play Cash Beast with Ding.
>> What? You got to go to Blackpool and
play Cash Beast.
>> You nasty virgin.
>> You're a nasty cash beast.
>> No, you're a nasty virgin. What do you
mean? I'm a nasty virgin.
>> You are.
>> Why do you mean should go to Blackpool
and have a sablo and chips in it? Do we?
>> No. I said you asked me how to make
money and I said go to Blackpool and
clean out all the cash beasts. Clean out
of all cash. I know. You know Monty was
live on Christmas and he said, "Yeah,
I've only gone live to see how many if
anyone joins me, they've got no family
for Christmas." And five people joined me.
>> And he was like, Timmy, he joined. Five
people joined. And he's like, "That's
five people with no family Christmas. I was dead."
>> But but but but you've but you was on
YouTube as well. You're just as bad.
>> What? For five minutes.
>> Yes. Instead of you still virgin. [laughter]
>> Yeah. But Timmy, these people's on YouTube Christmas.
>> So was you.
>> I like Monty Man. You know, he talks he
talks the truth about these people. This
community in it.
>> I don't like Monty man. I don't like
Weiss. And I don't
>> He doesn't He doesn't talk the truth.
Does he not talk the truth about
>> Does he not talk about Does he not talk
the truth about these people on YouTube?
>> No, because he needs to sort out his own
life before he does. He's with a woman
he never sees who speaks to a
loudspeaker. He's [ __ ] you know he's
his his mom
because he put all his life on YouTube
and tried to make his mind at nine n
months old cook dinner. BJ [laughter]
initiative. [sighs and gasps]
>> You're a funny guy. BJ I right just
because when I I'm not going to go into
this PJ at the end of the day, right? I
don't hate people on there. I don't know
them. They're not my real life. I don't
really give a [ __ ]
>> No, I hate them on here. But when I see
things like going on this site, I'm
going to have an opinion.
>> No, I hate these [ __ ] to me.
>> I don't I just laugh at them.
>> I want to get one of my hands on them to
me. You know, you used to be that
though, didn't you?
>> PJ for 10 years. took this cable
seriously. Used to hate people. It used
to be my life. I used to It used to
affect me. It used to It used to do
everything. Now just laughing.
>> It took over Tiger's life as well. It
>> took over at one time. PJ took over all
our lives. [laughter]
>> Not mine.
>> Yes, it does. PJ takes over yours
because you get triggered over us. Um um
um nons legs. [laughter]
>> You're funny to me. You really are funny.
>> Thank you.
>> Do you want to come to London today and
have a meet up?
>> PJ, it's not going to happen. I with my
family for two weeks. It's not going to happen.
>> We can go to Weather Spoons.
>> Why would I go to that [ __ ] off?
>> You remember when these people kept
saying you stole off Hype and they
repeated that for years, isn't it?
>> Yes, but PJ I don't give a [ __ ]
Back then I did cuz I thought I did. I
knew it didn't happen and I thought why
am I getting round up of a bunch of
[ __ ] clowns? This is why Hyper This
is why me and Hyper fell out because we
let you've been arrested over YouTube like nearly
>> I let trolls got in the way. Hyper didn't
>> Yeah, but you ain't been arrested over
YouTube. I have
>> uh PJ several times. I have.
>> I have about six times.
>> Yeah, but mine's not for [ __ ]
assaulting women, PJ. Mine's for like political beliefs.
>> No, I mean over YouTube. Have you been nicked?
>> Yes, I've been nicked over YouTube over
political beliefs. What did what did
what did the police what did the police
just come on your door?
>> Yes. And they said that you're going to
get nicked because you called Muhammad a nons.
>> How long was you with the police for
>> PJ? When I sh How can you nick me for
something on Google? They couldn't do
anything cuz he is a bacon. It's in the
Quran that he married a 911 year old.
>> No, but have you ever been nicked over
the Have you ever been nicked over these people?
>> Go and tell them that you're classed as
scum racist and you get banned. Have you
ever been nicked over these people on YouTube?
>> Yes, PJ. How many times have I got to tell
>> No, but like these the trolls and that.
>> No, mine's been political beliefs.
>> I have because of the trolls to me.
>> PJ, we've got a government that supports
terrorism, bloody rapism, supports
[ __ ] you know, the Muslim. You can't
There's no freedom of speech. You leave
a post on Facebook, you get nicked in
the middle of the night.
>> Yeah. By West Midland's police.
>> Yes, PJ. We live with a government who
is a Pakistani. >> Yeah.
>> Yes. Our new Labour prime minister is a Pakistani. [laughter]
>> You're funny, [ __ ] You are.
>> No, it's true. He supports [ __ ] terrorism.
>> Timmy, if I go if I go to vote, you get
>> Timmy, if I go if I go to the bookies
right now and I put 150 Frankie and I do
two pound spins, will I win?
>> I don't know, PJ. Why don't you go out
there and try?
What do you reckon I'll win?
>> I don't know. Go out and try.
>> Are you sure?
>> Yes, but sing this song with me before I
go. Chaos Lama is a wanker.
>> Yeah, but Timmy, what if I lose?
>> Then you just have to go to the food
bank, won't you?
>> Yeah, but is there actually a chance I can win?
>> I don't know. Go out and try. >> Really?
>> Everything's random. Just do what I do.
Vote for the best. [panting]
>> Not funny to me.
>> Thank you. [laughter]
>> Why do you laugh at everything?
>> Because the world is just [ __ ] So I
laugh at it all.
>> No, seriously.
>> Cuz I find everything funny.
>> You dirty. You dirty nuns.
>> What are you all about?
>> You dirty pe.
>> You can call me what you want. It's not
going to affect my day.
Look, this is when I used to play
roulette. Look, can you tell it's roulette?
>> Is that the one where you do your
bollocks and you throw a chair at your mom?
>> Can you Can you tell it's roulette?
>> No, PJ. I'm color blind.
>> You don't even know how roulette works, isn't it? >> No.
>> Yeah, but you don't know where 11 is on the wheel.
>> No. [laughter]
>> You funny.
>> Anyway, I'm off, mate. I'll speak to you later. Well,
>> I'll talk to you later. See you.
So yeah. Um, so you don't like the maid, Stephen Howard?
You don't like the maid? No.
You don't think she's good-looking?
All right. Do you remember that Nutty
Log when Nonss was saying that Sherlock
Cole was good-looking to fit in?
When he was saying it to fit in with the crowd,
but you said you don't think they're
good-looking, do you Steven Howard?
You don't think them two are good-looking, though?
Why did Why did Nleg say She car was
attractive? Steven Howard,
why did you start saying that?
Weird. Is it H
I don't agree with Timmy though. Steven
Howard. Yeah. Listen to me. What do you think? Yeah.
He says that these people
do it for a reaction. And I'm saying
that even if you don't react to them,
they will still do it.
Who do you agree with, me or Timmy?
He says they do it for reaction. But I
don't agree with that because even if
you done videos and you ignored them,
they would still do it. They would still
do it forever. I don't I don't agree with that.
They will never stop. Never ever ever
Nah. What do you think?
Yeah. I wanted to fit him.
Why do you think these people harass me
every day? UK asylum,
Steven Howard, why do you think these
people harass me every day?
Do you think they're jealous? Do you
think it's because they're disabled or
what do you think it is? Yeah.
What do you think? UK is silent.
But even if you don't react, they still
do it. UK asylum. I don't understand
when these people say that they do it
for reaction because even if you don't
react, they still do it.
I don't understand how so many people
can say that, bro. A lot of people say,
"Oh, they do it for reaction." But even
if you don't react, they will still do it.
They will still do it forever, even if
you never reacted to them again. I don't
understand people that say that.
I really don't.
Yeah, but I don't understand Steven
Howard. The UK sign him. You say that
they do it for reaction, but even if you
don't react to them, they will still do it forever.
>> I don't think they do it for reaction. I
think they do it.
If you left YouTube, they would still do
it. They would still do it. They would
still do it. Even if you left YouTube,
they'd still do it. Nonsar.
No, I think they would still do it.
Joseph Ferrar would still do it.
And even if you done videos and you
never went live, they would still do it.
I think they would still do it. They
I think they would, me, I don't think
they would ever stop even in 10 years time. Um, yeah.
No, I think they would still do it. A
lot of them would.
Depends who we're talking about. Nonss
would always do it.
They will never leave you alone. It's
like what Ronald Pump said, you're
better looking than them. You got more
money than them and it kills them.
They'll never leave you alone.
That's what he said to me. That's what
Ronald Pump said to me.
He said, "You're better. You've got a
better life than them. you're better
looking than them and you've got more
money than them and it kills them.
They'll never leave you alone. And he
said, "Get off YouTube."
Yeah, that's what he said to me, bro. I
never listened. I'm starting to think he
was right now. Ronald McDonald.
I think it is jealousy, bro. I generally
generally think it is, bro. Like, cuz
obviously I'm not doing anything now.
Yeah. Cuz I'm chilling and I'm saving
money, but that's my choice. I'm not
going out now cuz of choice, not because
I can't afford it. If you think about
it, bro, I am younger than these people.
I am better looking than these people,
realistically, bro. Like I I I think Huh?
They all are jealous, bro.
I think they all jealous. What life have
they got? These people UK asylum. What
life have they got doing this?
I don't come on here much anymore.
I don't go live much anymore, bro. I was
off YouTube for a week the other day.
I don't really come on here much, bro.
I'm on and off here. I don't really come
on much anymore, you know. People
could take a day off of YouTube. UK asylum.
Oh, I I come here to talk to Steven
Howard and Grezy. Yeah.
I need to feel him badly, bro. I
[clears throat] got toothache. [snorts] >> [laughter]
>> Oh man, it's horrible. Too fake, bro.
Horrible. Too fake. Is it?
Nope. Joseph Ferrar, I'm not having a
bet. I've just looked on the football.
I'm skimp, bro. I ain't even got5 pound.
You want to give me some money? I'm skimp apparently.
I might put 150 on Frankie.
Yeah, use some gum. What do you mean some gum?
Yeah, I've got the dentist on uh in a
couple weeks. I booked an appointment.
Oh, it hurts, bro.
Yeah, but what if I lose Joseph?
No, I only said that. I only made up the
story. I can't wait to New Year's Day,
Joseph Farah. It's going to be different
people, different comments. I can't
wait. It's not going to be the same
people. I can't wait to New Year's Day.
No, I'm skin, mate.
Chewing gum. Why would I [ __ ] chewing
gum? That's going to hurt even more. No.
Yeah. I can't wait. New Year's Day, Joe.
So, what? You don't like them women from
the house, mate? I think one of them was
sexy. Me, Steven Outwood. She's got
she's got a nice body
and that guy got to [ __ ] her. Well, madness.
But what I was saying is um I can't wait
to New Year's Day.
What do you think, Joe?
Yeah, they will still talk [ __ ] Even if
you had a Even if you was in a
relationship, they'd still call you single.
I think she is. Yeah. You You've seen
her. Steven Howard, you've seen the the
one in the horror film.
You would never get a bird in this
country. Oh, that Indian reply back
saying, "Do I know you?" I said, "Uh,
yeah. I approached you two months ago.
Oh yeah. Did you Did you Did you see it?
I like Sher Cole, Joe. Do you remember?
Do you remember? I like Sher Cole.
Your boyfriend said that to fit in. Your
boyfriend said that to show off. He knew
he wanted to follow the crowd. [laughter]
Joseph Nons likes to follow the crowd,
doesn't he? He likes to follow the crowd.
Yeah, he likes to follow the crowd.
He's always been like that, bro. Even
when he was younger,
happened to feel the need to fit in.
I like Sh.
Oh, you little copycat.
How about do I know you
[ __ ] rude [ __ ] Oh,
did you see it? Steven Howard.
the type of bro, bro. Poor [ __ ] [laughter]
I ain't seen that account for a while.
Wow. It might be busy over Christmas, is it? >> [laughter] >> [ __ ] Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ] [laughter]
I think she is me,
but I'm not like Yeah, but I'm not like
[ __ ] Yeah, but I'm not like nonsense. Oh,
she's showing off. I didn't know I
didn't know they were really famous.
Yeah, I'm not a copycat. You know what I
mean? But I don't know by names and
people that associated with footballers and [ __ ]
Oh, he's copying.
Yeah, he's he's he's a copycat. Yeah.
You don't like you don't like
who do you like then? Steven Albert Chev.
That's okay, bro. If you don't like her,
I'm not going to start calling you gay. Gay homo.
Don't worry, bro. I'm not going to start
calling you gay. I'm mature enough to know that
different strokes, different folks.
Different strokes for different folks, you know.
Different strokes for different folks.
I'm not going to say homo.
I could be a copycat, but I'm not.
Is that right, Joseph? I could be a
copycat, but I'm not. I could easily be
a copycat. Okay.
And show off. But why?
You have my little voice. I'm not a little copycat.
I'm mature enough to know that people
can have different preferences
and I don't go by names. [snorts]
Why did everyone say that Cheryl Cole
was attractive? Steven Howard, I don't see it.
Why did they all say that [ __ ] I never
ever saw it with her. You know,
I never ever like I never ever saw it, you know.
Why do they always say that?
that by one, you know.
So why did they all say that she was
attractive and [ __ ]
Why were they all saying that she was attractive?
What happens when you got a toothache, bro?
When you need a filling, it hurts here.
It goes right up to your [ __ ] ear
here, bro. And it goes right up to your
[ __ ] ear, bro. It hurts.
>> Yeah. So why does everyone keep saying
that she was attracted? I'm not gay. I'm like 3.
>> I'm not gay. [clears throat]
I'm not [ __ ] gay.
>> [clears throat]
>> Oh god, bro.
The tooth fake will be the death of me, brother. The death.
It'll be the death of me. This too, fake, mate.
It will be the death of me when I'll
stop going live and you'll see one
second bar. [ __ ]
I need to stop drinking sugar to be
fair, bro. I do. That's my problem is
the sugar, bro. I need to stop drinking
sugar for like 2 weeks.
I need to stop drinking sugar for two
weeks, bro. I said the same thing to my
mom. It will kill you, bro. It c it
catches up on you when you're older,
brother. Do you know what started it?
You know what started this whole thing?
I clean my teeth every day. Do you know
what started this whole thing? Yeah.
I had like a bit of a pain anyways. Not
much. Yeah. I went to the cinema and you
know them cherry sweets, the pick and
mix sweets, bro. Yeah.
You know the pick and mix sweets? The
pick and mix ones. The cherries with the
green. Oh my god, bro. Ever since you
need I need to stop drinking sugar for
like two weeks, brother.
I have. I brush them every day.
I brush my teeth every day. I've got an electric toothbrush.
You need to I need to stop drinking for
like two weeks, bro.
Two weeks, bro.
I need to stop for like two weeks [snorts] cuz
Yeah, you need to stop for like two weeks.
for two weeks. I need have vegetables, water,
uh, no coke, none, nothing. Nothing.
See, my mom, she doesn't have sugar in
her tea. I have sugar in my tea. I can't
have it. But you stop, bro, for a couple
of weeks. Vegetables, water. If you want
to have a tea, don't have no sugar. It
will kill you, bro. Trust me. You know,
when I was younger, bro, like when I was
like 14, 15, I used to have four
tottling I used to have four tottling um
tottling cakes. I used to have four
Tottenham cakes like when I was younger.
Easy. You could drink Coke, but as you
get older, bro, you can't be doing that [ __ ]
I do brush my teeth, bro. I do brush my
teeth. I'm going to brush them in a
minute again. It [ __ ] hurts, bro. I
need to stop, bro. I really do need to
stop because it will kill me, bro. Trust
me, it will. Even like two just see just
need to cut down on it. And if you are
going to drink sugar, you need like a straw.
Yeah, something like that. Yeah.
I need to go to the dentist in like just
over a week as well. I'm going to stop.
I'm going to brush my teeth now.
Yeah, I brushed them. I just drink a lot
of sugar. I brush them. I just drink a
lot of sugar.
Yeah, I got a filling last month.
Yeah, [snorts] coke will kill you, bro.
I'm going to brush my teeth right now.
One second. Yeah,
I got an extra toothbrush for Christmas. Look,
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
Yeah. What's it? I brush my teeth. I
brush him this morning. Yeah. People,
they'll kill you that mate. Yeah.
Don't drink coke. It will kill you
as you get older. Yeah, you know,
I just need to cut back on the sugar.
I have to take these pills, bro. These
painkillers for the tooth.
It will kill you though, bro. But it
will kill you.
Definitely will kill you.
So you don't like si you don't like
sweetie then Steven Howard. You don't
like her. Huh?
Hey, Dusty. I was telling uh Steven
Howard about the housemaid and the actor
in it. I thought she was good-looking
and had a good body, but Steven Howard
doesn't like her.
No, I'm just talking about my toothache.
People always dismiss my struggles, bro.
They will always dismiss my struggles.
This woman said to me on Reddit, she was
like, "It'll build your confidence going
to the gym and stop chasing every girl
for sex. Don't you want something more
out of life?" I turned around and said,
"I'm not chasing every girl for sex. I
want sex and a relationship." Uh, I
said, "Women have sex, so I should, too.
I've put more than enough effort into
it. Lack of sex makes you depressed."
And then she didn't reply back to me
when I said, "Why is it okay for women
to have a sex life then? You think I've
got a point? Yeah.
No more sugar than that. Oh, you can't.
What do you think, Dusty?
See, I could be a copycat Steven Howard
and say, "Oh, if you don't find her
attractive, you're gay." Yeah, I'm a I'm
okay gay cuz she's got 25 million um
subscribers on Instagram.
So, I could easily be a little copycat
if I wanted to be.
I could be like, "Yay!"
No, her tips are not fake. They're real, actually.
Yeah. Gay. Ho, is that right, Dusty? Okay.
>> Yeah, I brushed my teeth, bro. Gobble,
>> why do you think that woman didn't reply
back to me when I said what I said about
women having a sex life? Steven Howard.
Was I right?
>> I know it's so bad for you, but it
tastes so good. >> Hobo.
I can't believe nonsle legs called me
gay for not finding Cheryl car
attractive. Seaside Mark love child.
All I said is I didn't find her
attractive and he's like gay hobo. You're gay. Gay hobo.
You remember that? They all used to call
each other gay. Yay! Hobo.
Yeah, I'm going to stop drinking Coke,
bro. And the sugar in my tea.
It's only just caught up with me. I
think it's cuz I'm getting older, is it?
Yeah. I got I got called gay cuz I
didn't find her attractive. I like the
housemaid. I I like that the woman from
the house made seaside Mark Love child.
So, how can I be gay? I thought she had
a nice body to be fair.
Yeah, her boobs are real. The the housemaid. Yeah,
she's nude. If you type nude, she's done
like porn and that. Well, semi porn. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, [laughter] girl. Yeah.
Yeah. Her name's Sydney Sweeney.
Apparently, she's very very uh she's
very famous. I didn't even know. Uh
yeah, but Nonleg said that I was gay if
I don't find her attractive. I don't
find her attractive. I don't like dick.
Yeah, that's copying. That's copying the
crowd. putting celebrities on a [ __ ] pedestal, bro.
I didn't even know who she was until I
watched the [ __ ] until I watched the
maid, bro. The housemaid.
I didn't know who she was.
I didn't even know who the [ __ ] was.
And I've watched it and I was like, "Oh,
let me look up these people." And then I
was like, "Oh, shit." Not like [ __ ]
nonslegs. He went by the names, didn't he, Dusty? Oh, dang.
You know, there was there was a
difference. There was there was a there
was a big difference.
Uh, that started months ago, mate.
Months and months and months ago.
Yeah, I used to like Ariana Grande, but
then she doesn't have any boobs and no ass. So,
I like that Sydney Sweeney, man. She was
having sex. Seaside Mark uh on on a in a horror film, you know.
That's just follow the crowd. Yeah.
She was uh she was having sex, bro. She
was having sex and it was it was
tormenting and they done it several
times. I don't know if you're into
horror films, but this housemaid. She's
in the housemaid. He's the same age as
me, by the way. And she was having sex
with the husband. Oh, bro. Was
tormenting. Very, very tormenting.
I I said I didn't go to watch a [ __ ]
porno. I went to watch a horror film.
You see her boobs? Yeah, you do see her boobs.
There's nude pictures of her on Google.
There are some nude pictures of her on
uh on Google.
But yeah, the film you you see boobs. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. I was tormenting
because of the history that I've got. It
was tormenting cuz obviously Seaside
Mark, I've given up with the dating and
the women and [ __ ] because it's toxic
and it's boring and I I ain't doing it.
And obviously I went to watch that
horror film cuz I like horror films and
I was like, "Oh [ __ ]
it's tormenting, bro."
And I was like, "No, I definitely need
to try and join the porn industry
because I'm not using escorts." The
thing is I will never you I don't think
I ever use escorts against seaside marks
because uh I don't want to use a condom.
I don't like condoms.
So I wouldn't I wouldn't use an escort
for one of them reasons. So I'm
basically [ __ ] unless I can join the
pool industry. I'm completely [ __ ] Basically
I'm [ __ ] unless I can join the pool
industry. How unfair is that bro? You
know, that's my only hope is the porn
industry. Otherwise, I'm screwed. I'll
never have a sex life. I'll just accept
it. It's not a problem. But I'm just saying.
Well, yeah. That's the only way of
getting a sex life, isn't it? Suicide Mark. Love child.
Yeah, that thing was a trigger in that
horror film, bro. That that that that
Sydney having sex
and she cheated as well. Like the
husband cheated on his wife. It's not
good for the brain stuff like that, bro.
That isn't good, you know, for the
brain. That's why a lot of people don't watch porn.
So, unless I join the porn industry, I'm
[ __ ] Basically, the only way you're
ever going to get sex life without a condom.
Not fair, is it? Not fair, bro.
I won't get a woman eventually, bro.
I've been single most I've been single
[ __ ] most of my life, bro. I haven't
even I haven't even I've had one date
this year. I've had three dates and then
they were all in March. I haven't had a
date since March or April.
No, I definitely definitely weren't,
bro. Not in this country. Definitely.
Definitely. I've not had a date since
March or April, one of the two. And I've
been out lots and lots and lots and it's
just the same [ __ ] They're all the
same. Pretend they got boyfriends. Leave
the one. That's why I gave up, bro. I
ain't been out for ages. The last time I
went out, it was cuz I was forced to go out.
I gave up. It was too depressing, bro. I
was like, I'm not going through that
again. I've been doing this for years.
Nah, I don't think I will ever try
again, bro. I don't think I will ever try again.
I really don't think I will, bro. I
think I'm done.
I'm really done. I shouldn't have to go
out and try again, brother. I shouldn't
have to go out and try and not. I've
been trying for years.
So, do you like her now, Steven Howard
or no? You like her now or not?
I should have to try again. I've been
trying for years, brother. I should have
to try again.
So, I'm trying to find other
alternatives, i.e. the pool industry. I
should have to try again. I spent more
than enough money, more than enough
time. I've got more than enough numbers.
So yeah, that's why I was thinking of
other alternatives. I don't want to try
again. I don't want to go through it
You know, my mental health has been good
since quitting since quitting the dating
scene. My life has been good, bro. I've been chill.
I've been Yeah. normal.
Every time I go back to women again and
dating, I get depressed. Same old [ __ ]
again. Why I gave up? That's why I gave up.
I gave up and I feel better for it. Um,
well, I'm going to just just sign up in
it on the on the porn websites. Yeah,
I'm just going to sign up on the porn websites. Yeah, that's
just took some painkillers.
I'm just going to sign up and see it.
Oh, it's not good though, bro. I
shouldn't have to try again.
I'm 28 years of age, brother.
You know I shouldn't have to try again.
Suicide M. Why should I have to try
again? I've been trying for years.
[snorts] Yeah. You don't like that
Sydney Sweenie. I like her. Me
and she's the same age as me as well.
Yeah. And then seeing them sex scenes
are depressing, bro. Them sex scenes in
them horror films.
I should have to try again. I'm 28 years
of age, bro. I'm not 24. I'm not 25
anymore. I'm older. I shouldn't have to try again.
So that's where we're at in it.
So I'm not sure what what what the what
the solution is. If we can't join the
porn industry, I don't know what we're
going to do. H
mate, I've been all over the country.
Suicide Mark, you must be new to my
channel. I've been all over the country.
I've been all over the country. No,
she's not. Well, she's 28. She's the
same age as me. She's a month older than
You must be looking on the You must be
looking on the wrong one, bro.
There's two of them. One's 40 and one's my age.
Nah, women are the same everywhere in
the West. I've been everywhere, bro. Manchester, Liverpool,
Newcastle, you name it.
And I'm telling you, bro, I've traveled
all over the country for years and it
really isn't that much different.
And I'm 28 and I've traveled all over
the country, brother.
And Steven Howard will will be my uh
will be my uh support for that. And I
and I'm telling you, bro, I've actually
traveled all over the country. >> Yeah,
I I actually have, bro. Yeah, I've been
to loads of places. I used to go on the
pool in Leeds, Liverpool, Scotland. And
really, women are the same everywhere.
The people are much nicer.
I'm not even joking, bro. I swear to
God, I've traveled loads of I've been
to, bro, I'll tell you I'll tell you all
the places I've been. Yeah. And how many
times I've been. Yeah.
Yeah. I tell you. I've been all I've
been everywhere, bro. I've literally been everywhere.
And even up north, the women are stuck
up. Trust me, I found it to be the same.
The only way that was slightly easier was Newcastle.
Uh yeah, Newcastle was the only place
that was kind of easier, but everywhere
else. No, no, no, no. It's the same everywhere, bro.
I've literally been The only place I've
not been is Glasgow and Blackpool. I've
been everywhere, bro. You must be new to
my channel. Welcome. I've been
everywhere, bro. Everywhere.
I used to sublet this house and I used
to just travel. I've traveled a lot,
bro. Really? No, I seriously have. I'm
not even trying to be awkward or
anything, bro. Like, I can I can show
you the train line app. I've been
everywhere. Most places. Most most
Multiple times as well. I've been to
Manchester about 10 times. I've only
been Liverpool once and women are the same everywhere.
So, I know they're all the same. I'm
aware they're all the same.
Okay. Name me. Name me a couple of places, bro.
Name me a couple of places.
Cities. Yeah. Yeah. Go on.
I've been to most cities. No, I've been
to most cities, but anyways, go on.
Yeah, you Yeah, name me places up north
I've not been to. Go on, bro.
I've been to majority of the cities, but Okay, continue.
Go on, bro.
Oh, I smell bomb.
Yep. I'm smelling bomb now.
Uh, I have been to Preston. Yes, I'm
smelling bomb now, bro. Not going to lie
to you. Uh, yes, I have been to Preston.
I have been to Carlile. Yep.
Yes, I have. And you said up north. You
didn't specify towns.
So, what do you mean? I've been to a few
cities. I've been to majority of the
Bomb. I've been to majority of the
cities. I'm very very very well traveled.
And definitely women are the same everywhere.
They're even the same in Thailand now.
Well, a lot of them are not all of them,
but yeah, I'm definitely definitely
doing the porn industry thing because
the the way I see it, Stephen Howard, is
I I don't want to keep going around in
circles. I don't want to keep going
around in circles all my life. I
shouldn't have to, bro. You know what
I'm saying? Yeah. That's definitely
definitely bomb. As soon as he mentioned
the towns. Yeah, definitely.
Trust me, I know. I've been everywhere, bro.
Okay. Yeah. I've got nothing for life. Okay, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. That's more self-p
projection. So, yeah. Stephen Alward,
I'm I'm trying to think logically, you know.
You know when I stopped gambling,
Stephen Hardidge? Yeah. Why did I stop
gambling? Because I didn't want to keep
going around in circles.
Yeah. You wouldn't get in the industry
cuz you're a M. Yeah, that's self
projection. You won't come on camera and
show your face. You are the M. Yeah.
Stop putting yourself down.
Yeah, you are the M. Stop talking about
yourself. I've been to Derby. Yes.
Yes, I have been to Derby. And these
play they're not up derby's not up
north. Derby's in the Midlands. So try
again. That's how uh bad your uh Yep.
I've been to Doncaster and I've been to
Darlington as well. Try again. Yep,
bro. I've been everywhere. Everywhere.
Yeah. You're That's not nice telling me
that I'm not going to get in the
industry cuz I'm a M. Just cuz you're
fat and ugly with no family. You don't
have to put everyone else down.
No, it isn't. No, it isn't. Up north is
up. Up north, not the Midlands.
Yeah. Bye-bye, bomb. Sad bastard.
That's bomb. So, yeah. Anyways, I'm
thinking logically, how do we stop this
like going around in circles? Steven Howard
like with the gambling. You remember
when I stopped gambling and that? There
was for a reason why I stopped gambling.
And obviously this we need to find a
solution because it's just going to keep
happening and happening and happening
going out getting the same bad
experiences. Like you need to think long
term now. You you need to think
logically. You've been up and down the
country. You've tried more than everyone.
And I don't want to go back into that
toxic [ __ ] again. It ain't worth it,
bro. For me. You know, it's no life for
anyone. I've got money. I've got money
to go out and do what I want when I
want. Believe it. don't believe it.
So, we need to think about what you know long term.
I look odd. No one cares about what you
people think about my looks. It's all self projection.
No one cares.
No one cares. We've seen what you people
look like when your cameras are turned
on and you're fat and ugly. So, they're
projecting. So, yeah. Steen Alward. So, um,
What's What's the solution other than
the porn industry?
Or at least try them.
We want to try everything before trying
again. And I don't think I will try
again, bro. I'll just I'll just go
without. If I have to go without, I'll
go without. It is what it is. I should
have to try.
Like, you might think I'm being awkward.
You might think I'm being difficult, but
I'm not, bro.
28 is not an age to keep going out and
drinking, bro. It's more like your
priorities should change at this age,
brother. I've been with more women than
you've had hot dinners, so you're
definitely definitely self projecting.
Yeah, just got uh Bro, you're that
you're that [ __ ] repeating bastard
whose account was made 18 years ago.
It's the same spastics,
bro. You three mongos are the same
lonely people. That guy said the same
thing earlier. Tragic.
And your account was made 18 years ago.
What a loser. You can't even deny you're
an old man. Your account was made 18 years ago.
That's how we know you're an old man.
You're just wasters. Self projectors on
the internet. 18 years ago. Your account
was made 18 years ago, bro.
18 years. you. I told you they're old
wasters that have failed at everything.
That's why they come on here cuz they
got no one. They got nothing. They just
want to self-relect their failures onto
you. 18 years I saw that account made.
Yeah. See, the thing is, you cannot show
your face and pretend you're not ugly,
but there's certain things that you get
caught out with.
Account made 18 years ago, which proves
you're an old man. I was [ __ ] 10
years old. Um, the fact that you was on
YouTube Christmas, so there's certain
things that you can't hide, bro. You
will never show your faces. Yeah,
because you know you're ugly, but you
know, we can catch you out on [ __ ]
you know, 18 years ago that account was
made. If you click on the accounts, it tells you
18 years. That's an old man, bro. That's
an old waster on that account.
I was 10. I was 10 years old.
So that's how you know that these are
old wasters like that are doing this
sad people that ain't got nothing. So
anyways, what what's the solution, bro?
What's the solution to this problem? Steven Howard.
It's got to be tried to join the
industry, isn't it?
I might get a subo. Oh no, they're
closing till the first, aren't they? [ __ ]
Yeah, they're closing for the first.
Your account was made 18 years ago.
So, you definitely don't like that Sydney, Steven.
Get a KFC.
No, I don't know what I'm getting, bro.
ready to be careful with my um gums and [ __ ]
No, you don't like her. No,
I'm trying to think what I could do cuz
I don't want to go out drinking. I can
live without drinking, bro. I don't care
about drinking anymore. I'm like done, bro.
Yeah, you asking.
Yeah, you asking, Mr. 18year-old
account. [ __ ] waster. 18 years
account. That's more than half of my life.
Yeah, you are skin. You are a skin boy. Self projecting.
Stop talking about yourself like that.
Not nice. Mr. 18year-old account. 18
years. My dad was still alive. 18 years ago.
18 years ago. My [ __ ] My dad was
still alive, bro. I was a I was a [ __ ] child. 18-year-old account.
I was probably nine to be fair. I could
have even been nine.
Sat on YouTube on an 18year-old account.
What a waster.
What a [ __ ] waster.
So, what you going to say that you're
not old? Are you going to deny the fact
that you're an old man?
Are you going to deny the fact that
you're an old man, bro?
You sad sad bastard. Yeah,
>> just type nude. She's got nude. Steven
Howard. If you type her name and nudes
on Google images, it comes up.
But yeah, people that said that Chevro
Cole thing, that was definitely copying
because I didn't know about this this woman's name.
I didn't know about her before I said
that. I'm not a little copycat. Never
liked Rihanna. I never liked Rihanna. I
never liked Chevel Cole. I'm not a copycat.
Never ever copy the crowd. They're just
[ __ ] celebrities that are put on a
pedestal, bro, for no reason. They're
just [ __ ] celebs that for some reason
they're put on a pedestal.
And there's nothing special about them, you know.
The the thing with this housemmaid one
is I saw the acting and I saw the sex scenes.
So obviously that was that.
I've never put any of these celebs on a
pedestal, bro. Ever.
Cuz I'm not a copycat.
Yeah, you need to stop calling yourself
a M, old man.
You need to stop calling yourself a M.
You need to stop putting yourself down,
lad. Come on, bro. We're almost in a new year.
Still ain't got an email uh messenger.
You need to stop calling yourself a M.
You need to think of some different
comebacks for yourself, you know.
Yeah. I can't believe you people have
been on here for years repeating
yourselves. You really are autistic, is it?
Sat on here putting yourself down,
calling yourself a m. It's not It's not
good, bro. It really, really, really isn't good.
Sat on here calling yourself a m when
we've all seen Listen, listen. Remember
the bomb and all of these other people
that used to call me a m and what they
ended up looking like?
Fat and ugly. That's why it doesn't
bother me because we know the real you.
old, fat, ugly people with nothing.
That's why it doesn't bother us, you
little clowns. Cuz we all know what you
people are about here. We all know what
you people are about on here, brother.
Fat, lonely, ugly, 18year-old account
trying to bring people down on your level.
We know what you people are about now,
brother. It doesn't bother us.
You hate the fact that you're old and
ugly and you can't change it. I know
these people better than they know
themselves. You're old. You're ugly. You
got nothing going for yourselves. So,
you try to bring people down to your
level. That's what you do. That's what
you people do, bro.
That's generally what you people do.
Oh, you still there, Steven Howard?
You still there, bro?
So yeah, like these people are saying
that I've got a [ __ ] life. What makes my
life [ __ ] Because I don't go out
drinking every week anymore cuz I don't
want to deal with toxic women.
Yeah. Do you remember when you people
was on YouTube Christmas?
Yeah. Hey, do you remember when you
people was on YouTube Christmas?
Yeah, you are the M. Are you just going
to keep calling yourself a M?
Are you going to keep putting yourself
down and bullying yourself? Or do I have
to get you gone?
If you keep putting yourself down and
calling yourself a M, I'm going to have
to ban you, bro, because we can't have
this kind of negativity on my channel.
So, what makes my life [ __ ] then,
Stephen Howard? Because I don't go out
drinking every week.
Yeah, of course she was. Bye-bye. Now,
so like what makes my life [ __ ] because
I don't go out drinking every week.
I honestly don't know what to do, bro.
Steven Howard, I honestly don't know
what I'm going to do, bro. If this if
this porn thing don't work,
I'm being serious. I don't want to go I
don't want to go out and try again, bro.
I don't I refuse to.
I refuse to, bro.
It's toxic. It's very, very, very toxic.
What What we going to do, bro? You know
what I mean? What are we going to do?
I get no mood swings. I feel stable. I
do what I need to do now. I couldn't do
any of that stuff when I was dating, bro.
I couldn't do any of that stuff when I was dating.
You know what I mean? Like trying to
date and you know what I mean? Like I
couldn't do I couldn't do any of that
stuff, bro. It was always just bringing
you down, bringing you down, bringing
you down, bringing you down, you know?
You know what I mean? Steven Howard, bro. So,
and it's not money. This Joseph don't
know what he's talking about. I've got
money. I can do what I want, bro. And
even if I didn't have money, I can make
money. Yeah. These people don't know
anything. It's not about money, bro. I
just You just get to a point where you
think like, "Fuck that, bro.
What I do every winter, I stay for one
month or two months and then I do what I
need to do." But I don't know what I'll
be doing, bro. That's what I'm trying to say.
You know, I'm not sure.
That sex scene was triggering, bro. What
the [ __ ] That sex she scene was really triggering.
Well, what what are we going to do then,
bro? Cuz we can't keep trying
and we can't use escorts because I'm not
wearing a condom. See, with Ant-Man,
yeah, he has to he can't use a condom
because of his dick. I don't want to use
a condom, so I won't use an escort.
There's a few reasons why I won't do it
now, cuz obviously I'll [ __ ] and I won't
use do. So, I can't use an escort. And
if I can't join the pool thing, then I'm [ __ ]
The way I see it is, yeah, why would you
have sex with a condom when you don't?
You can get an ST test. You can you can
you can prove that you're both clean.
Why are you going to use a condom and
you don't have to? There's a reason why
people use condoms obviously, but
obviously there's there's ways you can
use it without. That's what STD tests
are for and they give you a certificate
or they do it over text nowadays. So, at
the end of the day, bro, like I'm not
going to it's like getting into the bath
with your clothes on. I'm not doing that.
Which I'm surprised USA is he wanted to
use a condom because why the [ __ ] do you
want to use a condom there? I know the
purpose of them. Obviously, I know the
purpose of them, but I mean, it just to
me, it's like, nah, bro. Nah.
So, I can't use a I wouldn't use a
condom. So, I'm basically [ __ ] Really?
It's bad, bro. You shouldn't have to
think about joining in the porn industry
at 28 years of age, [snorts] to be honest.
Cuz at 28, I'm not, like I said, Stephen
Howard, I'm not 24, 25 anymore. You're
28, you should be settled.
You should be with someone or you should
have some kind, you shouldn't have to go
out trying because you don't have the energy anymore
as as as I once did. And obviously, I
know what it's like and I shouldn't have
to keep doing it, you know?
And then the double standard and I
thought to myself, it's not worth it.
You need to think to yourself, is it
worth it? And it isn't. So,
you're just going to get yourself more
and more depressed and drink more and
more and more. And it's just never ended.
Why do you think I'm fine, bro? I don't
get depressed for nothing. I'm fine, me.
I'm fine, brother. I had a good
Christmas in the end. Yeah.
Like sex. I'd be happy to have it once a
month. I wouldn't even have sex much.
Maybe once a month, maybe a month and a half,
you know. I wouldn't even have sex. I'd
say if you had sex once a month,
that's fine. You don't even need it more
than once a month.
You should be getting it at your age,
you know, when you when you've still got
like when you still got a sex drive.
Once a month, bro. Yeah.
You know, maybe once a month.
You don't need it all the time, bro.
Yeah, once a month.
That's um that's enough. Once a month.
Yeah. That means I've got to go out
again, get played around with again, and
and get [ __ ] over again. And I
shouldn't have to be doing it, bro.
I shouldn't have to be doing it.
So, I don't know what we could do, bro.
What would you do, Stephen Howard? I'm
not keep trying. I'm not trying, bro.
I'm not sure, bro.
It's not about money. It's not about
anything, bro. It's not about anything like that.
It really isn't.
I'm happy I don't have the house now. I
still got money. I've got more than
enough money. I get money. I can make
more money. I don't have that
responsibility anymore. I don't give a
[ __ ] about the house. I've got enough
money, you know,
and obviously it's winter, so I could
save even more money. It's not about
money, bro. It really ain't about money,
you know. Really, really ain't.
So, I don't know what we're going to do.
Why do they have to play these sex
scenes in these horror films? I'll just
stop watching them. If they're all going
to have sex scenes in these horror
films, I'm just going to stop watching them.
I have to look up to see if there any
sex scenes. Um,
>> it was only a 15, you know, Steven, that
that film was only a 15. an amount of
[ __ ] sex scenes was in that film for
a 15 when you've got to be 18 to watch
porn and they [ __ ] ask you for ID
now. There was several different bro
there were there was it was several
and I'd go as far as say it was a
[ __ ] porno to be honest. So you know
that's that's that. But you shouldn't
even you know 15 is um
yeah but then what do I do after Jan and
February? I'm saving. I am saving,
but what am I
going to do, bro? After I save the
money, I'm not going to go out and try again. So,
if I could find someone where I could
just [ __ ] them without a condom and I
had to pay every month, I would do it. I
would do it, bro, and just be done with
the whole thing, I would.
I actually generally generally generally
would I've lost all hope. I'm never
going to find anyone. All women are the
same. We're done with that, bro. We
already know this. But now it's trying
to find an alternative, you know.
But this is obviously the problem, you know.
Yeah. When you give up, you feel so much
better. Steven Howard, when you give up,
bro, you just feel so much better.
so much better, bro.
You feel so much better when you give
up. After like two weeks,
you don't understand how much your mood changes, you know?
You feel so much better, bro. You really do.
I felt so good when I gave up, bro. Like
now, like so good.
When I had to go out with my sister, I
was so depressed, bro. I'm supposed to
be going out New Year's Eve,
but I'm not going to. No, I'm not going
to. But yeah,
I think March the earliest, bro. March the earliest.
[ __ ] hell, man. I don't know, man. I don't know.
It's not good, is it?
It's not good. All this
what to just give up forever in it.
Yeah. Yeah, I used to get mood swings
when I was dating, when I was dealing
with women all the time, the same
[ __ ] over and over and over again.
And then it just stops and then you feel better.
You feel a lot better, bro.
I did anyways.
Don't get lonely, nothing. I don't have
any problems, bro, by myself,
you know, cuz if you can't deal with
people that are normal, that can be
decent, I'd rather not deal with anyone at all.
Maybe that happens as you get older,
bro. But like that's it.
They can't offer you anything but sex.
There's nothing that they can they can
give you, bro. You know.
Yeah. The mood swings are a sign, you
know. They go away, bro. When you give
up, they go away. Yeah. So,
Giving up was the best thing I done, bro.
Felt so stable. I was able to enjoy Christmas
being around people.
Yeah, I saw it, bro. I saw it. Well,
I've seen the notification when I
clicked on it. I was able to enjoy
Christmas as well.
It gets you down. [ __ ] like that. Dating
women, gambling, it gets you down, bro.
But gambling is not even that bad
compared to dating. Steven Howard, you
know, when you compare gambling and
dating, I' I'd go back to gambling. If I
had a choice right now, they say you
either go back to dating or go back to
gambling. I'd go back to gambling
100%, bro. And that and that's saying
something, you know, when somebody would
rather go back to gambling than approaching women
cuz at least with gambling, you can win.
You can get a high.
You get a high, you get an escort or you
you know what I mean? You can go I'd
much rather go back to gambling than
than going back to dating. 100%, bro. 100%.
Yeah, bro. Yeah, let me see what he's saying. Anyways,
by Fruit King, you need to go nonss.
Yeah, just seeing it. Yeah, he just
stole Greavesy's video, man.
M is single for life and I love it.
Yeah, that's self projection.
Yeah, I just went on Timmy's video.
So what do you mean it's a sign then
Steven Howard to just give up forever? basically. Yeah, pretty much. Yeah.
I don't know what you could do, bro.
See, Joseph doesn't understand. It isn't
about money. I can go out. I can gamble.
When you get older, you grow tired of
this [ __ ] I haven't been going out for
[ __ ] 15, 16 months every week. What
the [ __ ] bro?
I don't get bored anymore.
But yeah, you give up with that dating
and watch your mood change in about a week.
No depression, no nothing. You see the world differently.
Yeah, but what what are you going to do
with the money, bro? What are you going
to do with the money? You know,
you're not going to go out trying again.
I won't try again, bro. No.
Yeah, I think sex a month is that's enough, bro.
Life is all about sex and that, but if
you could have sex once a month, I think that's uh
I think that's um
Yeah, that's good. What do you think?
Yeah, the most money I've ever had is
eight grand. I think a lot of that was
wins and [ __ ]
so I'm not sure, bro. Um,
an approach in ages, man. No,
I would never get married even if I met
someone. I don't want anything to do
with women, bro. You don't understand.
Like I said to that account, once you've
met one, you've met them all.
Once you've met one, you've really met
them all, bro.
So, yeah, if you could have someone you
could pay every month and you could [ __ ]
them without a condom, I'd do it.
I would actually do it, bro. And just be
done with the whole thing.
Yeah. Top Pro. Yeah, you could do that.
You have to use a condom though. That's
the thing. I don't want to use a condom. [ __ ] madness. Yeah,
I'm [snorts] not sure.
I need to change my diet as well cuz
obviously my teeth and [ __ ] in it.
Sydney Sweeney. How have I just found
out about this [ __ ] person?
25 million subscribers.
I still need to watch the Spongebob
film. Steven Howard.
Yeah, I still need to watch the Spongebob film.
It's my birthday in April. Steven
Howard, what you getting me?
What are you getting me for my birthday?
I'm getting hungry now, bro.
How does that feel, Steven Howard, that
there's not going to be any more um
there's not going to be any more ISIS? Huh?
One second, bro. Meow.
I fruit king.
I fruit king. Why did Nons leg say that
shovel car was attractive?
Fruit king. Do you remember?
I'm really hungry, you know, bro,
but I need to save some money, bro. So,
I can't really be buying takeaways and [ __ ]
Yeah, but he said that if I don't find
her attractive, I'm gay through King.
I'll just go to the chicken shop. Sorry, lad.
I can't be wasting money.
Yeah, he said if I don't find her
attractive, I'm gay. Pro king.
No, I don't think she's attractive.
I think Sydney Sweeney is attractive.
The housemaid. The one from the
No, I don't I don't like shovel car, bro. Never did.
Never did me. Never. No. No, bro.
He he he he said that she's attractive
just to fit in though. Freaking He just
said it to show off.
No, you mad. I'm not having a sub.
That's disgusting, bro.
I need to stop drinking as much Coke.
So, I don't know what I'm going to have.
I'm going to have to drink water for a bit.
That's stinking, bro.
That is [ __ ] stinking.
But what? No, I don't love them. Hell
lions. They're [ __ ] ranked. It's not
pork. I won't eat it.
So, do you think if someone don't find
chevel attractive fruit, they're gay?
No, I don't think they're gay. I think
they just got different preferences. No,
they say with fillings in your mouth, it's genetic.
I've had like two fillings. They say
that it is genetic. Yeah.
Yeah, man. I don't know. I'm [ __ ] I'm
hungry as [ __ ]
Well, I can go about food, but I don't
really I'm not really asked.
So, what are we going to do about this
women thing, Steven Howard?
What? You don't understand how someone
cannot find her attractive?
She's got no ass. She's got no tits.
She just doesn't do it for me.
Fruit King. She doesn't do it for me, mate.
Nah, she doesn't do it for me, mate. Not my copper.
She might be yours, lad. That's fine.
She's just not mine.
So, what are you going to do about this
women thing, Stephen? I would lad,
you can see why I don't want to try again, right?
You can see why I don't want to try again.
McDonald's. Yeah, I could do,
but I can't really be drinking Coke at the minute
cuz I got a toothache. I need to stop
drinking Coke and [ __ ] bro. I need to stop.
Yeah, it's probably my diet as well, to
be fair. I need a better diet, bro. Like
a nice salmon and veg and just drink
water. Yeah, we were saying about uh
this women's situation, Tiger. I'm not
sure what I'm going to do, lad.
Cuz I can't try anymore cuz obviously
it's the same [ __ ] They just lead you
on and play games. So now I was thinking
of joining the porn industry, trying to
join the porn industry.
I'm not sure what what what we can really do
cuz I've given up with dating for the
bit uh for a moment, Tiger, and I feel a
lot better. No more mood swings. No more depression.
I tell you the worst pain though was
that her tentonitis,
mate. That pain I had in my foot. That
was worse than a toothache.
I think that's got to be worse than a
toothache. [ __ ] You know, I couldn't
walk for six weeks, bro.
Yeah, I need like veg and salmon and [ __ ] bro.
I'm not sure what we what I could do,
lad. I watched this horror film, Tiger
Tiger. I don't know if you're into
horror films. It was called The Housemaid,
and there was like quite a few sex
scenes, and it was just depressing, bro.
It was very depressing. But I don't care
as much anymore.
Tiger, tiger. I'm not sure. I I'd be
happy just to have sex once a month for me
cuz obviously all women are the same.
They they've proven they're all the same
multiple times. But I wouldn't mind
having sex like once a month.
But obviously I can't use escorts cuz I
don't want to wear a condom. So
I'm not sure what you could do. If you
can't join the porn industry, I'm not sure.
And by you, I mean me. I'm not sure. So,
pretty much [ __ ] Didn't you really?
There's so many sex scenes in these
horror films, Tiger. When there's no
need for it.
There's no need for it, lad.
But yeah, my diet is [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
Catches up on you as you as you get
older, Tiger. I think I've only had two feelings. Yeah,
I think you're right, bro, about the
health thing. It's probably cuz my diet
is [ __ ] as well. I tell you what, it was
Tiger. You know them picker mixes. You
know the cherries and the picker mixes
in the cinema.
That's what kicked it off.
Them, bro, will [ __ ] your teeth up.
That's why I try not to eat sweets, you know.
them will [ __ ] you up, bro. Trust me. Yeah,
man. He hates it. Bless you, bro.
No, they won't. Women don't like simps.
Women don't like white knights.
That's the biggest mistake these fools
make. Women don't like white knights.
Women despise white knights and simps.
They don't like them.
And that's another thing, Steven Alward,
is that I don't want to get into a
situation. Yeah. Where I have to if I
get into an argument with someone and
then someone some s tries to get
involved cuz I would just end up
seriously hurting someone.
I would just end up seriously seriously
hurting someone, bro. And and it's not
worth it. I don't want that toxicity in
my life, bro.
Well, I quit the dating game for a reason,
you know. Yeah, I drink loads of Coke. Tiger Tiger.
That's what [ __ ] me up. Well, I can't
go to the dentist anyways for like a
week and a bit. I've already booked an
appointment. So, I think if I drink water
and clean up my diet, I think it should
be all right. Yeah.
Yeah, I need to stop that Coke. I mean,
the McDonald's Coke is not as bad cuz
you drink it out of a straw, isn't it?
But yeah, it will kill you, bro, as you
get older. Catches up on you.
But yeah, I'm not I'm not sure, Tiger,
what you could do about this situation, bro,
about getting a sex life and stuff. I'm
not sure you can do anything about it. I
don't think you can.
I don't think you can, bro.
I don't really care. It doesn't make me
depressed, but it'd be nice to have a
sex life, but obviously you can't get that.
Um, I went to cinema by myself. I wasn't
bothered until I saw that sex scene. So,
A detox on Coke. I can't live without
Coke, but I'm going to have to for my own sake.
If I stop drinking Coke for two week two
days, I get headaches. I've done it
before when Mr. Chan used to be on
YouTube. When I went to the gym, I drunk
nothing but water. But you start getting headaches.
I start getting headaches when I don't
have like sugar. But I'm going to have
to obviously I find a substitute.
Mate, you're lucky to get an appointment
on the NHS. Tiger Tiger. That's not even
that bad to be honest, mate. You're
lucky to even get one on the NHS. And I
think it's No, it's because they're on
holiday and that and they don't come
back. Normally you get appointment the
same day. But that's still not bad,
mate, for NHS.
It's hard to get NHS dentist nowadays.
So, but the country is a joke. You know
what I found so mad yesterday, Tiger
Tiger, is I went to go to the bookies.
They normally open at 8:00. They open at
10:00 and I'm thinking, okay, yeah, it
might be boxing day, but there's loads
and loads of football playing. Then
Sundays, they open the same time.
And then I was like, I don't want to go
all the way back home and then come back
out. I'm thinking, why is it opening 2
hours later when on a Sunday they open
the same time?
The country's [ __ ] bro.
You know what I find so mad is how like
a supermarket won't open until 11:30 on
a Sunday, but bookies open at 8:00. So,
you could gamble your money before going
into a supermarket and buying a pint of
milk. There's people not see what's
wrong with that. And yeah, you can say,
"Oh, get a pint of milk from a corner
shop." But no, get a proper pint of milk
from a [ __ ] Morrison's where you know
it's not expired. How can you go into a
place and gamble your money before you
can go and buy a pint of milk? That just
seems crazy to me. I don't know about
anyone else, but
these places are open. These bookies
around me open at about 7:00 in the morning
and at at Sunday is about 7:30, 8 maybe.
What the [ __ ]
The country annoys me, tiger, tiger. But
yeah, um, you're lucky to get a dentist
on the NHS, mate.
And it's cuz a holiday. Normally, it's
not that long. Normally, it is the same
day, but better late than never.
But it should be all right if I stop
drinking the coconut.
Yeah. Where do you live? Tiger. Tiger.
Do you live up north? I remember you
from years ago when I was like 22.
You've been on here years. You have.
That's all right, bro. As long as you're
not a hater.
I can't stand these haters on here, bro.
They're just [ __ ] haters. [snorts]
I'm trying to think what I can eat.
I like going to a dentist though. Don't
I I I appreciate it whenever I get a
dentist appointment. I do appreciate it
cuz I know how hard it is to get an
appointment for free.
So I appreciate it, bro. You know,
dentist is next level. It's hard to get
a [ __ ] appointment in this country.
I find everything bad about this country
though. The women, the people, the
waiting around for things, the
government having to fight for
everything. I find loads of things wrong
with this country. Tiger,
you know, if the weather if the weather
was better and the people weren't such
[ __ ] it would actually be a good
country. You know, a lot of the country,
the people ruin it.
The entitled [ __ ] ruin it. Um, you
know, if there was better weather and,
you know, it's it would actually be an
all right country, you know,
>> but there were so many [ __ ] in this
country. Oh my god. Like you, you know,
come to London, you you you'll see it.
So many entitled
[ __ ] It's Yeah.
Really, bro. Really,
it wouldn't be a bad country.
Obviously, not everyone's a [ __ ]
here, obviously. But, you know, there's
there's a lot of [ __ ] So, yeah.
What could I eat today?
I could have like fish and chips and a
tea with no sugar.
Sugar is a trigger for me, you know. So,
no, I don't want fish and chips. It's
too greasy. I don't I don't know what
I'm going to have. I'll just go to the
chicken shop, get some wings or something. Yeah. Yeah,
I've spoken to him. Yeah.
We got some wings, bro.
So yeah, I was going to go out New
[snorts] Year's Eve Steen Howard, but no.
[ __ ] [snorts] that, brother.
No, we got corn flakes, but obviously I
can't have the cornflakes cuz the sugar.
I can't have cornflakes without sugar. So yeah,
I [snorts] don't know what I'm going to
do, bro, about this women thing. Yeah.
I don't know what I'm going to do, bro.
I can't have corn face cuz of the um
sugar in it. So that's not an option.
I don't know what I'm going to do, bro.
Can't keep trying. No, [clears throat]
that is definitely not an option.
I don't know, mate. I really don't know. Oh god.
H. It's a hard one, is it? Stephen Howard.
Yeah. So, what you what can you do then?
What can you [ __ ] do, bro?
I can have maybe McDonald's today, but I
do need to change my diet. Seriously,
bro, cuz I it will end up killing me, bro.
I'm trying to see what I can eat.
Yeah. How you going to get sex though, Stephen Howard?
I might not even eat until really later, bro.
Don't really fancy anything.
Yeah, but you've got to use a condom, Steven Howard.
You've got to use a condom. That's the problem.
I think little [ __ ]
I wish I had hot dogs. I would have made
a hot dog.
You like Joe F. Steven Howard
is Jo one of the bro one of the
is he one of the bros.
He just needs to stop trying to troll me, bro.
That's all this guy needs to do is just
stop trying to troll me with these fake wins
and then that's it, bro. And yeah,
I'm so hungry. I don't know what I'm
going to have, bro.
I had Five Guys the other day. Five Guys
is lush. Oh, Five Guys is lovely. That's
what I could have instead of a That's
what I could have instead of a Coke. A
milkshake, isn't it?
Cuz obviously Yeah. There's no sugar in
milkshakes, is there?
So, I could just have milkshakes.
Yeah. Obviously that's not going to [ __ ]
your teeth up, is it? Milk. No. Nah. Not
like Coke. Be very surprised.
I could have a five, guys.
I'd love a Coke, bro, but I got to think
of my health, you know. So,
but Five Guys is expensive as [ __ ]
Yeah, but not as much as Coke though.
Not as much as Coke.
Not as much as Coke, mate. Coke is the worst.
So, what substitute drink could I have?
I can't just drink water.
I love Five Guys, bro.
Five guys is expensive.
I need to save money, bro. Can't be
wasting money, brother.
No, bro. It's still bad for you. And it
tastes disgusting. No, no, no, no. It's
still bad for you, bro. It's still acid and [ __ ]
No, no, no, no, no. It's It's still bad.
Maybe like a water or something with low
sugar. Like flavored water with low
You basically need to stop having sugar basically.
Otherwise, it's probably going to keep happening.
No, it's just as bad for you cuz it's
acid in the coke. Uh water is the same.
I don't know then.
I'm trying to think what I could eat.
I'm just going to have to have wings and water.
Just have some wings and water, bro. Straighten it. basically. Yeah.
If I change my diet, I think this tooth
thing will go away.
So, you really don't like that Sydney
Sweeney. No, Steven Howard, you really
don't like her now.
Don't like her at all.
Indonesian guy likes all of her [ __ ] pictures.
Guy is a creep. He is a creep.
That must be his type then when he was
talking about belongs and [ __ ]
Yeah, I think it was just that sex scene
for me, bro.
What do you say? should look like USA is he
or does she look like USA? Is it? Yeah.
[snorts] Well, she's blonde.
I had a nice dinner at my sisters, you
know, bro. She made a really nice
dinner, bro. Oh my god.
So, what do you think, Stephen? Howard?
Hot wings of water.
Hot wings of water. Is it?
See, Laney, you know when Laney has tea?
She never has sugar. She never has
sugar. So, if she had sugar all of them
years, her teeth would have fell out a
long time ago, bro.
So, what do you think? Like some chicken
and some water, Stephen. How with
chicken chips and water? Yeah.
Get a better diet and you and it should get better.
The pain should stop. Hopefully,
it's better now. You just need to stay
away from sugar. Just stay away from it,
bro. It's not worth it.
So painful, man.
Yeah, I can't have tea without sugar. I
have now. I had my tea without sugar. I
have to get used to it.
Even if it's for a couple of weeks. Yeah.
Do you miss USA? Izzy Steven Howard
cuz where I don't eat properly and that
it could be the reason for my mouth and
that where I don't eat properly and
you get miserable and that my sleeping
patterns all over the place. They could
be what like that tiger said.
Whereas if you eat some fresh food with
water and that you wake up at the same
time you eat good, it should get better.
Should get better.
Maybe you don't even need a filling.
Maybe it's it's Yeah. What he was what
he was saying.
Yeah. It catches up on you though. It
as you get older, mate.
Yo, I used to eat Stephen uh Stephen,
you remember uh you might not know it
cuz it's a London bakery, but you know
Totten [clears throat] cakes, I used to
eat five of them a day. Yeah. When I was
like 15, 16, 17. I used to eat like I
used to eat five of them a day. Every
single day, bro. Couldn't do it now. No.
Could not do it now, mate. I'd die.
I used to go out drinking every
Thursday, Saturday. Could I do that now? No.
I couldn't do that now, bro. No way. I
don't even like drinking anymore, bro. Yeah, bro.
[snorts] You like Joseph Farra Steven Howard?
>> Yeah, Joseph Farra is all right. He just
needs to stop stop showing fake wins.
Stop showing fake [ __ ] wins.
I know. I'm surprised I still have teeth.
Everyone's different, I guess, isn't it?
Yeah. I'm just going to get some chicken.
So, what do you think I can I I should
do about this women situation, Dusty?
Yeah, he knows he's Yeah, but Joseph F
knows he's a nons lover. I call him a
nons lover. That's my little nick That's
my little nickname for him.
He's a little nons.
He knows what his name is, bro. He's a
little nonsover, Dusty.
There's nothing you can do, is it?
You keep trying, you get more depressed
or you give up and stay more stable.
What can you do? There's nothing you can
do. I don't want to go out trying again,
bro. I'm not I don't really want to. I'm
tired of it all.
I'm bored of it. Um,
yeah, I know. I have given up. I have
given up. But how are you going to have
a sex life, Dusty?
Yeah, that's why I gave up. I've given
up. I feel much better, Dusty, for it. I
feel a lot better that I've given up.
But I want sex like once a month. Once a
month maximum is fine for me. You can
get on with your life. You can have sex
every month. I can live with that, bro.
Sex once a month and never ever have a
relationship. Never have to talk to anyone again.
What do you think, Dusty?
Why did that woman on Reddit not reply
to me when I said that? She said, "Oi,
listen, Dusty." She said, "It go Jim. It
will build your confidence and stop
chasing every girl for sex. Don't you
want something more out of life?" And I
said, "Women have a sex life, so I I
should I've put more than enough effort
into it. Lack of sex makes you
depressed, and I'd be happy to have sex
once a month." And she didn't reply back.
She knows I'm right, in it.
You more people should have gave up ages
ago, Dusty. It's a Mugs game.
It's a Mug's game, bro. It's worse than gambling.
Trying today is worse than gambling, Dusty.
It's a Mugs game.
With gambling, you win sometimes and
there's no double standards.
Think about it, bro. What's What's more
of a muggers game to you? Come on.
Gambling is way less of a mug's game
than dating women, bro. You know it. I
What's today? Saturday.
Dusty. I like shovel coal.
Dusty. Dusty. Dusty. I like
[ __ ] hell, bro. That'll never get
old, you know. Nasty.
Nasty. I like shovel.
Yeah, little copycat.
Anyone that's not blocked by N's legs,
you shouldn't trust. That's what Kieran
said to me, Dusty. That's what Kieran
said to me, Dusty. Anyone that's not
blocked by N's legs, don't trust them.
Yeah, I agree with that. Do you
You still there, Steven Howard? I can't
believe you've been alive for that long. Damn.
I do need to get some food in a minute.
So much self projection on this
community. M is single for life and I
love it. So much self projection on here, bro.
After today, I won't be on for a little
bit, bro. Don't expect me to go live every day.
Don't [ __ ] expect it, bro.
I'm gone anyways. Yeah. Peace.