Just checking to see if you lot are
still in YouTube. No life. [sighs] Just checking.
Just wanting to check see if it's the same people.
I couldn't believe that earlier, bro.
All of them accounts I unlocked and they
still couldn't bully me. I'm still back for more.
You definitely definitely did not get
any of my money stopped. You sad little
bastard. You did not get one penny of my
income stopped and I've still got more
money than you.
Yeah, straight on YouTube. UK asylum.
Straight on YouTube, are we? You're
straight on YouTube, lad.
You're just another red star.
Yeah. Another little stalker.
You still on YouTube, lad? My mouth
feels better today. It doesn't hurt.
I woke up. It didn't hurt. It's cuz I
laid off the sugar. I just made myself a
tea. I didn't put any sugar in it. Pet
really can't have sugar at the moment. No,
no, I can't have sugar for the moment.
Now, Red Star is definitely definitely a stalker.
A skinn stalker. Like the skin one. His
boyfriend. The new one. The skin one.
He's just like his boyfriend.
Red's just like his boyfriend. Both
skin. Both stalkers. They've got
something in common. They got something
in common. They both got no money
between them. They both got nothing in
life. Just stalking cuz they're losers.
They're two losers. The two all time
Yeah, I'm good, bro.
Yeah, I'm just drinking a tea with no
sugar. I have to lay off the sugar. I
didn't eat today, bro. I just woke up.
I didn't eat. Didn't even feel that hungry.
Red Star is a proper proper stalker in
it. He's a proper low life. That's an
act of a jealous man. That Red Star is
so jealous of me, bro. Just like Nons.
I've never known so many people to be
jealous of Peter Belly Bob.
All cuz you're younger and better
looking at them. All cuz you're younger
and better looking than these people.
It's a [ __ ] madness, mate. It's a [ __ ] madness.
Yeah, you never stopped any of my money.
But I stopped your boyfriend going to
events for four weeks, but you
definitely definitely didn't stop any of
my money, matey. You did stop a penny of my money.
And I can swear my dead dad and my mom
on that one. You did not stop any of my money, bro.
And I've still got more money than you.
This is what I was saying to them
yesterday, but they didn't understand
it. Brother, where's my passport? My
passport's in the drawer right next to
me. Why are you asking that?
Why are you asking stupid questions?
Uh, I've got a passport in my drawer.
No, I'm not proving it. I don't need to
prove anything to you.
Nope. If you don't think I've got a
passport, you don't think I've got a
passport. Okay, bro. I've got a passport
right next to me. I don't need to prove
anything to you, bro.
You know, I'm not showing you my
passport. I don't need to prove myself to anyone.
Okay. I can't prove it. Okay, good.
Okay, you keep telling yourself that.
Yeah. Yeah. I ain't got a passport.
Okay. You keep telling yourself that.
I'm not prove myself to people. We done
this yesterday, bro. I said if you want
me to prove receipts and stuff, you show
your face. That was the deal. If you if
you're not going to do that, I'm not
showing you anything.
You can call me skint, you can serve,
not got a passport, that's on you, bro.
I don't give a [ __ ] I'm easy.
Yeah. Yeah. Really? Did she? Okay. Good
for you, bro. Yeah. Did she really?
I don't need to prove myself to any of
you people. This is what these people
need to understand on here that I'm not
here to prove myself to idiots. And the
sooner they get that in, you know, in
their in their [ __ ] thick head, the
better. I'm not show I'm not showing
anything to you people. No money, no
passport, no nothing. I will not be
showing anything. No receipts, nothing.
So been there, done that. These people
will talk [ __ ] no matter what. Yeah.
When are you people actually going to
get a life and stop harassing people on
the internet that you don't know? It's
getting really boring now.
You know, it's getting really boring. Do
you reckon you you people could stop
your jealousy in 2026? Do you reckon for
one year you can stop being jealous of
people that you don't know or you just
going to continue to just be a low life?
You know, I'm just wondering, bro. This
is just a question.
I'm [ __ ] I don't know what
I just want to know why you people do
it. Are you jealous? Are you disabled?
Like, I'm I'm trying to understand why
you people do what you do, man.
I don't know what I'm going to eat.
Well, you won't be able to secretly
record because you get searched and that
trial is not happening in 3 years. So,
that's not happening anyways.
Yeah, that's not happening. But, okay.
Why are you so jealous of me, bro? Can I
ask you a question? Like, why are you
people so jealous of me when I ask you
that? Cuz you don't do it for reaction.
Because even when you get ignored, you
still do it and [ __ ] I just want to know.
I just want to know why you're so
jealous of Peter Belly
sat on here every day harassing
strangers that you don't know. Is it cuz
they're better looking than you? Is it
because you're disabled? Is it cuz
you're jealous of something in your
life? Is it cuz your skin?
I'm just I'm just wondering why you
people do what you do every day. I'd
love to get the answer.
I didn't eat today, Bob. Bill, I didn't
No, I didn't eat.
I just woke up.
Cuz I just woke up. Well, not so long.
I went seven miles.
I'm kind of hungry now. I don't know.
I have to be careful with my teeth while
I eat. I don't know.
You don't know, bro.
I don't know what to get.
Word. Definitely didn't get Peter Belly
sublet money stopped. Definitely didn't.
And LJ didn't either. He's another skint
one. LJ is another skint one begging for
donations. Why does this guy pretend
that he's got money when he don't? I
woke up thinking about this. Why does he
pretend that he's got money when he's
literally skint as [ __ ] Coming on here
acting like, "Oh, I own five
properties." The guy is literally skint.
I don't know why he comes on here
pretending he's got money when he don't.
He ain't got no money. He ain't got no
properties. He's skint on benefits,
begging for money. I don't know why or
people that disabled, they can't believe
they they they don't know what he's doing, bro.
The guy is literally [ __ ] skint.
The guy has not got any money. The guy
is on the bones of his ass.
I know that. UK asylum. I know that.
This is what I've been trying to say
that I've been trying to explain this.
The the the the the
um the landlord was trying to get it
back for like years, bro.
But he's still saying that he's took it,
but he hasn't. Because if someone
stopped my income, they would be getting killed.
You know why? Okay. Why do you think I
done what I done to legs the posters?
Even though people will pretend that I
never done anything because they're
jealous of me. But we all know what I
done and why I done it.
I went to his [ __ ] area. I stopped
him leaving the house for two weeks. And
people will make up stories that, oh,
he's had one over on me. When that's not
what happened. I went up, I put posters.
I had him running to the police for his
life, right? And that was because they
were trying to stop my benefits. That's
cuz they kept harassing me and trying to
stop my benefits. And it was a very
small amount of money, bro.
I said, "You don't ever try and [ __ ]
stop my money, you [ __ ] skin [ __ ]
with your fat, ugly girlfriend. You
[ __ ] skimp bastard. And I stopped him
leaving the house for [ __ ] weeks cuz
the ugly [ __ ] kept harassing me. The
virgin ugly [ __ ] with a nod stand with
the no money in the bed seat kept
harassing me. Yeah. And I had the
benefit kept calling me up. And this was
a small amount of money as well. That's
not the point. That's a small amount of
money. You don't [ __ ] start harassing
people trying to get people's money
stopped. You [ __ ] ugly ratfaced lanky
virgin [ __ ] And I said that as well,
bro. Yeah. And what did I do? I went all
that way and I put posters up cuz you're
going to learn, you skin little virgin,
you [ __ ] ugly rat [ __ ] that you're
not going to [ __ ] with people anymore. Yeah,
you [ __ ] virgin. You know what? Do
you remember what I said, bro? And how
much money was that? A small amount of
money. Yeah. It's not the point. I had
these people calling me up. Yeah.
Asking, "Oh, you need to show this. You
need to show that." And I was like,
"Mate, if I've got to do this, someone's
paying for it." And then I done the
posters. Even though Joseph Farra, cuz
he's jealous of me and other people will
pretend it never happened, will pretend
that I never had the [ __ ] not leave his
house for 2 weeks. People will pretend
that never happened. Because obviously
when when people are jealous of you,
when you're not fat and ugly like that,
like them, when you're not fat and ugly
like these people, they get jealous.
This is what it is with these people in
this community, these skin people, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, it doesn't matter, brother. It
doesn't matter. You don't come to the
internet harassing people and think you
call the shots. Yeah, I weren't going to
do it. Anything, but I weren't going to
do that, bro. But and when I had the
benefit people start calling me up cuz
of him and his boyfriend, I said, "Fuck
that. I'm doing posters. [ __ ] that."
And the first time I didn't even like
get arrested properly. So, I don't I
didn't mind that, bro. I got a free ride
from the police and the police dropped
me back. I don't mind, bro. It was worth
it. Not having you leave your house for
two weeks because of me was worth it.
Was absolutely worth it, bro.
Yeah. I had the benefit people call me
up, bro. I was like, "No, [ __ ] this.
This little skint in the bedit with the
no money in it is going to pay. This
little grand a month boy is going to pay."
Yeah. And that was a small amount of
money. That was like 180 pound, brother.
Oh, I won't get found guilty. I've got
everything to what he's done. All of the
harassment. Oh, trust me. I've got
everything to this little virgin. This
little skinned ugly virgin
with the loser with women, the loser
with [ __ ] money. He's a loser with
women. He's a loser with everything.
He's a loser with style. I've got
everything what this little [ __ ] has
done, lad. Yeah, it will do. It will do.
I've got everything this little virgin has done.
This little skid one. See what I mean?
And have you noticed UK silent, bro?
They always go to police in the end. They're losers.
They go to the police because they're
losers. Again, another thing that they
won't say. They're losers. Yeah.
They go to the police because they can't
handle you. They're losers because you
own them. Anyone that has to go to the
police on someone, you own them, bro.
They had to get the law involved because
you bullied them that mad. How can you
come on here and say you bully someone
when you cry to the police? When you run
to the police when you can't leave your
house? Was you bullying someone when had
you not leaving your house? had you not
going to events. Red stores got it all
mixed up, brother. I had him not leaving
his house. They never got any of my
money stopped. They tried to get my
money stopped two times. They tried it
two times. Yeah. In the space of two
years. Yeah. They tried to get my
benefit money stopped. They did not get
any of my money stopped. Yeah. I had him
stopping going to his events. I stopped
his boyfriend going to events because of
this mug. This mug here is the one that
caused it. They're getting themselves confused, bro.
They're getting themselves severely,
severely confused. I had this [ __ ] going
to the police over me cuz he couldn't
handle me. I'm too tough. You can't
[ __ ] virgin did not stop any of my money.
Did not stop any of my money. You tried
to stop my money twice. You did not stop
my [ __ ] money, bro. You did not stop
any of it. I explained it all yesterday, bro.
Cuz somebody would have been paying just
like Nonsex paid for. We're trying to
get £180 stopped. It's not the point. It
could be 20 pound, bro.
Who are these little skint virgin [ __ ]
to try to stop any of your money? Who
are these little low-life virgins with
no money in the bedset trying to [ __ ]
stop you, bro? You stop your money. [ __ ]
that. Doesn't matter if it was £180.
Buddy's buddy, bro.
It was the whole point of it, Dusty.
That's why I done That's why I went and
done the uh the posters.
I'm [ __ ] hungry now, bro.
It's not the point. It could be 20 pound, bro.
Don't know what I want, bro. I got headache.
I didn't wake up with a toothache. I
think it's because I've laid off the sugar. Dusty.
Yeah. Where I've laid off the sugar.
Yeah. It's It's all right now for now.
Well, they tried, bro. They tried. Well,
I think they were trying to get my other
money stopped, but obviously they're two
different departments, isn't it?
Yeah, it's two different departments.
So, I I I think their intention was to
try to get the other money stopped, but
obviously uh they couldn't because um
yeah, they're two different departments.
So, that's what I think it was, bro. But
it doesn't matter how much it was. It
was £180. £180. £180. These people are
not going to [ __ ] Bro, it's because
their skin. It's because they're jealous
of me, bro. They've been doing it for years. Empire,
how far is it? Uh, maybe an hour.
Nope. You ain't found a bird for me. I
don't I don't go near women. Women are
evil. I watched another approach video
today on Instagram. Another stuckup [ __ ]
I might put these videos up with this
guy approaching. They're so stuck up.
I didn't give them any information.
But these people are sad, lonely skinned
people. This is why they do this. It's
just like this red star. He's very
lonely, very skinn, very ugly. That's
why you always see him on YouTube, cuz
he ain't got nothing going for himself.
He's a loser. He's a saddest. He's a
sadistic loser. Just like dogs. They're
a pair of losers.
They're a pack of losers. Why do you
think they're on here every day doing
what they do? Because they're skinned
ugly and filled with jealousy. And
that's what they do, bro.
It's because they're jealous of me. The
truth is they're jealous of you. And
they they never admit it to themselves.
They would never ever admit it to
themselves that they are jealous. You're
younger than them. They're you're better
looking than them. They would never
admit it to themsel. That's why they'll
come up and say, "Oh, we just do it for
reaction." when we know that they don't
do it for reaction because we know that
even if you ignore these people, they
still do it. These people are jealous.
It's a tough It's a tough pill to
swallow, but I'm sorry, bro. For people
to be coming on the internet doing this
for years, they've got to be jealous of
something in life. They've got to be.
They've got to be. You know, you you
know, to to be on the internet, right,
doing this from the time you wake up to
the time you go to bed, they've got to
be jealous of something that you've got.
They've got to be, bro. They have got to
be jealous of something in life.
They've got to be jealous of something
that you've got in life. Family, better
looks, more money. It's got to be
something, bro. It's got to be something
that these people are severely jealous of, you know,
because if they had some stuff going for
themselves, they wouldn't be doing this.
They wouldn't have the time to do this.
If they had a job, if they had all of
the things that they're telling you you
don't have, they wouldn't be doing this.
Guys, there's a reason why none of these
people put their cameras on and show
their faces. Because they're fat and
ugly. There's a reason. It's cuz they're
fat and ugly.
It doesn't matter who I stay with. It
You know, that's none of your business.
We're not talking about who we who I stay with.
Why are you asking who people stay with?
Mommy's boy. Okay. Yeah, bro. Okay, whatever.
Uh, okay. I'm unemployed. Can't get a
girl. Okay, I'll correct you. Firstly,
uh, I've got money, firstly. Um,
secondly, I've had more women than you
have. I've shown more women than you
have. Um, oh, skin thing again. Boring.
We've heard all of this before. Just
skin thing. Uh, brother, brother,
brother. Okay. And what are you people?
Middle-aged in a bedit. No girlfriend,
no money. I'm younger. I'm better
looking than you. You people on the
internet. What have you got? No
girlfriend yourselves. No money
yourselves. A bed, no bed, no [ __ ]
house, no girlfriend. Look at you
people. Look at yourselves. What the
[ __ ] have you got on YouTube every day
from the time you wake up to the time
you go to bed? You're below me. You
ain't got no girlfriend. You ain't got
no money. You ain't got no looks. You
ain't got no youth. And you're talking
about me, bro. You're talking about
someone younger and better looking than
you. I've been with more women than you
have. I have been with plenty of women
over the years. More women than any of
you I've ever had combined.
You are [ __ ] old. You're [ __ ] ugly
and fat and you got no money. There's
everything to be jealous of. Okay, you
tell me then. Okay. Okay. You tell me
what you people have got sat on YouTube
every day. You tell me what you people
have got. Okay. Okay. [ __ ] me then.
Okay. Leave me out for a second. Yeah.
Okay. You tell me what you fat ugly
people have got sat on YouTube every
day. Sat on YouTube from the time you
wake up to the time you go to bed.
Where's your girl? Where's your money?
Where's your looks? Brother, you're
below me in every way. Yeah. When you're
talking about me, brother, you're not
adding yourself in it. You are way way
below me. You people are middle-aged.
You're ugly as [ __ ] That's why you
won't put your cameras on. None of you
have got girlfriends. All your goal is
is to try to bring other people down to
your level. This is what these people
do, Cory. Yeah, I'm telling you. But I
was saying this the other day. No, I
don't a football bet. Boxing day. I
don't know 20 pound football bet. I got
two out of four. Yeah.
These ugly people are to bring people
down to death. Fat ugly level. Okay. If
they've got a life, let me ask you this
question. If these people have got a
life, money, why are they sat on YouTube
all day every day? Why are they sat
lying around on YouTube every day? If
they've got Okay, answer me this
question. If you've got a money and
you're above me and there's nothing to
be jealous of. Okay, so why are you sat
on YouTube all day every day? Listen,
Richtor, I've had more women than you.
I'm better looking than you. I'm younger
than you. There's everything to be
jealous of a younger, better-l looking
person that's got more money and has got a life.
This is self-p projection with you
people. Just because I want to stay in
for a month or two months and save
money, I've still got a better life than
you. You know what I'm saying? I've got
a bum. I'm younger. I'm better looking.
I've had more women. I've got more money
than you. I'm in a better position in
life than you. I am better than most of
these people in this community. Don't
talk down on people that's better than
you. Yeah. Without adding your situation.
Brother, you don't have a flat. You
don't have a girlfriend. None of you
have got a girlfriend. Most of you are
still virgins. Listen, I've already had
a girlfriend. You don't have a
girlfriend. You don't have a woman. You
Most of you are virgins. Again, try to
bring people down to their level. You
don't have a girlfriend. You don't have
a woman. None of you people have a
woman. Again, put yourself in this
situation. Yes, I'm this. Yes, I'm that.
You are older. You are uglier. You don't
have a girlfriend. You don't have a
girlfriend. This is what I'm saying.
It's always self-p projection with these
people. They've got no woman, no
girlfriend, and they're talking about
someone younger and better looking.
These fat, ugly people don't even leave
the house. These jobless ugly people,
Cory don't even leave the house. They've
got everything to be jealous of. They're
sat lying around on YouTube, rotting
away on YouTube cuz they've got no one.
They were on YouTube Christmas, by the
way. I proved that these people was on
YouTube Christmas. They were on YouTube
Christmas. On YouTube Christmas. Yeah,
they were on YouTube Christmas, bro.
On YouTube Christmas. And I proved this
as well. Yeah, I proved this in a
roundabout way that these people's on
YouTube Christmas. Like, there's a
reason why none of these people put
their cameras on because they're [ __ ]
ugly. They can't even deny the fact that
they're fat and ugly. They can't even
deny it, bro. They can't even. Bro, I
put my camera on yesterday. I was
arguing with about 20 of these people,
Kie. And not one of them and not one of
them could put their cameras on. Not one
of these fat people could put their
cameras on. [laughter]
It's a madness. I've slept with more
women than you. You don't need to know
that. And I abandoned you now. You little self-reflector.
Self reflectors. Self-reflectors.
about what's there to be jealous of. I'm
younger than you. I'm better looking
than you. I've got more money than you.
I've had more women than you. What are
you people? Fat and ugly. Have you
noticed they don't add theirself in this
situation? Um Kyrie, they never add
themsel in it. You people are fat,
lonely, ugly idiots. [ __ ] [ __ ]
that ain't got a pot to piss in. You're
ugly fat people that ain't got a pot to
piss in. And you're talking about other
people. How can any of these people try
to judge anyone else? This is what I
don't understand. How do these ugly
single people with no girlfriend try to
judge other people?
Like, it's one thing [ __ ] God judging
you. Yeah. Or someone else, but who are
these people that are lower than you?
They're the lowest of the low, these
disabled mongos trying to judge you.
They've never had a girlfriend. They've
never had sex. They're fat, old, and
ugly. They ain't got no life. They've
literally got no life. You know why I'm
on YouTube, bro? Cuz I'm saving, you
know, for a couple of months. You know,
I'm taking a break from dating and I
can't be bothered with it. Okay. What's
these reason? What's these people's
reasons? They've been on it eight years,
non-stop. Eight years doing this. What's
their reason? Because they've got
nothing. They got no one. They've got
nobody. Just like Red Star, fat, ugly, a
loser, nobody, no life. They're all the
same on here, bro. This is why you don't
really see me on here much, Cory. You'll
see I won't be on here for like a week
or whatever. This is the same [ __ ] with these people.
Ugly, fat, middle-aged people that ain't
got no life. It's the same on here, bro.
All the time with these people. Yeah.
eat today. Call me. I haven't ate today,
bro. They're all projectors.
They are literally all cell projectors.
I haven't ate, bro.
Yeah, I was thinking about ordering
food, but I don't know what to get.
My mouth's been better. I don't have a
toothache now cuz obviously I cut down
on I cut down on the sugar.
Yeah, I've had to cut down on the sugar
cuz of my teeth and that.
Yeah, I was just watching Ed, bro. I was
just watching Ed.
Yeah, but at least Ed Yeah, but at least
Ed trolls are funny. They're not repeaters.
No, I just been drinking tea and water.
tea without sugar cuz of my teeth and
that in it.
I'm trying to think what I could have
lad. Yeah, I had a nasty toothache. I
think I need a filling now. I just don't
drink sugar. I'm not drinking sugar for
now, bro. For a little while.
It makes a difference. It's definitely
the sugar that's uh that does that.
It's definitely the sugar cuz I didn't
wake up with a toothache or anything.
So, it's definitely the sugar cuz I cut
down on sugar.
Yeah, I've been on kick, bro. Maybe I
just hadn't noticed it to be fair.
Look, bro. I'm in my little gowny. I'm
in my little gowny, bro. Have you
noticed? None of these people can show their faces. faces, bro.
None of them can show their faces.
Not one of them can show their faces.
Yeah, I've seen it. I seen it, bro.
Yeah. Yeah, I've seen that. I have
actually seen that where they get
swatted. Yeah, I see Ed get his haircut.
Yeah. And they were trying to get him
swatted in the [ __ ] um uh the barber
shop. And I've seen them get swatted.
I've seen it, bro. I've seen it. Yeah.
Yeah. I've seen it. I've seen it, bro.
I've seen it. I've seen it. They tried
to get him swatted in the barbers as
well. I was just waiting it like you can
see him here like he was getting his
haircut, bro. Yeah. And he was closing
his eyes and any moment you're waiting
for the police to just barge in it.
But the police didn't come that time.
But I have seen it. I've seen it. I've
seen it. I have seen that.
Yeah. I don't know why they do that.
What did you eat today, Cory? Lad.
I could just get like a Big Mac.
I could just get Yeah.
Big rack with like a water in it. I can
live without. If I have to go quake for
a little bit, bro, I'll do it. It's
obviously the teeth and that. You need
to be careful, man.
I need to be careful, bro.
Can you have water?
What about a milkshake? I don't think a
milkshake is as bad as Coke, is it? No.
I don't want no sauce, no pickles, no lettuce,
no onion. I just want cheese.
I'm sure you can have a milkshake. Yeah,
a milkshake. I'm going to get a
milkshake. I don't think that's as bad
for you as Coke. Is it?
It's not as bad, is it? Coke. A
milkshake as then Coke. I don't think
so. I can I can have a milkshake, I'm sure. Yeah.
Let's see what you look like.
That's nice, bro. Let's see what you look like. Um,
oh, different ones. Thank you, brother.
Let's see what you look like. Thought so.
Yeah, you are Ming and loser. Stop
talking about yourself.
Yeah, you need to stop talking about
yourself like that, brother. You need to
stop putting yourself down. These people
really put themselves down, you know, Cory. You know,
I can't believe they call themselves
ugly and a m and stuff. I can't believe
they put themselves down cuz all they
all they're doing is talking about themselves,
laughing at themselves, bullying
themselves. That's why sometimes I ban
them, you know, because it it's hard to
see people put themselves down the way
these people put themselves down. Cory
calling themselves hideous, laughing at themselves,
just picking on themselves and putting
themselves down cuz all they're doing is
talking about themselves. That's all they're doing.
Yeah. Just you you don't know how sad it
is when you see a bunch of people
bullying themselves. Just writing
negative stuff about themselves, bro.
It's not good.
A bunch of people bullying themselves on
the internet every day. That's why
sometimes I don't ban them. But then it
gets a bit sad like you know how people
can put themselves down the way these
people do. Calling themselves an incel,
calling themselves ugly.
They really do put themselves down. These people,
you know, they need to get some confidence, lad.
Keep calling themselves a m. It's not
good, bro. Why do they talk about
themselves like that?
It's not good for these people to talk
about themselves the way they talk about themselves.
Why do they talk about themselves like that? Meal add-on. What?
Trying to force me to get to get some nuggets. They're
forcing you to get some nuggets. What the [ __ ]
I'm going to order this.
Yeah. And I got a milkshake as well. Yeah. £14.
You [ __ ] virgin.
You skin [ __ ] virgin, [ __ ] You
Yeah, I got one.
I got a banana milkshake.
I like banana.
Oi Chubney. I was spending I was I was
spending Christmas with my mom, my
sister, my friends. What was you doing
Christmas all by yourself on YouTube?
Seems I had a better Christmas than you lad.
You was on YouTube alone Christmas. I've
already got my little evidence. Cory, so
do you want to know what I done on Christmas, Cory?
You want to know what I done on
Christmas? So I woke up. Yeah. And I was
like, I want to show you that these
people ain't got no family on Christmas.
And Body Man copied my idea. So what I
done was I went live. Um I was like, I'm
going to go live and I'm going to go
downstairs, make a tea, and then come
back. I went live, bro. Um I went
downstairs quickly. I made a tea. I went
up and they were on YouTube. I was like,
they're on YouTube Christmas. They got
no family. And then I quickly ended the
live stream. Uh it was about 5 minutes long.
I went downstairs without the phone. I
went back up and they all joined. They
were on YouTube on Christmas day. No family.
So all of these people that were sat
there saying, "No family. Your family
hate them." It was them all along. It
was them all along. Yeah, bro. They were
on YouTube Christmas. They were on
YouTube Christmas. No family. That's the
first thing I thought about when I woke
up to see if these people would be on YouTube Christmas.
It's sad, bro. that everything that they
do and say is just themselves. I don't
know how I I I generally think right
that they're so disabled that they don't
even realize they're talking about
themselves because you must be disabled
if you can jump on the internet right
for all these years talking about
yourself and you still don't realize
that you're only talking about yourself.
Yeah, but guess what Chubby, you was
alone Christmas, you don't have no
family. That's the only reason you're
talking [ __ ] about my family, bro. Cuz
you ain't got no family. Your family hate you.
Skin family hate you. No girlfriend,
nobody. Everything is you.
Everything is yourself. You don't have
no family. So, of course, you'd say that
you people ain't got And that's another
thing you'll notice with these people on
YouTube. They ain't got no family, Cory.
They've got no mom. They've got no
sister. They got no dad. They got no
family. If you've noticed with these
people here, they don't have family.
None of them have got family. If you've
not if you've noticed that. I don't know
if you noticed that, but I noticed that, bro.
They got no family. They were on
YouTube. Christmas. They were on
You're on YouTube.
You want me to put the video back up
when these people was on YouTube? And
then Monty Man copied me. Monty man
copied me. You know, bro, he says that's
five people without a family Christmas.
He's such a little copycat.
He's a copycat. No. No. He's a copycat.
You want me to put the video up?
You want me to put the video up? Sorry.
Quickly. I can put it back up, bro. I
want you to watch it.
They're all yo Christmas.
And I left I left to go to my sisters at
10, bro. I left to go my sisters at 10:00.
So yeah, I left to go to my sisters at
10:00. So I I went live at 9:00 for 5
minutes and I was like they're on
YouTube. They got all
Yeah. Why do these people on here call people skinty?
It's cuz they're skin themselves.
These people are skinned than a [ __ ] skin.
Yeah. Yeah, I just ordered some food, but
I got a milkshake instead of Coke this
time. So, it should be better, you know,
for the old toothies,
that Big Mac meal, and some nuggets.
I really need to change my diet, bro,
cuz of my um gums and [ __ ] I really do.
But yeah, milkshake isn't as bad as um I
just got a medium one.
Yeah, it's not as bad um as Coke. It
can't be as bad as Coke. A milkshake. Nah.
And trust me, for me to give up Coke,
bro, that's saying something.
For me to give up Coke, that is
something. That is something for me to
give up Coke, bro.
Got to do what you got to do, bro. I'm
giving up for a little bit and I'll go
back to it.
Yeah, I didn't wake up with the tooth
fake today, Dusty.
Yeah, I saw your video. Uh, your
roulette video, Timmy. Did you see it,
Dusty? Uh, Timmyy's roulette video. So,
so um Dusty, why do do you know when
like a man struggling with dating and
stuff? Why do people blame his attitude,
but yet when women be rude to people
that no one says anything?
Like when they've got a bad attitude
when someone approaches them, why does
no one say anything?
But yeah, when a man struggles,
apparently he's the worst person in the world.
Why do you think that is? I saw a couple
of approaches recently from this black
guy and these women were really rude.
Like really stuck up and rude, but no
one really said anything about it.
Strange, isn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. He's going to be mate. I him and
Nons legs are the are the biggest
virgins ever. Him and nons legs. Proper proper virgin.
Yeah. Well, the milkshake isn't as bad
as the Coke. It can't. It might might
maybe. Yeah, but it can't be as bad as
the Coke. Coke's got acid in it. Yeah, but
it still isn't as bad as Coke. One way
or another, it can't be. Coke is the
worst thing you can drink, though, bro.
Coke is the worst thing you can drink.
It is literally the worst thing you can drink.
Well, we'll see anyways. Bro,
you won't Yeah, but it won't rot your
teeth. Coke won't rot your teeth.
Yeah, I saw it. That's projection.
I spent all I spent all Christmas on
YouTube. No, I didn't. You must be
talking about yourself. I spent
Christmas with my family. Something that
you don't have.
And yeah, brother, same thing to you. If
you stop going on YouTube projecting
your life to people, you could get a job
or a skill. Same thing to you. Maybe you
should get yourself a job and get off of
YouTube before talking about other people.
I don't know why you're deflecting as
well, bro. You're the people that are on
YouTube Christmas. I've already proved
that you people was on YouTube Christmas.
You need to get yourself a job, you bum,
before talking about other people. Why
don't you get yourself a job? Get
yourself a job. Get yourself a
girlfriend and then come back on here
talking about other people.
Get yourself a job. Get yourself a
girlfriend. Get all of the things that
you don't have yourself and then come
back to me and then start trying to
preach to other [ __ ] people. You was
on YouTube Christmas, you people with no
family. I couldn't believe it. I said,
"They're on YouTube." Oh my god, Cory. I
went live. Yeah. And I was like,
"They're on YouTube. They got no family.
It was like a confirmation of what I
thought. It was like a It was just a
confirmation of what I what I thought,
bro. I was like, "These people are
watching no family." It was like
receiving the news, you know?
And I don't know why that L pretends
that he's not on YouTube Christmas when
he is. I don't know why he why they a
lot of these people as well will pretend
that that they're not on YouTube.
They will pretend that they're not on
YouTube Christmas when they [ __ ] are
because KBY, when I went live for 5
minutes, bro, there was 18 people
watching and two people commenting.
They're so scared because they know they
got no family. So if they if they're
caught being on YouTube Christmas,
they're going to get called for it.
Yeah. Same with you, Chubby. You jobless
bum. And you know what? You know what
you prove? being a keyboard warrior all
of these years don't change the fact
that it's you yourself with no job you
yourself with no girlfriend and all of
these things that you've said over the
years doesn't change the fact that it's
about you. So to think that if you spent
all of them years fixing yourself
instead of projection, you would, you
know, you would have fixed your life.
Instead of telling people to get a job
and you ain't got a job, you've never
had a job and you're on benefits, you
don't have a girlfriend, you've never
had a girlfriend, you're a virgin, you
would have actually been a better
person. All of this projecting got you
nowhere in the end talking about
yourself cuz in the end you was only
talking about yourself. It's like
Christmas when people said, "My
Christmas is ruined." These people was
on YouTube Christmas with no family and
I've got the evidence. Do Do you want to
see the evidence?
Dig money to mummy. Brother, you don't
even have a mummy. You ain't got a
mummy. You ain't got a job. You're just
a fat bum on YouTube. Oh, why don't you
come on YouTube and put your camera on?
Oh, wait. You're too fat and ugly. Sorry
about that. Anyways, Tori, do you want
to see this video? Bro,
mommy. Isn't it funny how you and Nonss
ain't got a mummy? You and Nonss don't
have a mummy. Is that where the jealousy
comes from? Cuz your mom don't want to
know you. Your mummies don't want to
know you. You bully victims. Your mom
don't want nothing to do with you and
nonslegs. That's why you're so asked
about people living with their mummy
because you don't have your mummy. You
don't have no family. You was alone
Christmas. And the evidence does not
lie, mate. Do you want to see my
Christmas? I'll put my Christmas up if
you want. I'll put my Christmas dinner
up if you want. I recorded it. Do you
want to see my Christmas?
Do you want to see my Christmas dinner?
Do you want to see what I Christmas?
I can put it up if you want whilst you
people sat alone on YouTube talking
about yourselves for another [ __ ]
year. Sat on YouTube putting yourselves
down on Christmas Day.
I don't know why these people keep
putting themselves down. Sorry.
I'll put it up. Yeah. Okay. One second.
These people's on YouTube Christmas Day.
[ __ ] hell, mate.
Two seconds. I got my tunnel, brother.
These people was on YouTube. No life
that under your job cuz they got no
family. You got no life.
Okay. One second.
These people your job. No life. Glory.
Yeah, I saw Timmy's um roulette video.
I'm putting a video up, by the way,
any second now.
No, it was actually coke that gave me it.
>> You know what I think? Sorry. I think
Lunch Legs needs to get himself a little
part-time job. He'll do the world of
good to get out of the house. He might
actually get laid. Get some money. Stop
showing daddy anywhere and he won't be a
virgin anymore. Get yourself a little
part-time job, you little virgin. You skin [ __ ]
I put the videos up, by the way, Bob. Did I?
Just a little part-time job. What's
wrong with a little part-time job?
He needs to get laid. He needs to lose
his vard. He got a diver virgin like to
me. And you can put up this disabled
girl a million times. It doesn't prove
the point that you've had sex. Oh, he's
a proper loser. He He needs to get laid.
He's going divergent.
He's going to [ __ ] ding. He is that
[ __ ] That cunt's going to divergent.
I like I like co I like coal. What? I I
like trouble co. You gay? You gay? I'm
I'm not gay, bro. What? Why am I gay?
Yeah, I know. He moans about me being a
virgin when the only virgin is Timmy and Nlex.
They're the two biggest virgins. The all
time virgins. The virgins of all time. I like
you. Remember that one, Cory? I like gay homosexual
gay. Uh, I'm not gay. She's just not my
type. I'm gay. I'm not homing.
I like some I have some. [laughter]
So, does he does he follow the crowd for
an easy life, Dusty?
I don't go off names. I don't go by
names and stuff.
>> Yeah, I'm all right. Fruit kick. He was
saying shovel was attractive to fit in.
That's what he was saying. He's a loser.
He's a [ __ ] loser. [laughter]
Oh, come on. Hurry up, McDonald's. I'm hungry.
I want a sip of my little milkshake and
eat my burger, you know.
Are you still there, Cory? I put a video
up of my dinner and my sisters. I had a
dinner boxing day as well.
I gobbled it all up. I was starving. I
was That Christmas dinner was yummy.
No, it was lovely that Christmas dinner.
Oh, mate. [ __ ] me. It was It was turkey and lamb.
Yeah, it was turkey and lamb and I ate the lot.
All right, Dusty, what did you say the
only way you can win on gambling now is?
Dusty, I don't know. I don't a far both
teams to score um on Boxing Day and I
got two out of four. All I needed was
[ __ ] Herafford and Enfield Town to
score and they never
Can you help me win some money on gambling, Dusty? Please,
Co. If you don't like Shevel Co, you're gay.
If you don't like Sh, you're gay.
No, you're gay. If you don't like Shucker.
[crying and laughter]
Yeah, it was lovely. No, if you don't
like shovel C, you're gay, mate. [ __ ]
gay. You like shovel.
I hate shovel girl. But then again, I'm
not a little copycat.
Yeah, I was telling people that I
watched the housemaid um the new horror
film and I like the maid. Her name's
Sydney Sweeney and she's apparently really famous.
Um she's really famous. Yeah, I didn't
even know about her until I watched the
film. See, I don't go by names. I go by
faces. I don't copy the crowd
cuz obviously, you know, Cole's
associated with a footballer or wasn't
associated to a footballer. So that's
why they all copy each other.
It's the name. I think it's the surname.
They all copy each other.
Yeah. I didn't even know who she was
until I watched this horror film um
circle. I then started looking them up
and I was like, "Oh, they're really quite famous.
So yeah, but I'm not like [ __ ] nons
gay. I'm gay
cow. I don't know. I think it's the name.
Yeah, I like I like go.
I like go. I like go. You like go. Yeah,
who's lush. Um,
who's lush? Cory.
Still being prepared. Hurry the [ __ ] up, bro. Starving, man.
No, I'm never telling that story again.
I didn't know who she was, though. Um,
Kyrie, until I watched this horror film,
I didn't know who she was, bro. I was
like, "Oh, what the [ __ ] I'd never ever
seen her in my life.
I just I watched the new horror film.
It's a good horror film. Go watch it,
bro, if you haven't already.
But I'm not like [ __ ] nons. I didn't
know the names and stuff before I
started saying that. He just started
showing off the next day in college. He
heard about it and then he was like,
He he just copied, you know. I didn't
copy. I didn't know who that they were, bro.
I just saw some sex scenes with her in it.
That is definitely definitely definitely
definitely definitely copying, bro.
That is definitely copying.
Definitely definitely definitely copying, bro.
I I would never say if you don't find
Sydney Sweeney attractive, you're gay.
Why would someone even say that, bro?
Why would someone say if you don't find
someone attractive, you're gay? That is
literally copying, bro. That's what I
mean. Copy. That's copying. They used to
do the same thing with Rihanna. They
used to say the same thing with Rihanna.
I don't know how people used to like
that Rihanna. have never found her
attractive ever. She's another one put
on a pedestal.
You know, she's another one put on a
pedestal. They put these people on they
put these celebrities on a pedestal.
They put them on a on a pedestal, bro.
These people, for some reason,
they used to do the same thing with
Rihanna. If you don't like Rihanna,
you're gay. But the thing is, you you
would never hear it from with a normal
person. Like for example, uh Cory, if
someone weren't famous, you'd never hear
someone say, "If you don't like that
person, you're you're if you don't like that person, um
you're gay." Does that make sense?
They're all copycats.
They only say about famous people.
They're all little copycats. Cuz why is
it everyone says the same thing about
Cher Cole? like nonslegs. If you don't
find how attractive you're gay, why is
why do you why do you see so many people
say the same thing? Because it's a
trend. Do you know what a trend is?
Oh, here we go. 4 minutes away.
Um, I don't know really.
Just while I'm trying to join the porn industry.
Yeah, my sister's got a little copycat.
>> Yeah, he's got no mind of its own. Um,
yeah. I'm going to try and join the pool
industry because when I watched that sex
scene, Yeah. it got to me. I went to
watch the housemmaid Cory and I didn't
think I was going to be [ __ ] seeing a
sex scene, bro. I didn't want to see a
sex scene. It was a sex scene in it. And
I was like, what are we going to do
realistically? We can't keep going out
and approaching and getting bad
experiences. I gave up with the dating
and the women. Cory, I've given up. I
haven't done it for over a month and
I've got no plans to ever do it again.
And I'm thinking, "Oh, I should be
having a sex life at 28.
I should be [ __ ] having a sex life at
[ __ ] 28, bro."
Yeah. It's like it's it's mocking you,
is it? And it And it was several times
as well. It was several times.
And the sex scene was several times as
well, Cory. It was several times, bro.
Several several times. It was,
you know, it was even like they just
kissed. No, no, no. It was It was constant, bro.
And the husband cheated on the wife with
her. It was bad. It's not good for your
It's not good for your mind, bro.
And I'm saying And what I was saying,
Cory, yeah, is a lot of people do not
watch Paul. Why does a lot of people not
watch Paul? Because it's it's bad for
you. You know, a lot of a lot there's a
lot of people don't watch porn. There's
a reason why they don't watch porn. You
know, there's reasons. We know the
reasons. So, when you go and watch a
horror film, you don't expect to be
seeing [ __ ] porno scenes. And it
basically is porn really because you you
could see her nude as well. So, I've
gone to watch a horror film, not watch a porno.
And it's 15 as well. Like I said, it was
15 as well. So, what the [ __ ] bro?
I don't go to watch a porno. I went to
watch a horror film
and look what happened.
So, I'm going to try to join the Yeah. industry.
See where we get with that. Yeah.
You know what I mean? No. Um,
Pific Pete. That's what my pool name's
going to be. Pific Pete.
Yeah, that's what my name's my pool
name's going to be.
Deme call me. Yeah, they've all got boyfriends,
>> you know. Prolific Pete. Oh, my Maki
should be here soon. Oh gosh.
Oh gosh, Dusty. So, anyways, why is it
okay for when is it okay for these women
to be rude and no one says anything
about it then, Dusty?
Why is it okay for these women to be rude?
There was a man that approached this
woman and she was like, "Oh, um, I'm on
the phone. Get away from me."
Like, and there was another one that
said, "Can you stop it, please?" They're
all just stuck up and rude. No one says
anything about these women being stuck
up. Why is that? Uh, KBY, why is that uh Dusty?
Oh, my Mackey's is here.
It might have more sugar than a Coke,
but I bet you it doesn't. Uh oh, there
was this black guy that approached this
woman and she said, "Oh, um," she said,
"I'm on the phone. Get away from me."
Yeah, she said, "I'm on the phone. Get
away from me." And then another one was
being rude. Why is it okay for them to
be rude and stuck up and [ __ ] Yeah. Then
so why is why does no one say anything about that? H.
Yeah. Yeah. One sec. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Thank you. [snorts]
That's the thing with a milkshake. It
always comes like slushy. But with Five
Guys, it doesn't. Five Guys is good,
bro. Five Guys is M.
No, it's not bad, you know.
Oh, the chips aren't that bad to be fair.
I'm always scared McDonald's is going to
come cold cuz most of the time it does. [clears throat] I don't
like cold always dusty but today they're not double. home today. All right.
I used to always have these when I was a baby.
When I was a little bubba, [snorts]
what what milkshake do you like? My
favorite milkshake is the peanut butter one.
peanut bar one from um
the peanut bar one from
from uh Five Guys
milkshakes are the best.
I don't milkshake and peanut butter.
No, we don't have it in London.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, we don't have good here, Mr. B.
Just like we don't have farm foods.
That milkshake is not even bad to be
honest considering ordered.
By Dusty, are you going to watch the new Spongebob movie?
I like Spongebob.
I like Spongebob because it's English.
It was made in London. Spongebob. Yeah.
Did you know that?
You know, do you know Spongebob was made
in um it was made in London? Yeah. [clears throat]
>> [clears throat]
>> The milkshake is nice, bro. That's how
you know. I think they took their time
with it because it's not busy. Normally,
that's nice, bro. That's perfect.
I Oh, I love banana milkshake. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, maybe. Yeah,
Sydney Sweeney. Oh, [ __ ] hell.
How did I know about this until just now?
So, you're saying, Dusty, that if her
name wasn't She Cole, um that um lunch
wouldn't be saying that stuff? No.
Not one celebrity
that's way better looking than another
person. There's not one. There's
literally not one, bro.
There's literally not one.
I don't know the hype for them. I really don't.
No, I'm saying if you did know her.
I'm saying I mean if she was well known
but not famous.
>> Cuz look at Okay, look at that woman
that I went on a date with, the one from
Italy. Yeah. Remember the one that I was
in a picture with with the Guinness, right?
Remember? And I would say she's better
looking than Sher Cole. But no one
started saying, "Oh, if you don't find
her attractive, you're gay." That's what
makes me think it's a copycat trend.
Copycat. You know what I mean?
Cuz look at look at some of the women
that I've some of them have got me
better than her or dated or went on a
date with whatever like just seen me
with, you know what I mean?
But you don't hear people saying
that if you don't find that you just the
name. It's the [ __ ] name.
It's pretty much nice. Too much. This
McDonald's is not actually bad, you know. So what?
I [clears throat and snorts] just don't
find attractive. No.
If I had to pick one, I'd pick that Gomez. But
I'm not saying that your [clears throat] game either.
What if you like black women? What if
you like blonde women with blue eyes?
You can't deny she's attractive. [snorts]
I put Gomez I would put Gomez there
but I don't put on pedestals. I've got little copies. [snorts] Um,
and that Sydney Swed is blonde. I don't
usually like blonde people. [snorts] Yeah.
They used to say about Beyonce as well,
Dusty. If you don't find Beyonce
attractive, you've got to screw this.
That's what my sister used to say to me.
That was another trend. Beyonce, uh, Rihanna. Um, yeah. Beyonce, Rihanna,
we used to cop each other. Yeah. [clears throat]
My kids are feeling a lot better today, Dusty.
They're feeling a lot better.
Must be from cutting down on the sugar, huh?
Yeah, they feel better today. That's it.
[snorts] Stay away from that punk.
Stay away from that polar, mated.
Jimmy Sav is a great guy.
Oh, you know what makes me laugh? Yeah.
When Ed goes to America and he's like,
"My name is Jimmy Savo." [laughter]
He's like, "What's your name?"
My name is My name is Jimmy Shovel.
And they say times because obviously I
don't know Jimmy Shovel in it. My name
is Jimmy Shle.
You never seen it. This is my name.
Obviously they don't know who he is. It my name
cuz they don't know the words over there.
This milkshake is lovely.
M lovely milkshake.
That is lush.
M I'm on my last chicken love it now. M.
Oh, I love it.
This is lovely though. This milkshake. I
don't like any other but banana for McDonald's.
Lady likes the chocolate one.
Well, I woke up about two hours ago, bro. So, yeah. Oh. Lovely.
My headache's gone away now. Call me
since I ate.
My headache's gone away now. M.
Best. M. Yummy. Yum. Yum.
The best the best milkshake. Five guys.
Peanut butter. And that you have to go
in and have it. You have to go in and
have it. That milkshake is the [ __ ] business, man.
That is the business.
That's the bees.
So yeah, I'm going to try and join the
porn industry anyways um in January.
Yeah, I haven't had the bacon one
because there's no point having a dick
if you're not if you can't use it.
Sorry. There's no point being with a
born with a dick if you can't use it.
It's mental, but it's worth it.
There's no point having a dick if you
can't use it. Hey,
that's what it's there for,
that's what it's there for, lad, you know. >> [laughter]
>> No, I'm joking. I don't really get a sex
drive anymore, bro. I don't even care about sex.
It's just that sex scene triggered me.
No, I'm going to get paid to do it. [laughter]
And I can't use escorts anymore, Cole,
because I don't like using condoms. So,
escorts are not an option unless I just
want a [ __ ] But I I've gone out the
[ __ ] phase now. I want sex again.
When I was using escorts for over a
year, I was only getting [ __ ]
Um, Cory, so it was all right, you know.
Just [ __ ] is all right, you know. Yeah,
you can get just [ __ ]
but obviously if you want to have sex, then
I I don't think I would, bro, because I
don't want to use a condom, and their
fann is probably very loose. It's all
right getting a [ __ ] from an escort
cuz you don't have to wear a condom and
it's just the same thing here. You know,
you know what I mean, bro? So,
would you get in a bath with your
clothes on? No, you wouldn't.
So, that's the same thing with having sex. [snorts]
It's not natural. Condoms are not
You know what I mean, Dusty? They're not
natural. Condoms are not a natural thing.
Oh, this milkshake is good, bro. [laughter]
Me and Laney's got different taste buds,
Dusty. Is that cute? Me and Laney's got
different taste buds.
Laney doesn't have sugar and tea. I do,
but obviously I'm not. M.
I don't want to become successful. As
long as I'm getting laid, I don't give a
[ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] about it being
successful, bro. As long as I'm getting
sex, I don't give a [ __ ]
This is nice, bro.
This milkshake is
Yeah, lady has sugar and I have sugar
and tea. Laney doesn't. But obviously I
don't now for now for a little bit until
cuz I want to trigger my tooth pain and that
is lovely. That is
Well, it doesn't matter. They're going
to be good-look anyways, so why not?
I might be the next Johnny Sims.
My mom and sister said they would
disowned me if I joined the porn
industry. I think that's kind of selfish.
Cory, I think that's kind of selfish to
disown someone for joining the porn
industry knowing the situation that I'm
in. You know, you can't get laid, you
can't find anyone.
Um, I think it's quite selfish me
obviously knowing my situation, you know.
Yeah. Vintage porn. Yeah.
Because the thing is, all right, Cory,
even if you got laid yet once a month,
that would be enough for me.
I don't know about you, bro. Like,
getting laid once a month, that would be
enough. I I I wouldn't need it any more
than that. Once a month, that's fine.
Keeps you stable and that you know you
got something to look forward to. I
wouldn't mind once a month. Worst comes to worse.
You should be getting it at your age. At
my age, I should be getting it. You know,
but you could be like, and Timmy,
they've never had it in their life. So
if you think of them two, you know.
Yeah, I got a 20 farfold. I got two
both. I got um two out of four.
[cough and clears throat]
Come out with you a money mic. Nope. I
won't be going out till midFeb March.
Why are you going to go out January? No
one goes out January, Dusty. You know,
if you try going out in January, no one
goes out. You do realize that? No one
goes out in January.
Mm- [clears throat]
No one goes out in January, bro. I tried
loads of times in January, bro, over the
years, and no one goes out.
I remember when I went to the Westfield,
bro, there was literally no one in it.
No one goes out generally, bro.
Not many people though. Not many people
do, Cory. Maybe, but not many.
Obviously, there are people that go out,
but not many people.
Not many people do though, bro. Not many
people do. Trust me. I went to a club. I
think it was February, January, February
I went out and no one went in it, bro.
And normally it's rammed. Normally it's
rammed. No one. Yeah. Mhm.
Yeah. You need to help me win money
gambling, Dusty. What What can I gamble
on to win? H
>> [clears throat]
>> That milkshake was [ __ ] lush.
I feel sleepy now.
Can you win gambling nowadays, Dusty?
Can you even win nowadays?
You can't win nowadays, matey.
Yeah, I was I was watching that King's Cleans, Dusty.
Like I said, he will never be stopping
me on the street, bro. Telling me that
I've got I've got dusty creps.
No, but I mean what's what's the what
have you got more chance of winning on
in real life or online, Dusty?
Online or real life, do you reckon
Well, you got more chance to win in arcades. Yeah,
cuz it's f online's too rigged, is it,
Dusty? My my sister's got a bookies
account. That's hard on the football bet
on Boxing Day. But nah.
Well, I can't get into any casinos,
Dusty. So, I guess the only option for
me is bookies, isn't it?
Um, sometimes I play Franklin. Yeah. Cory Franklin.
He's a lovely little character. Franklin
and his little [ __ ]
He's a nasty version. He is. Yeah.
So, what about online? It's hard to win
online as well, though, isn't it, Dusty?
you skin virgin.
Well, I heard if you win online on a UK
regul regulated site, they ask you for
proof of wealth.
What's my biggest habit? Um,
I like curry.
Yeah. If you went online, they asked for
proof of wealth.
Therefore, finding a girl. How do you
know that? What? In this country, Cory?
Yeah, right. You got more chance of pig flying.
You'll never find someone in this country, mate.
Yeah. Yeah. If you win online, they ask
you for proof of [ __ ] proof of income. Dusty,
if you win, did you know that
I can't because they I I was talking to
a 45year-old on Instagram and she was
playing the same games two weeks ago.
She was using distance as an excuse. Yeah,
she was using distance as an excuse. She
was playing the same games as these
these younger ones.
Yeah, I woke up. I went on YouTube and I
saw that Timmy done a video.
Yeah, I saw Timmy done a video. Oh gosh.
I like car.
Why don't you like chem?
I don't really gamble that much.
I might try that 100 to one roulette
that Joe does.
I like that one, Dusty. If you put a FB
in too much from we wouldn't sleep for a
week straight. [laughter] Yeah.
That's really true actually. Oh gosh. Yeah.
Hopefully Red Star won't be on YouTube
next year. Dusty,
isn't it Dusty? Hopefully
he won't be on YouTube um next year. I'm
I'm I'm I'm hoping, you know. All right.
I can't wait until the first of January,
Kyrie. It's going to be different people
on YouTube. No more repeating. I can't
wait. I'm looking forward to it.
I can't [ __ ] wait.
roll on the 1 of January because don't
forget these people have got an IQ.
These people are intelligent and tomorrow
it will be tomorrow.
You don't go at all UK asylum.
Well, at all at all.
I want to try the 101 roulette. You know
the 100 to one roulette in the in the bookies.
You reckon I'll win dusty?
You reckon I'll win on 100 and one
roulette in the bookies last Okay. Oh gosh,
I need to go to sleep in a minute. I had
to go to sleep.
That milkshake was [ __ ] lovely. Oh gosh.
My little voice is dusty. Yeah.
Well, I'm going to go now anyways. Yeah.
See you. What if I get to sleep after eating?