Who's on YouTube? Just check it.
I, you know, I always do my little
welfare check just to see if you people
are still on YouTube.
If you're still on YouTube,
hopefully not though. Someday people
should be with family. I I was sat in
Weather Spoon having a little breakfast
and I was just thinking
how disabled this community actually is.
Sat there having breakfast, thinking
about it. It really is a disabled
community. I was actually losing brain
cells. Thinking of it,
these um disabled people in this
community, I was actually losing brain cells, man.
Yeah, I was actually losing [ __ ] brain cells.
This Joseph Ferrar is one disabled [ __ ]
Oh, I was just thinking of it because
the breakfast was was a long wait.
It gave me time to think. Yeah.
Gave me time to think.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
Yeah, it's a disabled community, lads.
It is. I don't get what he mean this [ __ ] thing. [clears throat] >> [snorts]
>> You had PG up at 5:00 a.m. to turning
absolutely bored and how broke he is.
No, no money, no car. You Yeah, that's
self projection. No one cares about that
self- projection from the self-p
projection low lives. Um, I was thinking
about uh, yeah,
I will dress by his name. I do not like
him and never have. I don't know him.
All I ever said is that I find it near
impossible to believe someone that has
had a girlfriend 3 years a virgin that
you continuously defend him. Yeah, you
continuously defend somebody that you
claim that you don't like. It doesn't
make any sense. How can you keep
defending someone that you don't like?
It doesn't I don't know. You don't make sense, bro.
But yet when someone like me has
actually proved they've had sex, I don't
see you saying anything about me having
sex. So you want to make it make sense.
You really really want to make it make
sense if you are to say stuff in the
future. Um cuz obviously that's one of
your favorite words, make it make sense.
Yeah. You really need to make it make sense yourself. you know,
uh, you don't like someone, but you've
defended them multiple times,
saying that it's not possible for them
to be a virgin, even though it's way
more possible for them to be a virgin
um, than it is me. So,
make it make sense, mate. It doesn't
make no sense. Hey bro, I just ordered
some uh I ordered some breakfast in
Weather Spoons, bro. And it took like
half an hour and I was thinking about
how disabled this community actually is.
It really really is proper disabled,
isn't it? Like they've not got like a
brain cell between any of them. Like no
brain cell at all.
They really don't make any sense whatsoever.
And I was thinking of this Joseph
Ferrar. They really really don't. So,
you don't like someone yet you
continuously defend them and say that
they're not a virgin. But yet, when
someone like me has actually proved
they've had sex, you're nowhere to be seen.
I don't know about anyone else who's
watching this, but if I didn't like
somebody, I would not be defending
someone whether they were in the right
or in the wrong
um or even giving an opinion on a
matter. So, make it make sense.
And I was just thinking on way back. I
was like, I mean, it's it's more
possible for someone to be a virgin
that's been in a relationship for 3
years than someone that's actually
proved they've had sex.
But again, when you're younger and
better looking than these people,
they've got a problem with you. Isn't
that right, chicken neck soup?
So, you don't like So, okay, let me give
you an example. Someone I don't like, right? Okay. Um,
LJ, right? Yeah. So if somebody was
slating L J Yeah. calling him a virgin,
I wouldn't be there saying, "Oh, he's
got kids. He's got kids." I I wouldn't
be to his rescue. Whether he was right
or wrong, I would never be to someone's
rescue who I don't like.
You know, it just doesn't make sense.
Are you sure you're not a non-leg lover?
Cuz you're showing all the signs of
being a nonsex lover. A biased nonslegs
lover for that matter.
And then you say, "Oh, you know, uh,
what do you need me to defend you?" No,
I don't need you to defend me. I can
defend myself, but non doesn't need you
to defend him either. So why don't you
get from up his ass and let him defend himself.
[ __ ] bias and nonsle lover. Like what
Kieran said as well.
Yeah. I don't know why I was just
thinking of that cuz it's very very disabled.
Yeah. I just come on here to say that to be honest.
You say you don't like Reddit because
people on Reddit are keyboard warriors.
Oh, this is self projection.
And why don't you like me if you don't know me?
Right. His life will change next year
because he his life will change because
he will be another year close to 30 and
still no money, no job, never had a
girlfriend. You're talking about
yourself, LJ. You've got no money, no
girlfriend, no friends. That's yourself
and your fans. That's self projection.
That's self projection. Hey, bro. He's
projection again. He's projecting.
That's him. No girlfriend, no friends,
no money. That's him. That's LJ. That's
self projection. Bro, do these people
never get bored of self- projecting
their life onto others? Like, how many
more years are these people going to sit
here and self-reflect their [ __ ] lives
onto other people? Like, it really
really gets boring now, you know? Trips,
I've just come back from Weather Spoons.
I had a breakfast.
and I've just come back, bro. And the
breakfast took ages. It seemed like half
an hour it took. So, I sat there
thinking about this community and I was actually
becoming brain damaged. I was thinking
of it and actually becoming brain damaged.
It's like if I was a millionaire.
Yeah. I don't know, bro. I just I just
was getting brain damage thinking about it. Bro,
I'm I don't understand this Joseph
Ferrar's logic. He says sorry, bro. I'm
trying to I'm reading this. Yeah.
He says, "I don't like I will dress him
by his name. I don't like N legs. I do
not like him. I never have. I don't know
him. All I ever said is that I find it
near impossible to believe someone that
has had a girlfriend for 3 years is a
virgin." So, if you don't like someone,
why are you defending them? That doesn't
make any sense. When it's more possible
for someone to be a virgin being with a
disabled girl for 3 years, than someone
like me that's proved that they've had
sex. So if you don't like someone, why
are you defending them? It doesn't make
sense. It's like me going to Lord J
saying, "Oh, he's not a virgin. He's got
kids." And continuously defending
someone that I don't like. It doesn't
make sense. You're an undercover
nonslegs lover. You know, the thing is
with these people, Triple H, I think
they like him because they're they're
nons themselves. That's why they like
him because they're nons themselves.
Like they're undercover nons themselves.
That's why they like this guy, bro.
So I mean I mean he can defend himself,
can't you not? You know
like you can you can defend yourself,
can't you not? I mean I can defend myself.
I don't I think he can defend himself either.
So why are you defending someone that
you don't like?
And I'm pretty sure I can go on Nonsex's channel
right now and see where he's called me
and a virgin and no one has said
anything about it. Strange. Interesting.
What do you mean people's interests do
give themselves away? To be honest, I
just don't understand his logic. I was
thinking about this earlier. So, you
don't like Nodle Legs, yet you've
continuously defended Nodle Legs.
Apparently, he's not a virgin because
he's been with a disabled girl for 3
years. Okay. Yet, you don't like him,
but yet you've not brought up all of the
porn the pornos I've put up and all the
women that I've been with. So, am I
lying by saying that you're a nons legs lover?
Like it's it's
and no, he's still doing it for these
people have got no life. They'll never
stop doing it. H strange.
So you don't like someone but you're
defending them. Make it make sense. Make
it really really really make sense.
That's like right someone say that's
like someone calling that woman from
America a slag and me saying no she's
not a slag she's not a slag and me
continuously going to a rescue where I
don't like her that doesn't make any
sense you know what I'm saying it does
these people here are bro they are
actually disabled on here Triple H bro
sorry sometimes I shouting that bro it's
cuz I'm actually losing brain cells
because they generally do not make any
sense whatsoever But they're disabled, biased, jealous
for [ __ ] people that ain't got
nothing in life. Sorry, bro. I just lose
brain cells because of this place. They
really are disabled.
And I say to you, oh well, why don't you
why don't you say anything about me not
being a virgin? Oh, you know, I I don't
need to defend you. You can defend
yourself. Well, can't nonslegs defend
himself then. Same thing goes to
nonslegs. Can't nonslegs defend himself,
brother. If this was a 2 years ago,
Triple H, I'd go to leads today. But we
all know what's going to happen, bro.
They're not going to meet you. These fat
clowns are not going to meet you. This
Joe F. Yeah, he's another he's another
Bomb. If you go on his uh page, he's
using the same excuses that Bomb's using.
He's He's using the same excuses that
Bomb's using. Um you know
what where has he gone back?
He said in the reply you will meet next
week and then in the reply say 25th you
are all over the face of my all you want
to do is take a picture or video and run
off. All I all to say I told you so fat
disabled blah blah blah. Oh so you are
fat and disabled then. Oh so you are fat
and disabled by writing that that must
mean you are fat and disabled brother.
I'm not going to go to your city and run
away from you. That that is not going to
happen. Yeah. The same excuses that
Bomber used to use before his picture
got out there. Bro, I swear they're all
the same on here. Triple H.
And Lord J needs to [ __ ] whine. He's
naked, mate. He's 42. No girlfriend, no
money, no life, no future, no friends,
just a couple of ugly kids. No driving
license. He's got nothing but a couple
of ugly spasticated kids. That's all
he's got to his name. And it's not being
rude. It's the truth. That's not even me
being triggered. That's me saying the
truth. He's got nothing. Nothing, bro.
At 42. No driving license. Never been on
a proper holiday, no girlfriend, no
money. It's the same [ __ ] thing, bro.
With these people.
Which one, bro? Roger J. Yeah. No
friend. That's yourself you're talking
about. I've got plenty of friends.
Plenty of friends.
More money than him. Better looking than
You know, Rob, you're in your 40s and
you ain't got a girlfriend and you ain't
got no money. Never mind a 28-year-old.
This is what these people don't
understand. They like to judge people,
but they don't look at themselves. 42,
no girlfriend, no driving license, not a
single friend to your name. And then
you're talking about a 28-year-old
that's got a better life than you. Who
are these people to think that they can
judge anyone? Who are they to think that
they can judge anyone when their lives
are worse than yours?
Their lives are [ __ ] worse than
yours, bro. They ain't got their [ __ ]
together. A bunch of fat, ugly people
that lie around on YouTube that ain't
got a life. Really trying to judge other
people that's in a better position than them.
Come on, bro.
Strange lad. Strange.
Yeah. Adam Spoon's breakfast anyway is triple. Strange.
It's just self projection with these
people constantly, bro.
What What is it? Are they Are they
jealous? Are they disabled?
Are they [ __ ] skin. Are they
alcoholics? What is it with these people, bro?
But yeah, Joseph Fra does not make
sense. You don't like someone, but then
you defend them.
And yes, you saying they're not a
virgin, that is defending them. Uh, yes,
it is. That is defending them
in an argument. Dirty, stinky, non-slover.
But then he comes from um Lavy side. He
does come from Lavy side. So, I mean,
you're kind of expecting it. He's he
he's he's part of the Bongo crew. Anyone
that goes on that LJ's channel, they're
all the same. Fat, disabled, ain't got
no life, ain't got nothing going for
themselves. So, you you know, you'd
expect it. Anyone you'd expect anyone
that's on that channel?
And you people don't win, brother. What
do you people win? You know, what do you
people win? fat ugly people that sit on
YouTube all day ain't got not a pot to
piss in. What do you win? You failed at
everything in life. What do you win?
You're sat at home. You don't have no
friends. No one from that L channel. You
ain't got a pot to piss in. You ain't
got no mates. What are you winning?
Like, I've asked this question multiple
times and they can't answer you. You're
fat. You're ugly. You're skinn. You're
disabled. What are you winning? What What contest?
You can ask it over and over again. They
can't answer it. You know, simple.
What do you win being the world's
biggest projectors? Yeah, you do win
that, bro. Yeah, the only thing you win
is coming on YouTube talking about
yourself relentlessly for 10 [ __ ] 12
years and over. So, actually, yeah, that
is what you win.
[ __ ] madness, bro.
Australia. Has your boyfriend gone to
Australia? Mike, has your boyfriend gone
to China? Has your boyfriend gone to
Japan? No, I didn't think so. [snorts]
Yeah, he wasn't on here, Triple H.
And I was thinking of the biasness and
the jealousy on here to people that they
don't know. Lad,
they were on here Christmas. You saw Did
you see my video when I showed that they
were on here Christmas?
Did you Did you see the video?
They were on Christmas day as well. Did
you see it? I put my Christmas dinner up
as well. Yeah,
like I said yesterday, you wasn't on
here, bro. But these people in this
community, they're they're at a certain
level in life, the lowest of the low.
And they're try and what they do is they
try to bring other people down to their
level. That's what these people do.
They're fat, ugly, disabled, sad people
with no life, no family, nothing going
for themselves. That's me having an
opinion. That's not me being triggered.
That's what they are.
Yeah. Well, yeah. They were on YouTube Christmas.
None of these people come and come and
show their faces cuz they're fat and
ugly. You know, most, you know, most
communities. Yeah. They join Hangouts.
You know, most most communities they
actually join the hangouts,
you know what I mean, bro?
Most different like communities. No, no
one on here joins the hangouts. Not
really. Compared to how many people on
it, no one really joins. No one shows
their faces. There's a reason for that.
You go on any other community, you'll
see it, bro. People show their faces,
they talk, or they just talk. And then
you know, but these people don't because
they're [ __ ] ugly fat ass disabled people.
And it's not me being triggered, bro.
It's me spitting the truth. It's me spitting facts.
They ain't got no life. They're clearly
jealous of something. They ain't got no
family. Lonely people. They are.
Well, hopefully the first of January
will be different. Fingers crossed.
Yeah, you Yeah, you keep telling yourself that.
Yeah, but guess what, Mike? You ain't
been to half the restaurants I've been
to. You haven't been with nowhere near
as many women as I have. You haven't had
more life experience to me outside traveling.
So, I can name you a million restaurants
I've been to. I can name you a million
bars I've went to. I can name you all
the clothes I've got. So, I've got more
life experience than you in other ways.
And it's not a contest. This isn't a
contest. This is another thing. Why are
you trying to have a contest with a stranger?
Why are you trying to compare your life
to a stranger, bro?
Are you trying to feel better or what? I don't understand.
I can go to [ __ ] China tomorrow if I
want to. Got the money, got the funds,
but what's I don't understand your point.
What the [ __ ] bro? This community is
very disabled, bro. Very disabled.
Yeah, very disabled on the people on here, bro.
that Joe F is disabled as well. How can
you moan about keyboard warriors on
Reddit when he's never going to meet
anyone and say anything to anyone's face?
But you moan about keyboard warriors.
You're the biggest keyboard warrior
going. You're worse than bloody nons.
You can't even talk on the panel. Jesus Christ.
You only go out to approach women only
to be rejected again. I've had more
women than Jo will ever have, ever had,
and ever will have.
weird. These people are weird.
And then what makes me laugh is your
life is the worst it's ever been and it
won't change in 2026. And that's one
thing even you will agree with me on.
Now I'm telling you right now that 90%
of the people in this community has got
a worse life than me.
Like 90% minimum. I'd say probably
there's like 5 10% that's actually got a
life and [ __ ] But man, 90% of these
people ain't got no life outside of
YouTube. They don't leave the house.
They're on YouTube to the from the time
they wake up to the time they go to bed.
The sad bastards. So, how can my life be
worse than theirs? What the [ __ ] Like I
said, they don't come and hang out and
put their cameras on for a reason.
There's a big reason for that. Triple H.
Always remember that.
And always remember when they have been
doxed as well, these people
I wouldn't be talking about people on
Reddit being keyboard warriors when
you're never going to meet anyone and
say anything to anyone's face. I
definitely definitely definitely would
not be talking about keyboard warriors.
You know what I mean?
Disabled community, bro. Disabled community. Proper
Yeah, I was going to have a bass on the FOB's um
trip 8, but I never
I was going to play the slot. Yeah, I never
sniffed or set that under today. Are you disabled?
I mean, a disabled person would come out
with something like that. You must be disabled, bro.
Must be disabled. Saying something like that. Proper
Why did you watch Timmy's property video? [clears throat] Did you Did you? Yep.
Yeah, man. It's a madness.
How long did it take Red Star to come on
uh when I block them? Triple H.
Did it take like 10 minutes or what?
How long did it How long did it take? [laughter]
I'm bored today, bro. I might go watch a Spongebob movie.
I need to be careful with my teeth,
though. I need to lay off the sugar.
It's been been feeling better to be fair.
You need to be careful, bro.
How long did it take? before
to come on like 10 minutes.
Yeah, they will do something.
They will do something, mate. Trust me,
they will. They [ __ ] my teeth up.
That's why I'm cutting back on them.
Yeah, I had a milkshake yesterday from McDonald's.
Yeah, I had a McDonald's uh yesterday
[clears throat] when I woke up. I had a
Big Mac meal with nuggets and a banana milkshake.
I'm just cutting back on the cloak to be
fair. Just cutting back. I bought a can
today. I'm only going to have that can go.
Why don't you like the FB Triple H?
Yeah, he was playing ball roulette in it. Yeah.
have to gamble or spin. [ __ ] hell.
But you can win on it. Trip the bar
roulette. I put 60 in before I got to
a,000. I just took it one summer. But um
yeah, I remember that summer, bro. I had
bare money, bro. Oh my god. But I like 260 in. Yeah. Let's go.
There are so many stuck up [ __ ] in
this country, bro. So, I'm just on my Instagram.
Is there like any normal woman out
there? I don't think so.
I don't think so, bro.
Turn the final sense. What's up?
You know what? I think we're doing the
world of good. Just a little part-time job.
Part-time job will do the world of good, mate.
You're just as bad and as weird as PJ. Chilling, bro.
Yeah, I'm chilling.
Got no plans today. Yeah.
>> [clears throat]
>> What are you doing, brother?
stuck up [ __ ] in this country though,
bro. [ __ ] hell. [ __ ] I've seen recently. Wow.
I'm just seeing that, bro. That's why
I'm saying it.
No one ever says anything about that, do they?
Allowed to say any of that stuff.
You're not allowed to say any of that
stuff cuz that means you're skinned
apparently to Jo. If you say women are
stuck up or whatever, that means you got no money.
Yeah, that's Jose for all logic. Oh
yeah, I forgot about that, bro. Yeah,
you having to go on the fies.
You're not having to go on the fies, huh? [ __ ] that. Oh [ __ ]
Oh [ __ ] me. I'm in my little nest of course.
What the hell? >> Yeah.
So how you going to gamble now then?
Triple H, I know you going to gamble
with like £100 and doing fish and
frenzy, but it's not worth it, bro. You
can't even get a bonus on the [ __ ] thing. But
if I want to gamble, I just use my
sister's account and just do roulette on that.
Yeah, I was going to play fishing frenzy, but
when you next gambling. Oh, I don't
know. I done a football bet on boxing day. Triple.
Yeah, I done a fourfold both teams to
score. I got two out of four. I was so close, bro. kind of.
I was kind of close.
I could probably go out today and play some pool.
Have a few drinks, but no, it's Sunday.
Don't be bothered.
See, this isn't just YouTube, though,
bro. You know when people in here say
this is just YouTube, I disagree, bro.
Cuz these people on here tried to get
people's money stopped. They tried to
get people killed. So it's not just
YouTube. So when people sit there and
say, "Yeah, it's just YouTube." It isn't
just YouTube, bro. If it was just
YouTube, it would stay on YouTube. This
stuff on YouTube don't stay on YouTube.
So how could it just be YouTube?
Yeah. All I needed was Heraford and
Enfield time to score, bro. Almost. Almost, man. Morning.
It's not just YouTube.
There's no point playing chess with
Timmy. I will never play a game of chess
with Timmy, ever.
I will never ever play a game of chess with Timmy.
Yeah, I was looking at cavities and what
caus them and people say it's the net.
They say you need to avoid sweets and
and stuff a lot. Yeah, man.
Who knows? But I never I'm never playing
a game of chess with Timmy. Never. Never
am I playing a game of chess with Timmy. Never.
It's a waste of time, Nicole, playing um
a game of chess with Timmy.
Oh, I don't know if he's doing okay, but
I'm doing okay. I'm just in my little nesticles.
The dating's been crap. The call
same old stuck up women will never change lad'll never change.
I might go for a drink soon, you know.
Not today, but Oh no.
At least my mouth feels better. I was
stinking, bro. Oh,
nothing worse than a tooth faker. >> [laughter] >> H burger
that [ __ ] Okay.
Anything else? Yes.
There's greasy, man.
I'm just chilling, man. I had a
breakfast in Weather Spoons.
Are they still going on about that
burger trip rates? That's so old now. Gosh. Yeah.
Yeah. My my my tooth hygiene is good to be fair.
Yeah. Do you reckon you can get nonsle
as a part-time job to approach? Just,
you know, like a 50 a day cashing hand
job or something? He'll do him the world
of good. Get off of YouTube. He'll not
be skint anymore. Um,
you know, just like a little part-time job.
What do you think? You could get him a
part-time job, couldn't you? Like, you
know, £50 a day or something.
Get him out of the house or in his case,
get him out the bedsuit. Um, he'll do
him the world of good. I reckon that's
why I think a lot of these people on
here need a little job.
He'll do him the world of good.
Reckon you can get him a little job.
You reckon um you reckon you can get him
a little job?
Get a little part-time job.
Yeah. Nons said to Joe, "Why don't you
like me? You don't know me.
Well, I I know you. You're you you're a [ __ ] nons.
You're a [ __ ] virgin nons [ __ ] I
[ __ ] know you. You skin [ __ ] You know,
someone says you're just as bad and as
weird as PJ. What? Let's chill. Nah, bro.
I won't be drinking until probably
February, March, to be fair.
No, I drunk on Christmas.
I had a Guinness and another beer.
Yeah, I'm skin. Yeah. Yeah. Skin.
So, why are you on YouTube then? Are you skin?
How come you're on YouTube first thing
in the morning? Then you must be skinned. No,
I can't see the comments. I know.
Let me see. O,
no money, no woman. What have I told you
about talking about yourself, Red Star?
That's not nice to talk about yourself like that.
You've got no woman, no girlfriend, no
money. That's you. What have I told you
about talking about yourself? Gosh darn
it. Putting yourself down. We was
actually saying to Triple H about
getting your boyfriend a part-time job.
Get him get him some uh money in his
pocket, you know. What do you think, Red Star?
Your your skint boyfriend in a shitty bedit, you know.
Get him a little job, then he won't be
skinn like you. What do you think, Red
Star? That's good. You know,
>> Red Star, listen,
when you can join and show your face,
come back to me. Until then, I'm
ignoring you and I'm actually blocking
you as well. One second.
You're blocked. See you later. Bye-bye now.
I just blocked on the wrong channel. My bad, bro.
Yeah, come back when you've got the
balls to show your face.
See you later, keyboard warrior.
And that's how you know trips that these
people on here are skinn because of what
they do on here every day, bro. They
must be skinned to sit on YouTube every
day doing what they do. They've got to
be extra skin. The amount of time and
effort that they put into this, bro, it
just goes to show that they're
everything that they call other people.
Remember like Christmas, bro? Yeah. When
people were saying that, "Oh, you got no
family. You got no family." And I went
on live went on Christmas live before I
go to my sisters for 5 minutes and then
people's watching. Bro, what these
people really mean is it's themselves,
but because they're so disabled, they
don't even realize they're talking about themselves.
When they're calling people skin,
they're actually talking about
themselves, but they're so disabled,
they don't actually know that they're
that they're talking about themselves, you know?
You know what I mean, brother?
Yeah. Like I, like I said, I can go and
show money right now, Triple H. I've got
money. I can easily go and show money,
bro. But I'm not showing money to these
people because what happened before when
I showed money to these people.
You remember trips? What happened last
time? I showed money to these wasters.
You know how you know what they do, bro.
You know what they do on here. You're
younger and better looking than them.
They don't like it.
That's the truth, lad. The truth hurts.
Yeah, I have shown money. I've shown £6,000.
I've shown £6,000 and made you all run away.
Yes, I have. I've shown you £6,000 and
I've made you all run away.
But again, when you're younger and
better looking than these people, they
don't like you. I was thinking about
this on my walk home as well. You know,
yeah, you want to talk. Okay, join. Tell
Red Door to join the hangouts then.
You okay? You want freedom? Okay, join the hangouts.
The box is for people to join. Okay. Yeah,
these people on here are proper wasters.
Triple H. They're real wasters on here,
you know, bro. Proper proper wasters.
They're proper proper wasters on here, lad.
Proper proper wasters.
Proper wasters on here, lad. That red
star is another fat ugly mong with
nothing in life. It's a trend with these people.
They don't like people that are younger
and better looking than them. They want
people on their level, bro. Do you not
do you not understand what it is? Triple
H. They've been doing it for bloody
years. They were saying that my family hates me.
Yet these people was on YouTube Christmas triple.
They were on YouTube Christmas.
I can't afford to drink.
Yeah, I can't afford to drink. Really? Really?
Okay, you keep telling yourself that.
Yeah, these people must be skin. Come on
here every day doing what they do. They
must be skint themselves. They are skin
Red Star is a fat, ugly, skit [ __ ] Why
do you think he won't join the box? You
need an ugly [ __ ]
Just like Joseph Ferrar, just like these
other people. They're fat and ugly
That's why they need attention off strangers
cuz they're [ __ ] fat, ugly, disabled wasters.
Have you seen the [ __ ] that they accuse
people of on here as well? Um, Triple.
That's five people without a family on
Christmas. Do you remember Do you remember Monty?
Do you remember Monty? Um, preprates.
That's five people without family on Christmas. [laughter] Yeah.
It's always been projection with these people.
Always has and always will be.
The joys of being younger and better
looking than these people.
looking than these fat, ugly people on here. Yeah,
I say I'm the best looking on this
community. You know that. Uh, Triple,
why do you think these people harass me
every day? That boy, what's your opinion?
Peter B had been
uh I think these people on here are
proper disabled, bro. I I swear now the
[ __ ] that they come out with.
Yeah. Why do you think these people
harass me on here? It's weird, isn't it, lad?
I think they hate because I'm younger
and better looking than them personally.
That's why I think they do it. I'm not
saying I'm right. That's just my opinion.
There's loads of reasons they could do
it. You know,
I think they're jealous, bro. I'm sorry
if I sound delusional, but I generally
generally think that they are.
I actually do think they're jealous
cuz people that are happy with
themselves can't be on the internet for
[ __ ] eight years harassing people
that they don't know. They they just
can't. They they generally just can't,
you know, bro. They can't sit on the internet
harassing people that they don't know
for eight years. People that are happy
don't do that.
Yeah, they keep saying that I'm going
bold when I'm not. I don't know why they
keep saying I'm going bored.
And Pat mustard on the same thing as
well. They keep saying that I'm bald and
I'm nowhere near Bing.
Strange people, bro.
My beard's getting long to be fair, man. Look,
could really go barbber soon.
Yeah, I just got barbers, bro. Ski.
these [snorts] people on here are a lot
of people on here, bro. Really disabled, aren't they?
Do you like Joseph Fra? That boy. What's
your opinion on Jo?
I don't mind me. I just think he's a bit
of a biased nonslover.
And I don't think he should hate Reddit
for being keyboard warriors when he's a
keyboard warrior himself. To be fair,
that's the only thing I'd say.
You don't like Reddit because they're
keyboard warriors, but you're also a keyboard warrior.
So what the [ __ ] range? Yeah.
And this ain't about you. Yeah. And your
position in life, but you're in a better
position than they are,
you know. Is my life perfect? [ __ ] no, bro.
My life is definitely not perfect at
[ __ ] uh 28. But you got to understand
that these people are older than you and
they're in a worse position in life than
you are. Looks, money,
you know, they in every way these people
are worse than you. They're in a worse
position than you.
You know, you can never be a loser
considered to um compared to these
people. Does that make sense?
These people are old. They're bored.
They're fat, they're ugly, their skin,
they're in a worse position than you
would ever be.
Like that's that's what I mean on on
here, lad. You know,
you know what I mean?
My life's not even bad to be honest.
It's just like I I should be with
someone. I should be settled down with
someone, you know, at this age. That's
the only thing that's quite bad.
Um, other than that, I'd say my life is just
like normal, is it? It's not the worst.
It's not the best. Should be better.
Could be a lot worse.
Just like in the middle, you know?
And uh that's what I think me. >> And weirdo.
I'm not even ending it. See, this is
what I mean, bro. They're just They're
just disabled on here, bro.
I'm not even ending it, me. I can't be
honest. If it gets banned, it gets
banned. I don't really give a [ __ ]
That's what I mean. They're just
disabled on here, aren't they?
Proper proper disabled. I'm set.
I'm going anyways.