Oops.
I thought my charger was
[ __ ] legit thought my charger was
[ __ ] all good [Music]
Good. How many people drive?
I'm not reacting to these little self
projecting sounds anymore
by let them keep wasting their life
repeating themselves. Let them crack on,
man. They're only They're only
psychologically [ __ ] with their own
head. I won't be reacting to them
anymore. So, there we go.
I had this crisp in ages, man. Best crisps.
McCoy blame wheel
straight. Bless, bro. That's reload.
debate if I should get
um or not. Wow,
that's not [ __ ]
Get up. Go. weird. Stop
selfjection. It's no good for your
mental health. I've said this many times,
lad. You're doing your mental health no
good talking about
yourself. It's not good.
Stop talking about
yourselves. You've been doing it for 12
years now. Get a grip. Leave your house
once in a while. You might be happier,
man. Nah, never skint as you,
Timmy. Never skin as
you. Right. Listen, Timmy, let me tell
you something, bro. I asked you this
question just like I asked all of these people,
right? Are you
my Are you my personal bank
account? Or like, are you my personal
bank account? No, you're not. So, how do
know like how much people
have? It's weird, man. Like you call
people skint because you're skint
yourselves. And even if you had money,
what would you actually do? What would
you actually do with the
money? If you had money, most of you on
here are virgins. You have nothing but
projection every day. You don't leave
your house. Like what would you actually
do if you got given
money? Yeah, we're all scared. You are
all scared. Of course you're all
scared, bro. Most of the people on this
community ask him. Of course they are.
That's why they go on about skins
because it's their own lives that
they're talking about. And I'm not
repeating this anymore. Anyways, we're
not we're not reacting to these self
projectors. Anyways, I'm not talking
about this no
more. What I will show you though is I
showed you I showed you [ __ ]
£1,100. I showed you an £1,100 I showed
£1,100 two week uh no like two two weeks
ago and you couldn't show me nothing. So [ __ ] off.
You know, Gary, you
know, I'm meeting her
um next Sunday, but I want to try and
get some approaches in next week. I'm
going to do three days a week. I think
it's going to be very [ __ ] long cuz
I've got to keep my options open at the
same time, you know, bro. So,
uh, so I'm going to [ __ ] uh do that.
Yeah, I'm going to do a few days next
week. [ __ ] maybe maybe the week
after. I'm [ __ ] knackered, bro. Oh.
It's not that warm, bro. It's not that
warm. No, it's not that warm. It's not
going to get warm until
May. Yeah. Stop calling yourself skin.
It's no good for your mental
health. You people are skin. That's why
you go on about skin every day. Take
one. No one.
Yeah, you people ask you that's why you
go on about money every
day cuz you asking it yourselves.
Anyways, yeah, it's not going to get
warm until like May.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Of course
it is. Anyways, we're ignoring these
little self projected. Anyways, we're
talking about this the weather. Um the
weather is going to get better around May.
Sorry, Gary. Man, you're going to get
these little self projectors. Um,
they've been doing it for years now. The
same three, four people that just self
self-reflect their life on this
platform. Just ignore them. That's what I'm
doing. Just ignore the little spatics
and block him. That's what I'm doing,
bro. I'm not even entertaining him. I
was just talking to [ __ ] Timmy. So,
yeah. The weather is um the weather's
not getting better, bro. It's still
cold. It's warmer, but it's still cold.
So, you're not talking you're talking May, June,
maybe. Yeah, [ __ ] exhausted,
mate. Is exhausted,
lad. Uh just self projected like they always do.
Yeah, just self projecting like they
always do. Story of their lives.
Um, yeah, I had a date yesterday. It was
good. I ain't seen her until
uh All right, Chico, why don't you go
suck him up, you little
grass. Oh, it is. Yeah, I seen you on uh
what's his channel? Red Star's channel,
you little ducky boy. You little pussyo
trying to big up people for grassing. Go suck your
mother. How about that one, you little
[ __ ] I've seen you talk [ __ ] behind my
[ __ ] back. Go suck your mom, bro. You
[ __ ] I've seen you, you little
two-faced [ __ ] you little dirty [ __ ]
Go [ __ ] back to L, you
[ __ ] Yeah, you [ __ ] well are,
mate, cuz I've seen you comment on Red
Star's thing like [ __ ] like a month
ago. You're just like that Ricky
Millington. And you know what makes me
laugh about these people, Gary? Let let
me tell you something about these
people. Yeah. Let me tell you one thing
about these people, brother.
Yeah. You know, when I used to moan
about women being [ __ ] and stuff, like
I still think they are. I still think
they are all the same and [ __ ] but I
just get on with it now. But you know
what makes me laugh, bro? Is these people,
right? Yeah. These people go on about
women and how women are not the problem.
But ask yourself this question, Gary.
When was the last time these people went
out and spoke to a woman? Like, you
know, Ricky Millington, when was the
last time one of these people went out
and actually interacted with a woman?
And that will answer your question.
Probably over a decade. So, what the
[ __ ] would they know? That's the thing.
Like, when you know, if you come on here
and you moan about women and you winge
about women and they're trying to tell
you, "Oh, it's you. They're not to
blame." Where was the last time these
people actually dealt with women in
these westernized countries in this
climate? They haven't, bro. So, what
would they know? That's that's that's
the that's the thing that made me die
that. And that's it's like that Ricky
Millington. He doesn't probably doesn't
even leave his
house. Doesn't even have the balls to
approach a [ __ ] woman. What the [ __ ]
would he know? You know what I'm saying?
That's what you need to you need to really think, lad.
Yeah. Yeah. Going out approaching three
times a week. [ __ ]
me. Just the thought of it makes me
tired. Like literally the thought of it
literally just makes me tired, bro. I'm not even
joking. Like just thinking about it, it
just makes me fall asleep.
It's It's [ __ ] long,
bro. One second, bro. So yeah,
bro. No, I'm not putting a link in.
You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] man. Go
self-reflect on another channel. This is
what I mean. These people ruin my channel,
bro. Like Timmy self-reflectors, like
they did. They ruined the
channel. Like the first comment, yeah, I
was live for about 1 minute, Gary.
You're skinned Morgan owned you. Like,
you're not going to get a reaction. It's
boring now. You've been saying the same
old same old repeating now for [ __ ]
god knows how long. It doesn't even
offend or bother anyone. It's boring
now, you know? And that's and that's
what it is. It is boring. Like, you're
supposed to be psychologically [ __ ]
with my head. You're supposed to be
owning me, but instead you're just
sending me to sleep like a
codable. They're boring as [ __ ] They
just they because they they can't
psychologically [ __ ] with anyone because
they just repeat themselves. You see,
they repeat the same old same old. It
doesn't affect no one.
Anyways, I'll put a link up anyways. Yeah.
Yeah. I Yeah, I should be a psychologist
cuz I know what these people do. Like I
don't even know that guy saying I'm
skinn socially awkward. I was like,
"Congratulations, buddy. You've just
described your own life." You
know, you know, they they literally just
talk about their own
lives, their own their own existence,
social awkward, skin, no friends. It's
literally all theirelves that they're
talking about. That's why I think I
should be a psychologist,
bro. That's it, bro. Hello, PJ. It was
the will me. Sorry, I was trying to get
I was trying to get him Mongols and he
wouldn't let me in. So, I was changing
the names around. He's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
So, Timmy, I showed you 1100 pound two
weeks ago. That was two weeks ago,
right? PJ, let's have a serious chat.
You're going about people going on about
their lives on YouTube and that and you
go on about your life on here all the
time. So, you're being a bit of a
hypocrite, lad. No, I'm not. Yeah, you
are. You are.
No, but PJ, if you come on live and tell
the world you're a virgin or tell the
world, you're going to get a virgin.
Yes, I'm a virgin. I've never had sex.
I've never had two virgin. He keeps
talking over me, so I'm going to kick
him. You come on my channel, right? And
you called me skin. I told you that I
showed you £1,100 two weeks ago. You
didn't show me nothing. A B. The only
virgins on YouTube are you and Sha. You
are the biggest virgin Mary's going. You
are the biggest virgins going to
mankind. Like you and Sean are the
biggest virgins going. You two are the
only like the only certified virgins on
here. Oh, let me tell let me show you
something actually, Timmy. Since you
want to call me a virgin. One second.
Let me put this up actually. This is me getting a One
second. This is me getting a [ __ ]
There you go. That is me getting a
[ __ ] But why are you telling the
world you got a [ __ ] No one cares,
PJ. Let's be honest. And
that's me getting a [ __ ] Timmy. But
no, but no one gives a [ __ ] PJ, if
you've had a [ __ ] or what. But you're
still a virgin, PJ, cuz having a [ __ ]
is not technically a virgin.
PJ, I spoke to your wh house the other
day and they said that your dick
couldn't get it up. Do you know what to
me? Yeah. The day you and Shaw lose your
virginity, you'll be We've lost our
virginities, bro. You're the one who
hasn't. You've never lost your
virginity. You're still a virgin.
Anyway, PJ, you going to Are you going
to withdraw £1,000? Put it in the bank
and make the biggest virgins going to We're virgin.
PJ Okay, PJ, you got hard on now. PJ,
you got hard on now. PJ PJ I've been
seeing lots of women, PJ. I've had a lot
more women than you. And I'm not being
funny. Sean had a bird. So he's been
shagging that bird back in his [ __ ]
bed. He can't get How can you How can
you be a virgin when you've been
shagging a bird back in his bed? Because
he's never shagged the bird. He's still
a virgin. You know, he's just couples.
Listen, do you know how many couples
have not had sex for 3 months? Do you
know how many people relationships that
don't have a dick? PJ, we all know I've
never been in a relationship and I've
had more sex than you and Sean.
So that get more sex than people in
relationships. He's never shag no bird.
Okay. If I call myself a if I call
myself and are the biggest virgins.
Okay. If I call myself are virgins. He's
triggered today. He's done. The reason
why you and Sean going about virgins is
cuz you're one yourself. You would only
know to be one. I'm being triggered. I'm
telling you. No, you're not. You're
triggered. No, you and Sean are the
biggest virgins. So, how can I can I ask
you a simple question? Can I ask you a
simple Can I ask you a simple question,
PJ? If I call myself a virgin, would you
be happy then? Yeah. So, if Jean is a
virgin, if he's going to like stare at
his girl in the bed non-stop in the nude
with her tits hanging out, you know,
like as couples, she doesn't even see
her tits. She's Listen, listen. Okay,
let me ask you this question. Okay.
Okay. Okay. Let me ask you this
question. When when does he have when
does he have time to shag his bird when
he's on YouTube constantly stalking me?
He's not constantly stalking me. He's
off. Okay. Do you want me to show you
the channel? Do you want me to show you
the channel again? I've seen the
channel, PJ, and I do. So, we have no
time to be shagging that disabled. PJ PJ
PJ's triggered. He's triggered. PJ,
wait. Hold on a minute. I've literally
shown One second. One second. I've shown
me in bed with women. I've shown me get
[ __ ] And you still call me a
virgin. What do you want, Paige? I medal.