You know, just checking to see if it's
still the same people on YouTube or if
they've got a life yet.
You know what I do? My little checks, my
little welfare checks.
Yeah. I just want to see if it's the
same people who can't get off of YouTube.
Currently, it's zero people watching me. Yeah.
I won't be reacting to these ugly fat
losses anymore anyways. I've just come
on to see if it's the same people.
Yeah, I want to see when this IQ's
taking place. It's almost 2026 and you
see the same people on YouTube.
The same [ __ ] wasters, bro. They
ain't got a life.
Oh, you're still on YouTube, Bob. bills.
I've come on to see if it's the same
people on YouTube.
I won't be reacting to these wasters
anymore. By the way, I was talking to
Laney about this. And even Laney says
that they're jealous.
So, I'm going to stop reacting to these
uh jealous people. They ain't got a life
that's got nothing to. So, yeah. Bro,
I'll [snorts] be off YouTube next year
anyways. Well, I'm off YouTube now. I'm
I'm only coming to see who's on. I'll be
off here, man.
I've lost I've lost brain cells because
of these people.
I've actually lost brain cells, bro.
Because of these people.
No, he's not meeting me. I offered to
meet him. He will not meet me. He said
under any circumstances, he won't meet
me. So, he's another keyboard warrior,
which is mad cuz he complains about
people on Reddit.
He complains about people on Reddit
being a keyboard warrior, but he's a keyboard warrior.
Yeah, I'm live to see if you people are
still on there. Just like I was live on
Christmas for 5 minutes to see if you
people are still on there or here
rather. And no, he said he will meet me
under no circumstances. Bro, like I said
to you, I was in Weather Spoons
yesterday having a think about this,
right? and how it does not make sense. I
want everyone's opinion on this because
I actually developed brain damage when I
was thinking about this. Um, he says,
just listen to this, right? Speaking of
this, Jo, I will address him by his
names. I do not like him and never have.
I don't know him. All I ever said is
that I find it near impossible to
believe that someone that has had a
girlfriend three years a virgin that you
continuously say I defend him and call
him a virgin.
Well, you have done it multiple times.
And if you do not like someone, you
wouldn't defend them. And that is
defending them. Whereas, if you go on um
the the Skint Virgin channel, when he's
calling me Skint, when he's calling me a
virgin, you never see anyone say, "Oh,
he's shown six grand." You are a
non-slegs lover. If I don't like
someone, I wouldn't defend him. That
does not make any sense. So you are a nonslegs lover
because you know I have not seen you
bring up any kind of women that I have
that I have been with on nonslegs's
channel or the seven grand that uh what
was it the six grand that I showed? So
you're saying that you don't like
someone but then you're straight sucking
their dick when I'm calling them a
virgin. Make it make sense. You want you
want to make that make sense?
You would not see me saying, "Oh, well,
LJ's got a virgin because he's got
kids." I wouldn't even say that. I would
not defend anyone I don't like. So, he
does not. This is part I think these
people are actually disabled on here.
They don't even know what they're
saying. I generally think they are
disabled on here. I generally think they
are disabled on here, Dusty. You know,
so you don't like someone, but you've
defended them multiple times when yes,
it's possible for somebody that's been
in a relationship for 3 years with
someone that's got disabilities to be a
virgin. However, it's not possible for
someone like me to be a virgin that's
proved they've had sex, but I don't see
you talking about any of the polos. And
then he's and then he's and then he's
and then he's going to be like, "Oh,
well, you can defend yourself." Same as
launch legs. He can defend himself.
Same thing goes to him. He can defend
himself, but you're so far up his ass
coming out of his dick whenever I go for
him. Am I lying? Am I lying or am I
telling the truth?
Tell me if if you if you think I'm
talking [ __ ] because I think what I'm
saying is very very valid.
You know what your opinion on it?
So it does not does not make any sense.
Did you not just hear what I said? Did
you just completely dismiss what I said?
I want people's opinion on it. Thailand.
Ben, I've got a question since no one
since no one else will answer this for
me, bro. So maybe you could answer it
for me. You're in Thailand, I'm guessing.
Bro, I want you to I want somebody to
answer me this now. You're on here, Ben,
and you seem very very unbiased.
I want you to answer this.
To be honest with you, maybe you can answer this.
If I ask you this question, maybe you
can answer it.
So I was saying to this Joseph Ferrar
that he's a nons lover because every
time I say that non legs is a virgin
he's so far to his defense saying oh
he's not he's not he's not a virgin he's
not a virgin [clears throat] he's got a
girlfriend he's got a girlfriend and I
said why do you keep defending him when
you never bring up the porn no that I
put out you never brought up when I've
proven that I've had sex with women and
he he and whenever he's talking [ __ ]
about me I never see Joseph Roar talking
about where I've proved I've had sex and
when I say I proved I've had X I done
more than show a disabled girl for 3
years. Then he wrote um then he wrote Ben Furvy.
One second. He said because
[clears throat] I think you're the only
one that's going to answer this. Um he
said I will address him by his names. I
do not like him and never have. I don't
know him. All I ever said is that I find
it near impossible to believe someone
that has had a girlfriend for 3 years of
virgin. You continually say I defend him
and call him a virgin. You do defend
him. You are constantly up his ass
whenever I'm calling him a virgin,
right? But yet you claim you don't like
him. If you do not like someone, you
would not be defending them. And that is
defending them. It is entirely possible
for someone to have a disabled
girlfriend and not slept with them,
right? Whereas with me, there's it's not
possible for me to be a virgin. I proved
I've had sex. Now, if you go on Nonsex's
channel, you don't see this Jo talking
about the pool nodes, talking about the
money I've shown.
So, make it make sense. Make it make
[ __ ] sense. If you do not like
someone, you would not defend them.
No, it's not about a reaction. I was
talking to my mom yesterday. It's not
about a reaction.
I personally think they're jealous of
me. That's what I personally think, Ben.
And that's what my mom says as well. She
just didn't want to repeat herself.
It's not about a reaction. Even if you
ignore these people, they'll never stop.
It's nothing to do with a reaction. It's
cuz they're jealous of you. It's nothing
to do with a reaction. I was telling
Laney about this yesterday. But what I'm
saying is, Ben, why is he so far
defending him? Oh, he's not a virgin.
He's got a girlfriend. But I don't see
Joe bringing up the money in the women
I've shown on Nex's channel. You know,
I don't see him bringing up that. So,
you say that you don't like him. make it
make sense. It does not make sense. That
does not make sense. The whole statement
don't make sense. This is what makes me
think that they've got autism.
Like proper bad autism on here.
And listen, I stop blaming the reaction.
Even if you ignore them, they will still
do it. This is what I was trying to say
to Laney. Even if you ignore these
people for 10 years, they will still do
it. It's not a reaction. I think it's
jealousy with these people. They can sit
on it. I was like, "Listen, I was I was
on uh what was it? Red Stars thing
yesterday. I was on Red Stars thing
yesterday. Yes, I can show money and I'm
not going to be showing you money cuz
that's self-reflection." [clears throat]
So, enough of that now. End of that.
Yeah, I can show you money, but I'm not
going to. And you can call me skin all
you want. I literally don't care. See,
look at this. Right.
basically. And then but then he'll say
to me, "Oh, well, I don't need to defend
you." Okay, so why are you defending Nonlegs?
What? Okay, so why are you defending Nles?
Nons doesn't need defending. Make it
make sense. You don't like someone, but
you keep defending them. Make it make
sense. Make it make [ __ ] sense. And
this is what makes I personally think
men on here, I don't know you. I think
that they're jealous of me. That's why
they do all of this stuff, bro. I swear
to God, I think they are. You know,
Laney even says it as well. The only
reason she doesn't keep repeating it is
because she's sick of repeating herself.
I don't blame her. You know,
I think it's because they're jealous.
You're younger and better looking. I
stand by what I say, bro. I literally
stand by what I say.
I think it's cuz you're younger and
better looking. And where they failed at
everything in life, they hate you for
it. They take out on you. That's what I think.
Yes. And I've already put the proof out
proof out that he's a nod. So anyways,
I've gone on this Red Star thing. Nice
old photo by the way. And Autumn was
like, "Don't forget he's better looking
than everyone though." The absolute
nerve he has to call anyone fat. Yes,
Autumn, you are fat. That's why you use
filters. I'm not fat. I can put my
camera on right now. I can show my belly
right now. I'm not fat. I'm not long
woke up, by the way. Um, but you are
fat. I've got that nerve by calling you
are fat even with your filters. Just
like a lot of these people on here, they
are fat fat ugly people that ain't got a
life which is why they're not worth
reacting to. You know, part of why they
do this is because they're fat, ugly wasters.
But all I wanted to say, Ben, is that
that whole thing does not make sense.
And then this Joseph said, Ben, that he
has a problem with Reddit because
they're keyboard warriors. I said on two
occasions, I will come up to leads today
and meet you. and he was not having any
of it. So you your whole thing does not
make sense. You're sick on Reddit
because they're keyboard warriors.
You're being a keyboard warrior. You're
writing [ __ ] about people, but you will
never meet anyone. So you're just
another keyboard warrior. It's not an
outfit. It's a dressing girl.
And then Yeah. So like I said, he he
would turn around and say, "Oh, well uh
you don't need defending. Yeah, neither
does your boyfriends need defending, but
you keep sucking his dick every time I
go for him, you fat [ __ ]
And it is entirely possible for somebody
to be in a relationship for 3 years and
be a virgin because he's a big virgin.
It's very possible. Trust me, it is
because he is a virgin. So, it is
possible to answer your question.
So, yeah. And he's also been invited to
come to London multiple multiple times.
Yeah. Anyways, we're not getting into
these same autistic arguments. Anyways,
I just wanted to It's like someone I
don't like. Okay, Ben, I just I'm trying
to understand this. He's saying that he
does. Okay, so it's like Right. Okay, so
say Lord Say Lord Jay, right? And I was
saying to my mom yesterday, she doesn't
understand. Well, I think she does
understand, but you know, I hate these
people, bro. Like, you don't understand
how much I hate these people. If you
ever gave me 20 seconds with one of
these people, I would destroy them.
Yeah, he was at my door and he done
absolutely nothing. We're not having the
same argument, bro. If you're going to
keep bringing the same thing up, I'm
going to block you. Yeah, I am being
realistic. He hid he stood behind a gate
and he done nothing. Yeah, stop living
in the past. It's not a W, believe it or
not. So, yeah, stop being autistic. Stop
repeating yourself. [snorts] Anyways, um
he'll be like, "Oh, um yeah, you know,
he was at my door and he done nothing."
Only his little troops would think
that's a W. He literally done nothing,
bro. Literally. And we're not having the
same argument. I'm not autistic like you
people. I'm not going to sit here and
keep having the same argument over and
over and over again.
You know, brother, you don't speak
facts. You talk [ __ ] He was on my door
and he done nothing.
Yeah. I'm not going over the same thing
over and over again. It's not facts.
It's not facts. You just keep repeating
the same [ __ ] that we've gone over.
You are wrong. You are definitely
definitely wrong. He come in the door
and he done nothing. You're wrong. Yeah,
you are definitely definitely wrong. So
anyways, it's like me. It's like someone
calling LJ a virgin Ben and me saying,
"Oh, he's got kids. He's got kids. He's
not a virgin." But I don't like him. I
generally think this Jo has got special
needs. I generally generally generally
think that he has got special needs.
This guy, I'm not even I think a lot of
these people on here have got special
needs. You know, bro,
you know when you stay on here, Ben, and
you think about it. I was in Weather
Spoons and I waited half an hour for my
breakfast yesterday and I was actually
losing brain cells thinking about this place.
That's how autistic they are. They
actually make you lose brain cells.
Cuz what's as the old saying goes then
that when you surround yourself with a c
certain kind of people long enough, you
kind of turn into one of them. you and
that is the truth even with this you know
same repeating same projection and you
know I'm I'm sure you've known it you've
noticed it yourself you know you've
noticed it yourself with these people
like after 2 days you're like what the
[ __ ] was all that then you come back on
for a day and then it's like okay
whatever it's a day then you come you
come back on the second day and then
it's like and then by the third day
you're brain damaged
You actually turn into them, bro. You
You actually really do turn into them.
You actually do, bro. So, anyways, I've
gone on nonslegs's channel and never
once has Joseph Ra brought up where I've
actually proved I've had sex, where I've
shown money. H. So, I guess he is a
biased non lover. I never called him a
n. I called him a n lover. Does he
defend his nons legs? And yeah, saying
that someone's not a virgin because
they've got a girlfriend is defending them.
Yeah, no one cares about that, bro.
That's repeating. Bor off. You're not
getting a reaction,
brother. You're not getting a reaction.
Give it up. It's boring now. Me and
Elaine had a long chat about this um
yesterday. We watched the movie um
together. Brother, you can keep
spreading autistic lies. No one cares.
you know, you're not getting a reaction
in the story. Yeah. So,
there you go. So, yeah, if you go on
this channel, bro, um you will see. Um
but yeah, Al, I can call you fat because
you are fat. You are a fat bastard that
uses filters. I'm not fat. You are fat.
Your whole body is fat, you know. Yeah.
Yeah, I was watching Netflix yesterday, Dusty.
I was watching um Man versus Baby. It
was pretty funny to be honest. Yeah.
And then and it's autistic as well
because you'll explain something
over and over again, Ben, and they still
don't understand it. Okay. I'll give you
an example. Right. So, I'll turn around
and say, "Why do these people do what
they do?" And then they say they do it
for reaction. Then I'll turn around and
say, "Well, they don't do it for
reaction." Because even if you ignore
them, they will still do it. And then
you explain the same thing about six
times and it doesn't process in anyone's
brain. That's the that's part of the
autism with these people. They don't do
it for for reaction. You could start
doing gym videos. You could never go
live again and they would still do it.
They would literally literally still do it.
They would never ever ever stop. Whether
you reacted or not, they would never
because they're jealous. I know it.
Laney knows it. And that's that. Um,
put it this way, Ben. All of the people
that has done this in the past that's
been exposed has always been in a worse
position than you. And by you, I mean
me. So, just think about it like that.
Four, five people that's been doing this
for years and they've been exposed.
They've always been proven. Um, yeah.
because because what it is with these
people, they're fat, ugly losers.
They're wasters. So, if they can bring
other people down to their level, um
then then they're trying to succeed
because don't forget, you're younger
than them. You're better looking than
them, they're wasters. They've already
been shown to be below your level when
they've been exposed. Bomb, Pat,
Mustard, Gray Cat, they've all been
absolute no hope monsters. And it is a
trend with these people on here. There
is no way someone that is doing this is
younger and better looking than me, bro.
Otherwise, I'll take back everything I
said. If if anyone on here can prove
that they're the same age as me or
younger and better looking than me
that's doing this, I'd be very very very
surprised and I'll be like, I'm wrong
and it's not jealousy. But it's never
going to happen. It's never going to
happen. So, because they're fat, old,
ugly people. That's you know it, bro.
You actually know it. you know,
and it's not just YouTube. I don't
understand when people say, uh, you know,
uh, you you know what I mean? Like you,
it's not just YouTube as well because
it's what these people have done on
here. They've tried getting people's
money stopped. The [ __ ] that they've
done is not just YouTube. Like, I was
prepared to meet that Jo and I would
have smashed these [ __ ] faces and and
for being a biased nonslover, but he
will not meet me. I've tried meeting him
on multiple occasions the same day. He
would not meet me. He's just a keyboard
warrior. He's just a nonsens lover. So yeah,
he didn't come on yesterday. I was going
to ask him, why do you defend someone if
you don't like them?
Because I'm sure they can defend
themselves. I'm pretty sure dogs can defend themselves.
No. [ __ ] dogs lover.
Yeah. So anyways, if you can um if you
can um so how is it possible for someone
like me to be a virgin when I've when
I've proved I've had sex?
Why haven't you why haven't you brought
up on Nons's channel about the porno and
the women that I've been in bed with
multiple times and with the women that's
actually admitted to sleeping with me. I
don't see you on Nons's channel saying that.
And that's how you know Steven Howard
that he's a nons legs lover.
Cuz when Timmy was calling me a virgin,
Steven Howard was backing me up. Not
that I need I don't want to be backed
up, but I'm just saying, you know, I
don't need to be backed up. Nonsense
doesn't need to be backed up. Why are
you getting involved? Are you his
boyfriend or something? I don't say
stuff for the sake of it. Is that your
boyfriend or what?
These people's also on YouTube
Christmas, Ben. Oh, Ben. Bro, I woke up.
Yeah. And the first thing I thought of,
oh, I'm going to I'm going to see if
these people are on YouTube. I'm going
to see if these people are on YouTube.
I know. And And Joseph Farah doesn't say
anything about it. Joseph Farah never
brings it up. The money that I've shown,
the women that I've shown, he never
brings it up. And he says, "Oh, well,
you don't need defending." Well, your
boyfriend nonsense don't need defending.
Well, your boyfriend doesn't need
defending, but you keep defending your
boyfriend and getting involved. So, you
are a non-sl. You are a nonsens lover.
Whether you like it or not, you are. Cuz
someone that's not a nonsens lover will
not be like, "Oh, he's got a girlfriend.
You got a girlfriend, you know, and keep
like [ __ ] getting in the middle of
arguments. That is a non-sl." It is
possible that he's a virgin because he
is a virgin and he will die a virgin.
You know what I mean? Anyways, I was on
you, brother. I was on YouTube for for 5 minutes. Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no. Let me explain it to
you again because you people have got
this tendency of twisting things to your
advantage. So, let me let me explain
this again with this Christmas thing
because you've got a tendency to try to
twist things. So, okay, I was live for 5
minutes. Okay, I'll tell you exactly
what I done, Ben. I clicked the live
stream. I I I clicked the go live upstairs.
Then I went downstairs. As soon as I
went live, I went downstairs. I didn't
look on the phone. I made I made myself
a cup of tea, right? I was nowhere near
my phone when I went live. And I went
upstairs and I ended the live stream.
And there was people on YouTube. They
were on YouTube. I couldn't believe it.
They were on [ __ ] YouTube. All of the
people that were telling me that I've
got no family. All of the people that
were telling me that my family hate me.
These people was on YouTube sat watching
me in less than 5 minutes and they were
typing as well, bro. Cuz I was just
about to leave to go to my sisters. I
went to my sisters at around 10. So I
thought, let me go live for 5 minutes
and quickly end it. I'm not going to
look just just as an experiment. I went
live as an experiment to see if you
people was still on YouTube and you
[ __ ] was. He was on YouTube. [gasps]
You know, I don't Do you know what? I
don't understand. Can I ask you this
question? Yeah. Just be real about it.
You're gonna You're on YouTube
Christmas. Why do you pretend that
you're not on YouTube Christmas? Lord
J's on YouTube Christmas. All of these
people are on YouTube Christmas. Why do
you pretend? I don't understand. Just
own it and say that I'm on YouTube
Christmas. Um and that's it. Just own
it. Just own it, bro.
Just own it. Don't pretend that you're
not going to be on YouTube Christmas.
Yeah, I know, bro. I know. I know. I
know. But you could just be an
exception, bro. There's no, you know,
these people. There's no way that was
that many of these people on YouTube
Christmas and just own you on YouTube.
Stop pretending that you're not on YouTube Christmas, you know,
just stop just why do you why do you
need to pretend that you're not on
YouTube Christmas? When I was at my
sisters, I was watching Body Man and I
was with family. I was with friends and
I was watching Body Man for like a
minute cuz it was funny as [ __ ]
But Ben, I think we're the exception. I
generally don't think these people had
Christmas dinner. I definitely don't
think these people have family.
I think we're the exception, bro. I'm
not even just saying that. Maybe one
other person, but we're we're just the exception.
These people definitely did not have
Christmas dinner, bro. They definitely
did not get any presents.
They definitely definitely didn't. So, yeah.
to cut down on a Coke band because of my cavity.
So, I've had to cut down on drinking
Coke. I had one Coke yesterday. Well, I
had two. I had one of Weber Spoons with
a straw and then I had another one. Um,
I've got a can in the fridge.
Yeah, bro. Trying to cut down on the
Coke, you know, for the old tooth fees. Yeah.
I'm supposed to be going out New Year's
Eve, but I don't think I'm going to, bro. [snorts]
Nah, I don't think I will be.
I didn't eat, you know. I had breakfast
and I didn't eat again.
You still been gambling, Ben 10en. You
still been gambling.
You still been gambling?
And now when I have cups of teas, bro, I
don't even put sugar in it. [snorts] I
kind of got used to it cuz I knew I had
to do that, you know, for for the sake
of the toothies.
Yeah. Ant-Man lives there. Antman lives
in Thailand, Ben. And he teaches English.
Yeah, he teaches English, bro.
Um, and he's living there.
Stop making up autistic lie rumors.
Stop bringing your shitty rumors here,
you little waster. You're not getting a
reaction. Go back to the Lav Mong where
you come from. You're not getting a
reaction here. So piss off with your
little perverted sick autistic rumors.
[snorts] Anyways, Ben, um yeah.
Yeah, he lives in Thailand and he teaches English
talking about me yesterday about me
being living with my mom. Brother,
you're in your 40s. You're one benefit
yourself. You people in a worse position
than I'll ever be. Do you know what
makes me laugh with these people, Ben?
Yeah. Is that they try to judge you, but
they're in a worse position in life than
you are. looks, age, money, everything.
These people are in a worse position in
life than you are and they try to judge
you. This is what makes me laugh.
It's not even like God is judging you.
It's not even like people that are
higher a higher are judging you. These people, bro,
um these people are in a worse position
in life than you. Which is why I always
found funny when they try to judge you.
They're in a worse position than you
are. and they try to judge you. That's
funny as [ __ ]
But I guess that's just a way to make
themselves feel better about the the
fact that their life is [ __ ]
and [ __ ] Their life's [ __ ] and um Yeah.
I can't get over that Cole thing, bro.
It's so It's so copying, isn't it, Ben?
Hey, Ben. Did you watch the new horror
film, The Housemaid?
You should watch it. It's It's a good uh
Yeah, I will be, bro. I will be.
Did you watch it? See me, I don't go by
names, Ben. I I don't I don't go by
names. Me, I don't I don't like to show
off. I don't I don't like to, you know,
fit in with the crowd.
That's not me, bro. I don't do things like that.
I don't like to fit in with the crowd
like a certain person's
attractive. I can't get over that.
Sorry, [clears throat] bro. I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry. It just makes me
laugh. Someone hasn't to having to copy
other people to not feel left out. Uh
yeah, probably. Bro, he was just showing
off. If you think about it, Dusty, a lot
of the things in his life has always
been projection. Come to think of it,
when I was younger, I didn't realize
calling me a virgin. He's the virgin
himself. Saying that I'm gay, he's the
one that's gay. That's why he always
used to talk about Shevel Cole because
he wanted people to stop thinking that
he was gay. If you actually think of it,
all of it's been projection with this
little weasel skin. He's skint.
Uh, everything has literally been him. I
can't think of a one thing that has not
been this Orington loser in a bedet. I
can't think of one thing that's never been him.
I can't think of it, bro.
Did you know that? Uh, Ben, if you don't
find a certain uh celebrity attractive,
you're gay. Did you know that?
It's nice to have your sexuality
confirmed by a [ __ ] virgin who's
never had sex. >> [snorts]
>> Whoa, man. That's uh that's mad.
I'm a bit hungry, you know.
Yeah, I can call you um fat Autumn
because you are fat. I'm not fat.
I'm definitely definitely definitely not
fat. And I'll tell you one thing now on
that Red Star post, all of these people
that are trying to call me fat are
fatter than me.
Don't [ __ ] tell nonslegs that he will
call you gay.
Don't [ __ ] Don't [ __ ] um tell
nonslegs that. He'll go [ __ ] mad.
Yeah, this Joseph was like, "What the
hell? When was that madness? No wonder
he's on the egg diet. Christ."
Okay. Why don't you show what you Why
don't you show your face? Why don't you
show your belly?
You know, these people will never ever
show their faces. They'll never ever
show anything because they are I'm sick
of repeating this. Fat, ugly people.
Same thing with you, Wes. Why don't you
come on your Why don't you come on
camera and show your face?
Why don't you show what you look like?
Why don't you show your belly, you fat
bastard? Oh, another thing is as well.
Yeah. Do you know what made used to make
me laugh on air, right? When you'd gain
a bit of weight and they'd be like, "Oh,
you're piling on weight." When these
people are literally fat and ugly,
they're literally fat ugly people
telling you that you're piling on
weight. When these people are really,
really fatter and uglier than you.
That's what made me always laugh about
these people is they're fatter than you.
They're uglier than you will ever be.
And they're coming on here judging you.
Wasters. Absolute wasters.
New Year's. No, I'm not going out. New
I won't be going out New Year's. And I
will not be going out uh until March.
Like I said, Ben, I'm going to try and
join the pool industry. And yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. And then he's not going to beat me
and then another and then it's going to
go around and round and round and round
in circles again. But yeah, that Jo is
not consistent. He can't talk about
people on Reddit when what he's doing is
being a keyboard warrior. He will never
ever meet anyone ever. He said that he
will never meet anyone. Yet he still
talks [ __ ] and he does it behind
people's back. I said I said to him,
"Call me a call me a sad bastard to my face.
I said, "Call me a sad bastard to my
face, you fat slob." And he won't do it.
You will not do it, bro.
Right. And I'll repeat myself for the
hundth millionth time. Even if you don't
react to them, they will still do it. I
will repeat myself again, you know, for
the millionth time. Just like I used to
repeat my struggles with women that used
to get dismissed. Yes, I'm talking about
them now. Does it matter whether I talk
about them or not? Because even if you
don't react, they will still never leave
you alone. I've had to explain this a
million times, Ben.
Whether you react or you don't, they
will never leave you alone. So what's
what's the difference, brother? You
know, they will never leave you alone
cuz you're younger and you're better
looking than them. That's what kills
them. It's like what Ronald Pump used to
say. Why does it matter if you're
reacting or you're not reacting, they're
still going to do it? So,
right, do you really want to make a bet
in the new year? You really, really want
to make a bet. Okay, I'm going to make a
bet, right? Starting from the 1st of
January. So, if I come on here, right,
and I make videos and I don't go live
and I don't react to any of these
people. I will not go on their channel.
I will not go on their channel and they
will and they will and they're harassing
me, right? Is that what you're saying?
So, if I ignore these people for a year,
right, right, you're telling me these
ugly fat wasters will not keep harassing
me. Is that what you're saying? Cuz I
I'm willing to put a bet that they will,
bro. You know, I'm willing to put this
to the test. You know,
brother, you're already better than
them, brother. You're already miles
better than these people. You don't even
need to join the gym. You are miles
better than these people. You're
younger. You're better looking. You
don't have to come on the internet every
day harassing people like they do.
Harassing people that they don't know
because they've been bullied all their
life. You're miles better than these
people already, bro. You know,
you know what I'm saying?
You know what I mean?
So yeah, if you went, like I said, if
you do videos, if you do videos,
if you do videos, right, and you don't
act and you don't go live, they will
never leave you alone. They will never
ever leave you alone, bro. They will
never ever ever ever leave you alone.
They will never leave you alone.
Because what it is is you're younger and
better looking than these people. I
strongly think it is that Ben. I
strongly think it is jealousy with these
people. I generally generally generally
generally do if you go on people's
channels right you you will see the
amount of people that's obsessed with me
and and and it's like well and then you
got to think you're younger you're
better looking you need to think outside
the box. Look at these people that do
this. This Jamie Thompson fat ugly will
not leave you alone. Keep stalking you
every day. These people will not leave
you alone because they are jealous of
you. That's the only thing. It's got to
be jealousy. Elaine has said the same
thing multiple multiple times.
You do not understand how much time and
effort it takes to come on the internet
every day harassing people every single
day of your life. You do not understand
what it's like what what it takes, you
know, and they don't bully no one. They
show themselves up. These people talk
about themselves. They bully themselves.
They talk down about themselves. But,
you know, at the end of the day, they're
harassing. They don't bully no one. They're harassers. Yeah.
You know, ask these people to put their
cameras on and show their face. They
will not do it. Why would they not do
it? Because they're fat and ugly. What
I'm saying about them is right. What I'm
saying about Red Star is right. They're
fat and ugly and disabled.
Ugly people laying around on the
internet hating people that are better
than them in every way. Better money,
better looks. The reason I do not show
money to these people anymore, Ben, is
because every time you show these people
money, it's the same thing. It's the
same autistic thing. Every time you show them money,
you know, I have shown these people
money thousands. I've shown better
looks. I've shown better women and they
still will not leave you alone. If you
are younger and better looking on here,
they will never leave you alone. I've
noticed that, bro. I have noticed that
with these people. They turn their nose
up to anyone younger and better looking.
Because where all of these people are
fat, ugly wasters like Smokey Be Red,
they don't like anyone younger and
better looking. It reminds them of what
they could have been if they got off of
YouTube years ago. It's the truth. And I
stand by what I say. And I don't care
what anyone says, bro. I don't care what
anyone says. They hate that you're
younger and better looking. That's why
they turn their nose up. It's like what
Ronald Pump said, younger, better
looking, more money, better life. And it
kills them. It's so true. If you see the
harassment of what these people do every
single day, you know,
you are better looking than them. That's
why they do not put their cameras on.
You are better looking than these
people. You are younger than these
people. You have got more hope. You got
more family. You got more money than
them. You've got more money than these
people. You know that. And it's the
truth, bro. That's why they do not leave
you alone. They don't do it for no
reaction. They do not do it for no
[ __ ] reaction at all, bro. Cuz I can,
like I said, like you said, go to the
gym. I could go to the gym. I could do
videos. I could do a whole new different
content on this channel. Gym, whatever
it is you want to see. And they would
still do it. They would still do it,
you know. They would still do it, bro.
Yeah. Basically. Yeah. Cuz Timmy's
Timmy's a virgin himself. He calls me a virgin.
Yeah. Yeah, Timmy. I mean, Timmy calls
me a virgin. So, even though I've proved
multiple times I've had sex.
And that's another thing is Ben, why are
they asking people to prove stuff that
when even when people prove stuff, they
still talk [ __ ] I've shown more money
than these people, they still call me
skin. I've shown better women, they
still talk [ __ ] Like, they will always
talk [ __ ] about people that are younger
and better looking than them. This is a
trend with these people, bro. Um and yeah. Yeah. Um
that's that basically, bro. Um
[snorts] yeah, man. I don't know what
else to say. That's it.
And it's very dangerous as well, bro.
Cuz I know people shouldn't take this
[ __ ] serious. But if I ever find out
where one of these people live, if
[snorts] I ever find out where one of
these people live, I'm bricking their
window, bro. I'm I'm going to do the
most. I swear to God, I will I will
brick one of their windows,
you know? You don't know what I'll do,
bro. I don't find it a joke. I don't
find it a joke. You know, same with that
V. I don't find it a joke. All the [ __ ]
that they've done to other people over
the years, they would pay for it, bro. Trust me. you know, so
that's so bad. Like to think if you
actually left YouTube, bro, they'd be
coming on YouTube every day like looking for content.
Oh, that's funny. I don't know what I'm
going to eat, bro.
Maybe [snorts] get some fishing. But
that's quite far, isn't it?
Oh no, it's pre-order. It's closed.
Looks like I can only get McDonald's.
I had McDonald's.
Yeah, exactly, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
And you need to think about this as
well, Ben. All of the people that's been
caught doing this have always been fat
and ugly as well. Bomb, Graycat, Pat.
There's been other people, I'm sure
there has. Um,
they've always been fat and ugly.
They've used the same excuses. Um, you
know that Joseph Raw, he uses the same
excuses. Oh, I'm going to go to leads
and do a video proving that he's fat and
ugly, then I'm going to run off. That's
the same [ __ ] bomb used to say. That's
the same excuses he used to say. These
[ __ ] weasels, these weasels have got
the same excuses. Like, so you are fat
and ugly then. So I'm right then what
you're saying like I'm So I'm going to
come all the way to leads
and recall you and run off. Do you think
I'm going to run off from someone like
you when I've traveled all that way?
See, it's excuses with these people. I'm
telling you 100%. All of these people
that have been put out there um has been
fat and ugly um that's been doing this.
It explains a lot. Their looks explains
a lot, bro. You know,
they use the same excuses. This Joe F
does the same thing. So, you are fat and
disabled then. So, you are fat and
disabled. By saying that, you are fat
and disabled. So, I'm right about you.
Oh, I don't know. This guy gives me
brain damage. He He really does.
No, we don't have any biscuits, bro. I
don't know what I'm going to get.
Probably a McDonald's. [snorts]
I feel sorry for lady, you know.
But yeah, you need to stop reacting to
these people. They'll never stop
anyways. They will never ever stop. No,
McDonald's is not shut.
No, McDonald's never shuts here.
Have a look.
So, maybe I'll do a video to Joe asking
him if he could explain this cuz I'm
kind of um
cheesy chicken stack. No, that doesn't
look nice. I might just get a Big Mac again.
No, I won't be going out New Year's Eve, bro.
No, I won't be going out for a while. My
sister's expecting me to go out and
that, but I don't want to drink, Ben. I
I really don't want to go out and try
with women again, bro. And I really,
really mean it this time, bro. I really,
really, really mean it this time.
I'm like done dumb, bro. You know when
you're done dumb. And I've got money.
I've got more than enough money to do
it. I don't want to. Money doesn't
change my moods. I'm not money obsessed
like these people, bro. You know, I can
have all the money in the world and I'd
still say exactly the same thing.
You know, it's not about that.
I am really, really done with these
women in this country, Ben. You know,
I'm getting a banana milkshake. I don't
like strawberry, but yeah,
I'm going to get a Big Mac, I think.
No, actually I'm [clears throat] going
to get a I'm going to get a McChick sandwich meal.
with some nuggets. Actually,
I'm really done with these women in this
country, Steven Howard.
I've got no uh
Yeah, it might come cold. That's the thing.
I don't think so.
What could I do, bro? I don't know.
Maybe Peppies is open. Hold on. Let me see.
No, that's not even open. Surprising.
What should I get, bro?
I might just boil some eggs.
Yeah, I might just boil boil some eggs,
bro. [ __ ] it.
I'm supposed to be saving money, bro. Yeah, bro.
No, I've got corn flakes, but obviously
I can't have sugar.
I can't have sugar, can I? Cuz of um the toothpies.
No, I don't really want to make eggs
either. I don't know what to do, bro.
This puts me in a position
I can't have corn flakes cuz the sugar
in it. Hold a minute.
I don't know what I'm going to have, bro.
Unless I just get nuggets from
McDonald's. I can just get the chicken
nuggets. They're not going to be cold. Yeah.
Yeah, I'll just get the chicken nuggets.
Chicken nuggets won't be cold.
I like show
you're gay. We don't like I'm going to
do this video to Joseph.
Sounds pain. Sounds what?
What do you mean sounds pain?
Oh, there you go. Yeah, cuz obviously
it's not going to be cold, is it? All right.
Going to get some nugies and a milkshake.
You know what I was thinking that
nonslegs could do? He could get a little
part-time job, Steven Howard, like work
at a cap or something. Um, and, you
know, obviously he'll get £50 a day, you
know, then he could stop being skint and
showing his daddy's life savings off.
What do you think? Get himself a little
part-time job. Get him out the house.
Might even get laid.
What do you think? Might actually get
laid. He might lose his vard. Never know. Bye.
Yeah, it's £12 just for nuggets. I've
got a can of Coke.
Yeah, I've got a can of Coke. So,
that's fine. I've got a can of Coke. I
don't need a drink.
He's getting himself a little part-time
job. Little part-time job.
A little part-time job.
Have you ever had a cavity, Steven Howard?
Think a lot of people have had him. I
think mine's from some kind of
deficiency. I think I'm deficient in something
like vitamins and or something. I think
I'm I'm I'm definitely uh lacking something, bro.
with Ant-Man. Yeah. And it's supposed to
be 50/50. I'm not giving his cut.
I'm not giving him his cut. Bro, are you
mad? I'm taking that £100 for myself.
He says, "Oh, we supposed to cut because
obviously he told me about the guy, but
at the end of the day, I don't think I'm
being unfair to be honest. He's using my
details." So, yeah. And nah,
I'm not giving no cut, bro. I'm keeping
it for myself.
[sighs and gasps]
You know, I'm not going to give half,
but they using my [ __ ] You know what
I'm saying? So, no£100 mine, bro. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, I need to change my diet.
Seriously, bro. I'm [ __ ] uh
I'm supposed to be going to um
I'm supposed to be going for a meal New
Year's Eve that
I don't think I will. I just ordered some McDonald's. Meow.
I was looking for some digestive
biscuits, Grezy, but I can't I fancy
some digestive biscuits. Some digestives.
What do you think of that? Digestive biscuits. [sighs] Hi.
So, I watched the housemmaid horror
film. Have you seen it advertised? I'm
sure you've seen it advertised. And
basically, there's there was a sex scene
with this woman and I saw the sex scene
and I kind of developed a crush. And
unlike Nons, I didn't know about her. I
didn't know her name. I didn't even know
she was really really famous. I didn't
know anyone knew her. Um and then I
looked her up and um she was really
really famous and I and I didn't I
didn't know that Greavvesy. I didn't
know all I never heard of her before.
Nothing. Um I just saw the sex scenes
and thought it was my type. They were my
type. And it seems they've got millions
of followers on Instagram, but I didn't
know about them. I'm not a copycat. I
didn't know. I swear to God I didn't
know anything about them. I wasn't like
[ __ ] nonsense because the next day
going into college saying Cole Sh,
you know, it was a bit different. I saw
them in a sex scene and I didn't know
who they were. You know, I'm not a
little copycat. Oh, this guy is gay. Gay
calling each other gay. Copy him. [snorts]
Grezy, I've got a bone to pick with you.
I don't think, yeah, they should be
showing these um sex scenes in these
horror films. They done it about five
times, bro. And it's rated 15. The
horror film is rated 15. And it was
constant. It was constant. I mean, I
went to go and watch a horror film, not
a porno. I meant to tell you about this,
but obviously you haven't been on. I
think it's very unfair.
Why are they showing you something that
you you can't even get that you should
be getting at your age? It's almost as
if it's mocking you, you know.
You know, and it was constant. It was
constant grievy. It was constant. And it
was nude scenes as well. So,
you know, it's like you don't pay to go
and watch a a [ __ ] porno. You know,
what's your opinion on that? Yeah,
I'm I feel so much better that I've
given up with women, Grezy. I still
haven't tried. I feel so much better. I
think I'm asexual now, you know. I
genuinely generally think I'm asexual now.
Yeah, I'm definitely definitely asexual
now. [sighs and gasps]
Um 100% I am. I don't think about it anymore.
Uh, there was nudes.
Yeah, there was nudes. You saw You saw
her boobs and stuff.
Yeah, I'm so glad I gave up, bro. I'm so
glad I gave up.
But I've got a bone to pick with Joseph Farra.
I'm going to do a video. I want him to
answer this about this nons legs thing.
Yeah, it was nude. You saw her boobs and
stuff. Yeah. And it was worse because the husband
um basically cheated on the wife with
her and she was the housemmaid.
Yeah, bro. It's depressing seeing [ __ ]
like that. It was a little bit
depressing to be fair, but obviously I
had already given up. So yeah.
So yeah, I'm asexual now. Greasy.
Definitely definitely asexual.
I'll never try again. I was supposed to
go out New Year's Eve. I'm not going
out, bro. I'm not doing nothing. [clears throat]
I'm doing [ __ ] all.
I'd rather just sit and just save money.
I think that's the best option. You
know, Greasy, women are not normal. They
can't be normal. They can't be not stuck
up and not play games. So, what's the
point of anyone bothering with them? I
don't care who's in a relationship. I
don't care who's not in a relationship.
I don't give a [ __ ] I've given up.
Simple as that. So, yeah.
But yeah, bro.
It is up.
It is up. I was watching Mr. Bean
yesterday. Um, Greavvesy. Mr. Bean,
do you used to like Mr. Bean? Greavvesy?
What would you call me? Grezy, if I if I
if I started liking Sher Co. Grezy,
what would you think if I started liking
Sher Co? Would
you have an opinion on that or what?
Would you have an opinion on that? When
I was watching Mr. Bean, it it was
reminding me of, you know, Mr. Bean, the
account Mr. Bean that trolls Timmy. I
don't know why he just kept reminding me
of of him. Well, considering I rarely gamble. No.
No. I don't gamble.
A big fat dirty stinky coffee. [laughter]
I love you, Grezy. It's good to have you
back, Greavvesy. It didn't feel the same
without you. You and your little Stits
photo. I had a lovely roast at my
sister's, Greavvesy. I had a turkey. I
had a lamb. And I had some pigs in blankets.
I wish you was here to join us.
Yeah. Wish you was here to Wish you were
there to join us. Yeah. I got nuggets
from McDonald's because they're the only
thing I don't think that's going to come cold. Oh,
so you call me big fat dirty sticky copycat.
So what you're saying nonslegs is a copycat. M
well you know nonsex he needs to change
um his name uh he's not no king of the money game.
He was the king of the money game in a
certain year but it's 2026 uh in a
couple of days and you can no longer
show that money. So uh you're not the
king of the money game.
You're not the king of the money game at all.
You have not shown more money to me. You
never have and you never will.
And you can't show the money now. So
you're not the king of no money game. He
needs to change. He needs he needs to change. Uh
can Steven Howard why does this Joseph
Ferrar never back me up when non legs
goes for me? But then when I go for
nonsle legs, he he's so far up his ass.
Oh, he's got a girlfriend. He's not a
virgin. He's not a virgin, but he claims
that he doesn't like nonslegs.
H seems like a nonslegs lover to me.
I don't like him. I don't know him. I
don't like him. But you continuously
defend somebody that you don't know.
Okay, mate. Okay. But there's no solid
evidence to prove that he's not a
virgin. Okay, mate. Okay.
Yeah, I've seen it myself, bro. I've
seen it myself. I told him to meet me
and he will not meet me. He will not
under any circumstances meet me. I'm
going to do another video to him, I think.
Um, and I'm going to say to him, please
refrain from calling people on Reddit
keyboard warriors when I've offered you
multiple times to meet you and you will
never meet anyone. Don't don't slag off
something that you are. Yeah, I've seen
it myself. That's why I went live the
other day. But I said, "Come and call me
a sad bastard to my face." He won't do
it. He's a keyboard warrior.
He's another nonsle lover.
He doesn't find it possible.
He doesn't find it possible, bro, for
someone to be a virgin that's had a
girlfriend for 3 years, but he finds it
possible for somebody that's put a porno
up to be a virgin. Make it make sense.
Make it make sense. You do a lot of
defending somebody for someone that you
don't like. And yes, for you, you
backing up them not being a virgin is
the definition of defending someone.
That's like me defending Lord Jay. It
doesn't make any sense. Does it make
Does it make any sense? Stephen Howard,
you go out Reddit being keyboard
warriors, but you will never ever meet
anyone. You'll never meet anyone ever.
You never meet anyone, but you slag off Reddit.
>> You slag off Reddit for being keyboard
warriors, but you're the biggest
keyboard warrior [ __ ] going.
[ __ ] nonsloving [ __ ] fat nonslover.
Is he a non-slover? Steven Howard.
And I don't want him to defend me. I I
just want to know why he keeps defending
his boyfriend that he doesn't like so
far up his ass. Madness.
What a non-slover.
But he does come from um J. What do you
think? One fix.
>> My nuggets are here.
>> I don't judge him because he does come
from the the [ __ ] side of YouTube to be honest.
But yeah, it's um he's saying that he
doesn't like him, but then he defends
him. I don't understand. I [ __ ] up with you, bro.
You not find that a bit weird, Grezy.
Right. Now, Joseph Ferrar wrote the
other day that he doesn't like nonsense.
He will address him by his name. He
doesn't defend him. All he's saying that
is that he's not a virgin because he had
a disabled girlfriend for 3 years. But
then I don't see him ever defending me.
Long links doesn't need you to defend
him. You don't like him. So why are you
so far up his ass defending someone that
you don't like if they don't need
defending? Make it make sense. It
doesn't make sense.
And this is how these people make you
lose [ __ ] brain cells.
They don't make sense.
None of it makes any sense. It's an autistic community.
And then he's and then he'll turn around
and say, "Oh, well, no one said that
you're virgin." Okay, but I don't see
you bringing up the pornos um that I put
up. I don't see you bringing up where
I've literally proven that I have slept
with women, none of them that was not
disabled. And then he'll turn around and
say, "Oh, well, you don't need me to
defend you. I don't need you to defend
me, but your boyfriend doesn't need you
to defend him either, but you're so far
up his ass.
Why are you so far up his ass?" Talking
about this disabled girl as if that
proves he's ever had sex. I don't understand, bro.
I stand by my point. I think they don't
like anyone younger and better looking
than them. I stand I stand by my point, bro.
Sorry if it sounds harsh. I'm sorry, bro. But um
that's what I generally think.
Say I'm wrong. I don't really care, bro.
That's my opinion. I I just think they
don't like anyone younger, better
looking than them.
That's what I think.
Sorry, bro. You have to be cool to be kind.
Have you ever heard the saying only um
uh God can judge you? Yeah.
These people are not God.
Yeah. They're lovely and warm.
You know what I mean?
I'm going to do a video chat. Jo, [clears throat]
same thing to that. Um,
same thing to that [ __ ] Autumn. I can
call you fat because you people are fat.
I'm not fat. That's the difference. I'm
not fat. You're all You're fat all over,
mate. Yeah, you're fat all over. That's
why you've got to use booties, you fat [ __ ]
Yeah. Do you see me using filters? One second.
Do you see Do you see me using filters?
I'm just woke up. Why am I the only one
on here that that's not scared of
showing their face?
Ask yourself that question. Why am I the
only one in there that's not scared to
show my face?
Yeah, I've seen that Jo on um on um
Lord J slag me off, but he'll never say
anything to my face. He just uses the
same Bob excuses.
All of them people
Stephen Howard that was writing [ __ ]
about me on Red Stars, they're all
fatter and uglier than I will ever be.
Do you believe that? They're older,
fatter, and uglier than I could ever be.
But they talk about me. They talk about
me. This is why I don't understand these
these little clowns that I'm better
looking than younger than. It's talking about me.
these people are not even [ __ ] mobile, bro. So yeah,
but [ __ ] that is a flat.
Tell that Autumn,
tell that Autumn, right, to come on
camera with no filters and put and show
her face. She can't do it.
She can't do it, bro.
She's fat and ugly.
It's so autistic. I know what he's
saying, bro. I like I said, if you watch
it, you will lose brain cells. You will
actually lose brain cells, bro.
Even thinking about it, you lose brain
cells. It's proper proper autistic.
Ben's got special needs as well. He's
definitely definitely slow in the head.
Well, I wasn't an alcoholic anyways, so
I'm not even fat. What the [ __ ]
These people can't show their faces.
They can't they can't come on camera, bro.
Put it this way.
Everyone that's talking [ __ ] about you
is in a worse position than you are.
They're in a worse position in life than
you are. Just remember that. All of
these people that are coming on here,
they're they've got less money than you.
They've got less family. They [ __ ] it
in life. They're older. They're uglier.
They're fatter. All of these people that
are talking are in a worse position than
you. Just remember that before I'm
reacting to these people. Old uglyies.
And why do you care if it's possible if
someone's been a virgin? Why are you
getting involved? You don't like the
person. Why are you getting involved in arguments?
Listen, Stephen Albert, if this was me 3
years ago, bro, I would have just went
to all of their cities again and just
started doing the madness. I would have
just started doing the madness.
I would have just started doing the
madness again if I didn't know what they
were like, bro. Like they're all biased
and that I would just start if I
obviously if this guy agrees to meet me,
I would go to him. Obviously I would, you know,
but you learn what these people do, you know.
There's nothing fat about me. There's
nothing ugly about me, bro.
These people are fat and ugly. That's
why they sit around for eight years
hating on strangers.
That Jo is one sad bastard.
Sad biased fat bastard.
Kira told me anyone that's not blocked by nonsexs
anyone that's not blocked by nons you
shouldn't trust him Uh yeah,
they're all fat, ugly, and autistic on
here, bro. That's why I don't go on their channels.
Anyone that's not blocked by nonsense,
you shouldn't trust them. That's what
Payman said to me.
That's indeed a loss, but at least
you're not one of life's losers like
Peter Pike. Jamie Thompson, have you
seen your face?
Please, have have you seen what you look like?
Have you seen what you look like, bro?
And and you're talking about a life's
loser. Have you seen yourself,
please? Have you seen your face? Have
you seen your how fat you are? And this
is what most of these people here look like.
They're in a worse position than you
are. They're in a worse position in life
than you are.
The sad bully victims. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't own the lovely channel.
Yeah, I want to address your third point
because this third point does not make sense.
And yeah, you all you ever said was I
find it near impossible to believe
someone that's had a girlfriend for 3
years and a virgin, but you haven't said
anything about me on his channel. So why
do you feel the need to keep defending
somebody that you don't like when
there's not facts out there? Autism. Again,
I don't find it hard to believe that
he's a virgin.
>> I know it just sounds so immature and so
stupid and that, but it just shows how
biased they are.
It just it just sounds how it I need to
stop drinking um tea with sugar in it,
Grezy, because of the cavities. I've got
cavity. I've got cavity. So, I need to
sort my light out and stuff. But I know
it sounds so um stupid, but it is
important because that's how biased they
are on here.
You know what I mean? But it's it's the biasness.
That's what I'm saying. It sounds silly
to you, but it's it's a good point.
Why are you defending someone you don't
like when there's no proof they've had sex?
It doesn't make sense. You need to make
it make sense.
And I think that's going to be my last
say to this loser. Um and yeah,
in your absence
I said literally on Boxing Day,
I will come up I will come to Le and meet you.
I will come to lead share meet you
today. I put my coat on you never know
of it that he talks about people on
Reddit being keyboard warriors. What's
the What's the definition of a keyboard
warrior? Somebody that will [ __ ] sit on
the internet and talk [ __ ] continuously
but will never say anything to anyone's
face. That's what you are. You're a
keyboard warrior. You're no different
than anyone on Reddit. Yeah.
This is a proper proper autistic
community, bro. Proper autistic. Yeah.
Have a little part-time job.
A little part time job.
Cuz imagine that monster.
You didn't bring up any of the pornos
that I put up.
You didn't bring up any of the thing. I
want an account to this.
You know, I want you to give me an
account to my face. And if you're not
going to do it, you're going to get blocked.
I think I'm going to have to block that
Steven uh that joke that Joe Steven
Howard. I think I'm going to have to
block him. As much as he's all right
sometimes and stuff, I mean, I don't I
don't like biased people. I don't like biased non-lovers.
I think they're intelligent. I'm going
to have to put him on the block list. I
think, bro, after this,
I think I'm going to have to put him on
the block list. >> [snorts]
>> That is so weird to defend someone that
you don't like. I don't like Lord Jay. I
would never defend it. I would never
defend him if anyone
um calls him calling him a virgin.
I would never defend him. I would never
I don't know
Fruan, you know. So you must like the
person to waste your time defending
them. And yes, that is defending them.
And I'll say all of this in this video.
If that's the case, if you want to speak
facts, why do you not find it near
impossible when someone's got their dick
shove down a woman's mouth? And all of
the one night stand I've had, all of the
women that have had admitted to sleeping
with me cuz you're a non-slubber.
Just own it. You're a non-slber. And
that's it. You know,
I don't check his channel. I know what
his channel is about, bro. You do not
know what this JF channel is. It's about
showing fake wins to try to get me to
gamble. How do I know that, Greasy?
Because I've got an IQ.
Because I've got an IQ. So, I know what
he's trying to do. And it's not going to
work. I've got more money than you'll
ever have. You're never going to tempt
me into gambling ever. So, I know what
the channel's about. Do you not
understand what the channel was about?
with these fake wins and you're calling
me jealous, brother. I don't need to be
jealous. I've got money. I'm younger.
I'm better looking. So before you accuse
someone of being jealous, right? Back
up. Back it up. Back up the statement.
I'm younger. I'm better looking. I'm not
fat. I got more money than I got more
money than him. I've got designer
clothes. There is nothing to be jealous
of. A fat slob.
I don't give a [ __ ] about money. I've got money.
I have got money. I don't give a [ __ ]
about money. You know what I'm saying?
So in case you want to try and tell it's jealousy.
No one's jealous of no one, bro. You know,
no one's jealous of no one. I want these
people jealous of me. I'm not jealous of
them. I got money. I can do whatever I
want when I want.
How do you know? How do you know he's
got a job? Do you know it? And he
doesn't own his own house either. Um he
wouldn't even tell you that. Um, and how
do you know he's got a job? Do you know him?
Oh, he's got a job, does he? What What
does he do for work then? I didn't know
he had a job. What? What? What does he
do? What does he do as a job? And he
doesn't own his own house. And he will
tell you that he doesn't own his own house.
He would even tell you that himself. So,
he doesn't own his own house. And oh,
he's got a job, does he? Meaning, what
job does he have? I didn't know he had a
job. You obviously know him more than I
do. What job does he have?
Since you know him so well,
brother, he does not own his own house.
He will tell you himself he does not own
his own house. Anyways, what job? What
job does he have?
What job does he have? You said that
he's got a job. What job does he have?
Showing fake wins on the internet. Oh,
I'm jealous. Apparently,
I've got 200 pound jeans.
I've got designer trainers, designer
clothes. I've got more money than him,
but I'm jealous. Work that one out, people.
But I'm jealous. What the [ __ ] Okay,
bro. I'm jealous.
I love it when he says I'm jealous. I
might I might have that in the video as well.
Okay. So, I'm asking you what job does
he have? Okay. So, what job does he
have? How do you know it's his pension?
So, you don't know this person. You're
backing up someone that you don't even
know. You don't know it's his pension.
He doesn't own his own house cuz he
would tell you he doesn't own his own
house. And what job does he have?
Listen, brother. Listen. How do you know
it's his pension? Come on. I'm I'm being
real with you. Do you know this guy in
real life? No, you don't. So, shut the
[ __ ] up then.
You don't know him. You don't know that
he has a job. You [clears throat] don't
know that's in his pension. You don't
know him. This is what I'm saying.
You're defending someone that you don't
know. And I'm not even trying to be
awkward. You don't know him.
I can tell you what job he has. He
doesn't have a job. I can tell you what
job he has. What? When people have more
than me. Well, I don't because none of
you do have more than me. So I don't
hate it because you don't have nothing
more than I would ever have. So I
definitely definitely don't. You all the
clowns that come on here every day
harassing me. Oh, believe you me, you
people don't have 1% more of what I've
got. I've got more money, better looks,
more clothes, more family, more money
than you. You definitely definitely do
not have one penny more than I've got.
I'm not the one showing 30 pound jeans
and a 200lb phone, brother. You don't
have no more than me will ever have. I'm
younger. I'm better looking. I've got
freedom. I've got more money than you.
I'm not the ones harassing you every
day. You're the ones that harassing me.
You are the people that are harassing me
every day. I'm not harassing you.
No. No one on here show more than me.
I've shown more money, more women,
better looks, more money. Nope. Not one
of you on here has ever shown more than
me. No, you have not.
No, you bloody well have not. I'm shown
younger, better looks, better money,
better women. Nope. None of you have
ever shown a penny more than me. Thank
good now. See you later. Yeah,
they've got more than me, Stephen Hour,
but they constantly harass me every day.
They harass me every day and will not
leave me the [ __ ] alone. But they got
more than me. Really, bro? Yeah.
He doesn't know anything. These people
don't know. Listen. Listen. Steven
Howard, you know why I've not gone out
for the past month? I don't want to go
out. I don't want to waste money. I
don't want to deal with women anymore.
That's my choice. I've got money. Yeah.
Do you not remember what happened last
year, the year before that when I used
to do the same thing? Even when I was
getting the money from the house, I
don't want to do it
because you live and you learn. Just
stop going around in circles. Yeah.
So when that joke said, "Oh yeah, it was
good when you had money. Come here. I've
got money." Which I said to you multiple
times I've got money. Even though I told
him multiple times I had money, they
still told me I did have money. They're idiots.
I've got money. I can go out whenever I
want. I can make money.
Yeah. And that's another thing. I don't
want to go out.
All I'm going to do is try and join the
pool industry and that's it. [ __ ] that.
You don't understand how much better you
feel when you give up with this dating,
bro. And I want to keep that feeling. I
want to keep the peace. I don't want to
go back to it. You don't understand,
Greg. I don't want to go back to that
life. [ __ ] that.
The attitude, the [ __ ] the mind
games, the [ __ ] [ __ ] that, bro.
[ __ ] that. I am not going back to that. No.
I'd rather be single for the rest of my
life than ever have to go through any of that again. No,
I'm not doing that again. Oh, yeah.
I got two I got three left.
But yeah, I've seen that Jo slag off. I
said come and call me a sad bastion to
my face multiple times would not meet
me. But then he calls people on Reddit keyboard warriors.
And you know what the worst thing is
about this conceive now? It's not like
he's got a different opinion. He's
actually trying to insult people behind
the keyboard which makes him a keyboard
warrior. He's not saying, "Oh, I agree
with you on this. I disagree with you on
that. You need to get a life." No. He's
actually being a nonsex by trying to act
like the big [ __ ] but then when someone
calls him out, he's not willing to meet anyone.
So, he's actually acting the big [ __ ]
He's got a big mouth for somebody that
will never meet anyone. is a bit bit like nonsex.
Whereas someone that's not like nonsex
is like I don't know um greasy or
someone that will tell you you're wrong
and not agree with everything but they
don't they're not inclined to meet you.
They don't they meet you for just having
different opinions. But what this guy
does he acts like the big [ __ ] acts like
the big man talk the big man talk right
and then he would never meet anyone.
He's another nonsex. That's why I called
him nonsex's boyfriend. They make a good
couple. You're doing a lot of defending
someone for someone that you don't like.
And then he said, "I don't I don't need
you defending me. I don't need you
defending me." But nonsense doesn't need
you defending him. So why are you so up
his ass? You say that you don't like
him, but you up his ass.
Someone like me has proved they've had
sex. He has never proved they've had
sex. They have never proved that they've
had sex. No matter what disabled girl
they show, you know,
I tell you what though, Steven. Yeah.
The new year, we're done with all of
this. We're done with all of this
arguing. We're not going on anyone
else's channel. We're just keeping
everything for this channel and we're
going to try and bring new people on
this channel. So, it's just going to be
me, you, Greezy, a few of other people
and people coming from different
communities. I'm done with these people, bro.
In a new year, I'm fully done with these
people. That's even when I come on here,
bro. So, that will be it. Yeah. Not
another year of this [ __ ]
I I feel sorry for Laney, to be honest.
Yeah, it is, bro.
There's nothing fat about me. There's
nothing ugly about me. I look completely normal, bro.
I might bring that up in a video as
well. Like, bro, the comments, they
could annoy people, but then you have to
understand with these people that are
commenting, they're in a worse position
in life than you will ever be. They're
fatter than you. They're uglier than
you. So whatever they say doesn't really
mean anything. I bet that will get to them.
You do a lot of defending your boyfriend,
someone that don't like someone. That's
a lot of defending for someone that you don't like.
That's like me sticking up for
That's like me sticking up for Monty.
I mean, yeah, you you know, you're
entitled to your own opinion, but then it just
But then if you was entire to your own
opinion, why didn't you bring up all of
the sex that I've had?
You an impartial party, you dirty little non-sloving [ __ ]
Do I think when I say that?
Why are you right, Timmy? Timmy Eldridge.
Timmy, I don't like these people in this
community, bro. That's what it is. I
just don't like these people on here.
I don't like these people on here, bro.
I don't know about you, but I don't like them.
I need to brush my teeth in a minute cuz
I've just drunk Coke. [snorts]
I don't like these people on here, bro.
Every time you drink Coke. Yeah, you
have to brush your teeth.
I'm sure my oral hygiene now.
I like the skin one. No.
So, I'm going to do this video. Yeah. to uh
I know I'm going to say to this Jo, I'm
going to say, do you know what? You
should put up full gambling videos.
Every time you gamble, you should and
we'll see how much you really win and
you and you really lose.
That's what you need to do. You need to
uh basically put up every time you
gamble. See, with me, Steven Howard, I
used to show every time that I gambled.
Every time I gambled, it used to go on
YouTube. Whether I won or I lost.
Whether I won or I lost, it used to
always go on the channel.
Whereas, he only puts up wins. And if
they're real wins, he's only showing
wins. Again, not jealousy talking facts. Yeah.
If you can prove, if you can prove
right, that you've won more, I'll be
like, "Oh, fair play."
That's another thing. You need to show
every time you gamble, you know, because
that's the way a gambling channel is
supposed to be, you know, and if you are
winning a lot more than you're losing,
fair play. But we know you're not. We
know that you're full of [ __ ] We can
say that you're full of [ __ ] And trust
me, mate, we're not jealous of some
middle-aged man, right, with [ __ ] 40
pound jeans and a 200lb phone. I'm not
the one coming on here harassing you
every [ __ ] day, you know?
And that's that. See, see Timmy, he puts
up losses. He puts up losses,
don't you, Timmy? You put up losses.
Whereas this this chosen fraud only puts up wins.
That's not jealousy. That's stating what
you do. That is literally stating a fact
of what you do, not jealousy. There's a
big difference, you know.
you know, show every time you gamble
and if you win, then fair play. You've
won. But we know that that's not the way
that is. Not jealousy. Facts. Someone
telling you about what you're doing is
facts. You understand, dusty, that's not
jealousy. You know this Joe F account?
You know this Joe F account, right? If
he shows every time he gamles and he's
winning, then I'll be like, "Oh, okay.
Good. You're winning." Because I'm not
jealous. I'm younger than you. I'm
better looking than you. I've got more
than you. You're nothing to be jealous
of. Just because we're calling you out
for only showing wins, that's not being
jealous. That's saying that you're full
of [ __ ] In other words, you know, we
can sit there and tell someone that
they're full of [ __ ] without being
jealous. Is that not right, Dusty?
You know, and that's the truth. You
know, if you do five gambling videos and
you win in every single one of them,
[ __ ] fair play. I I'd be
congratulating you. But we know that's
not what's going to happen. No one needs
to be jealous of someone with 30 jeans
with a 200lb phone.
You know what I mean? No one no one
would ever be jealous of someone like you,
you know? And what I think he's doing in
some of the videos as well, Stephen
Albert, I think he's putting money in
and just taking the money out.
Um, because trust me, them properties
will rinse you dry, bro. Them
properties, you can't even win on them
nowadays. You know it and Dustin knows
that you can't win. So me stating facts,
I'm apparently jealous. So anyone that's
got a different opinion than you is
apparently jealous. Even though they're
younger than you, they're better looking
than you and they got more money than
you, but apparently that they're jealous of you. Really? Really?
That means that someone's that someone's
that someone's jealous. Really, bro?
Come on now. [clears throat]
>> All right. How you doing, lad? How you
doing? All right, lad.
>> Why is it so quiet? One second. Let me
rejoin. Hold on.
All right, there you can. [laughter] [clears throat]
I just find everything so funny when you stand. >> Hello.
>> How you doing? All right, appreciate.
>> Yeah, I don't know why the volume's so quiet. >> Hello.
>> Yeah, I think it's my phone. [laughter]
You've been gambling again.
>> What's going on? [laughter]
>> Have you been Have you been gambling
again? Sorry, can't stop laughing.
You need to stop gambling to me. [laughter] [clears throat]
Okay, I'm going to kick you now. You're
not talking. So, yeah. Dusty, what do you think?
You think I should just go to leads and
call this fat [ __ ] out? Steven Howard,
who who side are you on, Greavvesy? Mine
or Joe FS? Do you think I'm making some
good points again? You don't have to
disagree with me. You won't get blocked
for disagreeing with me. I just want to
know whose side are you on or who do you
think's got more points. I think I've
got some points with what I'm saying.
Uh, I think I've got some points with
what I'm saying here.
Yeah. I don't like people that slag
people off behind their back.
And that's why I called you out because
you never call anyone a sad bastard to the face.
You know, you never you would never call
someone a sad bastard to their face. So,
stop running on about [ __ ] Reddit.
Okay. So, what what what points what
points have I made then? Give me a
couple of good points of what I've made.
Okay. And what Okay, fair enough. And
what points have I made?
It's the biasness with him. It's the
biasness that the [ __ ] talking, the
trying to troll people is what I can't stand.
Okay. What about the non Okay, so what
about the nons legs point Greavesy?
What about, you know, what about when
I've said that he's so fast enough to
defend Nles legs, but he doesn't say
anything about the Paul nose that I've
put up. I think that's a solid point. I
think that is solid.
As solid as concrete concrete, cuz it
doesn't make sense. What he's saying
does not make sense, especially when
he's saying that he doesn't like someone,
you know? I think it's a solid point,
bro. And it matters because it shows the
biasness, you know.
Okay. If you want to have an opinion,
why do you not have an opinion when
people are calling me stuff?
That's the truth, bro. You know what?
Why? What? You know what I mean? Uh, Grezy.
Why would you defend someone that you don't like?
I'll do a video later.
Right. It doesn't matter what he says.
He hasn't said it on Nons's channel.
Right. Right. Right. Right. Right.
Right. Right. He said that I wasn't a
virgin when I brought it up. Yes. When I
brought it up several times, but he
hasn't said it on Nonlex's channel. He
hasn't brought up the pool nose. He
hasn't brought up the times where I've
showed thousands of thousands of pounds.
So, it doesn't matter what he said when
I brought it up. He hasn't said it. Um
he hasn't said it on Nons' channel. And
nonslegs don't have it blocked. So,
I mean, you're defending someone that
you don't like because they've been with
a disabled girl for 3 years. That does
not prove that they're not a virgin. Me,
I proved I'm not a virgin. So, why have
I not seen you on this guy's channel
backing me up?
Because you're a dirty stinking
nonslover. You're a big fat dirty
stinking nonsloving [ __ ]
I he's because what I'm saying Grezy is
he's saying that he doesn't like the
guy, right? So if I'm calling the guy a
virgin, why is he getting involved? You
wouldn't have an opinion. If you do not
like Summer, you don't have an opinion.
You have defended him multiple multiple
times because of this disabled girl that
he shown for 3 years. Okay, whatever. So
that proves that he's not a virgin. You
go on every single one of Nons's um
videos and community posts, you do not
see once this guy bringing up the pool
nose and he says, "Oh, well, you don't
need me to defend you. I don't need you
to defend me, but nonslegs doesn't need
you to defend him either. And you
apparently don't like him. So why do you
keep defending him? You dirty, stinky,
big fat nonsubber, you know,
and that's what it is.
Do do you see what I'm saying?
Do you not see what I'm saying? And why
and furthermore, if I'm calling him a
virgin, why does that bother you? You
don't like the guy?
You said that you don't like the guy, so
why are you defending someone that you
don't like? It doesn't make sense.
I don't think you understand the point
I'm trying to make, bro.
I do not see you on Nonsex's channel
bringing up all of the money that I've
shown, which was more than you. Um, also
bringing up the fact that uh I've
actually proved I've had sex, unlike
him, cuz he's a virgin. Um, you know
what I mean?
You know what I'm going to do? I'm just
going to end up going to Leeds. That's
what I'm going to end up doing, bro. I
can see this happening, Gres. I'm just
going to go end up going there and just
calling him out.
[snorts] That's what I'm going to end up
doing to be honest with you, bro. I'm
getting sick of this [ __ ]
you know, to last me a lifetime,
right? Okay. So, why has he not Okay.
So, what about somebody that's proved
they've had sex and they've been in bed
with multiple women? I've not seen him
bring that up on Donlex's channel. Okay. But then
why haven't you brought up the porn nose
that I put out? Why haven't you not
brought up me being in bed with women
multiple times? I mean, it's very more
likely somebody to be dating a disabled
girl to have not had sex than someone
like me to have not had sex.
I mean, it is likely because he is a
virgin and he's going to die a virgin.
Me, on the other hand, I've proved I've
had sex. Why have I not seen you on
Nons's channel talking about me having sex? You know,
you know what I'm saying?
I have not seen this guy. He is not
blocked by nons. So why is he not
talking about the p the porn that I put up?
And it is very likely because he is a
virgin and he's going to die a virgin.
And that nods legs is definitely a
virgin. I would not call him a virgin if
I did not mean it. So, what I'm saying,
Greavvesy, is I have actually proved
I've had sex. He hasn't. I've proved
I've had sex, and I do not see him on
Nons's channel bringing up all of the
[ __ ] that I've proved. So, can I call
him a biased non-slegs lover?
So, can I call him a biased non-slegs lover then?
So, is that not being a bit of a biased
nodle lover? If you know what the
definition of bias means, you're saying,
right? Okay. Okay. So you're saying so
so he's saying right that he's defending
him because he's got a girlfriend,
right? But I've proven that I've had
sex. I've slept with women multiple
times. I've had women admit, but when
nonsex is calling me a virgin, he's
nowhere to be seen. Do you not see the
problem with that?
Do you not see the problem? He's
defending his boyfriend for having a
disabled girlfriend, but when someone
has actually proved that they've had
sex, he's nowhere to be seen. Do you not
see the problem with that? If you're not
playing two sides of a court and do not
and he's not blocked either.
So, do you not see the problem with that?
He's so far to suck his dick when I'm
going at him, but he's nowhere to be
seen when he's going at me. I don't need
defending just like he doesn't need defending.
Do you not understand the point I'm
trying to make?
So, you got nothing to say about that, Quezy? No.
>> Nothing to say about that? No.
So, why does none of the things that
I've proved been brought up then?
H. You went quiet there.
I don't think you understand what I'm
what I'm trying to say to be honest with
you. I think Ben understood it, but you don't. Yeah.
So, you don't
This is autism, bro. This is This is
what I mean by it's autistic.
Turn the TV on, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. I don't think you understand
what I'm trying to get at, bro. I don't
think you understand what I'm trying to get at. Yeah.
So, someone that's been with someone
that's disabled for 3 years can
definitely not be a virgin, but someone
that's proved they've had sex is a virgin,
right? Okay. That makes a lot of sense, doesn't it?
Okay. Interesting. [clears throat] Wow.
Well, you learn something new every day. That's interesting.
So, someone that's been with someone
that can't consent to sex for 3 years is
definitely definitely not a virgin.
Okay. But someone like me definitely is.
Okay. Well, you learn something new every day.
I don't think you get the point of what
I'm trying to make. I don't think you
understand it. It might be a bit It
might be a bit high for you. I'm saying
to you, why is
I haven't seen any comments. Well, let
me let me go on some of them.
Right. Lonely skin. I don't see Joseph here.
Maybe I'm Maybe I'm Maybe I'm saying something wrong. Right.
Nope. Don't see it. Don't see Joseph on
any of these, bro.
Huh? I don't see him on any of these uh
comments. Uh Greavvesy
skin. I don't see him bringing up where
I've shown money. Uh, no.
I don't see any of this these Joseph
Ferraras comments, bro. No.
Do you know what I'm going to do? I'm
just going to go I'm just going to end
up going to Leeds, I think. Bro, that's
what I'm going to do, Grez. I think I'm
just going to end up going there.
Proper proper autism. Proper autism. [clears throat]
I'm just going to end up going to these
I think next week. I think I'm going to
end up doing that, bro.
Yeah. Turn this on. Sort this [ __ ] out
once and for all. Another
one bites the dust. You know,
I've just explained something about a
million times and it never got answered
again. You usual with this autistic community.
I'm still waiting for the answer.
Greavves. You didn't answer it. H. [clears throat]
Yeah. It's not possible for someone to
be a virgin in a threeyear relationship,
but it's possible for someone that's
proved they've had sex to be a virgin.
That's basically what they're making it
out to be. [ __ ] jealous of me. These
people are so jealous of me. It's unbelievable. Unfucking believable.
Let me ask Stephen Howard. I've not seen
him comment on any of his videos.
I've not seen him comment on any of the
videos, bro. Steven Howard, any of the
community posts, nothing.
But he's so fast to suck his dick when
I'm going at him. Let me go on the other
channel, maybe. But I don't see this
this account on any of these things
where he's where he's calling me. Strange.
Let me see.
I'm on his other account now. Uh, one second. Yeah.
I don't see him on any of these channels. Nope.
Greavves has gone quiet.
So Steve, so why have you not said anything backy?
I've been trying to get an answer out of
you for the past 10 minutes.
Why has he not said anything when he's
calling me a virgin on his channel?
I'm not I'm not trying to get you to
agree. I'm asking you the question.
He's saying that he can't be a virgin
because he's been with a disabled girl
for a couple of years, but I proved I've
had sex and I don't see him defending me
like he's defending his boyfriend. Is
that not not the definition of biasness?
Is that not the definition of being
biased with an agenda? Is that not Is
that not the definition of having an agenda?
Because it's the truth. Cuz you know
it's the truth, you know.
Why do you care?
Cuz I don't like biased people.
I'm coming off this community, bro. I'm
definitely definitely coming off this
community. It's so autistic. It's so
autistic that it's it's actually giving
me brain damage.
It's so autistic. It's giving me brain
damage again, bro.
Seriously. Seriously is. I'm actually
going to come off of it here, bro. I
think you're actually giving me brain damage.
I'm asking a question, Steven Howard,
and no one seems to be answering it.
And I'm asking the same question over
and over again, and it's not being answered, you know.
Right. Right. Right. Okay. So, I have do
I have to explain what I've just said a
million the a millionth time or what?