[ __ ] hell, bro. They just These
people will not stop when they're
jealous of someone, will they, bro?
These people generally will not stop
their jealousy towards me. I'm Do you
know what? I think I'm actually going to
come off of this YouTuber
after today when this Jo doesn't meet
me. Bro, I definitely definitely think
I'm going to I can't be arguing with a
bunch of jealous people. Like, it's it's
actually I'm actually losing brain
cells. I am actually losing brain cells
again. That's how disabled these skin
people are. They actually make you lose
brain cells. They actually actually do, bro.
Yeah. If this [ __ ] doesn't meet me or
arrange to meet me, I'm leaving, bro.
I'm 100% leaving.
Bunch of jealous ugly nerds jealous of
me. It's creepy as [ __ ] what these
people on here do. They're creepy.
Creepy, stinky, fat low lives. I'll be
off of here anyways, bro. 100%.
If this [ __ ] don't meet me today, I'm off here.
These stinky jealous low lives. I'll
leave them to their skint shitty lives
after today, bro. 100%.
100%. These jealous, ugly, harassing,
ugly people that ain't got a life. I'm
actually done, bro. After today, bro. 100%.
Yeah. 100% I am done, bro. 100% I am done.
Cuz their jealousy towards me is never
going to stop. They're never going to
stop being jealous of me. This is why I
left to begin with because they're so
jealous. They don't stop. And then at
the end of the day, you're just going to
spend all of these years arguing with a
bunch of fat, ugly losers, and you've
achieved nothing like them.
Arguing with a bunch of ugly, jealous
people cuz you're better looking than
them. Think about that, bro. [ __ ] that.
I'm not going into a new year. I'm I'm
off tomorrow, bro. 100%. I'm off
tomorrow. When this [ __ ] does not meet
me, I'm off of it.
I don't want to argue with people that
are jealous of me. I'm never going to
get that time back. These people are
stinking jealous. I've just got on that
L J's channel and they are stinking
jealous. They are lying to themselves,
bro. Yeah. The amount of time and and
and [ __ ] that they put into people that
they don't know, brother. They're
jealous of you. 100% they're jealous of
you, bro. And I'm not the only one that
has said it with these fat ugly people
on here. Yeah.
I'm going to wait today, bro. Then
that's it. I'm going to wait and that's
it, bro. Yeah. 100%.
Fat ugly people. All cuz you're younger
and better looking than them. At the end
of the day, do you know what? I could
blame Timmy for this getting me on this
community with these fat mongos.
You know, I could actually blame Timmy
for this [ __ ] I didn't know it was
going to be a bunch of jealous ugly
people with no life, no money sat on the
internet every day. But [ __ ] all in
their life. [ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that.
I'm off of here after today, bro. 100%.
Yeah, I'm 100% off here. But this [ __ ]
if this [ __ ] does not meet me so I can
smash his face in, I am off here today.
I don't want to entertain people that
are jealous of me. I'm never going to
get that tie back ever again, bro.
Never, never, ever, ever, ever, ever on
a community with a bunch of bully victim
losers that sit and talk about
themselves every day, calling themselves
skin, calling themselves every day for
years and they're still the same
pathetic, fat, ugly people. I'm done,
bro. I am done. Done. Done. Done. 100%.
We'll wait for this to reply today and
then I'm done, bro.
I'm done with these jealous losers. Let
them live their fat, ugly, virgin lives
on YouTube. They ain't got nothing going
for themselves, which is why they do
this every day. They're absolute bully
victims that have got nothing in their
life. That's why they rely on a reaction
because they're bully victims. They're
ugly. They're ugly fat [ __ ] That's
what they are, bro. Yeah.
All because I'm younger and better
looking than them. This is what this is
over, by the way. This is why they do
this. They do this. It's because you're
younger and you're better looking.
That's why that's why these ugly people
do this on here, you know, every day on
YouTube. Just cuz you're younger and
better looking than them. These people
are supposed to be [ __ ] older than
me. You know,
this self-projecting bastard. Listen,
I'm going to I'm going to say it for the
f last time. You did not get any of my
money stopped. I'm I've got more money
than you. I know you do not like hearing
this, right? When people have to repeat
this. I have got more money than you.
more money than you will ever have.
Yeah. I'm not the one that has sat on
YouTube Thursday, Saturday calling
people skint when you skint yourselves.
That's been doing it for [ __ ] 10
years. You know what I mean, bro?
Simple. I'm done, bro. I think I'm just
going to delete my account after today,
bro. 100%. I'm deleting my account.
Yeah, if this [ __ ] does not meet me
today, I'm deleting my account or
arrange to meet LA. I'm deleting my
account. 100%. I'm deleting my account,
bro. [ __ ] this.
It's creepy now. It's getting weird. A
bunch of Middle A people jealous of you
every day. [ __ ] that. I'm deleting my
account. They're never going to meet
you. They can't be a man and meet
anyone. I'm just going to delete my
account, I think. Yeah, 100%. I don't
want these [ __ ] ugly, jealous nerds
watching me anymore. This is one of the
reasons why I made another account to
get away from these jealous ass ugly
people. You know what I'm saying, brother? Yeah. That's facts.
[ __ ] fat ugly people that have got
nothing in their lives but autism.
That's what they've got, bro. They're
[ __ ] disabled on here. Why do you
think you have to say the same [ __ ] over
and over to them? Look at this guy. I've
just gone on the channel showing a 400
watch. You don't have money. Stop acting
like you've got money. You don't have
money. You're skint just like your ugly
kids. You're [ __ ] rotten ass kids,
you know? You don't have money. You're
not above anyone. You're skint as [ __ ]
That's why you beg people for money
every day. You know
these people, bro, like they're they're
[ __ ] skint as [ __ ] You know,
it's [ __ ] madness.