Yeah, still no response.
So, that says it all, doesn't it?
Another [ __ ] house that will do nothing.
Another self projector.
What's the time now? 12 minutes to 9 and
not a single response from this clown.
Oh, the irony, huh? Well, that's me done
anyways. That is generally generally
generally me done.
Yeah, that is definitely definitely me
done with these little bully victims.
Definitely definitely definitely one
million% done. We'll give it a bit more time
and then that's it. Yeah.
Jesus Christ. They commented on my video
first thing of the morning. What?
[ __ ] hell, bro. They really ain't got
a life. These bums on this community.
Their lives are so tragic. It's
unbelievable. and they want to talk
about other people. Oh, Jesus [ __ ] Christ, bro.
But yeah, I told I gave Smokey B the
same offer. Go live in anywhere in
London today and you'll see what will
happen to you. Simple. And that's all
I'm saying now.
Give it a little bit more time and
that's it. So, I've arranged now for the
fourth time to meet someone and they've
sh pants again. Uh but they will come on
here and reverse the psychology and say
that I'm the one that will do nothing.
So you've all seen it with your own eyes
eyes now with these people and that's that.
That's mag on YouTube first thing in the
morning if you've got a normal sleeping pattern.
Yeah, this is getting very autistic
again and very repeating again. So
anyways, I'm going to be coming off of
YouTube anyways after today. Um,
assuming this guy's not going to agree
to meet me. And that's me done for a
little bit. Autism again. Proper proper
autistic people on here, bro.
Yeah, I'm proper proper D. 100.
This is [ __ ] weird, bro. What the
Madness, bro. Absolute madness.
talk about themselves every day. Jesus [ __ ] Christ.
What the [ __ ]
Yeah, see me soon. You're never going to
see me soon, fats. So, your little
bullying tactics will never work with
someone like me. Go back to bullying
Timmy. You're not going to be seeing
anyone soon, Fatty. You ain't going to
in you. You didn't even go on Jaden's
door. So, I don't think you're going to
be coming on my door four years later
somehow. Your bullying tactics don't
work. You're not about nothing. Smokey B
is not about nothing and Jo is not about
nothing. You are about nothing. Listen.
Listen. Right. So, I assume that you're
not coming today. Yeah. Okay. Let's
let's keep up with your lie. So, I
assume that you're not coming today. Why
don't you tell your boyfriend to meet me
today, Jo? I will literally smash his
teeth down his throat today if he wants
to meet me, brother. I will go anywhere
you want me to today. I will smack his
teeth down his throat. That's my promise
to you. If you agree to meet me, I will
do it cuz you're not coming today, are
you? So, I mean, that's another day.
Tell your boyfriend to meet me today and
I will smack his teeth down his throat
and make a video of it. I'm easy, bro.
I'm very easy. And if you're not going
to do it, you'll do nothing. Someone's
trying to meet you and you're doing
nothing about it. So, what you mean is
you'll do nothing because someone's
trying to meet you now for the fourth
time and you keep ignoring it. You know,
I will smack his teeth down his throat
and laugh in his face. Something that's
outside of you. Come and do it then,
bro. Tell him to meet me. I'm here. What
What are you waiting for? I'm I'm free
all day today. I'm free all day
tomorrow. Come on. Let's go. I really
really really want to go. I've looked up
your watch, by the way. Nice 400 watch.
You are sklin skinted than a [ __ ]
skin flint. And you're talking about And
you're talking about uh Ant-Man's Ammani
watch, bro. I've looked up your watch
and it's £400. What the [ __ ] Your skin.
Your [ __ ] skin. Just admit it. You want benefits, [laughter]
bro. Just admitting that you want
benefits. You ain't got no money.
No, I'm just trying to beat this Joe F
today, bro. to be honest with you
because he's he's having a big mouth
again. He's he's a big he's got a big
mouth for someone that's a little [ __ ]
So, I'm trying to meet this [ __ ] again
for the fourth time now. This is the
fourth time. Yeah. 70% of my money. No,
it's not. You don't know how much money
I've got. Oh, how come you didn't get a
Rolex? Because you can't afford it.
You're [ __ ] skint. You are skint,
brother. My wardrobe is worth more than
your whole life. Is is literally worth
more than your whole life. Please stop
it now. It's embarrassing. Stop it. You
don't know how much money I have. [laughter]
You don't know anything.
That's why I'm laughing at you. Just get
your boyfriend to meet me today. Just
get your little gay bastard boyfriend to
meet me today. Trip 8, can you get this
bastard to meet me today? Can you tell
this bastard that I will meet him
anywhere he wants to today?
Can you please tell this lame bastard
that I want to meet him and laugh in his
face today? Anyone that knows who that
account is, I will happily meet him and
laugh in his bastard face. I like the
word bastard. And if he's not going to
do it, he will do absolutely nothing in
capitals, mate. Yeah. Simple.
Simple. I get more than £1,100. You
don't know how much money I have. And
you don't even get £1,100 a month.
You're on like £300 a month. You're
literally on 11 You're literally on
£300. You don't even get a grand a
month. This is what I was saying to you
yesterday. You're skint. That's why you
have to make up stories that you own
property and all of these things. You
don't own property. You're you're skint.
You don't even have £1,000. You silly
goose. You don't even have a grand. I
don't even know why you're talking about
a grand, brother. If I got £,100 a
month, I'd have more than you. I'd still
have more than you. You don't get a
grand. You don't have a grand to your
name. Crying. Cry again for you. Nah,
bro. I'd rather laugh at you. You was on
YouTube Christmas. Remember players? You
was on YouTube Christmas. Oh, I'd rather
laugh at you than cry. I'd rather laugh
at you, mate. I've got the video, mate.
Yeah, literally, I've got the video. I'd
rather laugh at somebody that was on
YouTube Christmas cuz they got no
family. I'd rather laugh, not cry. Thank
you, though, bro. I know you like to
hear me cry, but I'd rather laugh at a
loser on YouTube Christmas cuz you got
no family. And you know I'm right as
well. There's nothing you can say. I've
got evidence of you being on YouTube
Christmas. Some [ __ ] loser with no
family on Christmas trying to give it
the big brother. Do you want me to put
the video back up? You want me to put
the video back up? When you're on
YouTube Christmas, you [ __ ] loser.
You got no family, bro. If it's going to
end today, if this guy does not meet me,
if this Joe does not meet me, if this
bastard don't meet me, I'm done with
these people. I am 100% done with these
people, bro. I am not going into another
I'm not going into another year with
this again. If this Joseph Ross stinky
bastard that would do nothing, I'm
hoping he's listening to this. Remember
the question, "Brother, you don't have a
girlfriend. You've never had a
girlfriend. I've been with women." Yeah,
people have seen me with women. Yeah.
You don't have a girlfriend. You don't
have a mother. Yeah, I do remember your
self projection. Uh, question. Yeah. Oh,
wait. You don't have a girlfriend. Look
closer to home, brother. You don't have
a girlfriend. You ain't got a mother.
You You ain't even got a mother, let
alone a girlfriend. You ain't even got
no family, bro. You ain't even got no
family, let alone a girlfriend, you ugly
[ __ ] I I challenge you one thing, bro.
Yeah. Join right now and show your face,
brother. You've never been with a woman.
You ain't got a girlfriend. Why do you
keep putting yourself down? Because what
you people do on here, all you do is put
yourselves down. You are ugly. You are
skin. You have got nothing. You're just
putting yourselves down. All you do is
put yourselves down. You little retards
with autism on here. You just do nothing
but put yourselves down. You got no
money, no girlfriend, no family, never
been with a woman. You're constantly
putting yourselves down and then think
that you're bullying people by talking about yourself.
You got no family, no girlfriend. L is
showing a 640B watch because he's
absolutely skint. Brother, all you're
doing is deconstructing yourself. Every
time you come on here and you keep
talking about no this, no that. You're
only hurting yourselves. You're not
talking about me. You don't know me. You
don't know what I've got. I've got more
money than all of you. I got more money.
I've been with more women. I'm better
looking. I'm younger. So really, what
you're doing, you're just talking about
yourself. You're you're actually putting
yourself down. You don't know what my
monthly income is. And brother, brother,
I get more money than you a month. I get
more money than you a month, mate. I've
got more money than you a month. I get
more money than you a month. Yeah, mate.
You ain't even got a grand to your name,
brother. Brother, brother, you don't
even have a grand to your name. You're
skint. That's why you beg for donations.
You beg for donations because you ain't
got no money. Stop the lies. You ain't
got no money. I don't know why you and
and legs come on here and act like you
got money when you don't. Listen, you've
got six, you own six properties when
properties in Belfast would be like a
pound each. Your stories do not add up.
You have not got money. Stop acting like
you've got money. You ain't got money.
You know, I've got more clothes than
you. I've got more money than you. I
don't know how many times it's it has to
be proven. You do not have money. The
same thing with non legs. You don't have
money. I don't know why you keep acting
like you've got money. You don't owe
property. You're on benefits. Okay.
Okay. Let's ask you this question then.
How do you make your money? No woman, no
house, no money. Congratulations. You've
just talked about yourself. Oh, yep.
Yep. Yep. You're talking about yourself
again. Like I said, brother, you was on
YouTube Christmas. Whatever you're
saying is about yourself. It's not
bullying me because it's self
projecting. You were sat on YouTube on
Christmas. Let that sink in. You were
sat on YouTube Christmas Day and you
know it. So shut the [ __ ] up. Do
everything that you're trying to say.
You're just self projecting, right? Let
me tell you about you people. You got no
money. You got no girlfriend. You're all
old. You're all ugly. You're all YouTube
dependent. Not one of you have got a
single friend to your name. Everything
is about yourself.
You know what I'm saying? Everything is
about yourself, brother. You can keep
repeating that because that's yourself
you're talking about. I'm not going to
ban you. I'm not going to ban you
because you're talking about yourself.
So, I'm not going to ban someone that
talks about themsel. If you people had
anything, you would not be sat on
YouTube every day hating on people that
you don't know. You are talking about
yourselves. You're older. You're much
uglier. You're much skint.
You are talking about yourselves.
You are bullying yourselves. Why do you
think I'm not blocking you?
Oh, [ __ ] that. What's that? Oh, there
you go. So, yeah, man. Uh, you know, you
people are old, ugly, skinned, and you
got no friends. It's already been
proven. So, I don't give a [ __ ] what
comments that you write. Everything you
say is about your own lives. I mean,
I've had I had someone say to me, Triple
H, that I I pay for takeaways on Uber Eats.
Jesus Christ, brother. They would say
that because these people was lonely
Christmas. Their family hate them. These
people was on YouTube Christmas. Play
his number. Was you on YouTube
Christmas? You little loner. Was you on
Was you on YouTube lonely with no
girlfriend Christmas? Yes, you was. Do
you want me to put the video back up?
So, why was you on Christmas? Why was
you on YouTube Christmas? Answer us. Why
was you on my live stream in under a
minute when I was live on Christmas?
Because your skin, no girlfriend, no
family. That's you. You're talking about
yourself. You are talking about your
lonely self with no girlfriend. Exactly.
Yes. Because you're the one with no
girlfriend. You're the one that's old.
You're the one that's ugly. You're the
one that's a fat [ __ ] It must be you.
The evidence shows that it's you. The
evidence does not show that it's me. You
understand? Yeah. Simple. You was a
lonely [ __ ] No girlfriend, no family.
What you was laughing at me, brother.
You laugh at yourself. And you know what
I love about these people on air trip
rates? They will never show their faces.
They will never show their faces. No
money, no girlfriend. Brother, you're
talking about yourself. I've got more
money than you. I don't know why you
keep saying, "I've got no money and no
girlfriend when I've shown more money
than you. I've got more money than you."
I don't know why you you're keeping up
this lie. And the girlfriend, I've been
with more women than you. You're the one
having phone sex with a [ __ ] woman in
America. Brother, that is literally you,
LJ. If you actually say something that
is not about you, I will I will say it.
No money. That's you. You're skint. No
girlfriend. You don't have a girlfriend.
Why is everything you say about
yourself? The point is to try to say
stuff, you would be showing it. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. So, why are you people not
showing money then? Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay. If I had money, I would be showing
it. Okay. Let's see some of your money
then. This is how you This is how you
own these people, bro. This is how you
own these people. Okay. Okay. Yeah,
right. If you've got all of this money,
let's see all your money then. Of
course, it's jealousy, brother. Triple
H, they're fat, ugly, single people with
no friends. Do you not understand, bro?
Yeah. It's not even about women. It's
not even about money. These people are
sat on YouTube because they've got no
friends. This is their only social uh
interaction. Like, it's just it's the
only social interaction, bro. Because
they've got no friends, no family. Why
do you think they're on here? They're
little They're little weasels. They're
[ __ ] fat, ugly, bitter little
weasels. You know, anyone with a life
would everyone anyone with a life would
have [ __ ] off here by now. You know,
at the end of the day, bro, like there
are So, anyways, I put the link up. So,
why can't we see your money then? Okay,
show us your money then. You know
what it is? Do you not think that
there's a reason why none of these
people come on camera, bro? Come on now.
They're all fat and ugly. That's why
they never come on camera and they just keep typing.
I project my depression. Really? That's
funny cuz I'm definitely definitely not depressed.
Facts are no family. Yeah, you're
talking about yourself, bro. Again,
you're again come back when you're
saying something that's not about yourself.
Okay, brother. Come back when you're
saying something that's not about
yourself. When you stop projecting and
talking about yourself, then you might
have a point. Again, we've seen the
evidence of you people being on YouTube
from the time you wake up to the time
you go to bed. You have nothing. I've
got my evidence, my evidence pack of
what you people are. So, when you've
actually got something to say about me
that's not about yourself, come back to me.
Yeah, you need to come back to me when
you when you stop talking about
yourself, brother. Come back to me. And yeah,
that's it. Otherwise, you're not going
to bother anyone because you're just
talking about yourselves. And at the end
of the day, I'm waiting for this uh
Joseph Farra to reply back.
You didn't see my dinner, Triple H. It
was lush. It was lush. And LJ was lonely
on Christmas. No family, no girlfriend.
Yeah, they're just they're just all projectors.
Oh, players, bro. That doesn't hurt me.
We all know that I'm younger and better
looking than you. Your little your
little self-p projection words don't
hurt because everyone knows I'm younger
and better looking than you. The facts
are there. So, no one really cares what
you old ugly people say. Like I said, if
you click on some of these people's accounts ra
Yeah. 18 years ago these people uh was
made. These people are older and uglier.
So their words don't mean nothing
because they're sad, fat, old, ugly
single people. That's why their words
don't bother me, bro. Because we all
know that they're fat, bitter, and ugly.
That's why their words don't bother me
because they're talking about
themselves. All they're doing is putting
themselves down and embarrassing
themselves. Now, if they actually had a
life, they wouldn't be on there typing
to people that they don't know every
day. They wouldn't be on there. If these
people had a life and they had a family,
they wouldn't be on there typing away
and just bullying themselves, they would
actually find something else to do.
Because like I've said to you multip
millions of times, they literally bully themselves,
you know. No, I'm not agitating. I'm
just talking about you little
self-reflectors. How many how many
punches did it take? Brother, my nose is
not big. I'm younger and better looking
than you. Your words have got no effect.
I'll put the link up right now and prove
that I'm younger and better looking than you.
Right. I will prove it right now. If
you're better looking than me, come on
here and show your face
and I'll prove that you're a fat, ugly,
baldy bastard. I'll give it a couple of
seconds. I'll wait for you. You know
what I'm saying, mate? Yeah.
Come on, show us your good-looking face.
What have you got to hide? Come on, man.
I'm not going to dox you. I don't want
to know people's family, people's
addresses. Come on, let's see your faces.
Let's see your faces.
And that's where you always will win
with these people. Exactly. Bro, you're
laughing at me, but you was on YouTube
Christmas. You was on YouTube Christmas
and you're and you're older and uglier
than me. How can you laugh at me, bro?
I've got more money than you. I'm
younger. I'm better looking than you.
What's there to laugh at? Someone better
than you in life? You can't laugh at
someone that that's better look. I mean,
look at Okay, look at our Christmas. I
was at my sister's Christmas. I had nice
food. You was lonely on Christmas. How
can you laugh at me, Mr. Lonely? And you
know what I'm saying is correct. You
know what I'm saying is correct. You was
lonely this Christmas with no girlfriend
and no family. So why are you laughing
at me? Why are you laughing at the
younger and the better looking? It
doesn't make sense. I mean, is that is
that what you actually do? Convince
yourself that that uh you're laughing at
people younger and better looking than
you? that's got more than you in life.
Is that generally what you're convincing
yourself now? Because I think this is
actually a new thing, bro. I think this
is actually a new thing.
Are you actually convincing yourself
that you're that you're uh PJ's never
had a sex life? Oh, that's that's self
projection. I've shown women. I've shown
sex. I've shown money. Nope. That's
definitely you people.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. That's
definitely definitely you old ugly
people. Definitely not me.
Definitely. Definitely you old ugly people.
And you know what's so funny with you
little clowns is you would never meet
anyone in real life. You're just fat
ugly bully victims. Like you can't even
every time you try to leave your house
share, you probably get slapped up for
being so ugly. So that's why you come to
the internet. Yeah. Convincing yourself
that you laugh at people that are
younger and better looking than you.
Brother, are you sure you're not
laughing at yourself? Players, a sado
with no girlfriend, no life, lonely. Are
you sure you're not laughing at
yourself? I I generally think I do you
know what? Yeah. I think these people
are so disabled they get themselves
confused with you. That's where the
that's where the brain damage comes
from. PJs have had I've had a sex life
and I had have a girlfriend. Again,
another self-reflected that's got no
girlfriends. Oh, that's yourself. You're
in your 40s and you're a virgin. Again,
self-p projection. No, I haven't. No,
you haven't touched the nerve. No, no,
not at all. I've touched a nerve though.
I'm younger than you. I'm better looking
than you. No, I'm stating facts of what
you ugly people do on here.
I'm just stating what you ugly sad acts
with no friends do on here every day.
Not on earth. I'm completely calm. Just
talking about you ugly people with no
friends. You're going out to see your
friends today, players. Oh, wait. You
ain't got none ugly [ __ ] [laughter]
Come on. We could We should do this,
bro. All day. Come on. Double, bro. Sat
on YouTube from the time you wake up to
the time you go to bed, you people
really have got nothing. And you show
that you've got nothing. You know, the
more you do this, the more it shows you
got nothing. The more it proves my
point. The more you sit on here and the
more you do this, the more it proves I'm
younger and better looking. I've got
more than you. This is why I do this.
This is honestly why I do this because
it proves that people like you have got
nothing. It is a Monday today. These
people are not at work. They're sat on
YouTube. It's proving my point. It's
proving my point. Yeah, you don't bully
no one. You people don't bully no one.
Like I've said multiple times, you
people are fat, old, ugly, and you ain't
got a life. You mies have always been
bullied. You munties have always been
bullied. You're talking about your ugly
selves. You're all older. You all
uglier. You all ain't got no job. Look
at you on YouTube. You people ain't got
no life. No life, no job. Just a bunch
of ugly bully victims. And there's a
reason why you don't show your face.
It's cuz you're old, bummy, and [ __ ]
ugly. You've been bullied all your life.
That's why you're on here. Look at this.
It's Monday. Shouldn't you people be at
work? You're just bummy little bully
victims. That's why I don't block you.
Cuz you don't bother me. You You bully
victims don't annoy me. You bully
victims are just putting yourselves
down. That's why I'm not blocking you
because all you do is put yourselves
down whilst you and you should be at
work to be honest with you. You should
be at work. You people should be at
work. You should be with your
girlfriend. So, I'm not blocking you.
I'm just showing what you people are. Do
you know what? I might actually do a
video on this to be honest. You people
literally should be at work today.
These people should be at work. I'm not
going to top myself. What? over you
bunch of ugly little losers that ain't
got a life. Yep, that talking about
yourself again, brother. What have I
told you about talking about yourself, players?
Brother, you need to stop talking about
yourself. You need to stop putting
yourself down because I'm very, very
concerned that you might kill yourself.
Cuz like I said, all you people are
doing is bullying yourselves. You're
putting yourselves down and you're
wasting your life typing to me. I'm not
annoyed. I'm not triggered. I'm not even
going to say anything.
Why the [ __ ] are these people not at
work is what I'm going to wonder. Why
are these people not at work? Why are
these people not got any friends? I'm
just going to be saying these things
whilst they're typing stuff. They got no
friends. They got no looks. They're fat.
They're ugly. They can't show their
faces. They got no money. They've not
been seen with as many women as I have.
They've not been seen with more money
than I have.
I'm starting to think it's these people
that are really these things. I mean,
like I said, it is it is past 9 in the
morning. It is working hours. Um, people
should be at work. Um, isn't that right,
Triple H? I mean, nonslegs don't have a
job yet. Um, nonslegs don't have a job
yet, but I mean, we're working on that,
aren't we? I mean, he admits that he
doesn't work. He admits that he doesn't
work. Just a little part-time job. To be
honest, I think L J could get a
part-time job. Then he would stop being skinned.
Yeah. Like I said to you people, you're
just bullying yourselves. You're just
putting yourselves down. We have seen
you fat, ugly people numerous times.
That's why you don't bother us. I'm not
bothered. I'm not going to block you
because we all know that the people that
are behind these counts are sad, ugly
people that was alone on Christmas. So
it doesn't bother me because at the end
of the day only certain people in life
as the saying go can judge you. Ugly
people that's got no life, no money, no
girlfriend, no family can't judge a guy
like me. They're just talking about
themselves. These people literally I can
put the link up right now, Triple H, and
I'll show you. They won't come and show
their faces cuz they're very [ __ ] fat
and unattractive. Now if you see all of
these people before that's done this, I
can name you. I can name you four people
and they've all been fat and ugly. Oh,
bro, you were laughing at yourself.
That's fine, bro. You can You're You're
always welcome to come on here and laugh
at yourself. You was on YouTube
Christmas. Let that sink in. You're more
than welcome to come on here anytime,
bro. You're not blocked. I mean, you got
all of these people. These people are
supposed to be bullying me, bro.
And I'm still here. Yeah. Like I said,
you're talking about yourself again.
We've already We already know that
you've got none of them things.
We already know that you've got none of
them things. Why do you keep putting yourself down?
Yep. Yep. That's not going to work. No
one stopped my money again. You're
supposed to be bullying me, bro. You're
literally supposed to be bullying me.
And all I'm seeing is I'm younger,
better looking, and I've got more money
than you. That's the only thing I'm
seeing. I mean, I'm supposed to be being
bullied. You're supposed to be getting me mad.
But all I'm seeing is someone that's
younger and better looking than you
people. And that's what's making me feel
good. Okay, let's see if any of you
people can prove me wrong right now.
Let's see if any of you people can join
and show me that you're better looking
than me. I'm going to give these people
the benefit of the doubt. I'm so nice to
these people, Triple. Honestly, mate, I
give them chances. Let's see if any of
these people are better looking than me.
Let's see if any of these people have
got the bollocks to show their face.
Yep. That's not going to work, LJ.
Because no one stopped my money and I've
got more money than all of you. That's
not going to work. I've got more money
than you. I don't pretend that I've got
six prop uh properties. I don't beg for
£50 because I'm not skint like you,
which I mean a lot of people that what I
respect about like Monty man and other
people is, you know, they say what it
is, but this L J actually thinks he's
got money when he doesn't have no money.
If someone had money,
you know, if someone had money, they
wouldn't be wearing a £640 watch.
You're wearing a £640 watch. You haven't
got money. Stop acting like you got
money, bro. People that's got money rock
around in [ __ ] Rolexes.
28 and never been in a relationship. You
people are 48 and you're still virgins. Stop self-rejecting.
Stop self projecting.
You people are 48 and you've never had a
girlfriend or been with a woman. Look
closer to home. It will do you good.
I'm coming off now. Anyways, see you
later you sad fat ugly people. And I
will wait for Thingy's response later.
And that's it. You people are [ __ ]
old ugly ass people that ain't got no
life. See you later. Bye-bye.