Oh, what the hell? [clears throat]
How many people was on today?
Did they still ain't got alive?
I don't want to say cuz I'm done anyways.
I'm done 100%.
We're not having this song.
No, you don't win again. The reason I
didn't meet him is because you're all biased.
You win again. You don't win nothing.
You're a bunch of losers with no life
and no friends. You've never won
nothing. Why do you keep saying that
you've won? Oh, by the way, yesterday I
was on Lord Jay's. Yeah. And it's the
same people. They've got no friends and
no life. What do you win? What? Being
the world's biggest loser. Yeah, you do
win that. Anyways, the reason I didn't
meet you is cuz you're all biased. Uh,
that's one of the reasons why they meet
you is because you're all biased. You
done the same thing with Bob. You done
the same thing with Kevin Murphy. You're
all biased. No one's going to entertain
a biased audience. All right, let me
explain this PJ's evidence back here cuz
you seem to hear one, bro. Listen. No,
you haven't. Okay. If you had met him
and filled him in, then I would have
then I would Hold on. No, you wouldn't.
No, you wouldn't. You didn't do it when
I met Bomb. You didn't do it when I met
Mark Samson. You were biased.
No one's going to entertain a biased
autistic audience, bro. [ __ ] that. You
did it with the bomb. You did it with
Mark Samson. You did it with Kevin
Murphy. You did it with nonslegs. Get
the [ __ ] out of here. You all biased and
you're banned. See you later. Yeah. PJ's
evidence pack. Listen, bro. Yeah.
Honestly, the truth is why I didn't go
yesterday is they are biased. Yeah. They
are 100% biased. That's why I didn't
waste my time. I didn't waste my money.
I've done all of this before. And I did
say I was going to meet you. I did say I
was going to meet them because they were
pissing me off. But bro, when you think
about it, yeah, how many people have I
tried meeting on this community and they
have not turned up and no one has said a
damn thing about it. They've all been
biased. Lo yesterday said that nonstakes
owned me. Even when I've gone to Derry
three times and he did not come out.
So it's a waste of time, bro. They they
used to do the same thing. So I just
didn't waste my time to be fair. I'm not
wasting my time. They done the same
thing with Mark Samson. They done the
same thing with Nons. They done the same
thing with Kevin Murphy. You could
listen listen bro listen listen.
The whole of next year you could
actively try to meet all of these
people. You could travel wherever you
want and they would just talk. They
would continuously talk [ __ ] You show
them money. They still call you skin.
You [ __ ] you show everything and
they'll still talk [ __ ] They will waste
their time, bro. None of this in the new
year, bro. None of this in the new year.
None of it at all. They've already
proven to be biased. Remember, they're
saying about how, oh, I was running to
LT. LT was arguing with me yesterday. LT
was being a [ __ ] s trying to show off
in front of a woman on my channel. Why
the [ __ ] would I run for backup? What
the [ __ ] Never had to run to anyone. I
I I sent to LT to go and meet LJ because
LT had his own problems with LJ. I've
traveled by myself to meet people. I
don't need no backup.
So, yeah, they're just a waste of time,
a waste of money. They're all slobs.
Another thing PJ's evidence pack. Yeah.
I was on
this channel yesterday, bro. Yeah. I was
literally on this channel and you know
what makes me laugh? Yeah. They were
typing to each other for [ __ ] 20
minutes all in the live stream. And to
be honest, bro, I don't judge people.
Yeah. I don't want It's not for me to
judge, but I'm thinking, hold on a
minute. One second. One second. One
second. They have been on this now
typing to each other for the past 20
minutes. But then everyone else is skin.
Everyone else has got no friends.
Everyone else has got no life. Yet
they're the ones that are sat there
[ __ ] talking to each other all day
because they don't leave the house and
they're trying to judge me. They're
trying to judge me. This is what I
understand. How the [ __ ] bro, can these
people try to judge you when they are in
a worse position in life than you will
ever be? This is This is the thing I
don't get my I can't get my head around, bro.
Same name, same no life. They've got no
life, bro. They And this is what makes
me laugh when Joseph Frost says as we
laugh at you, brother. You laugh at
yourselves. You haven't even got a life.
Most of these people ain't even got a
friend to their name. They ain't got
nothing. Believe you me, they laugh at
themselves. And bro, that's what I
basically wanted to say. But that's
that's it really. I mean, what else is
there to say?
You know, they you're younger than them,
you're better looking than them, you're
in a better position in life than them.
There's a reason they don't come on
camera. And it's it's not even about the
jealousy. It shows that they've got
nothing. [ __ ] the jealousy. You will
see, bro. They will type to each other
all day. These are people that are
supposed to have money and friends. I'm
not seeing it. I'm not seeing it. And
then they're trying to talk about you.
This is what I'm saying is they're
trying to talk about you when you have
got more in life than them. How does it
make sense? It doesn't. So anyways, I'm
going for a meal tomorrow anyways. And
then I'm done, bro. The new year I'm
done with like these spatics on here.
And that's that's all I'm saying, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, they're jealous. They are jealous,
bro. There's an element of jealousy with
these people. Think of any millionaire,
you know, any celebrity, any
millionaire. Do you think they come on
here doing this? Nah. Not a chance in
[ __ ] hell. No, I've already got a new
channel. I'll just use this channel for
like hotel videos. I'll probably go live
occasionally, but I'm not arguing with
any of these people because another
thing is, bro, when you argue with these
people enough, you get a sore head
because they're autistic and they're
disabled. You keep arguing with them, it
actually gives you a headache. I had a
headache earlier, so that's why I didn't
say anything. Yeah, they actually give
you a headache. I bled it. I've already
I've already explained why I didn't go
because every time I've gone to meet
people in the past, you people dismiss
it. Uh, and that is a valid reason. And
that is a valid It's not even an excuse.
It's a [ __ ] reason. I can I can name
every single person that I have gone to
me and you come back like nothing's
happened. You're a waste of our time.
Literally a waste of our time. I can
name you. I can name you. Yeah. Listen.
Listen. By PJ's evidence pack. You want
to know the person that took the biggest
L on this community.
You You won't think who it was. Do you
know who it was? It was Mark Samson. I
went to this country's area two times,
bro. I was live for several hours and
you probably didn't even think he was
in. Not any time did these people bring
it up. He kept coming on YouTube acting
like the big and they just started it
all over again. Same as that Kevin
Murphy. You can get [ __ ] Yeah. I
ain't scared of no one. I'm stronger
than all of these people in this
community. But I'm not wasting my time
on them. I'm not wasting my time. I'm
not wasting my money. Been there, done
that, worn a t-shirt.
Um, so that's that, you know, cuz it
will never ever end. It will never ever
end. They're going to continuously be
obsessed. They're going to continuously
be jealous whether you show whether you
whether you show up or you don't show
up. And they're just never going to stop.
DJ's evidence pack. They're never ever
ever ever going to stop no matter what
you do. So I'm stopping. New year, we're
done with these people. We're done with
him now, but like proper proper like
nothing, bro. I'm done with these people.
[ __ ] give me a sore [ __ ] head, lad.
One sec. What's this person saying?
And yeah, that's that. So yeah,
I was on LA's [ __ ] yesterday. He's
trying to say nons owned me. Nonss owned
me. I went to the [ __ ] area three times
and I had him stop going to events
because of me. Yeah. And he owned me.
Really? Okay, bro. And that's what I
mean with them. They're biased and it
doesn't matter what they do it for. It
doesn't matter what the reason they do
it for. Just know that that's what's
going to happen in the future. Again,
whenever you try to meet these people, you know,
and that's what can happen, bro. It
would always be the same thing with
these people sat there calling other
people when they're sat on YouTube 24/7.
Get real, mate. Get the [ __ ] real, you
know, get the [ __ ] real. Uh,
it's like they're living their life and
they acknowledge what they are. They're
trying to call other people. That's the
thing that makes me laugh about it.
Well, it doesn't make me laugh about it.
It's actually quite sad. Actually quite
sad to be honest.
Be honest. Oh, I did open this one.
But yeah, I've already got a new channel
with like all of my approaches and
stuff. I have to be careful on Reddit PJ
because they stalk me on Reddit, but I'm
one step ahead of them. I've already got
a channel where I put videos on, you know,
it makes me laughing that Jo says that
he that I'll do nothing when I've done
more than him and his boyfriend. He
needs to stop lying to himself now. It's
getting boring. Very boring. But mostly,
oh, they give you a headache, these people.
And how you know they've got nothing in
life is because I'm I've been saving for
a while. I haven't gone out. I've took a
break from going out. And these people
seem to have more time in their hands than me.
And then you got the LT [ __ ] trying
to show up for a [ __ ] woman. And I'm
the one that's running to him.
Yeah, definitely. Definitely. He was
trying to show off in front of that autumn.
Yeah. And the Virgin done it as well. He
also went on our channel. The Virgin
done it. But you know, it wasn't no
surprise that the Virgin. Yeah.
So, we'll leave these people to pass.
Definitely next. Um,
we're done with these people 100%.
And I wouldn't cry that somebody did
stick up copy me. I was just explaining
how you're biased.
I was just explaining how you're biased.
That's all I was doing. I don't want
anyone to defend me. I don't want to defend myself.
I can defend myself. But I just find it
strange how you didn't
buy it. That's all I was saying. You're
biased. Here will tell you the same
thing as well.
They sit on him and call you a virgin.
Even though you prove you have sex, but
they still call you a virgin. They don't know.
But no, they ain't got nothing in life.
They got [ __ ] they got a friend to their name, you know. Hopefully that
no nothing worse than bird popcorn. [laughter]
Nothing worse in life. and yeah
just uh here I am
the truth. You don't get scared as you
get older. You get strong as you get >> Yeah.
I'm not doing it because they're biased
on it. You start giving people credit
and then people will start meeting new
people or whatever it is you're asking
us to do.
I've lentally proven that I've [ __ ]
had sex. I made a porn video that got
people's channels banned and they're
still calling me virgin. And I don't
give a [ __ ] what they're calling me, but
I'm just saying the biasness
and that's what they'll do in the
future. I'm giving you examples of what
these people do. You met I've met Mark
Stumps and everyone dismissed it. He
come on here a good 30 times before
people started calling him and they only
started calling him when they had a
problem with him. Mhm.
They only started when they had a
problem with him
and and that's that. And it was about 30
times you done it as well.
I could have got a win. Oh mate, I've
had many wins before but you just
dismissed it. You You want me to go You
want me to go over how many wins that
I've got and you've dismissed? I'll sit
here and do it. I I'll sit here and name
you every single win
that I've took that you've twisted and
you've and you've dismissed. You've
either twisted it or you've dismissed
it. I can tell you every single win
that's never been mentioned. I can do it
if you want. I've got all the time in the world.
So, if I went yesterday, you would just
miss the whole thing and start again
when I come back to London. I've been
there, done it, won the t-shirt, mate.
You know, I've been there, done it, won
the orange, pink, and purple t-shirt.
It's borrowing now, you know. >> Yeah.
So, did you give me credit when I went
to Liverpool and everyone run away? No.
Did you give me credit when I went to
Rob's area three times and I hadn't run
into the police? No, you didn't. Did you
give me credit when I went to Mark
Samson's area two times? No, you didn't.
Did you give me credit when I went to
meet Bomb two times and he didn't show
up? No, you didn't. Did you give me
credit when I went all the way to
Middlesborough to meet Trevor Dawson and
he didn't turn up? No, you [ __ ] did
not. So, the evidence is there. The
evidence is there. I'm not making it up.
So, that's that. You're biased.
The perfect way to describe this
community is an autistic biased
community. That's that is the honestly
the the way to describe it.
Again, long leg is a good ass whooping
and you still make up stories.
I had the punch stop leaving his house
for two weeks. Stop coming on YouTube.
No one ever mentioned that. You twisted
it and and said that he beat me because
he got the police involved when the
police didn't even arrest me the first
time. And you twisted it again like you
always do. Yeah.
[ __ ] on here trying to fool other
people, mate. When you on here 24/7,
24/7 you were on air and you're trying
to fool other people. Why you got
friends? Why you got a life? Why you sat
there talking to each other every day?
Come on. Exactly.
If that's what you are, that's your
problem. Don't start calling people that
you don't know. It makes you look stupid.
You've been embarrassed with the money
game multiple times as well. That's
another thing that's been dismissed. Oh,
mate. I can go on and on and on and on
and on and on. How many W's I've took.
And then you get some stupid [ __ ] Joe
trying to tell people that they'll do
nothing when they've done more than you.
Uh, it stopped him going to these events
for a month and he went running to the
police crying. So, yes, it it did do
something. Uh, yes, it did because it
stopped him going on. Let me let me give
you let me rephrase your biased memory.
Uh, yes it did because it stopped him
going on YouTube for two weeks. It
stopped him going to the events for two
weeks to a month and also had him
running to the police. Yes, it did. Did
he come back on YouTube the same day,
the next day or the day after? No, he
didn't. He ran off of YouTube for about
2 weeks. But again, you'll make up
stories because you're biased and
autistic, which is why people don't
waste their time with you. Yeah.
He stopped going to that place for a
good month. He stopped going to that
place and he ran to the police several
times over me and you still twist [ __ ]
and make up stories.
You continuously defend him for
apparently not being a virgin when he's
not proved he's had sex and I have again
biased autism. But brother, you're just
a waste of our time.
Just a waste of our time really.
You're just a waste of our time. You
really, really are a waste of our time.
You're biased. You're autistic. You're
low. All the genuine people that
watching this know that you're not that.
I'm not talking about you. And it's the
facts. It's the facts about you. You know,
the Mark Samson one was shocking as well.
No one ever mentioned anything about not
sings. That's another one. Yeah.
When people call me a virgin, you don't
bring up the porn nose. You don't bring
up the women that I've been with. Not
that I don't want you to back me up, but
you're talking about having an opinion.
Funny how you don't have an opinion on
that matter. But just because someone's
been with a disabled girl who he's never
[ __ ] apparently that makes him not a
virgin. Make it make sense since it's
your favorite words. You're just biased.
biased and autistic. That's that's the only
you're clearly jealous of something in life
or if you're not jealous, you you got
major problems to come on here every day
doing what you're doing and that's it,
mate. That is it.
You know, you people don't laugh at no
one. And by you people, I mean no J's
followers. You sit on YouTube from the
time you wake up to the time you go in
bed 24/7. It's your only communication.
Oh, you do not laugh at a man like me.
Trust me, you definitely do not laugh at
a man like me, mate.
You laugh at yourselves, mate. But you
don't laugh at me.
You can't laugh at someone who's better than you. That's that
big up. How hard can it be? You know,
he's a he's a decent guy, you know that
how hard can it be? Doesn't get
involved, doesn't start anything. He's
quite a good guy, you know. He come on
my door one time. Well,
I don't go and I don't care. These
people are irrelevant.
I didn't go on it,
but I remember I replied to her
yesterday. Yeah. And I had LT up my ass
straight away. He's trying to look good
for women. I'm not even starting [ __ ]
bro. I'm not even trying to start
anything. I'm just saying facts. Like,
he's trying to look good for women. And
then you saw the virgin as well comment
on her [ __ ]
Yeah, he was up my ass straight away. I
don't know if you saw the comment trying
to look good for women again.
No coincidence. It's no coincidence.
Why is it with these people trying to
look good for women? They have not
learned Have they not learned in years
that it's never going to get them laid?
You You know, no, she is fat. She She's
not curvy. She is fat. No, no, she is
she is fat. There's a difference between
being curvy and being a fat and being
fat. She looks like a fatal She looks
like a fat Palooa.
Don't me, mate, when you're the one
using filters. I'm not even fat. I don't
even know when that picture was taken.
My bro, I'm not even fat. So, firstly,
yeah, you are not curvy. You are fat.
There's a difference between curvy and
being fat. He is fat. Yeah.
Yep. 100%. Same thing with that USA
Izzy. She makes herself looks skinny,
but then when you meet when you actually
meet her, she's actually a lot bigger.
They're the big there's a difference between curvy
and then you got nonsense saying, "Oh, I
wish I could sleep with her. I don't
wish I could sleep with anyone, mate.
I've had enough sex.
I'm not like you still a virgin.
Obsessed with virgin still obsessing
over women." See, if your MS actually
gave you a sex life, you wouldn't be
obsessed with other women and women that
I've been with or women with.
That's because you're a virgin and you
don't have sex life. Um popcorn.
Yeah. L that uh L2 was trying to show up
in front of women again.
I don't understand why I like this. I
really really don't.
She was calling me. So I call her
simple. Don't start me.
I sound like a virgin. Oh, that's nice.
Yeah, that's nice.
That's nice. Feel sorry.
You want a You want a medal?
And yeah, it is it is the biasness on
here as well.
I sound like a virgin. Okay,
look at that. It's the bias. M
I sound like a virgin even though I
proved I' had sex multiple times. I say
a good one biased. That's exactly what
me and K talk. This is exactly what me
and K mean when we're talking about biased.
Do you understand what bias means? Challenge
is what these people are. They're
biased. Do you know do you know what the
definition of bias means? It's like
having an agenda.
So actually yesterday I was just making
Okay, so I was making a point yesterday,
right? Maybe it was the day before. I
think it was yesterday um that Jo said
that when I was calling him a virgin,
non a virgin. He says that he doesn't
like nons but he got involved multiple
times saying, "Oh, I don't think
somebody can be a virgin if they've got
a girlfriend." Yeah. when he's calling
me a virgin, I've never seen him bring
up the times I've actually proved I've
had sex. That's what you call biasness.
And I just thought it was a bit strange
how you claim that you don't like
someone, but then you're up their ass
continuously defending them. You want to
make that make sense,
you know? You want to make it make sense
when someone like me has actually proven
that they've had sex and they don't see
you on any of them channels. Yeah, I'm
done with them anyways. Challenge. I'm
And that Joe F. Yeah, he's just a little
nonch lover. He's just a lovely nonch
lover. He's a I knew it anyways, bro.
You know, I I knew about these people
anyways. And because we're we're a
couple of days from New Year's, bro, we
might as well just like I knew he was a
N lover. When he started talking about,
oh, he's got a virgin, he's got a
girlfriend, you know, he's mug, bro. You
can you can spot them a mile off. You
can spot them a mile off. He
continuously was sucking his dick every
time I went for him. I was like, "What
the [ __ ] bro?" All right, bro. Sorry.
Sorry. hurt your boyfriend.
So that's that, bro. So I'm done with
these people, but I I spotted it on my
spot a lot of these people.
Um like there was an account cuz
obviously these people got loads of
accounts cuz they ain't got a life
before that was saying about, "Oh, if
you say so." I said, "Yeah, I do say
so." Um and they were giving like bomb
vibes. I can spot him a mile, bro. I can
spot them a mile. I can smell like burnt
toast. They're just little low life ugly
people that ain't got nothing in life.
That's that in it. I'm not saying no more.
I'm not saying no more, bro. You know
what you doing anyways? You got your plans tomorrow?
Going for a mill tonight? Me? I'm not
drinking, but I'm going for a mill. What about here?
Where are you up to?
Yeah. I won't be drinking till next
year, man. Yeah. Yeah,
I was just I was just about to say the
same thing. You can't even spell liar.
Yeah, I was about I was about to say the
same thing to be back. Yeah. >> [snorts]
>> The mention challenge that they talk
about people being scared,
people having nothing when they're sat
on YouTube 24/7. It makes you laugh, isn't it?
Challenge. It does make you laugh, don't
it, lad? Yeah. See you, bro.
It does make you laugh. And I need to
block that JF, that lovely notch as
well. That's another thing. I need to
block that account once I've had one
last day. I blocked my I blocked a lot
of them to be fair.
I don't like anyone that comes from LJ's
channel. They all spazz him.
Big up Stephen Aldo.
And it's easy to do what you people do
every day behind the behind the screen
as well, isn't it?
I wonder if any of these people's going
to get life next year.
Just quit YouTube like I'm doing. I'm
quitting YouTube. I've got my other channel.
Maybe I'll go live once a month
to see Grezy. But yeah.
Wonder how many people in this community
are going to get a life. That should be
a New Year's resolution to get a life.
What do you reckon?
Got a little life.
You love YouTube. I don't love it.
You're giving me [ __ ] brain damage.
It's the same repeating people.
Same repeating people with no life. Oh,
I'd admish that, bro.
No, same people every day.
Bas mess me, mate. I just come on to say
about why I didn't come yesterday. Oh, [clears throat]
>> Yeah, I just come to say why.
Let me juice
because I put approaches on my other
channel and I don't want any ms on here
watching me. I don't want any Mongs
following me about. No sage, no [ __ ]
Jo. I don't want none of these Mongs
following me about.
So that's why I don't want these people
That's that cuz I'll [ __ ] the whole channel up.
But yeah, that should be your New Year's
resolution to get get off of YouTube and
get a life. A lot of these people on
there because they desperately need one.
Desperately, desperately need one.
The amount of people that was on that
live stream yesterday typing away, "Hold
on. Are these people supposed to have
jobs? Are these people supposed to have
a life? Are the Are these people
supposed to have girlfriends? All the
things that they accuse you of not
having where what do they have when
they're on YouTube 24 fucking7?
Seriously, bro. What the [ __ ]
That is lovely. That is
That is really lovely.
>> [clears throat] >> protection.
You mean projection? And yes, I know
it's projection with these people. It
will always be projection with these people.
Look, the same accounts all night. Mike,
the special Pete is heavily disabled.
Yeah, we've heard all this before. This
is boring. But like I said, um your New
Year's resolution, right, uh should
definitely be get a life. Get off
YouTube and get a life. Do you of good.
Definitely will do the world of good. What's this?
Uh not being able to sleep with you. Uh
another one that's obsessed with women.
This is another thing you you'll find
with this nonsle is that he's
everywhere. women are because he's a
virgin. He gets like obsessed with women
and stuff. A very very very sexually
frustrated virgin. Um will never will
never have sex. He would die a virgin.
Um it would it would not be the first
woman that he's done it to.
Can't believe that little [ __ ] used to
call me a virgin when he's the biggest
one going you [ __ ] mad. That [ __ ]
does not consent to any of your uh
sexual advantages. advances,
never has, never will. He would die a virgin,
you know. I was I was even trying to
help him, you know. You know, like get a
little part-time job. Cuz if you got a
little part-time job, you might be able
to copy more of my holidays.
You know, you might be able to go to
Belgium next time and you might be able
to go to Scotland next time. If you got
yourself a little part-time job, you
won't be skinn anymore. and uh having to
feel the need to show your daddy's life
savings which is let's face it [ __ ] all
so yeah that's that
proper proper proper proper [ __ ]
virgin that one but I say that there's a
lot of virgins on here
[snorts] anyways I'm going now yeah see
you later that's all I wanted to say is
that you're all biased and that's why I
didn't waste my time. So yeah, in a bit.
Anyways, see you.