[snorts] [ __ ] hell. Yeah, man.
This is my last live stream,
by the way.
I'll be live once once in a once in a
blue moon after this. Yeah. Therefore,
just because it's the same repeating people.
[clears throat] Yeah, therefore. Yeah, man.
What a [ __ ] [ __ ] man.
This guy's definitely definitely
disabled, bro. Definitely got disabilities.
How the [ __ ] did that comment go through
when I have this come blocked? Madness.
That's madness, bro.
It was 640. That's 70% of your month income,
brother. My wardrobe is worth more than
two years of your income.
Look who's [ __ ] talking.
worth worth two years of your income.
My income. You don't know how much money
I get a month. I tell you what I want
you to know. Remember that. I tell you
what I want you to know. And you don't
even have £1,000.
You do not even have a,000.
What are you on about?
If you get money, bro, you get money.
You're not left for over a grand. What
the [ __ ] bro?
Yeah, I had a good meal. Yeah,
I Joseph, I I don't agree with you on something.
By the way,
I don't agree I don't agree with you on
this money thing.
I woke up today. I got my money early.
got some more money from something that
I do. Getting money in a couple of days.
It doesn't change your mood.
Doesn't change your mood at all.
Nope. I woke up Oh, actually I woke up
in a good mood. Then I had then I was in
a foul mood after that.
I will never meet anyone.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that, bro.
All right. And that's another reason.
You know why I didn't meet you, Joe, as
well. I tell you why I didn't meet you
is because you're all biased on here.
Oh, sorry. I don't want to I don't want
to I don't want to dismiss that. Uh it's
cuz you're all biased. That's why I
don't waste my time. Now, you can This
is another thing cuz I'm not going into
a new year. You can keep saying that I
will do nothing and I've done nothing
when we all know I've done more than
everyone on here. I don't give a [ __ ]
It's funny to me when you say that now.
I've done more than anyone on here.
I woke up in a good mood. Then I went on
Reddit then it put me in a bad mood.
So money doesn't matter to me. Money
does not matter to me, bro. I don't give
a [ __ ] about money.
Really really don't give a [ __ ] about money, bro.
PJ Social life is No, that's you. That's self projection.
No, that's definitely definitely you people
are going large.
No, that's definitely definitely you people.
No, no, no. You you you are the ones
with no social life. No, that's
definitely definitely definitely you.
And I've seen with my own eyes. Yeah.
So, yeah, I'm not I'm not clinically
depressed. I'm not even depressed. I was
just in a foul mood.
Good thing I didn't go out drinking today.
Yeah. Uh LJ said it was 640. That's 70%
of your month income. I said my wardrobe
is worth more than a year of your income.
Yeah. What can you [ __ ] say to that?
You can't say nothing.
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. This guy's a
[ __ ] [ __ ] Honestly, he's an
absolute [ __ ] bro.
So, I didn't go out anyways.
I was a small part of me was like, I
should go out drinking, but nah, I'm not
I'm done with that [ __ ]
I'm done with that, mate.
Yeah, I did. Yeah. Okay.
But brother, we see you people on YouTube 24/7.
So you can keep saying that I've got no
friends, but brother, you people are the
ones that have got no friends outside of
YouTube. We've already seen this, bro.
So whatever you say, it doesn't bother
me. Everything you you say is pretty
much self projection.
No one cares about you being jealous or
not being jealous. You legitimately have
got no life. We seen you on YouTube for
20 We see you on YouTube 24/7.
You have got no life.
You literally have got no life. I don't
give a [ __ ] if you're jealous or not.
You've got no life. I was on Lord J's
and I was watching and I was like, "Nah,
these are not the same people that are
telling me that I'm skinn. These are not
the same people that are telling me I've
got no friends." No, no, no, no, no, no,
no. These are not the same people, bro.
This has got to not be the same people.
So, you just look stupid when you're
saying all that stuff. Yet, you're on YouTube 24/7.
24/7 of your lives. That's facts. All
right. Let me tell you something. I've
not been out for over a month drinking
by choice. What you people do is not by
That's the difference. This is what I
said to Laney earlier. I said, "What
these people do on here, it's not it's
not by choice. Me, it's by choice. When
I haven't been out, I can afford to go
out. I'm able to go out. I don't want
to. With me, it's choice. With you, it's not choice.
That's the thing. That's the thing. It's
not your choice. You got nothing else.
You got no money. You got no mates. You
got no life. You're not mobile with me.
It's choice. So, you can't even take the
piss out of it.
So, and 2026. Well, I'm going to be
trying to uh join the porn industry
tomorrow. Joseph Fra.
Yeah, I'm going to be trying to join the porn industry
and start with that basically.
And I'm serious. When I wake up
tomorrow, I'm going to see about it.
I won't be going out again, bro. You
don't believe me. If I wanted to go out
today, I would have went out today. I
got money and I got money from somewhere
else as well, which you don't need to
know. I could have easily went out, but no thanks.
You know, New Year's Eve is probably the
worst day to go out. You know that.
I think it is. You know, the worst day
to go out is New Year's Eve.
They really take advantage of this day
properly. Properly. Did I go out last
year? I can't even remember if I went
out last year on New Year's Eve. I don't
think I did. I think out last year.
I think nonslegs needs to get a little
part-time job. Joseph Ferrar, I think he
needs to get a little part-time job, you know.
I don't need a job, bro. I make money.
I make money, buddy. I don't need to get
a job. I can work whenever I want to.
And that's not even [ __ ] If I need
money from work, I can work whenever I want to.
But I don't need to work. So yeah,
I need to join the gym as well.
You don't need to know what I do.
You don't need to know that. That's for
me to know and you to never find out.
Just keep thinking that I'm scared. I
just keep thinking that it
my toothies are not hurting as much now,
Joseph Ferrar, cuz I've cut down on the
Coca-Cola and I've been using my
electric toothbrush that Laney bought me a lot.
So, my mouth's been a lot better.
Been cleaning my teeth regularly. So
that's a good that's a good thing.
You know, USA is got a worse hairline
than me. Joseph Fra, she is actually bored.
She is actually bored. I was on her
sister's Facebook earlier. Joseph
just having a little peek.
But no, all on on a serious note, um New
Year's Eve is the worst uh day to go out.
It is the worst day to go out.
No, it really really is.
I don't think I went out last year,
bro. I don't I don't need to prove
anything to you because even when people
prove stuff to you, you still talk [ __ ]
So even I could literally show you two
grand right now and you'd still talk [ __ ]
You would literally still talk [ __ ]
Just like all of the people that I've
met, you twist things and you dismiss
it. Even when people prove themselves to
you, you still talk [ __ ]
Oh, look. Perfect comment right here.
Why do you talk like a kid? No wonder
you haven't been laid. Even though I've
proved numerous times I've had sex.
Like, brother, you would always talk
[ __ ] No matter no matter what you're shown,
you've been you've been shown money, you
still talk [ __ ] You've been shown
women, you still talk [ __ ] You've been
shown [ __ ] everything. You still talk
[ __ ] I've met more people than anyone
on this community, including LT, and you
still talk [ __ ] You literally talk [ __ ]
time and time again. So, I don't know
why you're asking people to prove stuff
to you when you just talk [ __ ] Anyways,
do you want me to go? Okay, let let me
let me go down memory lane, right? Oh,
by the way, uh I don't need LT for
backup personally. Yeah, the only reason
I called LT for that L uh for that LJ
thing is cuz he had his own problem with
LJ and I was arguing with LT the other
day actually when he come on my um
video. He was trying to simp over that
autumn. He was trying to look good for women again.
Uh, yes, he did. Uh, that's not my
friend. I don't need him for backup.
Never have, never will. I called him for
Lord Jay cuz he had his own problem with him.
Yeah. You know what else? I don't need his backup.
What the [ __ ] bro?
And he was being a s again. Now that
that is sing. What he done is is actually sing
because because because because with the
USA Izzy thing. No, because Okay, I get
that he was just warning. No, no, not
not with that one. That is definitely simp
cuz think of it. You did not you did not
hear from this guy for months. Yeah,
this guy has gone off the rails for
months and as soon as you're arguing
with a woman, he appears again. What the [ __ ] bro?
That is definitely No, that is sing.
That one is definitely definitely simply sing.
He He hadn't been around for months.
You know what the [ __ ]
I don't ring him. I haven't spoke on the
phone to him for months. Four months. You know,
why is he trying to look good for women?
It's It's embarrassing as [ __ ] bro. You know,
yeah. When you when you people start
proving stuff, when you people start
proving stuff, then you come back to me.
When you prove that you can get in a
relationship, then uh I'm That's what
Ant-Man said as well. He said that you
know what you should say to these
people, you should ask them if they
found someone yet. And that's exactly
what I'm doing.
Yeah, man. When you prove that you can
get in a relationship, then come back to
me and ask me to stop pro. And anyways,
yeah. Uh, Joseph Fra, if you wanted to
know why I didn't meet you, uh, let's go
down memory lane. Let's go down memory
lane. What happened when I tried to meet
Mark Samson two times? You spoke [ __ ]
When I went to non legs three times and
he ran to the police, you spoke [ __ ]
When I went to meet bomb [ __ ] two
times, you sp every time I've gone to
try to meet people, you have spoken [ __ ]
and twisted things. That's why no one
waste their time on you. And I've and
I've tried meeting more people than LT
as well. Way more people than he has.
Yes, I have.
>> Yes, I have. And I've been to more
places than him. So, you really think
anyone's actually going to waste their
time on you again? No matter who you
are? Come on.
Come on. Listen, do you know what makes
me laugh? Yeah, I I said this earlier.
Do you know who Do you know who um took
the biggest L on here? It was actually
that Mark Samson
when I tried to meet him two times and
he would not come out and then then he
come on YouTube like 30 more times and
everyone took his side. What are you on
about, bro? And then everyone took his
side until they had a problem with him.
And then you wonder why people don't
waste their time on you biased people
on you biased people. And no, I'm not
out tonight, bro. I'm staying in. I had a meal. [ __ ]
And then you wonder why people don't
waste waste their time and you bias people,
you know? So, and I've more than proved
I've had a [ __ ] I've more than
proved I had a [ __ ] I've been in
several women different uh several
different women's beds. I've had women
admitted to sleeping with me. You've got
your own agenda. It's clear to see. You
know, it doesn't bother me that you've
got your own agenda.
So, yeah, that's what you do. You are
biased. That's it. [ __ ] that. Mark
Samson got away with coming on here 30
times, starting [ __ ] again before people
started calling him out. and they only
call them out when they've got a problem with them.
You're biased. It's simple. You're just
biased on here and that's it. I don't
give a [ __ ] either way. I'm not doing
this in the new year. You'll be arguing
with yourselves. So that's that. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Only woman I've had
I've paid for. Okay. You keep telling
yourself that, bro.
Yeah. You keep telling yourself that, brother.
But 19year-old, I never paid the first
time. Bro, you've seen everything as
well. I'm not explaining myself to you.
I went to Mark Samson's area twice and
no one ever said anything about it. Not one person
until they had a problem with him and
they still never said anything. They
just started going at him. He took the
biggest L and Ngs. I went to Nons's area
three times. He didn't come out.
Him and uh Mark Samson took the worst L,
bro, ever. And people still would twist
[ __ ] They still come on here and twist
I just laugh at them, bro. I just really
laugh at him. I don't really give a
[ __ ] you know.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. You knew
Mark was pathetic
when after the 30th time he come on
YouTube started acting like a big man.
Yeah. When you people started having a
problem with him. That's when you
thought he was pathetic. When you
started having a problem with him yourselves.
The same with Bomb. Yeah. Just same with problem. Yeah. No, no.
I have I have had more women than a lot
of people in this community, mate. And
I've proven it as well. It's not what I
claim. It's what I've shown. I haven't
claimed. I've shown. Uh there's a
there's a big difference. Um I have
shown more women than anyone on here.
I've shown more friends than anyone on
here. I've shown more money than anyone
on here. And that's not even me talking
[ __ ] That's facts. I've shown more
money, more women.
More money, more women, more friends,
better life. That is not even talking
[ __ ] That's being real. That's that is
it, bro. Really? Really? That that that is it.
They weren't escorts. All of the women
that I was sleeping with wasn't escorts,
mate. So, stop talking [ __ ] They was not escorts.
There was no escorts. Yeah, they weren't escorts, mate.
So, stop talking [ __ ]
And one second. Even if they were
escorts, which they weren't escorts. I
mean, you still [ __ ] them, though.
I've not shown one single friend. Yes, I
have. That's self projection. Yes, I
have. I've shown loads of money, loads
of friends, and loads of women. and you
still come here and talk [ __ ]
Autistic biased community, you know.
Yeah. A lot of self-reflectors, bro.
That's their life. And you know, the
saddest thing about it is these people
are still going to be doing this next
year. They're going to be doing this
next year as well. Projecting, repeating.
[ __ ] boring, isn't it? boring people, you know.
Yeah. I can't handle the truth. Yeah. Um,
no. I've shown you me with my army friends,
my other friend.
You don't need to feel sad for me, man.
You need to feel sad for yourselves.
coming on the internet every day
projecting. You don't need to feel sad
for me. You don't need to feel sad for
me at all. You need to feel sad for yourselves.
I've shown you with my army friends.
I've shown you me with friends. You've
seen me with friends multiple times.
We've never seen LJ with a woman or
friends. The irony. The irony.
Yeah, that's self projection, bro.
you're not in a relationship.
Anyways, I'm going to ban these
self-reflectors anyways cuz everyone in the chat. Um,
yeah. And that's Terry as well. See you later.
That account's Terry. When was the last
time I met them? Um,
a month ago.
Someone actually invited me out last
week, but I just said I'm not going out again. So yeah,
yeah, I said I'm not going out again.
That's what I said to him.
Yeah, you too, man.
Why Joe? Do you think this secular slot
uses real money or do you think he uses fake money?
What's your opinion on that?
You don't believe me in it when I when I
tell you I'm done, do you, Joe? You
don't believe me when I say I'm done
with going out. I'm [ __ ] done, bro.
The thought of it. You won't go out
unless you win money or you feel or you
feel okay to go out. You've admitted that people,
you are lying. You won't go out unless
you win money or you feel okay to go
out. You've admit, bro, I've won money.
I've won money and I listen listen. No,
that's [ __ ] Firstly, I won two
football bets two months ago and I still
didn't go out. Even if I win, I still
wouldn't go out. I still wouldn't go
out. I've got money to go out.
I've literally got money right now to go
out every week if I wanted to from today
from right now. But I don't want to, you
know, and yeah, the reason I didn't want
to go out drinking and I had to be
dragged out is cuz I didn't want any
more bad experiences with women. [laughter]
But yeah, I had to basically go out.
Yeah. Cuz I had planned it. And yeah, I
was guilt tripped into going out
basically. Yeah. Cuz I didn't want any
more bad experiences with women. donut.
Not because I couldn't afford it.
Well, yeah. You think it's money, but it
isn't money. And trust me, Joe, when I
had the house, I was I was more
depressed when I had the house. I was I
was I was [ __ ] depressed when I had
that house. Yeah, maybe if you win
money, you don't feel as depressed if
you win money. But I don't know why, but
I I would still not go out even if I
want money. So, I don't give a [ __ ]
about that. I was more depressed when I
had that [ __ ] house. You must have
memory loss, bro. You must have memory loss.
I've only lost that house the past 4 months.
Was it 4 months? Yeah, maybe it's just
gone four months. I was [ __ ]
depressed when I had that house.
I don't give a [ __ ] about money. You
don't understand. And I don't care about money, bro.
Well, well, I do go out. I just don't go out drinking.
I just don't go out drinking cuz I don't
want any more bad experiences. It makes
sense. It literally makes sense.
It actually makes sense. Why are you
going to do something when it's just
going to go around in circles? It
doesn't make no sense. That's why I said
about joining the porn industry or
trying to join the porn industry. It
makes no sense, you know? It literally
does not make no sense. I'm not dealing
with their [ __ ] anymore, you know?
And that's valid, bro. I don't want to
deal with their [ __ ] I shouldn't have
to deal with their [ __ ] anymore. Their
[ __ ] their lies, their excuses to
[ __ ] with them. Simple. That's what I say.
They are one sad bastards.
They are one sad bastard. Joe,
no. I just don't want any more bad
experiences with women.
It's not that. I just don't want any
more bad experiences with women. Simple as that.
I just think they're [ __ ] you know?
I just think they are absolute [ __ ]
and I don't contradict myself cuz I
don't go out talking to them. I don't go
out approaching them. If if I generally
thought I was wrong, I'd be out today.
I would literally be out now. If I
thought what I was saying was wrong, I'd
be out right now, bro.
But I'm not going to be because I hate
them. They are [ __ ]
in literally every [ __ ] way, you
know? And that's that, you know.
Yeah, it's just uh that.
And they say people Oh, they say people
like need a long break and that. Not me,
bro. Not me. Even after 6 months, I
still feel the same way.
You can't even watch a [ __ ] horror
film, Joseph Ferrar, without seeing a
porno in it.
Well, like I said, I'm trying to join
the porn industry. Um, and then yeah,
that's all I can do, is it?
If you keep if you continue to go out,
the same thing is just going to happen.
You're too old for me. You're too young
for me. You're not a Muslim.
I've got a boyfriend. I'm They're all
the same. The excuses are all the same,
mate. They're boring as [ __ ]
They really are boring, bro. You know,
they they are actually so boring,
you know? They are really really boring.
If you actually think of all the
experiences that you've had, it's
actually kind of sick of them.
It is actually kind of sick.
It is actually sick to be honest with you.
You know the [ __ ] they do, the leading
on the [ __ ] excuses. They're so
boring, bro. [ __ ] hell. They are.
They're such [ __ ] as well.
It's getting like that in Thailand now
as well. Very westernized.
Joseph very westernized.
I generally think I'm asexual now. You
know, Joe, I feel like I'm actually asexual.
I ain't even joking.
Yeah, proper proper asexual.
I'm not even joking. I really am. [snorts] Um,
I'm speaking to this woman on Instagram
from Trinidad, Joseph Ferrar.
Oh, she's just typing Joseph Ferrar.
She's just replied, "Joseph Ferrar
was speaking to someone from the Caribbean."
But no, Joseph Ferrar, these women are really rude. Joseph Ferrar.
Joseph Ferrar. This uh this uh woman, bro.
This black guy approached her. She's
like, "I'm on the phone. Move away from
me." Like, who do they really think they
are? Like, I don't even like watching
this [ __ ] bro. It annoys me. They annoy
me even when they're not saying it to me. reminds
my mind something of them.
But you are the one that
Yeah, but I didn't know what non Okay.
Yeah, but I didn't know what non legs
was like. I didn't know all of that
stuff until after. Just like when I met
Jack the Ripper. I didn't know he uh he uh shagged
I didn't know he shagged teddy bears
until after I met him. There was a guy
called Jack the Ripper of uh PlayStation
um Luke Lambbeath his name was. He used
to pretend to be American. Proper weird
[ __ ] And Monty told me and and I found
out that he used to shag teddy bears and
[ __ ] and stick stuff up his ass. And I
didn't even know that. [snorts]
Yeah, that that nons Yeah. Nonsense.
He's a proper proper weird virgin. I
didn't know any of that stuff. I was
only 17, 18 when I met Nons legs.
Uh, no. I stopped meeting him because
it's like with autistic people, he
becomes very obsessed with stuff
like very very very weird stuff like
that Cheryl Cole thing. That's not even
a joke. When I say that, I'm not even
joking. That was an actual thing.
And where he's so autistic, it turned
into an argument.
I'm not even joking. It was a real thing.
I do not like [ __ ] Shervel Cole and
I'm not [ __ ] gay. And he wouldn't
accept it. He's like, "Nope, you're
gay." I'm not even joking. You laugh it.
You know, you laugh at it, but it was it
was an actual real thing.
And then I didn't even know that he was
doing this stuff to fit in until after,
you know, he was doing stuff to fit in.
No, I just didn't like I just didn't
like her. What she done? She's a [ __ ]
And I didn't and I didn't properly and I
wasn't able to properly get revenge.
So what the [ __ ] That's a bit
different, isn't it? That's someone
[ __ ] you over.
This guy is still obsessed with me after
how many years?
After 10 years, this [ __ ] is still
obsessed with me. What the [ __ ]
So what the [ __ ] bro?
I know. There is no one in the world
that will love me. They're just [ __ ]
These women are just [ __ ] I was
born in the wrong era.
No, but how can you compare the Morgan
situation with Nodle Legs? That's a bit different.
That is a bit different. This [ __ ]
I didn't have sex with this [ __ ] He's
[ __ ] weird. And he's still obsessed
with me, you know, after 10 years.
No, he is literally literally literally obsessed.
There's a there's a big difference.
That is That is a big difference. M Jesus Christ.
No, I don't st I don't stalk family
members. Nah, not me. [laughter]
No, I don't stalk family members. I just
thought they had a right to know what
their what their sister and what their
daughter was like. To be fair. No,
no, they had a they had a right to know
to be fair. Yeah.
I didn't stalk I didn't stalk their family members.
I just messaged them. That's not
stalking. I just messaged them. Yeah, I
Didn't stalk them. I messaged them.
Yeah, it was funny, man. Funny.
Yeah, I messaged them. That's not
stalking. You said I stalked them. I
didn't. No, I don't do it anymore. I
haven't done that for [ __ ] over a year.
I haven't done it for over a year, man.
What the [ __ ]
No, I haven't done that for very very I
would never do it again. I've said what
I've had to say. Simple as that. So
Oh, [ __ ] waxies, man.
Now, Waxies is charging um £15 to go in after 10.
The Guinnesses are going to be like £10
a pint tonight.
Yeah, it's going to be about £10 um a
pint. How do I have dementia?
What? How do I have the me? I messaged
her family members which is not
stalking. There's a big difference
between messaging people and stalking.
There's a there's a there's a difference. No,
I like [laughter]
Oh, [ __ ] me. I was laughing at that
earlier, you know. Yeah,
it looks like the virgin [ __ ]
O, do you remember that one, Joe? When I
put the cut up,
um, that account was like, that looks
like the greeneyed monster virgin [ __ ] [laughter]
I haven't seen that account for a while.
Who found the virgin [ __ ]
Yeah. And if any and if people don't
find her attractive, Mr. Bean, they're gay, right?
Yeah, they're gay, isn't it? Yeah. Yeah. Gay.
Yeah. If people don't find her
attractive, they're gay, isn't it? Yeah.
according to people. Yeah.
Yeah. You're not you're not allowed a
different preference, Joseph.
Nah, definitely straight to being gay.
You definitely definitely like Nick. Copycat statement.
That's a cop. That is what you call a copycat statement.
Why is this [ __ ]
Hey, that is a copycat statement
[ __ ] used to do the same [ __ ]
thing with [ __ ] Rihanna.
Yeah, they done the same thing with Rihanna, Dusty.
It's uh it used to be a um trend to put
celebrities on a pedestal.
That used to be the in thing.
They all they all used to copy each other
by putting celebrities on a pedestal.
Don't know if you know what that means.
goes to Ferrar. Yeah,
they they used to do with Beyonce. Ridiculous really.
No, I've never like that chill. I hate Sh.
Nothing attractive about her at all. gay. Hu.
What if you only like black women? What
if you only like blonde women? Would
that still mean that you're gay? Copycat.
[ __ ] that is death copying. [snorts] Yeah, Rihanna stinking. Yeah.
I had an Indian. It was nice.
I'm going to have my can of Coke in a minute, Joseph.
Yeah, nice can of Coke, Mr. B.
Can't beat a nice can of Coke, can you?
No, but seriously, New Year's Eve is is
actually [ __ ] to go out drinking.
Best time to go out drinking is a
Thursday in March or April. Like I keep saying,
that's the best time to go out drinking.
If you think about New Year's Eve, it's
actually a mugs game.
Going out drinking New Year's Eve. Too much competition.
The It's packed. The prices are way
higher. You have to pay to get into
places. It's a mug's game. It actually
really is a monk's game. New Year's Eve
going out New Year's Eve.
Christmas time is just normal, but it's
just busier. But yeah. Yeah.
The Mugs game New Year's Eve.
Yeah, there's already fireworks. [ __ ] Oh gosh,
I'm so sleepy. Joseph,
I sleep like a baby today. Joseph Bless you. Yeah. Oh gosh.
I'm going to get my kind of the bridge.
Good old Joseph.
>> Look, I got a packet of crisps.
Packet of crisps and Mr.
These crisps are on sale, don't they? Gosh.
Yeah, I like these crisps.
Peter belly don't get two fakes anymore. Uh-uh.
not be ready any m
cuz I was drinking I was drinking coke
like all day now whenever I eat or drink
coke I just brush my teeth straight
after I wait half an hour and then brush
them after seems to do the trick
I like these crisps.
Oh, I just seen his post.
You know what? I hope he does get laid,
you know, in 2025.
I really do hope he loses his Valentine's card.
He's almost 31, isn't he? [ __ ] hell.
He's still a virgin.
That's That is That is epic. [ __ ] H.
I think this [ __ ] Lord J's got autism, bro.
I think he's actually got autism in it.
Definitely. He's definitely got autism, man. [laughter]
I haven't opened my drink yet.
Almost built this bastard drink
everywhere. There's a for
nice kind of quote that is lush, man.
That is the business. If you're watching
this, LJ, that is what you call the [ __ ] business.
The [ __ ] business, mate. All
right. Go in a minute. Yeah. Typing.
I don't know when I'll be back, but
you know, we're not going for another
year of this [ __ ] [clears throat] No, right. Right. See y'all.