Right, I'm just jumping on here quickly
um to just say this and I'm gone again
because I'm not entertaining these
losers in the new year. Um so yeah, uh
Joth, you are showing fake wins. You are
pumping machines and taking money out of
it. Yes, no one is jealous of you. I've
got more money than you. I'm younger
than you. I'm better looking than you.
There's nothing to be jealous of a loser
putting money in, right, and acting like
he's won, which is what you do. Yeah,
you fat bum. I can see through your t
your channel and I and I know what
you're doing. Simple as that, right? You
are the biggest loser. Just like L J.
You and L J. Yeah. You, L J, right? And
them people. You are the losers. Yeah.
You are the losers. You got no social
interaction outside of YouTube. You're
[ __ ] putting money in machines,
acting like you've won, and then when
someone's called you out on your
[ __ ] fatty, you're telling them
that they're jealous. No one's jealous
of you, bro. No one's jealous of a fat
poverty ridden loser with a 200 pound
phone. Believe you me, bro. I can back
up everything I'm saying. You're older
than me. You're uglier than me. You got
a poverty phone, poverty jeans, poverty
life. Bro, I've got more life experience
than you at 27 years of age, 28 years of
age. No one is jealous of a flat a fat
clown because I'm pointing out you
putting up fake wins. That is not
someone that is jealous. Yeah. And the
last I'm saying about this, I've only
come on here to quickly say this. Yeah.
You are the loser. You literally
literally are the loser. You are filling
up machines acting like you've won and
then telling people that they're jealous
when they've caught you out. Get a grip,
you s bastard. Yeah, I've only come on
here to say that. So yeah, and I will
not be replying anymore. Simple. You are
the loser. I've got more money than you.
I don't know how many times I have had
to say to this clown, I have got more
money than you. And he's still telling
people that they're jealous of him.
Brother, I've got more money than you. I
don't need to go out the to the bank and
pull out the [ __ ] money, right, to
prove to you again. Yeah, you are
filling up machines and then taking
money out of it. No one's jealous of
you. No one's jealous of you and your
fake wins. You lavong. You can't even
talk. End the story. And and the last
thing as well um I wanted to say was um
yeah, Red Star, you didn't get anyone's
money stopped. I've explained the story
multiple multiple times and I'm not
explaining it again. You didn't get
anyone's money stopped. But anyways, you
keep telling yourself that and I'm gone
anyways because I'm not entertaining
these losers. So, uh yeah, I'll give him
a couple of minutes and then I'm and
then I'm cutting the live stream off,
you know. [ __ ] this,
you know. Yeah. And that's another thing.
And you didn't get anyone's money
stopped either. I've got more money than
you and I've got side hustles that make
more than you again. Try again.
Sad sad people in this community. 2026
and you're still life's losers. You
didn't you didn't learn anything from
the the the previous [ __ ] years.
You're still on here being life's
losers. [ __ ] me. I'm going to wait a
couple of minutes. See if he comes on
and I'm ending this live stream
because I'm not doing this again in the
new year with some fatty showing fake
wins. [laughter] That's a madness, bro.
Right. I'm gonna give it a couple more
minutes. Gonna give it to five minutes
and I'm cutting the live stream off. So that's that.
Yeah, man. Simple as that. You and L J
are the biggest life losers. You are the
ones living under poverty. I don't know
how many times people have explained
this to you. Multiple I've told you
multiple multiple multiple multiple times.
No, he doesn't have big wins. What he
does is he puts money in machines and
takes it out.
He's showing fake stuff. I'm not
jealous. I've got more money than him.
I've said this multiple times, bro. I
have said this multiple times, right?
That I have got more money than him. And
no matter how many times you keep saying
it to this guy, he doesn't listen, you
know? No matter how many, but then
again, he's a lavy bong. So, at the end
of the day,
no, he's not hitting big, right? Do not
listen. Listen, I'm going to explain to
you one more time what his channel is.
His channel is about showing fake wins,
right? You don't you don't understand,
bro. You You You don't understand. His
channel is showing he's putting money in
and taking the money back out. I can
smell for his [ __ ] just like Lavy's
[ __ ] Do you understand? He's not
creaming on no fies. He's putting up
fake stuff. So then whenever somebody
says, whenever somebody criticize, um I
can tell you what his trick is. putting
money in and taking it back out. Acting
like he's one, you know,
literally like he is literally putting
money in, taking it out as if he's one.
So when people say something, "Oh,
you're jealous. Oh, you're jealous."
Bro, no one's jealous of a fat,
povertyridden, 200 pound phone mong like
you. I don't know how many times someone
has to say this. No one is jealous of
you. No one's jealous of dodge legs. No
one's jealous of you hacker lives. Yeah.
No one is jealous of you freaks. No
one's jealous of someone showing a fake
win time and time again. They're fake
wins. No one's jealous. I've got more
money than you. I've said this to you
multiple times. I have got more money
than you. Why is it going in one ear and
out the other? I have got more money
than you. I don't know how many times I
have to explain this. And the only
reason I'm not I'm not pulling out money
is cuz every time you show these money,
it's these people money. It's the same thing.
You know what I'm saying, Cory? These
people are actual [ __ ] bro. I'm not
staying on long, by the way, bro.
Bro, it's these retards. They won't
[ __ ] stop being obsessed with me. I
know, bro. They're [ __ ] weirdos.
You know what I mean, bro? They're
[ __ ] going on about me. This [ __ ]
Joe F. Yeah, just fat, obsessed,
povertyridden loser will not shut up
about me. They're [ __ ] so jealous of
me, bro. It's a madness. They're obsessed. You know,
it's a madness, bro. It is an actual
[ __ ] madness. Leave me alone, you fat
loser. You know what I'm saying, bro? I
don't know how many times I've said
this. Leave me alone. I don't want
nothing to do with you, fat, ugly
losers. Stop trying to draw me back in,
bro. Stop trying to draw me back in. I
don't want nothing to do with you fat
ugly losers. So, stop posting [ __ ] about me.
I don't want anything to do with you,
Jo. Your [ __ ] boyfriend, Laura J, the
Mong, the skint one. I don't want
nothing to do with you, bro. Stop
posting [ __ ] about me
with your little fake wins. Your little
fake account with your little fake wins.
And I've got more money than you. So
again, bro, if you are going to say
something, Yeah. back it up. You need to
back up what you're saying. Yeah. And if
you're not going to do that, you're
talking [ __ ] Simple.
I'm younger than you. I'm better looking
than you. I've got more money than you.
Just because somebody is pointing out
your fake wins. Yeah. You putting money
in and taking out as if you won doesn't
mean that they're jealous. It's common
sense. This is common sense, Cory. There
was not people going around bookies and
winning all of that money. Oh, believe
you me. You don't, bro. You don't even
hear people winning nowadays. You
literally don't even hear people winning nowadays. You know,
brother, you're fat, ugly, and have got
more money than you. Why do you keep
telling people that they're jealous of a
fat lavy mog like yourself? Because I'm
telling you that you're putting up fake wins.
He He hasn't got more money than me. He
literally has not got more money than me.
I've got more money than he will ever
have. I don't I'm not upset. I'm
younger, better looking, and I've got
more money. That's the 20th time I have
explained this now. That I'm younger,
better looking, and I've got more money.
That is the millionth time I've
explained this now over and over and
over and over and over again.
Because, brother, you're never going to
meet anyone. You're never going to say
anything to anyone's face. So, listen.
Take over. Why are you not at work?
Listen, Joseph. Joseph, no one is
jealous of you, loser. Fat loss showing
fake wins. No one's jealous of you. No
one's jealous of your boyfriend, Na
legs. No one's jealous of your fat,
ugly, foreyed skinned friend, Lord J. No
one's jealous of you, life losers. I'm
younger and I'm better looking and I got
more money than you. No one's to be
jealous of a fat, ugly clown like you.
No one is jealous of a fat, ugly clown
putting up fake wins. No one's jealous
of that. No one. And I've already
explained to you why I didn't meet him.
I've already explained to you why I
didn't meet him. I know, bro. It's 2026
and you're still doing this
and you're still That's what I'm saying,
Cory. They're they really are jealous of
something in life. This is what I'm
saying, bro. It's 2026. Yeah. I'm trying
to get away from these people and this
Joseph Ferrar keeps putting up these
fake wins and he keeps mentioning me.
[ __ ] off, you fat ugly life loser living
under poverty. Stop mentioning me. For
[ __ ] sake. It's 2026. I don't want to
know you, your boyfriend. I don't want
to know. I don't want to know you, bro.
Leave me alone. You fatty that can't talk.
You fat ugly [ __ ] who can't talk. Living
under poverty. Keep my name out of your
[ __ ] mouth. Yeah. Poverty boy who
can't talk, showing fake wins. Leave me
the [ __ ] alone. I don't know how many
times you've got to explain, Joseph.
It's not my fault that I'm not living
under poverty like you, bro. No one's
jealous of you. I've got more money than
you. The millionth time I've explained
this. I'm younger than you and I'm
better looking than you. I've got more
money than you. More money than you. [ __ ] hell.
Jesus Christ. This is 2026. It is
madness, bro. Absolute madness.
[ __ ] madness. The amount of people
jealous of me. It's 2026, bro. Like,
what the [ __ ] Get alive.
Joseph Fro. You need to get a life, get
a job, get some money, stop showing fake
wins. You really, really need to stop.
You know, you really need to stop. You
[ __ ] loser. You nonslegs. Lj, [ __ ]
get alive. [ __ ] hell. It's 2026. You
[ __ ] life's loser. Losers.
You [ __ ] life's losers. Still on the
internet at 2026, bro. 2026. You life
loser. Look, I could understand last
year. Yeah, it was funny. Whatever. And
you're still doing this. You're still
being a life loser on that channel in
2026. Come on, bro. Yeah. Simple.
Yeah. You don't win. Yeah. I I know
people win, but you don't win. You put
up fake wins. Yeah, I know, bro. I know.
I know. I know. But the thing is, you
don't win. You put up fake wins. That's the difference.
You didn't get anyone's money stopped.
You keep telling yourself that. But
anyways, you didn't get anyone's money
stopped. I'm sat here with more money
than you. You didn't get a penny of my
money stopped. Not getting into that
again. You're still doing this in 2026.
This is how you know these people are
jealous, bro. 2026. Yeah. People are
supposed to be having like New Year's
resolutions. Like they're like New
Year's resolutions. And you're still
being jealous of someone you don't know
in 2026. Look at your life, bro.
Literally look at your life.
Yeah. You pe I I listen. No one needs to
win. You're losing every single day,
brother. You people are losers. You
don't even leave your house. Yeah. You
people are the life's losers that don't
even leave your house. You ain't even
got any friends. All of you people that
come from LJ, you are the biggest life's
losers ever. You got no mate, no
girlfriend, no money, no family.
Brother, you was on here Christmas. You
people was on YouTube Christmas. You are
literally the life's losers. You got not
a friend to your name. You don't even
have family, let alone money, bro. Like,
literally, we have seen you people on
Christmas. Yeah. And anyways, yeah,
that's that's a way to clear this up.
Oh, yeah. Joseph, you really want to
clear this up? Go live and gamble.
Yeah, go live and gamble. Yeah. Yeah,
that's that that's what we were saying
yesterday, wasn't we, Dusty? You go live
and you gamble and I take back
everything I've said. Yeah,
bro. This is 2026. Like, just just stop
it now. Yeah.
Yeah. Just go live and do it. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. That's that's a good point.
Paul, you're saying that I'm a life
loser, bro. You people don't even leave
your house. You ain't got no mates. Look
closer to home and you'll see yourself
in the house, bro. You people have
literally got no life outside of
YouTube. That's all I've got to say
about you people, bro. Anyways, listen, listen, listen.
But it doesn't trigger me. I just want
this [ __ ] to stop talking about me. I
want this fat lav waster, poverty mong,
to stop talking about me.
No, I'm not crying, players. I'm not
crying, bro. I'm all right, man. Yeah.
Yeah, no one cares about that repeating.
Nah, I'm not crying, bro.
Brother, it's because you don't Yeah,
please. It's 2026. Can you stop it now,
bro? It's 2026.
Bro, it's 2026. Can you give it a rest?
It's boring now. Um, I've only gone live
to address this. This is This is really,
really boring now. It's 2026. Just leave
it out, mate. Yeah. You say that you've
got all of these things. Stop acting
like a spasm. 2026 and make your life
sound a little bit more believable.
Yeah, it's 2026 now and you're still
repeating the same [ __ ] in 2026. And
listen, you can go live in the bookies,
Joe. I've done it multiple times. So,
until you actually go live gambling,
then come back to me. Yeah, simple. No,
listen, listen. You go live gambling and
then come back to me. Simple.
You dirty lavy poverty ridden fatty with
a 200lb phone.
200 pound phone living under poverty
showing fake wins. What a waster.
Nothing, bro. They're just doing the
same [ __ ] in 2026. They just keep trying
to draw me back in, bro. I'm done with
these clowns and they will not leave me alone.
This fat Joseph Fra poverty m will not
leave me alone, bro. You got to be
jealous or something. 2026 and you're
still doing this [ __ ] [ __ ] loser,
bro. Absolute loser,
brother. Your wins are not real.
Jealous of LJ. No one's jealous of a
farey with no money that begs on the
internet with no mates. No one's jealous
of any of you clowns.
You bitter spasticated clowns. No one's
jealous of any of you keyboard warriors.
Know what I mean, bro.
No one's jealous of any of you little
low lives. This is why I've come off of
it here. Cuz you're all low lives. You
ain't got a life to stand on. You ain't
got nothing. And you keep drawing me
back out. They're still doing this, bro.
I'm literally I'm literally trying to
come off this [ __ ] and this Jo keeps
talking about me, bro. He's obsessed
with me. He's like his boyfriend. Nons,
are you sure that, bro? Are you sure
that's not your boyfriend, bro?
Brother, are you sure that's not your boyfriend?
Joe, are you sure that's not your
boyfriend, bro? Cuz you two seem to have
the the biggest obsession with me, bro.
Listen. Oh, are you a Lavong? We don't
have lavry mongs on this channel. Sorry.
We don't have lavry mongs on this
channel. So, Joseph, are you sure that
ain't your boyfriend, bro? Cuz you
you're you two are like so obsessed with
me, bro. Bro, it's the same argument
because of this [ __ ] povertyridden
Joe F. He keeps mentioning me, bro. [ __ ]
off. You poverty ridden fat ugly man
that's scared to talk. You povertyridden
fat ugly waster that's scared of
talking. Leave me the [ __ ] alone. I
don't want nothing to do with you. And
the same arguments, the same repeating.
[ __ ] off, you poverty ridden 200 pound
phone man that's scared to talk what I'm
doing right now. [ __ ] off. Go back to
your boyfriend's channel. Yeah,
you [ __ ] waster. And go put some more
fake wins on your channel, bro. Bro, it
it it is giving. They keep going on
about me. I'm trying to get away from
these fat, jealous people, but they keep
going on about me, bro. They keep going
on about me. They will not leave me
alone. They're so jealous of me. It's unbelievable, bro.
It's not my fault that I'm younger,
better looking, and I've got more than
you. I've got more than you, bro.
Joseph Ro, you're the one that's in
denial. You're living under poverty and
you're talking, brother, I've got more
money than you. I've got more money than
you. I don't know why you keep ignoring
the fact when I'm saying this stuff to
you. I'm younger than you. I'm better
looking than you and I've got more money
than you and you're still talking your
[ __ ] Give it a break.
Yeah. See you later. Anyways.
Yeah. When are you going to stop this
[ __ ] bro? This is 2026 and you're still
doing this and you're still asking
people to show money, bro. We've been
through this before. This is really,
really boring. No, this is really,
really, really boring.
Joseph, this is really, really boring.
You need to get a life. Honestly, this
is 2026 now and you honestly need to get
a life cuz I am actually starting to
feel sorry for you. You really need to
get a life and sort your jealousy out.
I'm And I'm being serious. Like, I am
not even like, "Yeah, we've been through
this before. I'm going to keep repeating
myself. Brother, this is 2026. Give it a
rest. Give it a break.
You are. The more they do this. Yeah,
Cory. The more they're showing they're
jealous of you. The more they do this,
the longer they keep doing this, it
shows that they're jealous of you. It's
proven my point every time, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Last year was a mad year. We can
think, "Oh, yeah. Los brother. This is
2026. This is the second day of the new
year and they're still doing this, bro.
They're jealous. Do not let them tell
you otherwise. They are jealous of you.
All they've got is negativity and
they're trying to pull it on me every
day. Bro, it's a new year. I don't want
nothing to do with you mongos.
You sad, pathetic low lives. I don't
want nothing to do with you [ __ ] sad,
fat, ugly people that have to come on
YouTube every day for a reaction because
you've got no one. Relying on a reaction
from strangers because you've got
nobody. Yeah, that's your life. That's
not my life. You wasters.
Yeah. And you know who you are, bro.
Like, [ __ ] me. Give it a [ __ ] break.
Get a life. It's 2026. Get a life. Most
people most people Yeah. Like I said,
they they've already they've already
made their New Year's resolutions. These
people are doing the same thing.
They're doing the same thing, bro.
They're literally doing the same thing.
Brother, you're the one that's living
under poverty. You're the one that's
living under poverty. No one else. My
wardrobe is more worth more than your
whole life. I've got a better phone than
you. I've got everything better than
you. You're the only one living under
poverty. Stop fooling yourself. I have
literally got more money than you will
ever have. More garments, more assets,
more everything. So, at the end of the
day, you keep showing your fake pension,
loser. Keep putting £1,300 in a machine.
Act like you've won. You poverty mter
that's scared of talking. But do you
know what? this time. Put put £2600 in a
machine and act like you've won because
you don't win. Yeah. Someone is telling
you Yeah. about at the end of the day.
No, no, no. I'm telling you that you're
living under poverty. I'm saying under
on purpose because you're living under
poverty. Your cheap holidays. Look at
your holidays, bro. Your motor holidays,
your fake wins, brother. The only one
living under poverty is you right now.
The only one I can see living under
poverty is you. Cheap300 pound holidays,
200 pound phone, 30 pound jeans. I'm
started to think you're the one living
under poverty, bro. I'm not going to lie
to you cuz it doesn't look like I'm
living under poverty. It seems like you
are the one that's definitely living
under poverty, not me. 200 pound phone,
cheap multi holidays. I don't know, bro.
It seems like it's you. I can't lie to
you. I can't lie to you. It seems like
you are the one that's projecting your
poverty life onto me. I've got designer
clothes. I've got um Yeah, we know that,
bro. That's just him self-p projection.
Yeah, we know that, bro. That's just him
self-p projectioning. We know this.
Yeah, we know this, bro. This is This is boring now.
Yeah, look at him. Yeah. Yeah, we know
that, bro. That's just him projecting.
There's a lot of people like him on this community, bro. Yeah.
You are the only one living under
poverty. And I said under again. I don't
know why you keep telling people that's
got more money than you. They're living
under poverty when they I have literally
got more money than you. How many times
have I said that now? Has it has it processed?
Has it has it processed? What this Joe F
does? I tell you what his channel is,
right? You want to know what his channel
is? His channel is putting money in
machines and acting like he's one.
So, uh, when someone says
when someone states the obvious, he can
turn around and say, "Oh, you're
jealous. Oh, you're jealous. Oh, you're
jealous." When no, no one's jealous of
you. I'm younger than you. Got more
money than you. Better looking than you.
Been with more money than you. Got more
than you. Got family unlike you. Got
friends unlike you. Live in a better
city than you. Everything about me is
better than you. Yeah. People stating
the obvious does not mean anyone's
brother. I can put it right. Listen.
Listen. I can prove it again. Listen,
listen. Do you want me to put Do you
want me to put a link up and give you
the the chance to show your face or
you're going to run away again? I mean,
I can put the link up if you want,
right? And it will show how fat and ugly
you are for one. Yeah, that's the first
thing we'll get out of the way that
you're fat and ugly, brother. No, no
one's reacting like it. It's because you
keep mentioning my name. Everyone knows
that you show fake wins. I'm not going
on about it. I'm not going on about it,
Fatty. I'm not going on about it, fatty
poverty. I'm not going on about it. I'm
not even going on about it. I know that
you show fake wins. I know that you show
fake wins. That doesn't bother me. I've
got more money than you. It would never bother me.
Yeah, that is true. To be honest. Yeah.
It's it's it's a madness, bro. Like, why
do you want me to see Oh, I mean, you
judge me. I mean, Joseph Rod, don't you
judge men's looks. Don't you judge men's
So, someone that's younger than you,
better looking than you, that's got more
money than you, is better looking than
you. Make it make sense, bro. To be
honest with you, you're probably
disabled. You probably can't even leave
your house. And I'm jealous of you. And
I'm jealous of you, bro. What the [ __ ]
And I'm jealous of you.
someone that's older, uglier, and got
less money than me. Make it make sense.
When you're going to say stuff, bro, you
need to make it make sense.
Yeah, bro. Cuz you're obsessed with me.
I'm not talking about these [ __ ] I'm
not talking about these fake wins. I'm
talking about you keep going on about
me. You're just another nonslegs, bro.
You're just another non-legs.
You Lord J and Nlegs, you're jealous of
something in life. You need to figure
out what it is, bro. This is 2026. Leave
it out, mate. It's 2026.
It's 2026, fatty. It's not my fault I'm
younger and better looking than you, bro.
Like, it's not my fault I'm younger and
better looking than you, bro. Give it a
rest. It's 2026. Leave it out, mate. Go
back to LJ's channel. Go suck his dick
some more, the foureyed skint [ __ ]
begging for donations. We don't want you
on this channel. Why do you keep coming
back on this channel if you're not going
to join? and talk like a man. You little
funny. Yeah. Then just go away. No, they
don't trigger me. They don't trigger me
at all. It's boring, bro. That's what it
is. It's very, very boring. These people
are very, very boring. This is 2026 now.
We get it, Joe. I'm better looking than
you. I've got more money than you,
brother. You didn't even go to that pub
yourself. Listen, Joe. Joe, you didn't
even go to that pub. Have you got a
video of you in that pub? Have you got a
video of you in that pub, Fatty? Before
you trying to say that people bottled
it, listen. Listen, Fatty, let's see you
in that pub. Let's see you in that pub.
Fatty, let's see you in that pub. You're
in that pub that you told me to go to.
Let's see you in that pub. Have you got
a video of you in that pub? Have you got
a live stream of you in that pub? No.
So, shut the [ __ ] up then. You didn't go
anywhere yourself, you [ __ ] stupid
[ __ ] You [ __ ] stupid fat [ __ ] You
didn't even go anywhere yourself. You
don't You You don't even live near that
location. You didn't go there yourself.
You little fat [ __ ] You [ __ ]
bastard. That bastard that's scared to
talk. You bastard that's scared to
bastard talk. You didn't even go there
yourself. You literally did not even go
there yourself. Yeah.
You literally did not even go there
yourself. You bastard that's scared to
talk. So don't tell people how they're
bottling it when you weren't even there yourself.
You wasn't even there yourself. You
bastard [ __ ] who's scared of talking. Yeah.
But we didn't see you in that [ __ ] It
is the same old [ __ ] Triple. This is
why I'm trying to get away from it. But
these people Yeah. I'm just literally
going to stop going on their channel.
I'm literally just going to stop going
on their channel, bro. 100%.
100%, bro. What the [ __ ] man?
It's a madness, bro. It's a madness.
Give it a break.
Give it a [ __ ] break, you bastard. You
Jo, you're a bastard that's scared to
talk. I love how someone that's scared
to talk gives it the big on the
internet. Someone that's scared of talking. [laughter]
That is comedy right there. You're so
disabled you can't even talk. And you
come online giving it the big. Oh,
you're so lonely. You're so [ __ ]
lonely. It's [ __ ] sad, bro. It
really, really is.
You You're doing this again for another
year. Wow. Wow. Another year of this
[ __ ] And you say that you've got a life.
And you say that you've got a life, bro.
Yeah. This is why I'm I'm off of it. Um
Triple H, I've just come on here to
quickly address this little low life. Yeah.
It's a madness.
Same thing with Red Star. You didn't
stop any of my sublet buddy and I get
money and I've got more money than you.
You didn't stop any of my sublet money.
I've already proven how how the house
got took. You sad sad bastards in 2026,
right? For these people to be doing this
in 2026, bro, they are just jealous of
something. I'm telling you, bro, for
these people to sit on the internet
every day being jealous of people that
they don't know, bro, their life [ __ ]
I'm telling you 100%. So, anyways, the link's there.
The link's there.
Brother, I've got You don't know how
much money I've got. I've got more money
than you. That's all you need to know.
And brother, you didn't get any of my
money stopped. [laughter]
I had the house for 4 years and you
didn't stop any of my money. Joseph,
it's more money than you. It's more
money than you will ever have to Okay,
listen, Joseph. Right. You join the
hangout and you talk and I will come and
I will meet you today. What's the day
today? It's Friday. I'm willing to do
this. I'm willing to actually do this.
Yeah. You come and hang out and you talk
and I will travel to you today. Yeah.
Come on, big man. And I'm actually
serious this time. Come on, big man. Cuz
you weren't even you was not even in the
pub yourself. Yeah. 100%. Come on. Let's
Let's just end this. Yeah. Let's just
end this right here, right now. Come on.
You bastard that's scared of talking. I
will I will meet you today. I will meet
you today cuz this is not going to be
another year of this [ __ ] This is not
going to be another year of this [ __ ]
Come on. You bastard that's scared of
talking. You fat bastard. Fat ass
bastard motor holiday. Come on. Come on
[ __ ] Come on. Come on. And I will I
will meet you today. I will [ __ ] meet
you today cuz I've had enough of this
[ __ ] fat ugly povertyridden [ __ ] nons
legs loving little lowife bastard keep
[ __ ] coming on coming coming on here
mentioning my [ __ ] name.
Come on you [ __ ] poverty bastard.
Let's have it out today. Come on. The
link's there and I will meet you today.
I will [ __ ] meet you today. I will
listen. Listen. Stop saying that people
won't go anywhere, mate. You didn't go
anywhere. You didn't go anywhere.
Listen, your word, you can't even say a
word. You can't even talk. Listen,
listen, listen. [ __ ] the words. You
don't have a word. You're scared of
talking. Listen. The link's there, bro.
If you want to arrange a meet today,
join the hangouts. I will meet you. I I
will meet you anywhere. You didn't show
up last time, you bastard. You didn't
even show up. Yeah, you didn't show up,
you fat [ __ ]
Stop talking about words when you're
scared of talking. You're a scared to
talk bastard. That's what That's what
your new name's going to be. You're just
a bastard who's scared of talking.
You're just a lavy mong. A non-legs
loving mong. A poverty [ __ ] who's scared
of talking. That's what you are. Listen,
join the hangouts and let's meet today.
Come on. What are you waiting for? I
will meet you today. I don't mind. I
don't mind. Come on, you [ __ ] bastard
who's scared of talking. If you're if
you're saying people's word don't mean
nothing. Let's hear a word. Let's hear
your words. You're scared to talk. Yeah.
Let's hear your words. The word you
can't word it cuz you're scared of
talking. You povertyridden bastard
throwing fake wins. Come on. Let's go.
Are you joining or not? Are you joining
or not? You bastard. Come on. Are you
joining or not? Exactly. That's what I
thought. So shut the [ __ ] up, you scared
little bastard that keeps running away.
Exactly. So, shut the [ __ ] up. Shut the
[ __ ] up. You didn't even go anywhere
last time yourself, you [ __ ] You
didn't even go anywhere last time
yourself. Shut the [ __ ] up, mate. So,
let's call it a Let's call it a draw cuz
you didn't show up and even did I show
up. I will show up today. It's Friday
today. I don't mind traveling. Come on.
Let's go. Come on, you [ __ ] bastard
who's scared of talking. You bastard.
You You little lathery mong. You little
dick sucking bias [ __ ] Come on. What
are you waiting for? Come on, you're
such a big man. Oh, people won't do
this. People won't do that. You didn't
even show up yourself, mate. If you
actually showed up yourself, then you'd
actually be able to say that, "Oh, yeah,
you didn't show up. You didn't show up
yourself, you bastard." So, how are you
trying to [ __ ] How are you trying to
claim a a win when you didn't even show up yourself?
So, are you coming or not? Are you
coming or not? Listen, are you going to
join or not? Cuz I don't mind coming
today and booking a hotel.
Oh, so you're just another bastard that
will do nothing again. So you're just
another cowardly little bastard that's
run away again. Just another law. That's
what you are. A [ __ ] nosebleleed over
some fat [ __ ] like you that's scared to
talk. Some fat [ __ ] like you who's
scared to talk and scared to meet me.
Get out of here, you little [ __ ] Mate,
it doesn't matter what people lied
about, what people didn't lie about. You
was not there yourself. You was not in
that pub yourself because you're a
scaredy-cat bastard who's scared to talk
and you're not going to do nothing about
it. I can say all of this stuff to you.
You're not going to meet me. You're not
going to join the hangouts. You're not
going to talk because you're a bastard
that will never do nothing.
You are a bastard
that will never do nothing. And I'm
willing to meet you today. Simple.
Yeah. So, if you don't want the beef,
you fat ugly [ __ ] You'll do nothing.
Projection. Let's go over everything
that you go that [clears throat] you say
about me. You'll do nothing. You're
scared to talk. You're scared to meet
anyone. Poverty. You're the one that's
got no money. You're the one showing
fake wins. You're the one with a 200lb
phone. Everything is about you, bro.
Bro, I ain't got autism like you. I can
talk unlike you. I don't need autistic
pills, bro. I'm not the one that's
scared to talk like you cuz of your
autism. Your autism don't even let you
talk. Your autism don't even let you
come on the hangouts and talk, you
autistic [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah, that's
what you are.
You're an autistic bastard that's scared
of talking. You're so disabled you can't
even talk. How is anyone supposed to
take you serious?
[ __ ] me, bro.
Shouldn't you be busy sucking Laur's
dick, you sad bastard. Shouldn't you be
busy sucking your boyfriend's dick, you
sad bastard who's scared of talking. Or
is that another Joe? Maybe it's another
one to be fair. You know,
you got to pity people like this, bro.
You really do. So, I'll put the link out
again. Brother, you people can you
people don't even have a friend to your
name. You don't laugh at no one. You
people on here are losers. Listen,
listen, listen, bro. Listen, listen. You
and the L J crew are losers with nothing
in life. You are the laughing stocks of
society. You don't laugh at no one else.
You people are life's losers. You laugh
at yourselves. You're on YouTube from
the time you wake up to the time you go
to bed. You are the laughing stock
losers. No one else. No one else, bro.
You are the people that are the biggest
losers ever. You'll go on a law J
channel and you literally go on the
hangouts, bro. And it's the same people
with no friends. People like that don't
laugh at me, bro. Joe, people like you
that's scared of talking, living under
poverty, don't laugh at a guy like me.
You people with no friends, no money, no
life, can't laugh at a guy like me. It's
almost illegal cuz you're living your
laughable worst lives. So you can't
laugh at a guy like me. You laugh at
yourselves when you wake up. No friends,
no money, no girlfriend, not no family.
But you don't laugh at a guy like me.
You definitely definitely a bunch of
losers can't laugh at a guy like me.
Definitely definitely definitely not.
You autistic boring losers don't laugh
at a guy like me. Trust me, you really,
really don't. You laugh at your ugly fat
selves. I mean, Joe, I've got you scared
of talking. You can't even come and talk.
You can't even come on a hangout and
talk. What are you laughing at, bro?
Your disabled self. You literally can't
even come on a hangout and talk. You're
that autistic. Who are you laughing at,
bro? Yourself. No one else. You're not
laughing at a younger, better-l looking
guy with more money than you. You're not
laughing at someone like that.
Uh, and that's it, bro.
Bro, like I repeat myself again, bro.
You people are sat on YouTube every day
from the time you wake up to the time
you go to bed. Look at you people.
Before judging other people, look at
your look at your loser selves. You
don't Do you know what? It's not even
about being jealous yet. You know what?
No, listen, bro. It's not even about
being jealous. It's not even about that.
You people have got no life outside of
YouTube. Let that sink in. Like
literally no life outside of YouTube.
You have not got no life outside of
YouTube. Imagine that, bro.
Yeah. And that's it. And anyways, the
link's out there, so if you want to
join, you can join. And that's all I'm
saying. I'm coming off in a bit. Anyways, yeah.
If you're not going to come and arrange
to meet me today, then that's it. You're done. Simple.
Yeah, that's it.
Yeah, bro. Listen, Joe, you don't
Listen, Joe, you're probably a virgin,
bro. You're probably a virgin. You've
never been with a woman, Bro. You're
probably a virgin.
Nah, these people don't bully me off.
They bully themselves.
These people bully themselves. They bore
people off. That's what they do. They
bore people off. Listen, Joseph, listen.
Let me tell you something, bro. How How
can a 28-year-old have had more life
experiences than you, bro? Can you
answer that? How is a 28-year-old
younger than you, better looking than
you, and got more money than you?
Explain that one, bro. How is a
28-year-old got more life experience than you?
Can you explain that one? I'd love to
know that one. You know that. I would
love to know that one.
Yeah, if he's not going to join. Yeah,
that's it. Yeah, 100%. I'll put the link
up one more time. I'm going to give him
five minutes. If he won't join, I'm blocking him.
Yeah, it is pointless arguing, bro. This
is 2026. This literally is 2026. So,
yeah, if you don't join and agree to
meet, then that's it. You You are blocked. Yeah,
you are blocked.
How you not got a girlfriend, bro? You
don't have a girlfriend yourself. Stop self projecting.
You ain't got a girlfriend yourself.
Stop self projecting.
Anyways, bro, the link is there, so
we'll wait for him. He's not blocked. I
I don't mind traveling today, bro. It's Friday.
Nah, he bullies himself. And you can go
away. Fantasy stories. You're borrowing
now. See, these people are so
predictable. You actually know who they
are. Like, he's I just told you that
he's fantasy stories, bro. Listen, the
only people that get bullied is
yourselves. Oh, Joe. So, you're not So,
you're not going to talk and not meet.
So what you're basically saying is
you're going to do nothing.
So what you're saying is that you will
do nothing. So that's what you're
admitting. I don't mind traveling today.
I've I literally don't mind booking a
hotel and traveling. I don't mind. It's
Friday today. Yeah. I'm I want to show
you what I'll do. I will literally show
you today what I'll do. And if you're
not going to talk, then you're the one
that will do nothing. So stop talking
about yourself. Stop talking about
yourself, you waster who's scared of
talking. That will do nothing. I'm
trying to arrange to meet you and you
keep running away.
You keep telling people they'll do
nothing and then when people want to do
something, you keep running away.
Make it make sense.
I am deadly serious, bro. I'm deadly,
deadly, deadly serious. PJ is skin. Oh,
no one cares about that. That's self-
projecting repeating, bro. Like I said,
this is 2026. No one cares about
self-projecting comments. I am serious.
I'm deadly serious. I am deadly deadly
So, you're not going to meet me. So,
what you're saying is you'll do nothing
then. So, so you'll do nothing. Is that
what you're saying? The link's there.
Oh, 100% I want it. I 100% want it.
You know, I 100% want it. You join and
let's arrange it. Come on. You join and
arrange it. Come on. I do really want it. Yeah.
But you're just going to be like your
boyfriend nonslegs, a runaway man. You
go to his area three times and he's a
runaway man just like you, Joseph.
You're just like your boyfriend. Why?
Steven Howard, isn't Joe F just like his boyfriend?
Listen. No, no, no, no, no, no. You join
and you talk and you'll arrange it
properly. Yeah, you'll arrange it
Come on. Come on. No, no. Join and talk.
PJ got money. Stop. You didn't get
anyone's money stopped. But if that
helps you sleep at night. Yep. You keep
telling yourself that, bro. Well, listen
to this, bro. Right. You are the one
that's on YouTube 24/7 stalking people.
So, you're the one that must have no
money cuz you're the one that's on
YouTube and it's 2026
and you're still on here. You're still
on here, right?
Uh, Triple H, mate, I went to Newcastle
three times and you didn't come out
once. Please, let's not talk about that
life, bro. I went to Newcastle three
times and you didn't and you didn't show
up. Don't get don't get yourself
involved, bro. Do not get yourself
involved. Anyways, you come on Hangouts
and you talk and you arrange this by
talking else I'm not meeting you.
Simple. I put the link up. I said if you
come and you arrange it, I will make my
way. Other than that, I won't.
But yeah, listen, listen, listen,
listen, listen. Triple, triple, triple,
bro. I went to Newcastle three times.
You didn't come out once. Stop it, bro.
Like, you you really need to stop it.
Yeah. You confirm it by voice and I'll
travel to you and I will leave literally
right now. Not some [ __ ] [ __ ] that's
scared of talking. No, no, no, no, no.
You join and you tell me you're going to
meet me, right? And I and I will start
making tracks. Yeah. Simple.
And this is why I don't waste my time on
these people, Dusty. This is exactly why
I don't like this is why, bro. This is
exactly why I don't waste my when you
argue, bro, with biased autistic people.
This is what happens. Yeah. You become
like one of them. Listen. Listen, Joe.
Join the hangouts and talk and I will
meet you. Simple.
And then you got Triple H. Someone
that's not showed up and you've gone
free. This is what I mean. It's the same
[ __ ] with you people, you know? It's the
same [ __ ] with you boring repeated
people every year. You disabled people
low life on the internet. This is why I
don't want nothing to do with this [ __ ]
bro. You know, I don't want nothing to
do with these fat lowife rejected
weasels. This is why I come off of this [ __ ] bro.
Okay. Trip rates. Okay, whatever. Why
didn't you come out when I went to
Newcastle three times? Okay, whatever.
Cool. So, when I went to Newcastle three
times, why didn't you come out?
Yeah. Yeah. If I'm not about it, why
didn't you come out? And that was before Prime.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Yeah. I'm not about
it. Whatever. So, why didn't you come
out when I went to Newcastle three times
before the Prime incident?
I went to your city three times and you
did not come out. So, can you explain to
everyone why you didn't come out? We're
waiting, bro. We're waiting.
No, my life is not exactly the same.
Your lives are the same. Your lives are
the same. You're coming on here repeating yourselves
every day. Little low lives, even in a
new year. No. No. You people are the
same. You will not leave people alone.
This is why I'm on here. Yeah. Saying
this about you low lives. You sad lonely
losers. My life ain't the same. I'm
trying to get off here, but you keep you
people keep mentioning my [ __ ] name, you know.
No, it really isn't. It really isn't.
Listen, between you people are the ones
that are sat on YouTube year in year out
with no friends. Take a year take a
closer look to home, bro. Trust me, your
lives are YouTube. You have got no life
outside of YouTube. We have proven this
multiple multiple times when we have
gone on large. You people sit on YouTube
from the time you wake up to the time
you go to bed. You sad bastards.
You're on YouTube from the time you wake
up to the time you go to bed. You sad
bastards. Stop talking about yourself.
You are on YouTube from the time you
wake up to the time you go to bed. You
sad bastards. Do not try and talk about
me, bro. Show the trade. Listen, Triple
H. Why didn't you show up when I went to
Newcastle three times? I'm asking a
question. When I went to Newcastle three
times and why didn't you come out?
Why did you not come out? I'm asking you
a simple question. Tell everybody why
you didn't come out.
Yeah, okay, bro. I'm scared. Whatever.
No one cares about that self projection
[ __ ] Anyways, why did you not come out
when I went to Newcastle three times? Tell everybody.
Tell everybody why you did not come out.
Uh, Joseph. Joseph. Now, do you remember
when I spoke about uh people being
biased? Yeah. Like yourself. Yeah. And I
was trying to make you understand what
the word means. Uh, I went to Newcastle
three times and Triple H didn't come out
once. I'm not starting on Triple H,
right? I'm not starting on Triple H. I'm
stating the fact that I literally went
three times and he didn't come out. I'm
not starting on him. I'm start I'm
stating facts. Yeah. Listen, like I
said, Joe, if you want to meet me, join
and talk. Yeah. Simple.
Yeah. You said that skin thing about 10
times now. It's pretty boring. Can you
think of new things to say?
I'm just stating facts, bro. Like, um, yeah.
Yeah, I'm not going to train fair.
Triple H. You're not going to trigger
me, bro. Stop it. You're really really
not going to trigger me. Like, it's
boring, bro. That's not going to trigger
anyone. Listen, join the join the hangout
and um yeah, just just let's let's agree
to meet. Come on.
You know, simple.
Okay. You want to meet at that pub? Okay
then. Okay. Let's meet at that pub.
Okay. We'll meet in that pub then. Yeah.
Okay. Okay. We'll meet in that pub.
Yeah. Okay. Right. I'm going to leave in
about an R. What's the time? What time
do you want to meet again,
bro? You said skin about a million times now.
Yeah. You've said that about a million times. now.
Right. So, okay. Okay. So, we'll see if
you go to that pub then. Yeah. I'm going
to leave in an hour. I'm going to leave
in an hour. Right. And we we're going to
see if you're in that pub. We're going
to see if you're in that pub. Yeah.
We're going to see if you're in that
pub. So, you want to meet at 600? Okay.
So, let's We will see if you're in that
pub then. Yeah. We will see if you're in
that pub. Okay. Yeah. Fine. Fine. Fine.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. We will see if you're
in that pub. Let's call this cunt's
bluff. Yeah. Let's see if he's in Let's
see if he's in that uh Let's see if he's
in that pub. Right. Do you know what
he's trying to do? Steven Albert, do you
know what? Do you know what this guy's
trying to do? Yeah. I Bro, they're so
predictable. Like, it's it's it's it's a
joke. Do you know what he's trying to
do? I tell you exactly what he's trying
to do, bro. I know these low IQ these
low IQ people. You don't know what he's
trying to do. I can tell you exactly
what he's going to do, bro.
So, we'll see if he we'll see if he
turns up to this pub. Yeah, we'll see if
he turns up to this pub. He wants me to
go all the way there, right? He wants me
to go all the way there so he can say,
"Oh, I made you go there. I control
you." I know exactly what he's trying to
do, bro. So, we'll see if he goes to
this pub. We will see if this guy goes
to this pub, right? We will see if he
goes to this pub. Cuz what he's going to
do is he's going to say, "Oh, I've made
you go there. I control you. I [ __ ] with
your head." I know exactly what he's
going to do. So, we will see if you are
in that pub at 6:00. Yeah, we will see
if you are in that in that um pub at
6:00. I know you better than you know
yourself. It's so predictable. It's so
predictable. And if I'm wrong, bro, if
I'm wrong, we will see him in that pub
at 6 p.m. Yeah, we will see if this fat
looney is in this pub at 6 p.m. End the
story. Yeah, we'll see it. Yeah. Okay,
we'll see then.
Yeah, I've got no money. Yeah. Okay,
bro. Whatever. Anyways, um so we'll see
if he's actually in this pub. Um 6 p.m.
then that's it,
you know. No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. We'll see if he's in this
pub. Cuz if he's not at this pub, bro,
if he's not at this pub, he can't say
anything. He can't say anything about
anyone. If he is not at this pub, he
can't say nothing. He cannot say
nothing. I'm going to show you train
tickets, bro. I don't need to show you
train tickets, you fat [ __ ] So you can
try and call the police. Come on, bro.
Come on. Come on. Yeah. I don't need to
show train train tickets, right? How are
you getting there? I don't need to show
you train tickets, bro. So, you can get
the police involved, brother. I'm not
low IQ like you. I don't need to show
you anything. Yeah. Just be at the pub
at 6 p.m. Easy win for you then, isn't
it? It's an easy win for you. If you're
in If you're in that pub at 6 p.m. Yeah.
Then, uh Well, yeah. You get a win.
Oh, he's another Lavry Mong. Steven
Howard. He's a Lavry Mong. He is
literally a Lavry Mong.
He is a Lavry Mong, bro.
He's a [ __ ] Lavry Mong.
This Jo is a Lavry Mong, bro. So, if
you're at that pub at 6:00, then we'll see.
You know, I'm not show I don't need to
show you any [ __ ] train tickets. I
don't need to show you any train tickets.
I don't need to show you nothing. I
Uh, so anyways, we'll see. Eh,
yeah, he's also a nonslegs bubicker as
well. He's Nlex's boyfriend.
Yeah, he's also Nlegs's boyfriend as
well, Steven Howard. So, be careful what
you say about nonslegs. Um,
you know, Steven Howard because you
don't want to upset his boyfriend.
You'll [ __ ] have another meltdown.
The fat [ __ ] [ __ ] who's scared to
talk. We'll have another [ __ ]
meltdown. Well, we'll see. Yeah.
Yeah. I've got nothing. Yeah, it's 2026.
I was famous. It's 2026. Yeah.
No, we'll see if Joe's there. We'll see
if Joe's there. And Joe, if you don't go
there, you you haven't won. Right. If
you do not go to that pub, you have not
won. So don't come back with saying,
"Oh, you bottled it." When you're in
that pub, you can claim a victory. Yeah.
You can claim a victory. Exactly. You
can claim a victory, you know.
Then that's it. So yeah. Yeah, man.
I don't need to prove anything to you.
Okay. You want me to show you? Okay. You
come and talk. Okay. So, you want me to
show you? You want me to show you
tickets? You want me to show you
tickets? Right. Why do I need to prove
tickets when you're scared to talk? When
you if you can't come in a panel and
talk, why have I got to show you
tickets? I can show you tickets and not
go. I can show you tickets and just not
So, I mean, what does that mean? You
come on a panel and you talk and then
I'll show you tickets. That's that I
think that's a fair deal. You're asking
me to prove myself to you again. Again,
this is you are asking me to prove
myself to you yet again when I don't
need to prove myself to some fat [ __ ]
who's scared to talk. But anyways, if
you really want to see book tickets,
okay, you talk and I'll book him now and
I'll show you it. Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
No one has to prove themselves to you
fat, ugly people. I don't know how many
times you have to, you know, before you
get that in your [ __ ] thick skull.
People don't need to prove themselves to
you fat wasters.
Don't know how many times. And yeah, you
said that you're you're you're 20
minutes away. So go to that pub then. Go
to that pub.
First fight. Nope.
So, yeah. When you show me you in that
pub, bro, come back to me. Yeah.
Cuz what stops Okay, Greasy, let me ask
you this question. What stops me
going all the way there and him saying,
"I made you go all that way. I made you
go all that way." Just like Bomb did.
just like a couple of other people done.
What stops that from happening? You tell
me right now what stops that happening.
He's not meeting anyone for crying out
loud. He'll never meet no one. He's just
like his boyfriend Nles legs.
He's just like his boyfriend Nlegs. He's
not meeting no one. Jesus Christ. Stop
it. [ __ ] me.
This is bad, bro. Really, really bad.
You are skin. You've said that about 30 times now.
Yeah, you've said that about 30 times
now, mate. Yeah, it's getting boring now.
So, the only way I could actually win is
if I was going there anyways.
You know, when I went to Bomb, it wasn't
like a huge loss because obviously I got
laid. I got sex when I went. So,
actually bomb actually got me laid, but
he's trying to make me go all the way
there so he can say, "Oh, uh, yeah, I
made you go there. I made you go there.
I made you go there. I win."
Yep. You are skin.
Yeah. You've said that about 31 times now. It's 2026.
I've turned up to loads and loads of
people before. Listen. Right. Steven
Hour, do you want me Yeah. to name you
every single person I've met and they've
shut their pants. Should we go down
memory lane? Greavvesy Steven. Should we
go down memory lane? Every single person
I've tried meeting that has not shown up
and no one said anything about it. I'll
do it. I'll do it again if you if you
want. Right. A wise man learns from his
mistakes with mongos. That's what I'd
say. You know,
mate, I have turned up multiple multiple
times to you to meet you [ __ ] bongs
and you talk the same [ __ ] and you will
forget about it. Well, pretend to forget
about it. So, yeah. Yeah. Greasy,
how many people have I tried meeting on
this community since I'm biased? Huh?
How many times?
I have never turned up for an agreement.
An agreement fight. Oh, really?
Right. We're done with this anyways,
bro. This is boring now.
This is really, really boring. Anyways,
just stop going on this Joe F channel,
bro. He's just another [ __ ] Lavry
Mong. I'm going to stop going on that
channel, bro. Um, I'm not even
subscribed to him. So, we're just going
to wash our hands with these clowns,
with these sad bastards now. Anyways, yeah, bro.
It's 2026 and they're still doing this.
They got nothing in life, bro. They
prove our [ __ ] point.
Yeah, we're going to get rid of these
people now anyways, bro. A few.
Yeah, a few. There's been a lot more
than a few, bro. There's been a lot more
than a few. There's been a lot more. I
went to Liverpool. Kevin Murphy didn't
show up, yet he still comes on here and
talks like nothing's happened. I went to
Newcastle three times. Triple H didn't
show up, but he still comes on here
talking [ __ ] So even if you even if you
went today, right, even
even if you went today, right, to try to
meet that Joseph Ferrar, they're just
going to stop when you come back.
They're never going to stop. They're
never going to stop. Even if you showed
up, they're never ever ever going to
shop. Stop. Sorry,
Triple H. I'll repeat myself again. I
went to Newcastle three times and you
didn't show up. Yeah. Three times I went
to your [ __ ] city and you didn't show
up. Another W for Joe. And this is why
we do not waste our time with you biased
people. You're proving it now. This is
why we do not waste our time on you
biased, jealous people. That's exact.
Why do you think I didn't show up the
other day, Steven? Because I knew
exactly what was going to happen. He's
not going to show up and they're all
going to forget about it. It happens
every time with these autistic people.
That's why we don't waste our time on
them. You know, I've gone to Newcastle
three times. Triple H Saint showed up
and he's still talking like the big man.
And this is what I'm saying. This is
this is exactly what I'm saying, bro.
Bro, meet me, brother. I've gone all
over the country and none of you clowns
have met me. Yeah. You people will never
meet no one. You literally you people
will never meet no one. Yeah. I don't
need to show train tickets. That's what
Lavarie Bong says. I don't need to prove
myself. I don't need to prove myself.
I am not showing nothing. I am not
proving myself to these fat ugly people.
Nuh-uh. I am I refuse to prove myself to
these people. When this [ __ ] can prove
he can talk, then come back to me. Yeah.
When you when you when you prove you're
not scared of talking, then come back to
me. Yeah. Simple.
Yeah. Exactly. I turn up with no
arrangement. Okay, bro. You keep telling
yourself that. You keep telling yourself
that. Yeah, you keep telling yourself
that, bro. Yeah, you keep telling
yourself that. I mean, I can name you. I
can name you some people that I did go
to that we knew that was in, but they
never done nothing. I mean, I can name
you I can name you some people if you
want. You know,
I put up post when I was when I'm on the
train home. Really?
So when I went to Mark Samson's area two
times when I was live for 3 hours, I
done that when I went home. So when I
was live in Manchester, I tried to meet
Bomb when on my way home. Really?
Really, bro? Okay. You keep telling
yourself that. Yeah, you keep telling
yourself that, bro. When I went to Nle's
area three times and he went running to
the police. Okay, bro. You keep telling yourself that.
If that makes you feel better, bro. You
keep telling yourself that. Yeah. Right.
Right. We'll see if you're in that pub. Anyways, Joe,
we will see if you're in that pub. If
this guy is a man of his word, it
doesn't matter if he called me out or
not. He was acting the big [ __ ] on the
internet. I don't give a [ __ ] if he
called me out or not. I don't give a
[ __ ] He was acting the big man on the
internet and I was live in his area. I
don't give a [ __ ] if he called me out. I
called him out in his area. He was out
to the big man on the internet and I
called him out in his area and that's
good enough for me. Again, you're all
biased. And anyways, Joe, listen. I will
see you when you're in that pub. Yeah. I
will see you when you prove that you're
in that pub. Yeah. Simple as that. We
will see if this big man goes to that
pub. Yeah. And that's that. Simple.
Triple H again. I have gone to your area
three times and you have not turned up
again. Triple H. Brother, brother,
listen. Listen, Trip H. Listen. The
first time I went to your area, I called
you out. Oh, I'm in the hospital. I'm in
the hospital, bro. You have shat your
pants three times when people have tried
to meet you. You have shat your pants
three times when I've tried to meet you.
Stop acting like the big man. You're not
about it. Yeah, I traveled 300 miles to
come and see you three times and you
[ __ ] your pants. Stop typing on the
internet. That's a good boy. Even LT
knows the score, bro. Stop it now. It's
embarrassing. Yeah, it's really, really,
really, really embarrassing. Stop it
now. Really, really, really stop it. Stop it. You know,
and that's it.
Yeah, basically greasy. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I do. Yeah. Yeah. That's the only
way I know that this [ __ ] is serious
about meeting me. Yeah. It sounds
ridiculous, but Yeah. That's the only way.
I know it sounds ridiculous, but that's
the only way.
Otherwise, the same thing's going to
happen like when I've, you know, met
Bomb and tried to meet Bomb and that. Yeah,
pretty much. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro. No
one cares about that unannounced [ __ ]
bro. Stop talking [ __ ] You people
was in. You don't even leave your house.
Shut the [ __ ] up, bro. Every time
Listen, I have gone live in people's
areas multiple times. Stop the excuses.
They're boring now. It's 2026,
brother. It's 2026. Yeah.
Simple, bro. Joe's not going himself.
He's not going himself. Joe's not going
nowhere, bro. He don't even leave the
house. Brother, brother, brother,
brother, brother. The guy don't even
leave his house. He's not going anywhere either.
So, yeah. God, this community is so [ __ ] disabled.
Yeah. Okay, I'm still not about it.
Okay, bro. Anyways, we're going to be
banning these people now. Anyways,
brother, I've gone live in your areas
and you haven't shown up. Stop it. It's 2026 now.
Yeah. Well, you show me when you're in
that pub. You show me when you're in
that pub, big man, and then you can take
and then you can take your victory. It's
an easy win for you then, isn't it? It's
an easy win for you. If you're actually
20 minutes away from that pub, then you
can show you in that pub and then that's
an easy victory, isn't it?
That's an easy victory. Huh? There you
go. That's an easy victory.
Yeah, I'm petrified. Okay, bro. Yeah,
you keep you keep telling yourself that.
I'm not the guy that knows where people
live but won't do anything. I'm not like
you people. I don't have people's
addresses but then choose to just talk
[ __ ] on the internet. You know,
brother, he didn't get the W because if
I go there, he's not going to meet me.
Brother, brother, if I go there, he's
literally going to say, "Oh, I made you
go there, brother. You didn't win. We
know your game. It's boring." Joseph,
your game is very predictable and it's very boring.
Yeah, that's repeating and self-
projecting. That can get banned.
Yeah, I know your game, Joseph. I'm too
intelligent for you, poverty man. I'm
too intelligent. I know what I know what
you're trying to do. Oh, I made you
travel that way. You're a lavy bonged. I
know what I know what your plan is. You
lo a dick sucker. I'd even put money on
it right now. What you're going to do,
you lo a dick sucker. You want me to go
all that way so you can say, "Look, I
control him. I control his life." It
ain't going to happen, mate. I know you
better than you know yourself. I know
you better than you know yourself will
ever know yourself, mate.
Brother, you need to stop trying to look
good for women, bro. You need to stop
trying to look good for women. You
embarrassment. Trying to show off in
front of all. Try to act the big bad in
front of women.
Trying to act the big man in front of
women. That's some beta male [ __ ] bro.
Didn't hear from this guy for months.
Mr. Bean. And as soon as I'm going at a
woman, he's acting like the big man. [ __ ] hell.
Okay, Joe. Okay. Okay, Joe. How about
this then? Yeah. How about we meet halfway?
No, I'm not. I'm not. He's not getting
it. I'm just saying that he's a s.
Getting what, bro?
You know what I'm saying? Why are you
trying to look good for women, bro?
That's embarrassing. You say you get all
these women. Yeah. You say you get all
of these women, right? But you're trying
to look good for women on YouTube. What
a simp. I'm not even talking about that
USA thing. I'm not even talking about
USA. I'm talking about that autumn, bro.
That is some beta male [ __ ]
Why do you Why are you trying to look
good for women, bro? Some fat ugly woman
that uses filters. That is some beta
male [ __ ] bro. It makes you look so
beta. That's what it does. It generally
does. Why do I only have mouth online?
Do why do I You want to know the answer to that?
Do you really want to know why? Why why
I do this online, bro? Because every
single time people try to meet these
people, they don't show up. That's why
it's just better to have mouth online,
isn't it? I mean, yeah. I mean, when
people literally try to meet these
people, they don't show up. So, does
that answer your question?
Yeah. Joe, you people don't even leave
your house, you ain't got no money. You
ain't got no life. You laugh at your
fat, ugly selves, Joe. You people ain't
got no life and no friends. Your life's
losers. You get laughed at every every
time you and the L crew try to [ __ ]
leave your house. You get laughed at.
You get bullied. You're the bully
victims. You're not the bullies. You're
the bully victims. Listen, like I said,
you ain't got no life outside of
YouTube. You people, right? You, Joseph,
um, LJ's fans, you got no life outside
of YouTube. You're literally life's
losers. And you keep saying that you
laugh at someone younger and better
looking than you, bro. Give your head a
wobble. And I think that's the first
time you've been laughed at. Laugh at,
bro. Laugh that. You can't even talk,
brother. You can't even talk on a panel,
Joseph. You can't even talk on a panel.
You can't even talk. You're that
disabled. You can't even talk on a
panel, bro. Really? Really? I made
myself look like a right sausage, bro.
You didn't even show up the last time.
Yeah, brother. You didn't even show up
the last time. I have tried to meet you
people multiple times and you don't show
up. It's the same thing with LT uh
sorry, not LT, uh Triple H. I went to
Triple H's area three times. He didn't
show up and he's still acting like the
big man. And it will be no different
with Joseph Ferrar and Steven Howard.
This is the truth. This is not [ __ ]
bro. This honestly is not [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm going to use Triple H in this
example right here, right now. I have
gone to Triple H's area three times and
the [ __ ] house did not show up and he's
still coming on the internet acting bad.
This is what these people do, bro. Even
if you meet them, Yeah. or you you try
to meet these people, they're just going
to carry on and on and on and on and on.
That's why I'm done with these people. I
don't want nothing to do with these
people. They keep mentioning my name.
Yeah. They keep drawing me the [ __ ] out.
Brother, listen. He did not come out.
Period. It doesn't matter. He did not
come Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Fair enough. So if he did not come out,
he told me he would meet me. He told me
if I went to Newcastle, he would meet
me. That is what he said. That That is
what he said. He said that he would meet
me, but he never. But then he's trying
to act bad. He's trying to act bad. And
I'm not being funny. If you're not going
to meet someone in a normal way, you're
not going to meet someone for a fight.
That's the way I see it. Okay. You It's
not You told me that you would meet me
if I went there. You told me that you
would meet me if I went there. That is
what he said. That's not [ __ ] He
actually did say that. Yeah. So, okay.
So, what if somebody travels to meet you
for a fight? What you all of a sudden
going to come out? It's not going to
happen. It's not going to happen.
You know what I'm saying? It's not going
to happen. And we're not talking about
triple. We're not even we're talking
about loads of different people. Kevin
Murphy, Nonss, Mark Samson, the list
goes on and on and on and on and on and
on and on and on and on. You know, I can
name you dozens of people I've tried
meeting and you still come online
talking [ __ ] You know, the list goes
on. It never stops. I've got a I've got
a list as long as my arm.
Bomb nons. Uh bomb nonslegs. Mark Samson,
uh Terry as well. I've tried with Terry,
uh Trevor Dawson, but I can tell you the
people that took proper LS and you still
come online acting bad. So, what do you
want people to do, bro?
And that's why I didn't meet uh Joe um
was it last week or the week before?
Yeah. Yeah. Uh that's why LT before you
want to get involved. Uh because I know
how the cookie crumbles. People don't
get scared with age. I haven't all of
Bro, I was reckless [ __ ] 3, four
years ago when I was trying to beat
these people. Do you think I'm suddenly
scared of them now? Bro, I'm not scared
of none of these people. I just know
what they're going to do what they like
what they always do.
You know, Kevin Murphy's another one.
Another little [ __ ] house that comes
back on here periodically. Like, you
didn't go to Liverpool and run the show.
Run the show.
You know, I went to Liverpool and I run
the show. I literally run the show and
they still come online acting bad. I ran
the show, bro. When I went to Liverpool,
I ran the show. I was live multiple
multiple multiple multiple times, right?
And Kevin Murphy still comes on here
acting bad. Acting like the bad bad. So,
you know what I mean? It's uh that's it,
right? Okay. Okay. And what about all of
the people And what about all of the
people that I have tried meeting? What
about all of the people that I have tried meeting?
What about all of the people that I have
tried meeting? You tell me where I once
got credit from any of these people.
Mark Samson, Nles, Trevor Dawson, Terry
Bomb. You tell me. No, no, no, no, no.
You tell me. You tell me where one of
these people have gave me credit. You
think I can't go today to leads and slap
the [ __ ] out of this joke? Easy, bro.
I've got the money. I've got the time. I
can do whatever the [ __ ] I could go
today if I wanted to, but I know exactly
what's going to happen and I bet money
on it. I can tell you exactly what's
going to happen. I can tell you exactly
what's going to happen in the way it's
going to happen. You know, you know,
lost money. Nope. I've got plenty of money. Simple,
right? It doesn't matter. It It doesn't
It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter.
I've still had loads of W's. I've still
I You know, I' I've still had loads of
W's. Okay. Okay. So, you tell me this
then. What is the chances today that I
go to leads? You tell me this. Tell me
this. Tell me this. Right. Or where is
it? Uh have a gate. He said, "Yeah, you
tell me. What's the chances that I go
there today? And this guy's going to be
like, "Oh, I made you go there. I
control you." You tell me. What's the
chances of that happening, bro? Cuz I'm
telling you, I'm telling you quite high.
Yeah. No one's worried about any of you
people. You people don't bother no one.
Yeah, I know, bro. Yeah. Yeah. No one's
worried about any of you people, bro. No
one's bothered about any of you people.
Like, we we know Joseph will never ever
show up. No one's bothered about any of
you people either,
you know. No one's bothered about any of you people.
people as well. I'm not scared of any of
these people. I was trying to [ __ ]
meet all of these people [ __ ] 3 years
ago. And the same thing happens. And the
same thing happens, bro. The same thing happens.
Yeah. An old tiny man. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And guess what, bro? And guess what? And
guess what else? We've seen 90% of these
people in this community not showing up.
So, go figure. Yeah. Yeah. We've also
seen 90% of the people in this community
not showing up.
We've seen that on this community as
well. Yeah, we've seen that on this
community. We've definitely definitely
definitely seen that on this community.
And you twist things anyways. And that's
another thing. You twist [ __ ] anyways.
You twist things anyways, you know.
Yeah, you twist mad things. It's like
LJ, I said, you come on the door and you
done nothing. It's not even It's not
even a full W. What that guy done is not
even a full W. I was like, bro, you
stood behind the gate and you've done
nothing. I stood in front of my mom. You
had several chances to hit me and you've
done nothing. And then I tried to meet
you again in the same location. Like,
you did not win. I will go as confident
as say you did not win. No one was
scared of you. Yeah. I did not have to
open that door. I did not have to open
that door, bro. I did not have to open that door.
I did not have to open that door at all.
No one was scared of you, bro. No one
was scared of you at all. And then I
tried to meet you again. You didn't even
put your camera on. Did I win? No, I'm
not saying I won. I I'm not You didn't
win. You did not win, bro. that you did
not win. Trust me. Yeah, I didn't. I
didn't. But yeah,
brother. Jay done nothing, brother. He
stood behind a gate and he done nothing.
He's not about it. If I traveled Yeah.
to another country, I would be breaking
the person's [ __ ] windows. Yes. That
is not a win. He is not about it. He
come on the door cuz Bquest gave him
money and he shut it. Yeah. He had two
chances to kick the door in my face. I
saw it as well and he done nothing. He's
not about that life. Yeah. He is not
about that life. Trust me. Yeah. Simple.
I saw it. And that is not a man that's
about something. If I travel to another
country at I would be breaking in that
in that house. I would be I would be
smashing that window. That guy is not
about it. And he had several chances to
kick the door in my face. That's not
even [ __ ] It's not even the same as
a prime thing, bro. It's not even the
same as that prime incident. That is
nothing like that prime incident. He
come to argue and he is not about it. I
told him [ __ ] off to his face. Yeah, but
you would always twist things if he s
about it then. Okay. Okay. If he sucks
about it, why did he put the camera on
then? Why didn't he put the camera on
then? When I was in the same location as
him. Okay. Why didn't he put his camera
on? I went to the same location as him.
Why didn't he put his camera on, bro? I
didn't need to go and smash someone
outside of the house. The guy done
nothing. I opened the door and I told
him to [ __ ] off. I didn't need to go out
and kill someone. I didn't need to do
that, bro. I was in front of my mom.
He's not about it. Yeah.
Simple. That guy is not about it. That
is not even a W, bro. Like that. That
should just get like put in the bin.
Simple. And that was like four years ago
as well, bro. Give it a rest. It's 2026.
Come on now, bro. It's 2026. The only
The only person Yeah. that can keep
rinsing what they've done is that prime.
That's the only thing that these people
got is that prime. The only thing that
will will continue with will continue to
be relevant is that prime incident. No,
nothing else. L is not about that life,
bro. That is not someone that's about
it. He had several chances to boot that,
bro. It's not extra me measures. You
come on someone's door from another
country. Yeah, there's no extra [ __ ]
measures. Bad man. You paid that money.
You couldn't even kick the door in my
face. I was standing in front of my mom.
You were st stood behind the gate. Yeah,
you took the you took the extra messages
in the first place. And I don't even
know why we were talking about this.
This is all boring, bro. We've already
been over this before. This is boring,
bro. Come up with some new content.
Simple. Let's You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Yeah, he has. Jake, what have you done?
What have you done? Yeah. Jake, what
have you done? Have you come on my door?
No. So, stop [ __ ] stirring. Have you
come on my door? No, you haven't. Have
you come on my door, [ __ ] house?
Before or after LT? No. So, stop trying
to stir something, you [ __ ] house, when
you ain't done anything your [ __ ]
self. Yeah, you [ __ ] idiot. Someone
was supposed to meet me last week.
Nothing happened. He started it, by the
way, as well.
Give it a break, bro. Like, give it a
break. It's 2026. Give it a break.
You know what I'm saying,
brother? Listen, I can remember
traveling around the country and calling
these people out about 4 and a half
years ago. I remember traveling to
different places and saying if anyone's
from this area. Yeah. Let me know. Do
you remember that Steven Howard? I can
remember it quite uh quite a lot
actually. And no one ever used to come
forward. They used to come on liberries
and talk [ __ ] and talk [ __ ] and talk
[ __ ] and talk [ __ ] and not one person
would come forward from all all of the
places that I went like and you're still
doing this bro. Come on now. Just stop
it. Really really really really just
stop it. What is Can I tell you what is
the point of all of this?
What is the point of all of this? Doing
all of this again, bro? Like, what is
the point of doing this? Because even
when you take L's, you just twist [ __ ]
What is the point of this, bro? I don't
understand. What is the point of this?
Wasting your time even speaking about
meeting the M. This is boring, bro. This
is regurgitated [ __ ] I I only went live
today cuz this guy keeps banging on
about me, banging on about me, banging
on about me.
You know, you got the same excuses. You
talk about this. You know, it this is
just pathetic, bro.
It's 2026. I will always be a loser.
Yeah, you people are losers. Stop
talking about yourselves. It's 2026, bro.
Seriously, stop calling yourself a
loser. Stop calling yourself a loser in
2026, bro. You know what I'm saying?
No, I really, really don't. I really,
really don't. Okay, bro. Listen, I just
gave you an example. Listen, bro. I just
gave you an example of what would happen
today if I went to Harriet. I told you
it's just regurgitated. No matter what
you do on here, it's just regurgitation.
That's all it is. You can like listen
listen. Okay. Right. You literally can
show these people money again, which I
can show them money, but I choose not
to. You can travel to meet these people
again. You can, I don't [ __ ] know,
show more women than them, whatever the
[ __ ] And they're still going to talk
[ __ ] for another 10 years. What the
He didn't call my bluff. If when he's in
that pub, he can start talking [ __ ]
When he's in that pub, he can start
talking [ __ ] He didn't call anyone's
bluff. He's a keyboard warrior. That's
not calling someone's bluff, loser. He
didn't even show up to the pub himself.
Yeah, he didn't even show up to the pub himself.
Simple, bro. Like, what the [ __ ]
Calling my bluff. You're calling my
bluff when you go to that pub, not
talking behind the keyboard, which you
keep doing. Give it a break, mate. [ __ ] hell.
You know what? Yeah, there is a way to
do this with this Jo, right? You really
want to know how we can do this with this Jo?
Get him to meet us halfway. That's
that's the only way you're going to
prove this guy is full of [ __ ] Right.
The only way you're going to prove this
guy is absolutely full of [ __ ] is
uh Exactly. Ignore LT, bro. Shut the
[ __ ] up, you loser. You You will give me
£100, bro. You're going to have to give
me more than £100.
You're going to have to give me more
than £100. It's going to cost more than
I'll give you a deal, right? Okay. You
really want a deal? No [ __ ] 100% no
[ __ ] Yeah. Okay. You really,
really, really want the deal and I'm not
going to go back on this now. I swear to
God on anything deadly serious now.
Yeah. Okay. There's two things, right?
This guy this guy can either meet me
halfway, right? Or you you you send me
you send me £300 to my bank and I'll go.
Simple. You send me £300 to my bank and
I'll go. Those are the two options.
Those are the two options. I don't need
I Bro, of course I need money to go. I
don't want to waste my own money on some
loser. Yeah, I I don't need the money.
I'd like the money. Yeah, because I want
to get paid to prove that it's the same
old [ __ ] again. Yeah,
brother. How many times have people
wasted their money on new people to only talk [ __ ]
No, bro. Why won't you do that? Listen,
listen. Why won't you do that? Listen,
listen, listen. Why won't you Why won't
you do that?
Why won't you? Why won't you, bro?
Brother, you people don't laugh at
yourselves. You people are sat on
YouTube every day with no friends. I
laugh at you. Trust me, bro. I get more
laughs out of you than you will ever get
out of me. You people are sad, pathetic
old men sat on the internet. Trust me,
you don't laugh at someone younger and
better looking than you. Oh, you don't
laugh at someone younger and better
looking than you. I assure you that,
bro. But let me tell you what I laugh
though. Every time I go on Lord J and I
see the same sad, lonely people, I laugh
at you. I give I have more laughs out of
you than you would ever ever have out of
me. You're sad, pathetic, lonely people
with no friends and I laugh at, bro. I
laugh at you people. You're sat on
YouTube with no friends. Who are you
laughing at, bro? No one. No one. No Simple.
Simple, bro. So, you want me Okay,
Stephen H. So, what these people want me
to do? Yeah, they want me to go out
again, waste another £400, and this guy
is going to be like, "Oh, oh, I control
you. I control you." That's what's going
to happen. I bet you any money, bro.
That is going to happen. I bet you any
money that is going to happen. You're
going to go all that way. Listen, this
is what's going to happen. You're going
to go all that way and he's going to be
like, "I control you. I bullied you. I
know what these people do, bro." Okay,
I'll put you the link. I'll put the link
up. I'll put the link up. Yeah,
I know exactly what's going to happen, bro. you know.
That's it. Where's halfway? I think it's
like Peter B, is it?
No. Where was it? Where was halfway?
Bro, I can tell you exactly what happened.
losing my last benefit money. Bro, I've
got money. You don't know how much money
I've got. I've got more money than
you'll ever have. You don't know how
much money I've got,
>> bro. Yeah.
Anyways, you're going to join. You
wanted the link. So, you going to join or what?
I don't know what food king does, bro.
But I know what these people do. I know
exactly what these people do cuz they've
done it before. They've literally done
You're going to waste money again. This
is what's going to happen. I tell you I
tell you exactly what's going to happen.
Like you you want you want to know
exactly what's going to happen. Okay.
I'll tell you exactly what's going to
happen, bro. You're going to go This
guy's not serious about meeting This guy
is not actually serious about meeting
people, right? So, you're going to go,
you're going to waste four or500
probably over the weekend. Uh you're
going to waste four or 500, right?
You're going to come back. This is
what's going to happen. Listen. Listen.
You're going to come back and then it's
just going to start again and start
again and then a whole year with
nothing. A whole year and nothing again.
That's what's going to happen,
you know? You know, and that's it. And
then it's a whole year and nothing
again. That is it, bro. That is it. That
Germany Germany Germany Germany is it.
That Germany Germany Germany Germany is it. So yeah,
that's exactly what's going to happen.
That is exactly what's going to happen.
Yeah, they're all the same on here, bro.
They literally are all the same on here.
They literally literally are.
Yeah, you people don't owe no one.
Another year of you sad, self-projected
people that ain't got no life. Maybe.
Yeah, but you don't owe me. You ain't
got a life. I weren't even going to come
on until this guy started talking about
me. Listen, like I've stated many, many
times, I'm going to keep repeating
myself. You people on YouTube, from the
time you wake up to the time that you go
to bed, you own yourselves every day.
Sad, lonely, fat, ugly people. That's
what you people are, bro. Yeah. That's
literally what you are. Sad, ugly people
with no life. You ain't got a life, bro.
Nah. Nah. And I'm not even I'm not even
using your favorite word anymore.
Jealousy. It's the truth. on YouTube
from the time you wake up to the time
you go to bed. You sab bastards and you
want to talk about me, bro.
Yeah, you're talking about yourself,
Trips, bro. You're talking about yourself.
Oh, this is a fake Timmy, by the way.
You're talking about yourself, bro.
Your Mrs. dumped you for another man,
bro. I mean, your child is calling
another man daddy.
Your child is calling another man daddy,
bro. That could never happen to me. But yeah,
another man is bringing up your kid.
That's facts. And that is actually like
me being honest. That's not even me.
You'll fill me in, bro. Of course you
will, bro. Yeah, of course you will, man.
Yeah. Hey, Jim, can I ask you a
question? How old are you? Just out of
curiosity. How old How old are you?
I was in Newcastle three times and he
didn't show up. Uh, I was in Newcastle
three times and he didn't show up. So,
you might have dementia or something.
Um, but I've already gone to Newcastle
three times and he didn't show up.
Anyways, uh, how old are you, Jim? Just
just just wondering.
Yeah, I'm a virgin. Okay, bro. Uh,
anyways, Jim, how old are you?
How old are you, by the way?
How old are you? 34.
Your account was made 18 years ago. [laughter]
Jesus Christ. 18 years ago your account
was made. Are you sure it's me that
ain't got a life, bro? Seriously? Yeah.
Are you sure it's me that's got no life, bro? Really?
Are you sure it's me and not you? Your
account was made 18 years ago, bro.
You're a lot older than 34, mate. Put it that way.
So, it's like, yeah,
this is just madness. This is, bro. Do
you know what? I keep saying this [ __ ]
I don't care what people do, bro. I
don't give a [ __ ] if people have got a
life, if people don't have a life, what
people look like. I don't I don't give a
[ __ ] bro. Like, this is what I'm trying
to say. I don't care about what other
people do. But when they're trying to
talk about me, someone that's better
than them, and they're worse off than
you. Just just make it make sense once
in a while. They sit there and call you
all of these names under the sun. You're
this, you're that, you're this, you're
that, you're this, you're that. And then
you literally go on L J's and you see
the same friendless people typing to
each other cuz they got no mates. They
got no friends. They literally have got raong
on YouTube. What? A bunch of [ __ ]
disabled low lives on YouTube. Oh,
sorry, bro. Cuz that's the demographic
you're talking about. What? So, because
a bunch of middle-aged skin low life
with no friends and no life outside of
YouTube laugh at me, is that supposed Is
that supposed to help? Is Is that
supposed to Is that supposed to affect me?
You people are literally
losers. Life losers. Life's losers. I've
said this about like God knows how many times.
You know, you're fat, you're ugly,
you're skinn, and you got no life.
That's why you're on him in 2026 still
doing the same [ __ ]
>> Hello PJ. Why are you so rattled on the second?
>> I'm not man. I'm just talking about these people.
>> But PJ, why are you talking about these people? >> YouTube's
not getting attention.
>> Why are you Hello, Tim. How are you my
lad? Happy New Year. Why are you so
pissed off over a fiber active cable?
>> No, I'm not pissed off man. I'm just
saying that they're boring.
>> You going
this and that. Look this.
>> He is drill. Let's get LJ back on it.
Let's get L actually.
>> No, but Joe is owning your ass cuz
you're back in Yorkshire and you're going to
>> I go I go live every day. I don't think
so, man. I don't think I go live every day.
>> Then interest in your own bloody life.
Now I'm in London. You want to get to
Penge so I can kick your head in.
>> Jimmy, you can't fight. Oh,
>> why don't you go live in pen and I'll
show you what who's busting.
>> One second. Is he going to Is he going
to Is he going to let people pass 46 minutes now?
>> One second. I'm going to kick Timmy out
cuz he just keeps talking over people,
>> brother. Okay, listen. Life loses, bro.
You people are middle-aged.
You got no girlfriend, no friends, no
money. Look at you people again. You
need to look at yourselves. You people
probably live in a capsule bedsit. No
money, no friend. Yeah, your life's
losers. Yes. And I'm calling you a
life's loser. Just like this life's
You still show your fake watch.
>> You still showing your fake watch.
>> My fault that you're jealous.
>> This watch is like 70% of your monthly income. That's
>> No, it's not. No, it's not. You don't
have a wrist.
>> Okay, bro. My wardrobe My wardrobe is
worth more than a year.
>> Your wardrobe is years. My wardrobe is
worth more than a year of your income.
>> You don't even get Okay, bro. You don't
even get £1,000 a month. Your skin don't
even have a grand your name. Show us
Show us a grand. Show us a grand right
now. Show us a grand right now. One
second. One second. One second. One
second. One second. Show me my let
You're not letting You're not letting
anyone talk. Show me Show me my monthly
money. Show me my monthly money. Come
on. You seem to know so much. Show us.
Bro, you you lie. You lie about You lie
about owning You lie about owning You
lie about owning talking over people
again. Talking over people. Talking over
You lie about
I just showed you.
>> I just showed you your monthly money.
It's on the wrist.
>> You You You lie You lie about owning
property when you're on You got nobody. Listen,
>> you're 28 years old, practically 30, and
you wasted it all on YouTube.
>> Oh, you are in your 40s. You got no
driver license. Listen, not let not let
me talk again. Got your money.
>> You didn't get any of my money stopped
again. I will repeat. You didn't get any
of my money. I've got more money. I've
got more money than both of you. You did
not get any of my money stopped. I've
explained the story multiple mult. I
don't beg for donations. I don't beg for
donations. Listen. Listen.
seems very triggered right now.
>> Seems very triggered.
>> Listen, listen, listen. Who's the one
that begs for donations? Who's the one
that begs for donations? You. Cuz you're skint.
Oh, I own six properties. I own six
properties. You don't own
You ain't even got a driver license. You
ain't even got a driving license, you
life loser. You're 42. You're life
loser. No driving license, no money, no girlfriend.
Should we talk about the phone? You
didn't get any of my money stopped. You
didn't get none of my money stopped.
>> You didn't get none of my money stopped.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I've got more money than both of you.
>> Both of you.
>> Are you listening?
I spending a few hundred. Listen.
Someone told me you called Joe. You were
going to meet Joe.
>> I've brought more money to both of you. Listen. Listen.
>> You're not a boat. Have
>> you shown Have you shown Have you shown
more money? Listen.
>> Show us £1,000. Show us £1,000.
>> I just showed your £1,000. Come on. Stop
changing the subject. Show us £1,000.
>> Look, PJ, it's not on the wrist. >> Your
monthly. Listen, bro. Bro, my wardrobe
is your yearly income, bro. My wardrobe
is your yearly income. That's your
yearly income. You don't even get You
don't even get a grand a month,
>> bro. You don't even get a grand a month.
Your skin a month. That's why you make
up stories. That's why you make up
stories. That's why I'm making your
income on my ow, bro. That's not my exact
You don't pay for You don't know how
much money I've got. You're the fooling
yourself. You're the one begging for
donations cuz your skin You're the one.
Okay, let's go. Let's go and buy the
evidence. Let's go and buy the evidence.
>> You got money online cuz you got no
money. You beg for drinks. You're
wearing a 640 watch because you can't
afford a Rolex yet. You're saying about
how you [ __ ] owe six.
You're saying that you owe six
properties, but you're wearing a 640
watch. You're begging for money on the
internet. Why you ain't got no money.
>> You literally
stop acting like you got money. You
ain't got no money. You got no money.
Man has sex with dog. It's madness.
>> You've literally got no money. Stop.
You don't even get madness.
>> You don't even get a grand a month.
That's how bad it is. You don't even get
a grand a month. You do not even
my month. What? So I get £640 a month.
Bro, WHY ARE YOU NOT WEARING A ROLEX?
CUZ YOU CAN'T AFFORD IT.
>> Cuz you can't afford it.
>> Let me [laughter] ask you this.
>> I own six properties. He's having to
make up stories cuz he's skin. Listen,
bro. Listen. Listen
on your witch. When you have sex
on your wish cuz you ain't got no money.
You got no money, bro. Sax life controlled by
money. He thinks he's got money. Think
about this though. You're saturated for control.
>> You and nonsense. You think you got
money, but you don't have no money. You
think you got money, but you don't. Why
do you think you got money? You don't
own no property. You You don't own nothing.
>> Football. We can't have
>> You're begging for donations cuz you got
no money. You're begging for money
online. That's not a guy that's got money.
>> Are you a guy that's got money? That's
not a guy that's got money, bro. That's
not a guy that's got money.
>> That's not a guy that's got money
wearing 640 on his wrist. That's not a
guy that's got money. That's a guy
that's got skin.
>> That's a guy that is skin. 640 on your
wrist thinking you got money.
>> Where's your Rolex? Why do you Why don't
you have a Rolex? I should just
>> Why don't you have a Rolex?
>> Yeah. When he shows himself in the pub.
Yeah. When he Why have you got money gambling?
>> Why is money gambling?
>> Listen. Listen. Why have you got
>> smoky? No, you never got any of my sub
buddy. Stop. You keep telling yourself
>> DJ T D T D T D T D T D T D T D T D T D T DJ Show
>> You didn't get any of my I've got more
money than you. I've got more money than
you. So, how's that possible? So, how much
>> your autism is today?
>> You can't even spell
your autism. PJ,
>> you was talking about Ant-Man's watch
and you're wearing a 640. Correct.
>> Bro, you're wearing a 640 watch. You
don't have money. You don't have money.
Stop acting like you got money,
>> bro. I don't.
>> You said the other week you never wore a
watch. I'll ask. Are you going to let me
answer you? You going to let me answer
you? No, I don't have a
[ __ ] talking over me again. He's
talking over me again cuz he knows I'm right.
>> Your autism. Here comes the autism voice.
>> Here comes the autism voice.
>> What What do you have again?
>> Yeah. Go.
>> LT wants to know what you got.
>> Uh Tess uh PRX.
>> Where's your Why not the Rolex?
>> Why would I wear a Rolex?
>> Because you ain't got no money. Could
you cuz you can't afford it. We all know
anyone that's got money. Yeah, we know
if anyone's got [ __ ] money.
>> Do you have a Rolex?
>> Bro, listen, brother.
>> You saying I could go out I could go out and buy
>> brother. I can go out and buy your watch right now.
>> I'll tell you what. You go and buy the
watch and I'll refund.
>> I can literally go and buy your watch right now.
>> Go and buy the watch and I'll refund you the money.
>> I can literally I can literally buy that
watch right now. Bro,
>> if you go and buy that watch right now.
>> I know. I know. A 640 watch a Rolex.
I'll refund. I don't know much about
watches. I don't know much about
watches. No, I know I've never been into
>> I've never been into watches, but I know
a £640 watch is nowhere near a Rolex.
That's what I know. I know. That's all I
>> Buy the watch and I'll refund you.
>> 640 WATCH, MATE. I'VE got clothes worth
more than that. I've got
I've got clothes more than that. Jesus.
>> When you PJ, listen PJ, listen. PJ,
listen. For me. I understand your listen
PJ. When you were getting bullied and
had to leave school, I was wearing Stone Island then.
>> Bully, bro. No one's ever bullied. [laughter]
>> When you were getting bullied and had to
leave school that gets bullied around Stone Island.
>> You're the one that gets bullied.
>> Think about that. Think about the levels of this.
>> And you're banging on about Stone Island
like it's a big thing,
>> bro. I'm not banging on. I'm saying my
stolen 20 years ago.
>> I'm saying to you my wardrobe is worth
more than your yearly. Your wardrobe is
worth talking about income, bro. Cuz
you're talking about income. I've got
more money than you would ever have. I
have more money than you will ever have.
And I would never flex a£640 watch. I
would never flex a£640 watch. What the [ __ ]
>> Take a deep breath.
>> Your autism's bad. Take a deep breath.
>> Yeah, my autism is bad. You can't even start.
PJ PJ didn't get your money stopped.
>> He literally did not get my money
stopped. I've explained the same thing
over and over again. I've explained the
same thing over and over again.
>> You haven't bought anything.
>> I've explained the same thing over and
over again. Listen, Red got your money stopped.
>> You did not get any of my money stopped.
I've got more money than you.
>> No, he didn't. And I've got more money
than both. I didn't get your money
stopped. Red got your money.
>> Red Star never got my money stopped. And
I've got more money than both of you.
Listen, I bought new clothes last I
bought I bought new clothes last month.
You're not You're not a catalog.
>> I literally bought clothes last month,
>> brother. You literally
>> your sister's catalog.
>> You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
>> A cat catalog. [laughter]
>> Jealousy. Jealousy. The jealousy. The
jealous. Oh, so I got it from the
catalog. I got it from the catalog.
Really? Jealousy again. So even when
people prove they've got more money than
you, you still talk [ __ ] That's what
I'm saying. This is what I'm saying.
Even when people prove they've got more
money than you, you know, if you That's
why I don't argue with you. You're a
[ __ ] LT. That's why I don't argue
with you. You're a [ __ ] as well.
You're a [ __ ] as well. I've noticed
I've had to explain the same thing over
and over to you again as well.
>> Did you go to your sisters for that lamb?
>> Mate, I've never used a
skin like when you said you were going
for something and you wanted to sisters
to have a lamb.
>> I'm not someone that I'm not someone.
When was when did you lost by new clothes?
>> Did you enjoy her?
>> One second. When did you lost my new clothes? >> Today.
>> Let's see them.
>> I was in town. B them.
>> Let's Let's see them. Let's see your
clothes. Come on. Cuz you brought up
>> Why would you uh
>> Because you're [ __ ] skin. Cuz you're
[ __ ] Do you remember when he was
trying to say that he gets three GRAND A
MONTH? DO YOU REMEMBER WHEN HE was
trying to say he gets three grand a
month? He gets nothing. He's a loser.
He's a life loser. You really think
someone that's got all this money would
sit on YouTube while they begging for
money? Do you think a guy that's got
money sits and begs? Are you meeting?
>> Do you actually think you actually think someone
>> Listen, you are disabled.
>> LT, you are disabled and you and you
tried to look good for women as well. >> Disabled.
>> Oh, listen bro, you are PJ. PJ, why did
you meet LT then?
>> Why didn't you meet LT? Why didn't you
meet LT when he offered to go blackpool
your [ __ ] out?
>> Listen. When Well, listen, listen. When
Why didn't you meet LT?
>> No, no, no. Why do you meet LT big man?
Don't [ __ ] drive on me. You little
[ __ ] out. [ __ ] off. You didn't meet LT
yourself, you [ __ ] stupid.
>> LT WAS OUTSIDE YOUR MAN'S HOUSE, WASN'T IT?
>> LISTEN, LT was in the same location as
you. [laughter] You would have put your
camera on. You would have put your
camera on your house.
>> Shut the [ __ ] up.
>> Money for you and you didn't have the
balls to go out.
>> Well, cuz I don't need £1,000 cuz I've
got skin like you with a 640 watch.
>> You lost money.
>> Literally, it's madness. It's bad as [ __ ]
>> How did you lie? You, like I've said
multiple times, you ugly people don't
really know. You bully yourself.
>> You're on YouTube in 2026. YOUR LIFE'S LOSERS. >> 266.
>> LISTERS, you people are life's losers.
You're on YouTube IN 2026. YOUR LIFE'S
LOSERS. I'm on here to see the life's
losers with no friends. LIKE LY, WHY
HAVE WE never ever seen you with a friend?
>> Why have we never ever seen you with a
woman on money? Can I ask you a question?
>> Can I ask you a question? Can I ask you
>> Have you never had a girlfriend?
>> Why have we never seen you with a friend
or woman or buddy?
>> Sounds like projections. I haven't had a
girlfriend. You've never HAD A GIRLFRIEND.
>> YOU'VE NEVER HAD A GIRLFRIEND. You're a
[ __ ] virgin. You are not even yours.
You're a [ __ ] virgin. You have a
[ __ ] virgin. They're not even your
kids. You think someone that's got kids
can sit on YouTube 24/7? You think
someone on YouTube with kids can sit on
it? You're on YouTube 24/7, you loser.
You've never had a girlfriend yourself,
you loser. You can't even get a woman.
>> You're right. [clears throat]
Throwing you out.
>> Joe, have you met Listen, Joe, have you
met his kids? Have you met his kids?
>> When your mom's neighbors get mad at us, you're getting
>> Joe, have you met his kids? Joe, have
you met his kids? That's what I thought.
Stop sucking his dick. Have you met his
kids? One second. One second. One
second. Hold on.
>> Mom's going to throw him out. He's not.
He's talking over me. When he talks When
they talk over you, you know you've won.
You know you bully them. Listen, Joe,
have you met him? Have you met his kids?
>> Have you met Have you met his kids? Joe,
have you met his kids? One second. Have
you met his kids? What's his kids'
names? Have you been to his house?
Exactly. So, stop sucking dick, you
[ __ ] You scared PJ's ring. No, listen.
Listen. Stop licking ass. Stop sucking dick about PJ.
>> I'm going to
cry over some 42y old that ain't got nobody
and has to beg for money on a
girlfriend. a 42y old with no driver
license and no money flexing 640 on his wrist. Bro,
>> I don't think so. >> Jesus,
>> you are 42. You got no guilt driving
license at 600. I've been sorry for your
life, bro. You don't need to feel sorry
for me. I don't need to beg money.
>> Here PJ, let me ask you on the internet.
I don't let me Okay, let me ask you.
Listen, I look flashing a 640. Why were
you saying that
because he lives in his own bed? Are you
sure for your mom?
>> You are the one that's got nothing
on the internet.
>> Begging for money on the internet. Make
listen, you know, if you if you want
supporting himself. If you want to own,
you want to make it make sense. You want
to make it make sense. You want to make
living on his own in a bed show that was
bullied. All of the people that was bullied. Yeah.
>> 2020 were still bullying PJ L. You and
your goons, bro. LJ, bully me. I'm still
on here laughing at you. You're talking
over me because you know that I'm right.
You're not bullying no one. I'm still
here talking about how you're 42, 640
watch, no money, no driving license.
You're just talking over people. LT, you
and your goons have been bullied. Your
autistic cousin's been bullied. You got
bullied all your life. That's why you
come on the internet acting like you're
a bad man. You're no bad man. You and
your [ __ ] you and your goons are
nobodyies. You're bully victims. That's
why you come on the internet acting bad.
You're bully victims. What are you on
about, bro? Come on now. You talk over
people time and time again. Lj, you're
42. No driving license, no money. You
don't even get a grand above. LT, you're
the one acted bad on the internet, bro.
You've always been bullied. Yeah, that's
what we wanted to hear. I'm not scared
of you or anyone that you know. You
don't scare me, bro. You do not scare
me. Stick to bullying Natalie G. You
don't scare me. You do not scare me.
Yeah. You was always bullied you and
your cousins. Simple, bro. Yes. You That
is what I wanted to hear, bro. You and
your cousins have always been bullied.
You've never been a part of nothing. You
think I ain't I ain't asked Venom about
you? They don't know you, Taylor Swift.
They don't know some loser trying to act
good for women. Listen, they don't know
some [ __ ] wannabe loser. You think I
didn't tell Venom about you? Then no
one's heard of you, Taylor Swift. No
one's heard of you. Stop acting Stop
acting bad on the internet, bro. No
one's heard of you. No one's heard of
you, Taylor Swift. The only thing that
we know of Taylor Swift. Yeah. Is you
trying to look good for women on the
internet. That's all we know about you,
bro. We don't know anything else. We
don't know anything else about Taylor
Swift other than he's trying to look
good for women on the internet. We don't
know anything about you. We literally
don't know nothing about you, bro. Simple.
We don't know anything about you, Taylor Swift.
Apart from trying to act bad on the
internet for women, I don't know
anything about you. Why don't you tell
us? Come on.
Why don't you tell us, Taylor Swift? We
don't We don't know anything. We don't
know anything else, you know?
Yeah, bro. Listen listen to me, bro. You
know that day that that window got
smashed, I was actually in the police
cell. Yeah, bro. Yeah, I was in a police
cell. And trust me, your friend would
have been getting knocked the [ __ ] out
if I was in that if I was in that house
that day, bro. Your boyfriend would have
gotten his ass whooped. I got nicked. I
even proved the papers when that
happened. Yeah, your boy ain't about
nothing. That boy ain't about nothing.
You're not You don't bother me, bro. You
don't scare me. Go on Natalie's G's
channel and stop threatening her, bro.
Don't threaten me. You don't scare me.
You don't scare me, bro. You do not
scare me one little bit. I don't know
how many times I have to tell you this.
Yeah. Yeah. Good for him. Yeah. Good for
You're acting bad cuz you smashed
someone's windows when I weren't even
there. Brother, I literally was not even
a house in that house that time. My mom
was in there and the windows got
smashed. And you're still acting bad.
You're still You're still acting bad.
You're still acting bad, bro. If
somebody smashed your mom's window,
she'd be calling the police. Yeah. And
I've had this conversation with you
before. Oh, she wouldn't. Oh, she
wouldn't. Yes, she would. Yes, she
would. Yes, she [ __ ] would. Bro,
that's not even a flex. You broke the
window when someone's mom was in the
house. Seriously. Seriously, bro. Come
on now. Come on. Come on. Come on. Yeah.
Come on, bro. Come on. Come on.
Seriously. Come on now. Yeah. You ain't
got no Yeah. Simple, bro. Yeah.
Why are you trying to look bad for women
on the internet as well? He didn't answer me.
[ __ ] L. He's got 640 on his wrist and
think he's got money. I can go I can buy
that watch right now. I can buy three of
them watches right now, bro. More than
three of them watches. I can literally
buy more than three of them watches
right now. He's got 640 on his wrist
thinking that he's got money when I've
literally got clothes in that wardrobe
worth more than anything he's got in
that house. more than anything that he's
got in that house. Man's got a 640
[ __ ] watch thinking he's got money.
What the [ __ ] bro? And no, I'm not into
watches. I've never been into watches.
Never have, never will. I've never worn
a watch in my [ __ ] life. But I
wouldn't be flexing 640 on my wrist when
you're [ __ ] trying to take the piss
out of someone's [ __ ] Ammani watch.
This guy was mocking Ant-Man's Ammani
watch when he's got 640 on his wrists.
640 on his [ __ ] wrists. What the
That is mad, you know.
Bro, you're boring, brother. You're
boring. You are boring.
You are boring, bro. You've done this a
million times. You are boring. You are
boring. You have got no life. You do not
scare me. Yeah, you are just trying to
act bad on the internet. It's boring
now, bro. No one cares. I don't need to
I don't need Yeah. One sec, bro. Yeah,
you are boring. I've said it like ages
ago. You're boring, bro. You're boring.
You're boring. You're boring, bro.
You're boring. I don't need to step
outside and whoop you. You're not worth
my time. You're literally not worth my
You know, you're not worth No, actually,
I [ __ ] had to I refreshed the page,
bro. You're not worth no one's time.
It's 2026. Like I said, I'm done with you losers.
I am literally done with you losers. I'm
not doing this in 2026. You're doing it
to yourselves, bro. You're doing this to yourselves. Yeah.
Listen, you are doing this to
yourselves. This is 2026 and I'm not
doing this with you anymore. Simple. I
don't care who the [ __ ] you are. Been
there, done it, worn the t-shirt.
Willing to meet anyone else, bro. Will
[clears throat] who have I met? Who am I
willing to meet? Who am I willing to
meet? Yeah, I'm a funny hole. Bro,
you're boring. It's 2026.
It's 20 and you're still doing this.
You're low lives. I'm done with you.
Simple. I'm done with you. Simple.
And another thing is as well, who have I
met? I I just told you I'm not meeting
Jo. I just told you I'm not meeting Jo.
Bro, if I was going to meet people,
you'd be the first one I'd meet. You
don't scare me, bro. You do not scare me
one bit. If I was to meet anyone first,
it would probably be you, bro. You don't
scare me. You're no alpha male. I'm not
beating Joe. I'm not meeting no one on
here because we all know what you do.
I've just spent the past two hours
[ __ ] talking about it. Yeah.
Simple. And that's that.
That's that. Yeah. The link. I'll give
you the link. I don't give a [ __ ] bro. Simple.
You're just nothing but online
harassers. Who have I met? Who have I
met? Who have I met? Who have I met?
Tell me. Who have I met?
Listen. Honest. Stop trying to [ __ ] stir
when you're not going to meet no one.
You're not going to meet no one. Yeah.
yourself. So stop [ __ ] stirring when
you're not going to meet no one. Because
you know what I'm going to end up doing?
I'm going to end up saying I will meet
you if one of these people come with
you. If one of these people come with you. Yeah.
If one of these people come with you,
then I'll meet you. And that's what I'll
just end up saying.
Stop trying to [ __ ] stir when you're not
going to do nothing yourself.
That's the [ __ ] that [ __ ] pisses me
off, you know.
Joe, you had no intentions of meeting
either. Listen, Joe, you can't even
talk. And I told you why I'm not meeting
you. I've explained to you why I'm not
meeting you. I have literally explained
to you with evidence why I'm not meeting you.
I've literally explained why I'm not
meeting you. And it's very valid. And
it's not an excuse. is very valid
because you're all biased.
That's all. You're all biased. That's that.
And it's not an excuse. It's valid.
That is valid. That is not even an excuse. Yeah. One sec. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, go now. So, wait. 100 times
I've come to your house.
>> Boring, bro. You're boring.
>> No, no, no. Forget that. Let's talk. So,
100 times when I've come to your house,
you're now trying to say I'm not the one
that's about it. See what I'm saying
with you? Every time when someone tries
to pull up and meet you and someone
actually wants to with you, you don't
want to smoke back. Yeah. But every time
when it's someone far out, someone that
can't really get to you, then you start
taking advantage and you start trying to
say, "Oh, yeah.
I literally came in I literally came
into your stream today. I came in your
>> How am I taking advantage?
>> Wait, listen. Listen. I came in your
stream today and I literally I came in
in the middle when you said that you
want to meet this guy and you're going
to go I don't even know where he was.
You said you're going to go to him or
whatever. Then more listening to you
even further more about like 10 15
minutes later then you then said oh
let's meet halfway. That's why I
intervened and I told you I would even
give you £100. I won't going to
obviously I won't give you nothing at
first but just to just see if you're
going to actually go and then you then
you move the go and then and then you
move the goal post again. No, no,
listen. You moved the goal post again
when I offered you £100. You then said
£300. So I have to pay for all your
ticket know in full well I'm just not
going to do that. Why am I going to pay
a stranger £300
why I asked that? Are you going to let
me I said £300? Why did I ask for £300?
What's £100 going to get me? Bro, you
know what? Well £100 [laughter]
you Well, you was willing to not pay.
You was willing to go and pay
everything. Well, so you say
>> if he shows himself in a pub. Yes. If he
I said no. What is with all Listen, what
is with all these stipulations on this
[ __ ] bro? Listen, you're calling You're
the one that's calling people out. It's
you. You've done it to me several times.
I've never even called you out many
times. You've done it to me. Oh, no
one's coming to my house. No one's
coming to my house. Brother, I'm telling
you right now, yeah, all these people
might not, but but if you if you want me
to, I can come there within 2 hours. Are
you going to step outside?
>> I said I said if you going to step
outside, that's what I'm asking. I I
want you to confirm to everyone else cuz
you said it multiple times before in the
past and then when I end up coming and
then you don't step outside and end up
smashing the window or something then
you quickly tell everybody oh he smashed
and no one's asked you to come anywhere.
>> No one has but you're calling everybody
fat. So obviously you're addressing me
now. Like no no no when you're saying
everyone come on my channel. No you come
on my video. Yeah trying to go at me cuz
I'm going at this autumn. That's why I
called you I don't even know who you're
talking about to be honest with you. I
don't even know who you're talking
about. I just saw I just watched some of
your video and then I heard you
criticize people and you said that
people are all fat, all bald skinned and
old talking about autumn and I was
mainly talking about autumn now. How
come you not been on the scene for
months and all of a sudden you've come
on when I'm talking about a woman? That
seem dodgy to you. That is dodge.
>> It's the Christmas period. I'm free. Do
you not understand that? What the hell
are you talking about? Like listen, I
tell you how the real world works here.
I tell you how the real world works.
People are normally busy. At my age, I'm
34. Yeah. I don't have time to be
sitting on here watching everything that
you got going on. I listen, you know,
I'm subbed to you for all this time. But
the thing is, I even turn off your
notifications. I don't unsub from you, I
just turn off your notifications so I
don't see any [ __ ] on my phone.
Sometimes I don't want to see it. And
then sometimes when I turn it back on
and I'm seeing the madness and I'm like,
"Oh, so I've not missed nothing." And
then I'm seeing you just ranting and
raving, calling people out. So I said
something the other day cuz I said to
myself, "Wait, hold on. You're calling
people fat? Like what? Do you think that
you're a good specimen here? Like what's
going on?" Bro, I'm not as fat and ugly
as them, bro.
>> You haven't even seen most of them. And
yeah, that's another thing you said.
People don't show their faces because
they're ugly. Huh?
>> Yeah. Yeah,
>> they are.
>> That's not exactly true as well. >> Ugly.
>> No, no, but listen. Listen. That's not
exactly true as well. Anybody that's got
Listen to what I'm saying. Listen to
>> Before giving it Lord, what they look
like when they've been docked, what they
>> Oh, yeah. Buzz. Yeah, I know that.
>> Yeah. There you go.
>> But what I'm what I'm saying what I'm
saying is Yeah. Like anyone that's got
any type of brain on here and if anyone
wants to is is even remotely ambitious,
why would you tie yourself to this
sector? Number one, if I just type in
MTO Stratford Yeah. on Google, brother,
I swear to God, I'm not lying. A whole
bunch of your [ __ ] I saw mad channels
that's recorded your stuff. Like they
record all your
>> No, listen. Listen. I'm trying to get
away from they keep drawing me back in.
Yeah. I didn't start today for no
reason. This Jo keeps drawing.
>> What do you mean? You're a grown ass
man. What do you mean they draw you back
in? You're a grown ass You're a grown
ass man. All All it takes sh is you to
just just uh what do you either delete
your channel or just don't watch. Like I
don't watch these people. Like that's
what I'm saying. Subscribe to No. No.
No. And he's trying to act like the big
man. Like people ain't trying to meet
people several times and you've seen it
yourself. So why why do you want to meet
him? Why do you want to meet him?
>> Huh? Because he keeps talking [ __ ] He's
got a big mouth, bro. He don't Do you
not go on channel?
>> You talk [ __ ] Hold on. You don't go any
channel. Do you hold on? How many times
do you talk [ __ ] about everybody?
>> Okay. And how many people have I tried
meeting? A lot. No. Okay. I might have
to tell, but how many people I tried meeting?
>> You tried to meet You've tried to meet a
few people, but there were some names on
that list there where I have to check
you out. Yeah. Where you said something
about Liverpool and Newcastle. I No,
listen. The Liverpool one and the
Newcastle one, you didn't go there to
fight anyone. You went there to
socialize with people. Yeah. Now you're
trying to change it and say, "Oh, you
tried to meet Triple H." You didn't,
man. You tried to meet him as a social
as a friend. Go on.
>> Okay. But he didn't meet me.
>> Yeah, he didn't meet. But that's not
because he was scared of me. That's not
because he's scared of you. See, in your
little braveness, what you actually
think as well? Go on.
>> Listen, listen. But he told me he would meet me.
>> Yeah, I know.
>> But then he But then he he ghosted you >> because
>> No, wait. So you're saying that So
you're saying that if it was for a
fight, he then would meet me? >> No.
>> Who know? He probably would.
>> Okay, bro. Well said in my video the
other day. Listen, to be honest with
you, to be honest with you. To be honest
with you, what would it look like? What
would it look like? Yeah. Like, do you
know what? If anyone if anyone of decent
size puts their hands on you, like, it's
over. So, what's the point? Like,
>> Liverpool one, listen, that Liverpool
one. Yeah, I was actually live in
Liverpool and they all went, so that's
it's a bro, I know you was there. I'm
not saying you wasn't there. I'm not
saying you're not he wasn't there, but
you wasn't calling no one out, though.
You wasn't trying. Okay. No, no, no, no.
But you don't understand. They all went
silent and they slaughtered their [ __ ]
when I come back. Do you not understand?
>> Yeah, they to me, too. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I know this. But what I'm saying is you
personally w and then and then one
second nonslegs um Mark Samson and bro there's
>> there's Yeah but you know those people
Yeah. You know that those people are not
going to meet Come on you come on Mark
Samson and come on you know bro the guy
called me out. What do you mean?
>> All right. Yeah. All right. Fair enough.
Yeah. No. Mark Samson called you out.
Yeah he did. He did.
>> And they never said nothing until the
people do say stuff they started having problems.
>> People say stuff. People do say stuff.
People do. Even when you went to bomb
that time, people do mention it and they say
>> two people. Yeah, two people.
>> But because Yeah. But your history
because you've got more history because
you've got more history of not turning
up then actually turning up. So it's
like it's overshadowed all the rest of it.
>> That was before the prime thing. That
>> Yeah. But because you've got history
even from the start before you've got
history of just like running away, not
turning up, and just doing coward [ __ ]
Yeah. So, it's like all of that stuff
when you do do something, it's like it's
easy to forget because you know what I
mean? You've got more crazy L's than
than anything. Like we've before
anyone's ever turned up on you, we've
got things like when that even when went
to he was the first one that went to
your house, was he not
>> years ago? Yeah.
>> He went to your house, you end up
calling police on him. I went to your
house, you called police on me. Jay went
to your house, you call police on him.
>> People No, no, no. People here called
the police on you. I didn't call the
police on J.
>> No, no, no, no. How many times? No, no,
no. It's not only one time I've had What
are you talking about? You was live
streaming. You was live streaming and I
sm and I tried to smash the window. This
is the time. Yeah. The girl went on at
my door when I was 21. I was a little girl.
>> That doesn't matter. You're a grown ass
man. You're a grown ass man. You're a
grown You're a grown ass man. What are
you talking about? 21. 21. You're a
grown ass man.
>> Anyone [clears throat] could do that though,
>> you know. Well, why don't you do it then?
>> I can go for someone younger than me and
and act like, bro, that's not a W. Come on.
>> What do you mean?
>> Seriously. What do you 21 years a grown
ass man? I don't know what you think.
You know, there's a big difference.
Listen, there's a big difference.
There's a big difference if it's like a
12year-old kid against a 14y old kid.
There's a big difference like that. Yes,
that's a big difference. If you're a
grown ass man, 21 to someone that's
maybe 31, that's
a grown ass man.
>> If I was in Okay, so if I was in that
house now, you're telling me you'd come
back on my door
>> if you didn't before? >> Yes.
>> No chance, bro.
>> You're asking me if I would.
>> I'm asking him. I'm asking you if God would.
>> Oh, if he would. I can't speak for I
don't even know him. When I came to this
place, he was just on the verge of like
leaving. So, I don't really know him
like that. I don't I don't know what
he's what he's about or anything like
that. I just know that he he punched up
therapy, though. I know about that. But
>> yeah, [snorts]
>> that's about it.
>> But, bro, these people keep drawing me
out. You don't understand. I did you not
listen to what I said? I don't want no
part of this. It's 2026. I don't want no
>> If you didn't want any part of it yet,
why are you coming online then? Because
this guy keeps [ __ ] talking [ __ ]
>> Well, then go and sort it out then,
>> you know. Yeah. And then what's going to
happen? The same thing again.
>> Well, why do you do things for
validation? Cuz number one, if you're
going to go to places Yeah.
>> Why would you care? Oh, if these people
are going to like say, "Oh, they're
going to be biased and that." Why would
you care? You're going there for
yourself. When I pulled up on some of
these people, I went there for myself. I
would go in there for for people to like
um what do you call it? Uh solidifi like
see if I'm solid or not. I don't care.
But then the whole thing is just Yeah.
But then it's just a waste of time though.
>> Yeah. But you feel the difference is
Yeah. You feel the need to come on here.
Yeah. And tell people your life story
and everything. Then you get upset when
people laugh at you and criticize you
for it. That's what you get. You're
coming on here. It's like a circus act.
You're coming on here like showing all
your ills, just talking crazy about your
own self here, telling people this
madness, and then you expect people to
just sit there and agree with you. That
doesn't make sense.
>> I don't want people to agree with me.
>> Yeah. But when people don't agree with
you like me, like you don't like it and
then you start coming out of madness.
Then then you start talking. You just
start reaching for things all the time.
You start reaching for things. If
someone tells you the truth like even
now that you're not going to go to meet
that Joe, then you get upset and you
know deep down in your head.
>> I'm not going to go.
>> So then why are you But I came in when
you're the one that's calling him out. I
didn't see him like saying anything. I
didn't see him. I didn't see him say
>> if he if he meets me halfway, I'll go.
>> No, that's fair. No, but then that's you
changing the goal post again because
when I first came in, you said that
you're going to go to him. You want him
to tell you if he agrees to it or
whatever. Then he agreed to it and then
you like you said, "Oh, now he's got to
come back on. He's got to come on and
speak to you." Why? Why did people have
to do all this madness like just to just
meet you? It's like he just moved all
the goal post goalpost all the time and
then if he was to come online and he did
just talk like how I am now, then you'll
say something else. There would always
be something else. Then you'll say,
"Okay, not today. Tomorrow because I'm tired."
>> When you when you meeting that prime guy,
>> you even said you wouldn't meet anyone
that I don't talk.
>> Say it again.
>> You even said you won't meet anyone that don't talk.
>> Yeah, of course I said that. What's the point?
>> Yeah, that's what Yeah,
>> but that's me. Yeah. Yeah. I said I
wouldn't meet anyone that don't talk. Of
course not. What am I? But you you're
the one that's calling people out
though. I never called out anyone and
said that I'm going to meet them,
>> you know.
>> So, so you're angry today for what? I
>> keep talking [ __ ] bro. I'm not angry for the
Wait, wait, but I I tuned in. I tuned in
the other day. I don't know if you saw
me or not yet. I tuned in the other day
and you was very angry that day as well.
Like, why are you always angry, man?
It's the festive season. Why are you always
>> I just hate these people. Well, if you
hate them, why do you still entertain
people? Isn't that crazy? Isn't that mad madness? Huh? >> Huh?
>> Isn't that madness?
>> I just hate these people. I just hate that.
>> I just think you know they die. I hope
they all die of cancer and I'm not
that's not even me saying that. But
>> yeah, you shouldn't wish that, man. You
know, you shouldn't you shouldn't wish
that because the first thing that would
happen was might even happen to your
mother and then you're not going to look
after her in it. So,
>> well, I don't care if these people died
of cancer. I hate them, bro. They're all
biased. They're all [ __ ] They all
biased. You know they're biased as well.
>> Not all of them.
>> Well, most of them.
>> All I say, all I say right now, yeah,
it's 2026. Yeah.
>> Listen, listen. If this [ __ ] is going to
continue, Yeah. Just meet someone,
please. Cuz at least if you take a L and
you met someone. Yeah. At least people
will say, "All right, fine." Like, you
had the Even me, I'll clown you about
like taking a L, but then I can't count
you. I can't clown you too much because
I'll say like, you know what I mean? You
finally had the balls to go and actually
get beat up or something. You know what
I mean? the end. Even if you Okay. Okay.
Let me Okay. One second. One second. Let
me let me say something. Yeah. Do you
remember when this was going on a couple
of um years ago? Just listen to me.
Yeah. And we thought, "Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Let's meet someone." And then I've gone,
for example, to meet Bob and we thought,
"Oh, the first time." And then I've gone
a second time. Has it ended?
>> Has it?
>> Can I tell you? Can I tell you
something? No, no, no. Can I tell you
something about being a man? Yeah. Being
masculine. Look, men are not supposed to
be online all the time. Not even online.
Men are just not supposed to be arguing
all the time. That's bit That's female
stuff. It is honestly like you see when
my you see when my oldest child starts
whining to me. Yeah. Do you know what I
tell him? I saying you've been around
your mother too much. Because my dad
didn't raise us like that to be whining.
We just figure stuff out and we sort
things out. If you're not going to sort
things out as men. Yeah. Then why don't
you just why don't you just like call it
quits and just go your separate ways?
That's what I tried to do. That's what I
tried to do all these years with with
Bomb. Like you're not going to meet me.
Okay, cool. So then why don't I just
block you and I don't speak to you and
then leave me alone. But then he would
create all these different accounts just
to try and annoy me. I don't get that. That's [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but do you not get the point I
just made? You don't understand what I'm saying there?
>> I understand what you're saying. But
what I'm saying is why don't like if
you're if this is going to go and you
feel like this is going to go on and you
can't stop it.
>> Meet the guy then. Go and meet him.
>> But then but it's not going to stop.
Even if you do that, that's what I'm
trying to say.
>> Well, at least it's one person, isn't
it? At least you get at least you get
yourself over on one person.
>> But I don't if he's willing to meet you.
I don't know if he's willing to meet you
or not, but I'm saying like,
>> you know what? I'm No. Do you know what
he's going to say?
>> Most of the time it's you start anyways.
You know what? No, no, no, no. Wait.
[ __ ] that. Most of the time it's you
that started. It is. It's is you. If
someone don't agree with you, cuz I
don't think this guy's just trolled you
cuz I've seen these comments.
>> No. He's definitely No, no, no. He's
definitely trolled me, bro. He's
definitely definitely troll me.
>> He's definitely trolled me. He goes on
like his whole channel is dedicated to
trolling me. Like, you don't understand,
bro. I've caught him talking [ __ ] behind
my back on LJ's several times as well.
>> About what? No, no, wait, wait. Cuz when
you say people talking [ __ ] is he
telling the truth about something and
you just don't like it or what?
>> No, he's he is literally talking [ __ ]
He He defends nonslegs and his boyfriend
when I'm arguing. He's continuously
sticking up for them when I'm arguing with them.
>> Okay. Okay. What's it about? Just just
tell me like a gist of like whatever
you're angry about. Like go on.
>> His whole Bro, go on his channel.
>> I don't I can't I don't even know how to
get on to all of that. Like because um
the chat or whatever. Yeah. It doesn't
allow you to click on their channel. I don't know.
>> He's trying to He's trying to troll me,
bro. like being an under you know what
they're like when they're being like
trying to be undercover trolls and [ __ ]
You get it?
>> Yeah. Well, there's many of them that do
that to you and you you don't have a
problem with it.
>> Well, I've got a problem with him. No,
but he's got a big mouth. That's why
because he's got Cuz he keeps telling
people they'll do nothing when he's
never done nothing. He's got a big
mouth. It's not
>> to be fair. He's not lying though, is
he? Like you're you're not going to do anything.
>> I've done more than him.
>> What has he done? He can't even talk.
>> That's because he don't have no problems
with nobody. I don't think
>> he doesn't have any problems with
anything. Why does he need to do something?
You know, and he keeps showing these
fake gambling wins as well. And then
when people call him out on it, he keeps
saying that they're jealous. Bro, no
one's jealous of you. [ __ ] hell. Do
>> you know what I've noticed about this
place? I'll tell you something. Yeah.
You see when you have any unless this is
any to anyone, you see when you have
just anything just anything normal like
for instance, I just heard you talking
about um Jay's watch. Yeah, I know about
watches and I know that a Swiss watch is
elite. Don't matter if it's like the you
can you know you can buy Rolex. Well, I
don't know about now yet, but like about
10 years ago, you could buy like
secondhand Rolexes like that a bit older
for like £1,100. [clears throat] Yeah,
it depends what one I'm talking what
make and all that. But what I'm saying
is, yeah, I just heard you saying
something, oh, 650s um not not Rolex
quality or something.
>> You know why? You know why? Do you not
know, but I can just educate you on
something now. any Swiss watch, it
doesn't matter the the the money, how
much it will cost or anything,
>> you can always get a return on it.
>> Elite watches compared to anything else.
Now, I've seen Monty or I can't
remember, I've seen someone on here
trying to flex her boss watch or some
[ __ ] like that. And those watches are
absolute trash. Those watches are
absolute trash. Yeah. So, if you've got
a Swiss watch, there's always a return
on it. hands. I know the watch that he's
talking about. Now, people do say, I'm
not going to lie, people do say that's
the poor man's Rolex, but that's still
it's still a [laughter] No, no, no, no,
no. But it's it's still a flex, though.
It's still a flex. Yeah. Because Rolex
is that they're saying it's a poor man's
Rolex. It's it's expensive. They're like
20 bags, 30 30 bags and that. So, if
it's a poor man's version of that, then
that's cool. It's like a Chrysler against the
It's not about the watch. It's not about
is he he's coming on here trying to talk
about other people being skinn when he
is the one that is skinned. That's the
only reason I said that.
>> How do you know? No, no, no. I'm Listen.
How do you know? I'm just being
objective. How do you know? Cuz you you
call everyone You call everyone this
like skin. How do you know?
>> How do I know? Okay, I'll tell you how I
know. He continuously begs for money. He
never goes out. He never does anything.
He just sits on YouTube 24/7. He lies
about owning property when he absolutely
does not. Bro, it all adds up
>> to that. I swear a couple years ago to
to be giving credit I swear a couple
years ago he took his family on holiday. No
>> what? Where
>> I can't remember like I swear it was
that he took them on a decent holiday
though his kids and that
>> I don't know
>> maybe. Yeah.
>> Yeah. It was Portugal. No, I swear he
did that. Right. >> Right.
>> Okay. Now I'm a father. Yeah. I took my
kids on holiday last year summer. Yeah.
I know that shit's expensive. That [ __ ]
ain't like it don't matter even if it
was a cheap place. Yeah. in Europe
somewhere. It It's [clears throat]
expensive. It adds up. Do you know what
I'm trying to say? So,
>> but bro, I can I can buy a watch. I can
go on holiday. Do you understand? I can do it.
>> PJ PJ PJ, a day trip on a [ __ ] train
to Belgium is not a holiday.
>> I said, did you just hear what I just
said? I said I can go.
>> You can do that. I'll do it then. I
don't need to do it. See, that's a
Listen, that is a [clears throat] flex.
You see me? When I go on holidays, I
make sure I take mad pictures, videos,
and everything. Yeah. Just to just put
them on my social media. Yeah. Yeah.
Right, bro. The guy went to Vegas for
five nights cuz he couldn't afford to
stay any longer. Bro, make it make sense.
>> Could you afford to go there?
>> Huh? Yeah.
>> If I wanted to. Yeah.
>> Of course I cannot work.
>> Bro, listen. Even if I had no money,
listen to what I'm saying. Even if I had
no money, I have a credit card. See,
it's just basic things like that. Just
basic things like that that you don't
understand. Even if I had no money in my
bank accounts at all, nothing. I have a
bank I have a I have a credit card. more
than 10,000 pound limit on it. So yeah,
of course of course I can still do that.
>> I could buy that watch. I could buy that
>> Well, okay. We'll buy we'll buy something.
All I hear you doing all I hear you
doing is talking about your wardrobe,
your Stone Island wardrobe. And now I
just asked you something in the chat
where I asked you. I said, "Not one of
your Stone Islands or anything." Yeah.
Cost more than even the Pradas that I
showed years ago. Them £800 Prada. You
ain't got not one.
>> They're more than what he's got. They're
>> How do you know?
>> Some people, you know, you know. All
right. Can I tell you another thing?
I've got a boss. Yeah. I've got a line
manager. I swear to God. Yeah. If you
look at him, you would think he's the
biggest [ __ ] The biggest [ __ ] Yeah.
Because he don't he don't wear no nice
clothes. Even these suits that he wears
to work here. They're all crinkled up.
They're not ironed and stuff like that. Right. >> Yeah.
>> Now, do you know where this guy lives?
>> Where do you know you know Shen, you
know, um in Essex? Shenfield.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Do you know what those
houses look like? There are people like
that. I get the point you're trying to make.
>> That's what I'm saying. So, when you're
on here just talking about people's
clothes, not everyone's a closed type of
person. No, not everybody cares about um
>> It's not just about that. Like the go
the guy goes on like he's got money when
he really don't. And I don't care
anyways. I really don't care, bro. I don't care.
>> So, so what's money to you then? Because
at the end of the day, I think just a
normal person that has a regular income.
Yeah. That's not uh what's how do I put this?
If you if you have to what? Wait until
you get a certain time of the month or
whatever just to get your money to do
things. Yeah. Then you're broke. I'm
sorry. I don't care if you me though.
That's not me, bro.
>> Do you have money for a rainy day? >> Yep.
>> I can tell you this like that. I can
tell you like this right now. Yeah. A
few months ago, there was a crack in my
windscreen on my car. Yeah. Now, some
people, if that happened to some other
people, they wouldn't be able to get
that fixed. they would have to leave
that car like kaput and they wouldn't be
able to get that fixed. I paid to get
that fixed there and then. So that's
what I'm talking about. Do you have
money for a rainy day? So when you come
up with emergencies, >> huh?
>> Yeah, I do.
>> I don't think you do.
>> Okay, then that's your opinion.
>> What's the point of asking? If I didn't,
I would say I didn't
>> because I've seen the way how you I seen
the way how you go on. I saw that uh the
thing where he was racing to go to the
bookies for 100 pound or something.
>> You know why? I can I can I I can
explain that. Do you want to know why? I
can explain that. You know why? Because
I weren't going to let them I hate these
people so much. I weren't going to have
let them have the last laugh out of me. >> Who?
>> The people. No, no. What it was is I put
I put the football bet on. Yeah. The one
that I won in it and I left the barcode
on it. So they were going to these
people in this community was going to
try and cash in before me and I was not
going to have that.
>> Fair enough. I didn't even know that. I
didn't even know that. Fair enough.
>> Yeah. So I went at like I went to
Stratford at like 7:30 the morning, bro.
Like I stayed up all night. They weren't
getting that, bro. And I was going too
far. I wouldn't stay up like that's too
I get it.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] that.
>> Nah, bro. I'm not going to have them
like that. You know what I'm saying?
Like, nah, bro. You never hear the last of it.
>> So, so what's your problem with Triple H now?
>> Nothing. He just keeps coming on saying,
"I'm not about I'm not about." And I
just said to him like, "You don't listen listen.
This is what I'm saying about you. He's
not even trolling you. He's just
basically just telling you, listen. If
you know if you've got a track record of
doing something on here, right? And then
you start like for instance the other
day I heard you call out someone you're
going to go somewhere. You didn't end up
going yet and what 3 4 days later now
you're doing the same [ __ ] again. So of
course people's going to say bro just
stop it. I even made a video to you. I
don't know if you saw it but I told you
just stop it. Just behave yourself
>> cuz it doesn't make sense. Yeah. You're
just on here. You're going to keep doing
the same [ __ ] How much times you
calling people out calling people out
and when you don't show up and you don't
weigh in then what? I don't care what
your little troll sympathizers say.
Yeah. When they're like, "Oh, this
person, that person." Listen, they're
trolling you themsel. I hope you know
that. Then them people are trolling you
themselves cuz they know what's what as
well. But they're not then it's being a
yes man. That's even worse being a yes
man. So what I'm telling you is I don't
even think Triple H was even trolling
you. You've just got a track record of
doing this type of behavior. So he's
calling you out on it and saying it.
>> But it doesn't matter what you do
because they're still going to talk
[ __ ] That's what I'm saying.
Do you know why? It's cuz it's you. You
forget all your history.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Whatever. Whatever, man.
>> No, I don't think I think these people
are jealous. I I I might sound
delusional when I say that. Yeah. Like,
I know what you're going to say, but I generally
>> It's not jealousy, but it's I definitely
think they are. >> What?
>> Bro, you're younger. You're better
looking than them.
>> Listen, listen. You're not even young
like that anymore. I don't even know why
you keep saying that.
>> I'm younger than them. I'm younger than
>> Yeah, but you're not even Yeah, but
listen. You're not even young like that
anymore yet. Normally it's women that
get like jealous.
>> Are any of these people in their 20s? No.
>> You're barely Listen.
>> Okay. Are any most people are most
people are most people in his 30? Okay.
You Okay, let me give you an example,
right? Yeah. Tell Jo to come on right
now and show his face.
>> What's the point?
>> It will explain a lot. It will it will
explain a lot. Do you know?
>> Why would I tell [clears throat] to show
his face? No. No. Let me tell you
something. That's the most stupid.
Listen. If you've got anything going on,
you use filters. Listen, listen.
Awesome. You use filters. Come back to
me when you take them filters off.
Anyway, it's gone.
>> Oh, is that the same one you said I was
sing over? Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Come on. Come on, babe. All right.
>> It looked that way.
>> No, I just I just I was listening and I
just heard you saying something about
fat and you calling people fat and I'm
just like, what?
>> You know. >> Yeah.
>> So So you're not going to go meet him
now? I'll give you £100. You know,
honestly, I'll put in your bank account.
>> You You You give me 250 and I'll do it.
>> I'm not giving to What for? What? For
what? For a bit of entertainment for me.
>> The [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Well, no, cuz mate, I'm going to
have to [ __ ] pay for train. I don't
want to waste my own. I've got money. I
>> You suggested it. It's because you
>> and and you know, after I've had this
conversation with you, there'll be
within a week you'll be calling someone
else out again. I guarantee you it.
>> No, I don't. A few days ago, you was
calling someone else out. Yeah. I don't
even know. And then a few then a couple
weeks before that he was calling out
that Smokeoky Bee, I saw your um video,
but I didn't bother to even say anything.
>> Yeah, cuz he he said that he was going
to come in the door. He he actually said
he was going to come in the door. He
actually said that.
>> No, but you
>> That was ages ago. That was ages ago. That wasn't
>> That's Yeah, that's the last one. Yeah,
that's what that's what I that's
he said that he was going to slap me up
in front of my mom in front of his wife.
That's what he said. >> Yeah.
>> And then he [clears throat] never And
then no one said nothing. So, bro, what
>> Oh, he did. He did. And he said that
>> why didn't he I don't I don't know. I
didn't say anything.
>> He said he was going to but
>> he never So, but no one says anything
about that. So, >> yeah.
>> So, so you calm down. Okay. So, why has
no one said
>> why has no one said about all the times
that um L was supposed to meet people
never? That's that's what I mean by
biased. Do you not understand? And
that's what I mean by biased
>> because it's you like you.
>> Oh, another thing, another thing. Oh,
another thing. I got a bone to pick with
you as well. That bouncer thing. Yeah,
you that that's you being biased about
that bouncer as well. You know all the time.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Bounce. Yeah, some
bouncers do. I've got I've got a friend
that's a bouncer. My brother owns a
flipping club. Yeah. That has bouncers
and stuff. So, I know there is obviously
a few bouncers that bend the rules and
they go out their way. But there is some
people out here like for in Okay. It's
like with me. Yeah. Let's me and that bouncer guy.
I'm not going to do anything whilst I'm
at work. I'm always going to be
professional. I'll speak professional
and all the rest of it, right? But if
someone put their hands on me, I'm not
that type of guy that's just going to like
>> accept it. I I will put my job on the
line. If someone put their hands on me,
and there's no reason to because I don't
deal with the public in my job. Yeah.
But I'm just saying if someone else was
to put their hands on me, I would
probably lose my job because I'm not
going to have it. And that's me being
stupid. Normal person would not put
their hands on their back. They just
call the police and wait for that to get
resolved. Right now, what I'm saying is
you see that bouncer and I've got
friends that are bouncers, so I know
what I'm talking about.
>> They're not going to they're going to
try and diffuse a situation. Now, if
you're getting rude and you're talking
about suck your mom and all that,
>> I looked at that guy's eyes yet and I
swear I'm not just saying this. I'm not
I promise I'm not just saying this. It
was a thing where he he kind of wanted
you to touch him. If you had touched
him, then that gives him every right to
defend himself and mash you up. And I
promise you, he would have matched you
up because number one, I'll tell you one
thing. Most bouncers, I'm not saying all
of them are tough, but most bouncers,
they have been trained to restrain
people. They have been trained um
especially how to grips people up just
like how the police has been trained to
subdue you. Same thing as as those
bouncers. Yeah. So, I know for a fact I
know for a fact he he was too calm and
he was too, you know, he was he was not
scared. I'm telling you, someone scared
of him either. I weren't scared of him
>> But you're the one that was laughing off
to me kiss you. No, because you kissed
his teeth on me. I said, "Don't kiss
your teeth on me."
>> Yes. Because when you're at job, when
you're at your job and you're being
professional and someone telling you,
"Suck your mom." It takes so much,
what's the word? It takes so much.
>> It takes so much restraint. It takes so
much restraint to have to hear that.
>> You think someone for no reason?
>> If I was him and someone told me my mom
knowing full well they haven't put their
hands on me, I would have to accept that
and I'll probably kiss my teeth too cuz
it's you're taking started it. Yeah. But
he started it.
>> It doesn't matter. The problem is
>> that's another thing. But you do realize
that contradicts everything um about the
bus thing then. What you're saying
contradicts that then is it?
>> No, it doesn't. It's it's different
scenarios. The the bus guy was
different. Yeah. And he would lose his
job as well though. Don't get
>> different. People react differently.
Listen listen to what I'm saying. People
react differently to the competition.
>> No, but he was that security guy was
definitely 100% worried about each job.
I'm telling you this right now.
>> Okay. Okay. Let me let me tell you
something. Can I just mention another
thing? Can I bring another factor that
contradicting. You're contradicting.
>> Let me let me bring another factor. The
security guard contradicting yourself.
>> You never know. You see that security
guard? He might be already on like a
yellow card or something. Yeah. Because
or a disciplinary because he's done
something else a couple weeks ago to
someone else. You don't know these
things. You know what I'm trying to say?
>> Okay. But people Okay. Okay. Listen. But
people done the same thing with Kenji as
well when he was at work and he called me out.
>> Yeah. No, no, no. I backed you with that
one. Yeah. He did. He called you out,
right? And then you end up going there
and then all of that. Yes, that's fair.
But there was another time when you
mouththed off to someone in a job. Uh I
think he the guy was gambling. He was
behind a screen and because you lost,
you was getting rude to him and you're telling Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But that's what I'm
saying. But that's what I'm saying. It's
a regular occurrence with you doing
these things. Yeah. I don't think you're that
>> I can tell you about the bouncer. I can
tell you about the bouncer thing. It was
a Weber spoon. Yeah. I went to walk in.
He asked me for ID. I said, "You're
asking me for ID, bro? Really?" And he
kissed his teeth out here. And it's not
even one of them scam. That's not how
that's not how you're breaking that
story down a bit. Like that's not how it happened, bro.
>> Why would he kiss the teeth? Why? Why
would he just give you attitude straight
away when you did like
>> Cuz I said to him, "Okay." Cuz I said to
him, "Why you asking?"
>> Because I was saying to him, "Do I not
look of age or something?" I was saying
that, "What the hell?"
>> Yeah, I saw the video. Yeah. Yeah, I saw
the video. And that's why you ask his
teeth. He kissed his teeth. Yeah. When
you insulted his mother because he took
restraint from him. That's That's him
restraining himself. No, bro. Before
that, he did kiss his teeth. Why would I
for no reason? That don't make sense.
Say it again.
>> No, he kissed his teeth before that as well.
>> Oh, maybe he did. But I'm just saying,
yeah, the part where I saw him kiss his
teeth as well after when you told him to
suck his mom. And that just takes
restraint cuz in in my culture, we know
what that means. If you go to jail Yeah.
and you tell a boy suck his mom, he
better like he has to [ __ ] you up. And
if he doesn't, the whole jail will get
on him. Like that's what I'm trying to
say. People, we know what that means in
in in my world where where we're from.
Like that's what you know what I'm
trying to say. Ask anyone.
>> I think Yeah, but if that guy was white,
you wouldn't have said nothing, bro.
Come on. Be real. You were loved. You were love.
>> What do you mean? I wouldn't have said
nothing. How many times have I stuck
[laughter] up? How many times have I
stuck up for people that's wet when
you're chatting [ __ ] to them? What are
you talking about? You just like to
bring You personally
like to bring the guy in the book. You
never backed him up. I'm not even trying
to [ __ ] You never backed up the guy.
>> Cuz I don't have time to back every
single person. But when I see something
foul what you're doing, like for
instance, when you was in a park
screaming at that girl because she
didn't want to let off and give you give
you give you her
>> Yeah, but that's a woman. That's a
That's a woman. Yeah, I told you about
you didn't go on about it like that. You
>> Yeah, but I told you about yourself and
you still you still had a problem with
me when you went to go and meet those
Patel girls. Yeah. All the way in
Nottingham that day and I end up
breaking into your house myself. Yeah.
Like that was me. That wasn't because I
fancy anyone or anything like that. I
just thought you're a cow.
>> You just wanted to show off.
>> It's not about showing off. No, I wanted
to show you that you're you're a punk
for that. Like you only a [ __ ] does
stuff like that. You go all the way to Nottingham
>> to try and threaten some females.
>> I was in Nottingham, you idiot. No, no.
You went there for them. No, no, no. I
remember that fully. Listen, listen.
Don't try Listen. This is what you
always do. You always You always try to
change the narrative every single time.
And you went there specifically for
them. Yeah. And then you changed your
mind and you done something else after.
Right. So, I told you when you went
there for them, you forgot the week
before, I already broke into your house
and I chased you out your own house. So,
you know, when you're telling these
people, "Oh, yeah, you only smashed the
window. I smashed the window with you in
it and you ran out." Yeah. You abandoned
your house and I was in there. Like,
what are you talking about? the first
time and then the second time when you
went to Nottingham which was a week
later. Yeah. For the Patels. I told you
I wrote on your I wrote on your YouTube
thing. I said, "Oh, you're going there
for so you're going for females. I'm
coming to your house again tonight
then." And then then you said to me then
Yeah. Then you laughed at me and you
said, "Yeah, I'm all talk." Yeah. And
then I came to your house middle of the
night, right? And I stood over your
tenant and I took his [ __ ] Remember
>> you get a lot you get a lot of white
knights in in the clubs as well, though.
You actually do. You get
>> it's not about white knights. It's end
of day. Yeah. At the end of the day, we
all know that females are the I'm not
trying to be
>> No, I've said it before like people
said, "Oh, about women." I said, "I'll
talk to them how I want." I've told you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. That's cool. But if I'm in
public and I'm looking right and I'm
seeing someone I'm seeing I'm seeing a
grown man with a fully grown beard.
Yeah. Trying to mouth off and just like
intimidate a fem. I'm going to look at
her body language. The first thing I'm
going to do, the first thing I'm going
to do is I'm going to look at her body
language. Yeah. And she looks like she's
absolutely [ __ ] it and scared. I'm
stepping. I don't care. It's got nothing
to do with white now. It could be the
fattest ugliest girl on
>> earth. What was the What was the Patel
doing? [clears throat]
>> What was the Patels doing? What was the
>> They're winding you up.
>> There you go then. So, they were doing
something with them, weren't they? They
weren't innocent, were they?
>> Yeah. They're winding you up. But take
it. It's the internet. You w me up all the time. >> Yeah.
>> Okay. So, why? So, you should have took
it when Shagger was like calling you out
then. So, then you I can say the same
thing to you.
>> No, no, no, but no, no, but that's
different. See, that's not a female
though. Yeah. He was calling me. He was
he was being derogatory talking about
slavery and all this other madness. So I
said, "All right, fine. I'm going to
come to your territory and see if you
can say it to my face. And if I don't
get touched, then that means you're the
[ __ ] then because I'm I'm coming to him
in it." And and nothing happened to me.
So that's that's just all it was. I
don't keep going on about that. I don't
even talk about it.
>> I don't talk about that. >> Huh?
>> I'm just saying is it?
>> Yeah. But see see the difference here.
And people [clears throat] Nobody ever
mentions that with me, right? But do I
come on here? I don't need validation
for it. I know what happened. I know
what I did. Like just like Fruit Kings,
I know what I did and all that. I don't
need I don't need people to say, "Oh
yeah, he did he didn't do this or
whatever." But you you need you're
saying people are biased. You're not
going to jail after you called him out
because people are biased. So you're
that means you're you're living on here
for people trolling. That's what you're basically saying.
>> Not really.
>> You are.
>> You know,
>> you are because I guarantee you in a in
a week or two you'll be calling someone
else out again because this is your
pattern. You always do. You can't help yourself.
>> I could never I could never own a black
guy and you would admit it. Put it that way.
>> What do you mean? Because every time
every time you do do it's not even a
black guy. It's anytime you do do
something to most people or whatever.
It's it's always in the most serious
coward cowardous way. It's all the time. [clears throat]
>> Okay. Okay. Back to the bus driver. Back
to that bus driver. Yeah. When he was
mouthing off. Yeah. You you you said
something about, "Oh, we missed our bus
stop." Right. Then he got pissed off
with you. He was probably angry at work
for whatever reason. He stressed out.
Yeah. And he told you about yourself.
And then what did you do? You was very
calm and quiet when you was on the bus
and there's no escaping, right? Then the
minute the doors open, that's when you
called him a name and you ran. You
That's when that's that's the type of
[ __ ] that I call out. Like, how can you
do that and stand on here and try How
can you be on here and then try to act
like you're this big tough guy when
you're doing [ __ ] like that? You think I
I don't do stuff like that?
>> Yeah. And if I went back on him, people
were just going to say that he's going
>> If you went back on him No. No. If you
went back on him and he end up beating
you up anyways, I would laugh at you for
getting beaten up. But like I'll say I
respect it cuz you didn't run. You know
what I mean? I don't respect people that
run. I can't like no cuz I'm not being
funny or anything but like
>> I've had things done to me. I've had
things done to me and I didn't run at
the carnival like years ago when I was
younger and I didn't run. I like you
know what I'm trying to say. I got
stabbed everything. I did not run.
That's what I'm trying to tell you. I
never left my friends. I don't run.
That's just what it is. And any of my
friends ran what? Like nonsense.
>> I just don't but he didn't actually
physically run from you. He just didn't
turn up. Yes, he did. He went running to
the police station when I was live.
>> Yeah. He didn't physically run. He
didn't see you and then run off, did he?
Like he just didn't turn up. That's what happened, right?
>> And he went running to the police.
>> Yeah. I think that's coward. Yeah, that
is coward. Of course it is. Like you Why
you even ask me that? You know what I'm
going to say.
>> Yeah. There you go.
>> Did you just bring that up cuz you want
me to say that? Yeah.
>> Talking about cowards. You're just talking about
>> any man on here that's calling police
for including yourself cuz I don't know
why you call talk about other people
calling police cuz you call the police yourself.
>> But am I am I doing videos about you
every day? Am I talking about you every
day? No, I'm not. There's a
>> difference. Difference.
>> Not every day. But you do you do do your little videos?
>> No, he doesn't. No.
>> Or or there's times when uh you'll come
on here and then you'll just bring me up
for no reason into your little
arguments. Like today for instance, you
arguing with J because you was on my my
channel the other day.
>> Yeah. So, but if you But why bring me up
if you know you're not going to say
nothing to my face? Like that's that's
that's the type of [ __ ] that you get
angry at Shortn for doing it cuz Shorty
brings you up just discussing the
situation, what not, right?
>> No. And then you get upset at him. Huh?
>> No. He literally does it all day, every
day. He harasses every day.
>> There's no difference to what you're
doing as well. That's how I feel when
you're saying my name. That's exactly
how I feel when you're saying my name.
>> Have I got a channel of you? Yeah.
Posting about you every day.
>> No, you don't. No, you don't. But but I
still It's still the same thing. Like,
why you why you talking crazy about me
when you're the one that runs? And like,
you know what I mean? You're the one
that actually runs. I'm not the one that
runs off. You've never come you you know
when you talk about, oh yeah, you
>> This is what I'm saying with these This
is what I mean with these biased people.
One second. He goes for nonslegs because
he's a weak target. This is what this is
why I don't waste my time on you people.
This is because you're biased. That's
why that is honestly, bro. Why I don't
waste my time. That is why I don't waste
>> Who said that?
>> That's why I don't waste my time.
>> Wait, he just said that. He said it.
>> Trip. That's why people don't waste
their time. You think it's because
people scared, but they're not. They're
not. Like you they're not. They're
really not. They're really really not.
>> Am I lying though?
>> That's That is funny though.
>> It's not funny though because
>> No, but no. The thing is that's why people
>> I will I will I will um elaborate on
that though. I will tell you what you do
is you do go for how do I put this for
instance you know when you're like M
>> Hold on hold on wasn't he wasn't he
wasn't he wasn't he pretending to meet
people for fights >> events >> legs
>> yeah one time years ago
>> no he done it multiple times he done it
>> when you talking about that time in Leighton
>> he's done it in Leighton he's done it in
Tottenham he's done it in a few places
>> he done it in he done it in May >> when ages ago.
>> What? For who? You,
>> bro. I need to say Yeah. And I don't
give a [ __ ] if he's a weak target. If I
see him, I'll smash his face in. There's
no weak target about it. I don't give a
[ __ ] I will smash your ugly face on
whether you're a weak target or not. I
don't give a [ __ ]
>> Listen, I'll be honest. Yeah. I know
that you would actually meet him. Yeah.
There's a few I've said it before. I'm
not going to like be biased about I'm
always an objective person. I'm fair.
Yeah. There is a few people on here that
I know that you would actually meet, but
the majority of people you're not
meeting. Like if you if you got an
inkling that people would actually happy
to meet you whenever you said you're not
going to meet them.
>> I actually I actually wouldn't meet
anyone on it. To be fair, I actually would.
>> Yeah, but you would. You're saying that now because
>> No, honestly, I wouldn't.
>> But you're saying that now why can't But
then like you you always you're the one
that calls out people though.
>> Yeah, but I actually wouldn't. That's
what I'm saying. I
>> So you wouldn't meet Wait, hold on.
Wasn't that uh what's his name? Prime.
Wasn't he coming down to London a few
months ago or something? See, this is
how a lot later I
>> That's what he said. That's what he
>> Yeah. What happened? What happened to
that? You said no. No. Cuz I remember
how you was going on that time. You said
you're going to beat him and I remember
you were saying you saying London, happy
new year, brother. Hope you and your
family have a safe one.
>> Just a quick one, London, cuz I don't
want to be long. He's got a point when
it comes to Shawn, right? Sean is the
biggest [ __ ] on this community. Right. He He
>> No, I know that. I never disagreed.
Listen, I never disagree.
>> London cuz I'm I'm in a rush. He trolls
PJ hard and PJ the reason why he trolls
you hard because don't kick me out
because you can't handle a [ __ ]
opinion you lefty right because the
reason why he trolls you hard PJ and
I've had this conversation with you many
[ __ ] times is because you keep
reacting to him. No, no,
>> you do, PJ. You react.
>> Okay. So, he But he's reacting to me as
well. So, it doesn't make sense. It's
the same conversation. It's the same
It's the same thing,
>> PJ. People troll you cuz you can't
handle an opinion. The reason why he's
trolling you is cuz you keep reacting to
him. If you stop reacting to him, he
will eventually give up.
>> No. London Taylor, he'll never stop. No.
No. No. What do you think, London
Taylor? I don't think I think PJ London,
give your opinion. Give your opinion on
this. You reckon you reckon non legs and
redstone will ever stop? Even if you
ignore it? I don't think they will, bro.
Be honest. Be honest. Be honest.
>> Yeah, but yeah, but you got to
understand something, PJ. You're the
present on here. You're the present.
You're the one. [clears throat]
>> PJ, you're the You're the one that gives
us everything what we need on here.
>> No. No. If there's no you, Listen,
listen to what I'm saying. If there's no
you, there's no watching this. Is a low
life idiot, but sits in his bedit all
day wanking over you. And you should be
the one who should be laughing at him
that he's got an obsession over you, but
instead you're getting rattled over it.
>> I don't get rattled over. I don't get
rattled over him. I don't even respond
to him to it.
Respond to the clown.
>> I don't even respond to the clown.
>> You do, Pete.
>> No, but listen. Yeah, but no, no, no,
no. Al, I don't think they would ever
stop. I think they would [ __ ] with you
about that. I don't think they would
stop. I don't think they would, bro. I
don't think they would.
>> Why don't you just unsubscribe to them
and don't watch them? London's been
trying good advice for the past hour, mate.
>> No, it's true though. If No, but that is
true. If you don't if you don't like
like them or whatever, you just
>> PJ I don't watch Banger cuz Banger goes
on about me. I don't watch Winchester
disc cuz he's got an obsession. I'm not
subscribed to these [ __ ] They can talk
about me 24/7, [laughter] PJ, and I
wouldn't give a [ __ ] So why are you
bothered what Sean says about you?
>> I'm not bothered.
>> You are talking about him being a [ __ ]
PJ? No, I brought him up because he's a
[ __ ] That's what I was That's why I
brought him up.
>> Always rattled over long um um nons you
want to call him. >> Never.
>> Yes, you are, PJ. Stop lying.
>> You are rattled over a fiber cable and
it's beyond tragic.
>> Every time I come on here, PJ, you're
always you're always raging every single
time I've come on here.
>> I'm going to just don't like these people. Simple.
>> If you don't like them, why do you entertain everybody?
>> Most of them. Most of them.
>> Listen, listen, listen. You come on here.
>> Yeah. Like, you come on here and you
give them a show. So, how could you say
you don't like You like the attention.
You like the [ __ ] You definitely do. 100%.
>> I don't. You do.
>> I don't. I don't.
>> You do. It's that It's that It's that my
girl. Yeah. Every once in a while, she
wants a madness. She wants arguments
every once in a while when she has when
when things are running too smoothly
sometimes, she actually stirs [ __ ] up.
Yeah. To try and get something out of
me. Yeah. to give it a bit more of a of
entertainment for you're just the same.
Like you need madness on here sometimes.
>> Yeah, but I come on here to talk to the
decent people, you know.
>> No, you don't. Well, why can't you find
Don't you have friends? Why don't you
chat to them?
>> Of course, I've got friends, but this is
funny as well.
>> That's what I'm saying. You You got more
friends than anybody, right? Why don't
you go and chat to them? Why are you coming online?
>> Okay. Why Why are you acting like Why
are you being sarcastic, bro, when these
people on YouTube 24/7? Do they have
>> you say you've got more friends than all of us?
>> Have they Well, have they got friends
then? who I don't know their lives. I
No, no, no. See, I can make an
assumption. Listen, listen. No, no, no.
I can make an assumption and tell you
that many of them don't. And obviously
like that. Yeah, clearly. But, but I
don't know all of them to really like be
100% accurate about that. From how
judging from how people move on here, I
don't think a lot of people got
anything. But it is what it is,
>> you know.
>> But when when you Huh.
>> Yeah. I'm just saying. Yeah. That's what
I say as well.
>> Yeah. But you you're not actually 100%
certain though, are you? >> Well,
>> the reason why I say it No. No. The
reason why I say it, yeah, is cuz I
personally I find it crazy that like
someone can dedicate so much of their
life just trolling people every day.
Like I get it sometimes. That's what I mean.
>> I don't understand. I personally
couldn't like maybe it's just me. I
couldn't personally sit down behind a
screen making mad accounts and stuff and
just trolling dudes every day like no that's dead
>> for years. I can't. I've got too much
things I need to do like in a day and
stuff for me to do that.
>> What? So, you're referring to Red Star.
>> I'm just saying, but don't try Listen,
don't try to bring in names for me to
try and seem like I'm helping you. Yeah.
Don't Don't do that. I know your tactics
by now. Stop it.
>> Well, when you said that Well, when you
Well, when you said that, the first
person that come to mind was Red Star. >> So,
so my bad. It's true, isn't it?
>> But and it's not even that. They've been
doing it for years as well. So that's another thing.
>> Yeah. But in the same time, you're
you're just as bad as them in in like
when you think about it because you sit
around, you call people out, you say the
maddest things to people. So I kind of
don't blame them as well at the same
time. It's just that I don't have the
time to keep to keep to stay angry all
the time. You know what I mean?
>> I I I don't blame them cuz you forget
maybe nowadays you've been a bit more
softer cuz you've been nicked a couple
times now and things has happened. Yeah.
But I mean like when I first came around
the first two years or something, you
forget the type of madness that you were
saying to people.
But I thought this year would have been
different. I thought it would have been
different people. That's why I was
planning to get off cuz I thought it was
going to be different people. You know,
>> you was never planning to get off. You
can't leave this place. You will We're
going to see you turn great,
>> bro. These people can't even take a day
off of YouTube. >> Huh?
>> Yeah. These people can't even take a day
off of YouTube, bro.
>> But But can you?
>> Yeah. I've took weeks off YouTube
without even going on it. They can't.
>> Yeah, but you're taking weeks off, but
you're secretly watching the background. No. >> No.
What you when you take the time off
here, what are you doing in that time?
>> I'll just go on my other channel.
>> Well, you totally avoid these people.
So, you're not even saying
>> other channel other channel other
channel. Reddit go out just different
things and I'll come back after like
two, three weeks. I've done it before.
So, I need to ask you why can't these
people take a day off YouTube? That's
the real question.
>> Listen to me. Yeah. All right. Let me
tell you something. All right. Was you
around Christmas time?
>> What? In London? No, like on YouTube.
>> No, just just after just after just a
few days ago.
>> So before So before I went to my
sisters. Yeah, I went I went live to
like a little test. I went live. Yeah, I
kicked the live button. Then I went
downstairs. I left my phone upstairs in
it. I made a tea. I walked up and these
people was on YouTube and I was like, "Hold on."
>> Yeah, but why does that concern you?
Yeah, but why does that Why would that
concern you though? If if that's the
case, then Fair enough. No, no. If
that's the case, then fair enough. But
why do you need to test out to see if
people are on YouTube after you not?
Okay. So, so 2 weeks, 3 weeks before
Christmas yet, these people is making it
their goal to try and ruin my Christmas.
You don't You don't understand it cuz
you're not on it, bro. Two, [snorts]
three weeks before Christmas, these
people are worse. Have you noticed that
before? Have you never noticed that? You
ain't noticed, have you?
>> No. No. I remember your last Christmas you like.
>> No, even before that. No, no, no. Bomb
used to do it as well. Don't you
remember around December time? They
don't, bro. They're worse. All year.
What are you talking about? It ain't
just for December time. It's all year round.
>> No, but it's worse in December. No wor.
What are you talking about? There's no
worse in December.
>> Not one single month. That's That's
different. It's every month, every week.
>> But it's worse in December. But it's
worse around Christmas time. That is
true. Yeah. They don't They're worse.
They're worse, bro. Like they It's like
their goal is to try to ruin people's
Christmas. You don't get it. You don't
get it. You don't get it, bro.
>> No, not really.
But they tried. But they did try. It was
like they oh your family hate you.
You're going to be alone Christmas. They
were saying madness. They weren't
stopping as well. There were like 30 accounts of them,
>> you know. Oh yeah, that's another thing.
So you see when you bang on about
people's families and people don't have
this and poor people don't have that. I
promise you right now. Yeah. I don't
know a single one of my friends or
family or anything like that. Yeah. That's like
had no Christmas. Like their family's
abandoned them for Christmas. I don't
know anyone that's that's happened. No,
on here it has. On here it has.
>> Yeah. To you.
>> What do you mean to me, bro? I was I was
with family Christmas. What about
>> your last Christmas? I'm talking about
last Christmas. Yeah. Yeah. Last
>> That's madness. No. No. But even for me
to even like that don't even sound
normal. Like I swear my is that that's
not even a punishment. It might I don't
even think if you know what if my family
done something to like that to me, I
don't think I'd ever even chat to them
again. Like that's just that's gone too
far. I don't care what a punishment it
is. Yeah. That's gone too far. I wasn't
I wasn't Yeah, but I was with people
Christmas. I was with people.
>> I'm not talking about this Christmas.
I'm talking about the last one.
>> Yeah, even last Christmas I was with
people, not just not them.
>> Oh, okay.
>> So, I wasn't by myself Christmas, I was
still with people, just not them. But
still, what I'm saying is these people
these people was trying to ruin
Christmas. Bro, you don't you don't
understand what I'm trying to say, do you?
>> I do understand, but at the same time is
they can only ruin it. They can only
ruin it if you allow them to. Because at
the end of the day, Yeah. You give
people, you give everyone on here a form
of entertainment, even including myself.
Like sometimes, this is what I'm trying
to tell you. Like now it's been
entertaining for me because if I was
just sitting around watching you all the
time, I'll be so bored very quickly. But
every now and again, I come back to
watch your stupidness. Yeah. And it's
actually fun for me. Like now I actually
enjoy it because seeing you kick off,
right, it puts it puts a smile on my
face when you just saying craziness.
Listen PJ, I've told you before. I know
for the most part. Yeah. Like you don't
even mean what you're saying. Like it's
just anger for you and that's how you
get your anger.
>> I mean it. I mean it.
>> You don't PJ. Okay. Okay. So if Red Star
was to go to your door Yeah. just
randomly like I don't know.
>> It would never happen.
>> No, I'm just saying though. If he was to
go to your door randomly in the next
week to your house. Yeah. What are you
going to do about it?
>> Would I know it's him? How would I know
>> Exactly. You wouldn't. You know what I mean?
>> He told me it's him. I'd beat him. I I'
I'd stick on him if I knew it was him.
>> PJ, I just think you say these things
here because you know it's not going to happen.
>> Okay, bro. Okay.
>> I don't I don't think you would actually do that,
>> but he's never ever going to do
anything. So, I don't even know why.
Like, it's [clears throat] it's it's
hypothetical, isn't it?
>> Yeah, but again, you don't you don't
even really know where people are as
well at the same time. It might be too
far for him. He can't be
>> I've been all over the country calling
people out. Come on now.
>> You know better than me.
>> I told you about the Newcastle and
Liverpool thing. Yeah. All right. I'll
give I'll give you the other one. Um,
who's the other person you went up north
for? Oh, yeah. There's Bomb, isn't it? >> Okay.
>> I'll give you that.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Trevor Dawson, Bomb. I went
to Terry. He didn't turn up the second
time. Even though he called me out, I
didn't just randomly turn up, bro.
There's been a few of them. Mark Samson.
>> Uh, yeah. Yeah, they're legitimate ones
that you've mentioned. But who else?
That Guna Chan one. Yeah, you did. You
didn't go there. Okay. You did go there,
but you was at I remember I phoned you
that day. Yeah. You was at home when
that video went up.
>> Oh, I know. You're trolling me behind
that account as well.
>> What account?
>> That you accused of being Joker. You
know that um Nicola account?
>> That's Oh, stop it.
>> Well, who is it? Cuz it ain't Joker.
Well, it ain't Joker.
>> What the
[ __ ] are you talking about?
>> The account that said Yeah, there was an
account that said you can't come off of
YouTube and um deprive Greavvesy off of
content. The poor [ __ ]
>> That was you.
>> How does that mean? How does that mean?
>> But it wasn't Joker cuz I've spoke to
Joker in it. He come on here a couple
weeks ago on the Hangouts.
>> Okay. But
>> who who is it? Because they know
>> I don't know the account that you're
talking about to be honest with you. But like
>> they know too much. They know too much.
>> So So it's got to be me.
>> Maybe it's like someone from your family
or something. I don't know.
>> It's nothing to do with me. I'll tell
you that. No. If if I'm going to come on
here, I definitely would just use my
actual account. Like that's just
>> that says and they was like, "Oh." in
the account said, "Oh, did you touch
Isabella's boobies and stuff?"
>> Who is that?
>> Yeah. What do I say? Stupid [ __ ] like that.
>> So, how are you blaming me?
>> It's weird, is it? It is weird.
>> I don't say I don't say like nursery stuff,
I will agree with you, PJ. Sean is a
[ __ ] [ __ ] He's a grass, right?
Because I I was meant to say that early
night in the hangouts. Sean with Lond
London. Sean trolls PJ. PJ's gone to is
basically tried to confront him and
Sean's phoned the police like a [ __ ]
now I've I've I've already spoken to the
police about Sean and I said look do do
some proper police [ __ ] work stop
wasting your time with this [ __ ]
autistic weasel what's got no [ __ ]
life spends all day on the internet
trolling this [ __ ] intel ma right
[laughter] know sort your [ __ ] self
out now I have actually spoke to said do
I said do some real police work and Stop
[ __ ] around this incel from London
who's got no life, who spends all his
time at the granny station, the social
club dancing with pensioners cuz he can't fing
me. Yeah, he said he got a [ __ ] last
month and his dick was hurting for three days.
>> Well, he was bragging on about his
misses and his misses got [ __ ] false
teeth. I can even put the photo on my
[ __ ] communal picture, man. The teeth are like
>> Timmy Timmy's done his Timmy's done his
bollocks in um Global Jaw Roulette.
>> Sean don't gamble. He can't even leave his
>> No, you didn't. I said you, Timmy. You,
>> I don't talk about people doing their
balls in PJ when you've been ranting and
raving for two and a half hours. Rattled
over a fiber cable.
>> Timmy still plays with that.
>> PJ, you need to sort your life out,
mate. You rattled over [ __ ] Jo. You
rattled all these people. These people
don't matter, PJ. They're not
>> PJ. I was your age when I joined this
little sector here, you know. I'm just
letting you know.
>> I mean, I mean, London, don't get me wrong.
>> I was your age. I'm 34 to get angry.
Hey, listen. Listen, LT, do you remember
that Ben Furby account?
>> Yeah, he lives he lives in Birmingham.
>> But you know, you know him.
>> Wait, he's from London. Yeah.
>> Yeah, he he said listen. He said two
years ago. Yeah. New Year's Day. He
said, "Same people, same story. See you
next year." And he'd come off for a
year. And he come back. I was dead.
>> But But PJ, right? But PJ, everybody on
here has tried to give you good advice, including
>> Same people, same story. That's true.
I've even heard Bon trying to give you
good advice before. I've even heard
>> of YouTube PJ
>> give me good advice about what he's about.
>> I've heard him I have even even before
like everyone trolls you sometimes.
Yeah. But I mean I've have heard people
on here even muscle I've heard him even
try to give you advice one time a few
times actually just about like girls and
how you're moving and how you're winging
>> it's the same every day.
>> But PJ but PJ look it is the same people
every day. Is it
>> PJ come and meet me in Penge? But listen
PJ people every day.
>> PJ, but you're But PJ, it's the same
people every day, but you're the one
who's entertaining it. You're the one
who's obsessed with it.
>> We need a mix up. Do you know who Do you
understand? You need You need a mix up.
You need a mix, you know, like a mix.
>> Who gives a [ __ ] if it's the same people
every day? Who gives a [ __ ] if
properties? Who gives a [ __ ] if Banger
can't get a credit card? Who gives a
[ __ ] if Dusty calls everyone obsessed
because he's a leftwing [ __ ] [ __ ]
What? Can't handle an opinion? Who gives
a [ __ ] PJ? Who gives?
Why you mad that a Why you mad that a
guy's got a watch? That's a nice watch,
you know. I'm not even going to lie.
It's a nice watch for the price as well.
It's quite It's quite good.
>> It was £640. [laughter] >> So,
you know, you know, you know, you know,
my son for this Christmas. Yeah. Hey,
hey, my son bought my son bought me, my
son bought me a 9 karat gold um bracelet
thing. Yeah. It's 9 karat gold.
Obviously, that's not worth like, you
know, let me not talk that loud, but
it's not it's not worth that much. Yeah, I
>> he keeps talking over people. That's why
it's cuz he keeps talking over people in it.
>> You know when you
>> Yeah, he talks over people in it.
>> Um maybe he just can't hear cuz I
couldn't hear a lot of the stuff.
>> Do you watch them? Do you watch them kick streamers?
>> Yeah, I do. You know, sometimes I do.
Yeah, that's just You know what? I'll be
honest with you. This is why I'm bored
of like I've been bored of this place
for a while cuz a couple
>> who do you watch who do who do you watch
on the kick?
>> Um I watch what's it sometimes now. You
know what? Cuz my son, my oldest son,
yeah, he watches um like he's a fan of
the ice show speed guy in it. So I watch
some of his streams. It's quite lit.
It's I'm not going to lie. It's quite
good. There's him. [clears throat] Then
there's another one called Aiden Ross
that I watch. Um who else? I don't
actually Ross is not on Twitch. I think he's on
Matthews, isn't it?
>> Yeah, I do. I do. I do. I watch um H H H
H H H H H H H H H H H H H H H H H H H H
H H H H H H H H H H H H H H H H H HS was
it HSI or whatever?
>> Yeah, that's the black guy.
>> Yeah, makes
>> you know what they Bro, do you know what
they do to them? They troll them next,
bro. They get them slaughtered and [ __ ]
You have you seen
>> Bro, listen listen. Yeah, this guy,
>> bro, listen. He was getting his haircut
in it. Yeah, this Ed Matthews was
getting his haircut in it. Yeah. And
they said, "Oh, we're getting the
police. We're getting the police." At
any moment you're waiting for the police
to pass through the [ __ ] noise. You
know when you know when you're lying
back like getting your beard shaved up
and closing your eyes at that and you're
expecting any [laughter] police to come in.
>> That's what I'm saying.
>> Like this is for anyone that if you're
going to be that bored. Do you know
what? Even let me let me give some game
to some people. Yeah. Because like just
being on your [ __ ] like I'm not going to
lie. I feel like I lose brain cells from
watching you sometimes. That's why I just deliberately
>> I lose brain cells when I go on Lord J.
I lose brain cells.
>> There's a there's a channel Yeah. called
Diary of a CEO. I've been binging on
that most lately because then it's like
a little podcast thing for maybe an hour
or two. I just sit sometimes even at
night time and whatever and I just and I
just listen to it when I'm going to work
and I I just put my earphones in. I just
listen to it. That is insightful. Do you
know what I mean? Like if you really
want to like get some
>> He Yeah, he lives in Brentwood. It's not
That's not far Brenwood. No,
>> my oldest My oldest brother lives in Brentwood.
>> I know somebody used to live there.
>> Yeah, I've been there. Yeah, that's
that's not far from you.
>> I know.
>> That's that's where they filmed the um
the uh Only Ways Essex. >> Really? >> Yeah.
>> Was it Sugar Hut or whatever it's
called? Yeah. Yeah. [laughter]
>> Would you bang that Autumn? Be honest.
>> I don't know who you're talking about. >> Autumn.
>> I Listen, when you mentioned this name
earlier, I really I don't know who
you're talking about.
>> Let me show you. Let me show you.
Oh, is that her there? Yeah.
>> Yeah. Does that get your pecker hard?
>> Um, I don't know, man.
>> You must know her.
>> I don't know. I'm I'm What would you
want me to say?
>> Would you bang her or not?
>> He looks like a regular girl that I see
all the time.
>> Yeah. So, would you would you bang her or not?
>> Would you?
>> No. Would you?
>> I don't know. I haven't seen her
properly. I don't even know. I don't
don't talk like you know what I mean.
>> It's not about knowing there's more to
it. Listen, you see at my age right now.
Yeah. Like number one, I'm not single
anyways. But number two, there's more to
it than just looking at people now. I've
gone through women when I was younger
and stuff of banging.
>> I'm not talking I'm talking about a
booty call, bro. I'm not talking about
that. I'm talking about just
>> talking about just just spare them.
Yeah. Well, I'm a dog. Like I keep it
real. Like I'm a dog. I banged a lot of Of course.
>> At least you're not a copycat. Yeah. At
>> You mean
>> at least you don't copy people in it?
>> Why would you?
>> What cop? I don't copy people. No.
>> No. No. I'm saying you asked me that
question. Would you?
>> What? Bang. Auton. >> Yeah. >> No.
>> Why not?
>> Not Not for me, mate.
>> Well, what's wrong?
>> She is using filters. She She is using filters, Dusty.
>> Wait. Wait. What's What's wrong with
her? What's wrong? I don't get
>> bit too fat for me. She uses filters.
Well, that's what I'm saying. I I did
I've not even seen her. You just put
that picture up. I I didn't really find
nothing wrong with it. Like, she was
just normal. It's regular girl, isn't it?
>> Yeah. You obviously obviously you
obviously know her. Yeah. Does she have
a channel or something?
>> Yeah. A YouTube channel. >> Okay.
>> She's a labyrin lover.
>> All right. >> Yeah.
She's not your cuppper. No.
>> I know. It's not my cuppper. Like you
asked me, would I just do like a
Anyways, I'm not getting into your
little stupid game.
>> Okay, that was just a question, is it? >> Huh?
>> It was just a question, is it?
>> No, cuz you know she blatantly in that
chat and stuff and you want me to say
something negative and I know you're
>> I'm not saying I'm not force you to say nothing.
>> Yeah, but why would you even just ask me
that knowing full well that people are
there? They're listening. Why would you
ask me that?
>> Cuz it doesn't matter who's listening.
Who cares what they think?
>> Who cares what they think? Huh? Who cares?
>> You don't normally ask me that about any other female.
>> There hasn't been any that's been on the
channel. She's new.
>> Did you Hey, listen. I got sent a link.
Yeah. Um of Vinnie Vids of uh Jane
Jane's black teeth. Did you see that? I
sent it to you. >> Yeah.
>> I couldn't believe it. You know that
woman? Yeah. She told me years ago that
she had veneers. Yeah. She bought
veneers for 20K or something, right? So,
if she bought veneers years ago, why the hell
Does her teeth look like that? No. And she
>> But you don't Yeah, but you don't go to dentist.
>> I don't go. What? How are you mad?
>> I go I go private dentist. How about
that one? Do you know Do you know Do you
know how much I have to pay
[clears throat] just You know what? I've
never had a feeling in my life. I I'll
be honest with you. Never ever had a feeling. >> Huh?
>> I have. I have.
>> Have you?
>> Twice. Yeah.
>> Yes. Exactly. But if you go regularly
Well, you see, I'll be honest with you.
I don't really eat sweets and stuff like
that anyway. So that's like if you look
at my diet and stuff, you can tell that
I don't really the only the only
sweetening thing that I eat is fruits
really and that's not refined sugar.
It's refined sugar and processed food
that ruin your teeth.
>> Processed food, refined sugar, fizzy
drinks, alcohol, all that [ __ ] ruin. And
I'm not I'm not a regular It's
impossible. It's impossible to just
drink water though.
>> No, it's not. I drink I drink water like
80 about say about 90% of the time. I
drink at least about 2 liters a day.
>> I use I use an electric toothbrush. >> Yeah.
Well, you've never had a feeling. [ __ ] off.
>> I swear to God, I've never had a feeling.
>> You know, no, you know, it's also
genetics as well, though. Like, yeah,
what you're saying is true about diet.
>> You know, Can I Can I be honest with
you? Can I tell you something? See, can
I [laughter] can
>> Can I tell you something? See, when I
was a young kid, Yeah. You see my
parents, how how my parents raised me. I
used to be jealous of my cousins and
stuff. I used to be mad jealous of my
cousins and stuff because my jeal um
because my cousins and that they used to
always like get money left for them to
go to McDonald's get to they get to go
to like you know kebab shops all the
time like all the time at least about
four times in a week they used to always
go to like kebab shops and McDonald's
and that for dinner right and my parents
only used to cook homecooked meals they
never used to like for me to get
McDonald's or something it's like a
luxury do you know what I mean so I used
to be jealous of my of my cousins and
that when they used to get that so I
wasn't find these kids. Yeah. Like my my
parents, they made me what's I used to
wear retainers when I was a kid as well,
you know, like not the proper braces,
the train tracks. I Yeah. So like my
parents, especially my mom, she was very
much on me for like for our teeth and
stuff. That's why now when I see people
with missing teeth and stuff that just
that I just get revolted by it, like you
know what I mean? Cuz I think to myself,
did you not have like an upbringing
where people just looked out for you?
Even Okay. Okay. You see my 2-year-old
now? Yeah. My 2-year-old has never
tasted any fruit juice.
>> So, what if they end up not doing it then?
>> My 2-year-old, do you know my Do you
know you know what my 2-year-old has?
Because obviously he's got his teeth
now, but when he just had gums, why am I
going to give sweet things to a kid?
Yeah. To a baby that don't even have his
teeth yet. You know what I mean? Water.
That was it. And he didn't know any different. Water.
>> So, what do you go to the dentist world?
You never had a filling.
>> Oh, check. So, I get my teeth whitened
by them. Uh, checkups. Yeah. I get
cleaned by them sometimes. Do you know
what I mean?
>> If you started drinking coconut, you
would you would soon get a cavity.
>> Say that again.
>> If you started drinking Coke, you would soon get
>> I don't drink fizzy drinks. I don't If I
do, if I do No, but if I do drink those
type of drinks, yeah, I drink um like
orange juice or apple juice or stuff
like that. I don't drink fizzy drinks.
>> Yeah, but you know that's Yeah, but
that's got sugar as well.
>> I know it does.
I know it does. But I brush my I also
brush my teeth minimum times like twice
a day. Like when I wake up,
>> whenever whenever I eat a drink, I brush
my teeth. Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? That's what it all
counts. And it's also not just that.
It's the food that you eat as well. Like
you always eat curries and stuff, right?
I don't like that's that anyone would
tell you if you always going to eat
curries. Yeah. That food's bad for you.
>> It's bad. Not only is it bad for your
health, it's also bad for your I've cut
down on like [ __ ] like that
>> because of it.
>> Yeah. Cries are bad. Have you had Loads
of diet dies in it. Huh?
>> Have you had a toothache before?
>> Um, no. Just like a migraine. I've never
had a migraine before either.
>> Well, you never had a Well, like what
about headache, which is a migraine, but
you know what I mean.
>> I've had a headache, but I've never had
a migraine before. >> Mad.
>> I think No, no, no, no, no, no. I did
have something with my tooth. Yeah, I
did. Wisdom when I had my wisdom my
wisdom teeth was younger though,
[clears throat] is it? It happens when you're younger.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I just remember my
wisdom teeth was coming. I had some some tooth.
>> They just give you antibiotics, isn't it?
>> Uh yeah, years ago.
>> That hurts. That does hurt.
>> All right. But you know
>> Okay. So, what's all right then? So,
what's the worst pain you've ever had?
>> When I got stabbed.
>> No, but like not getting stabbed like as
in like something like like an ache
that's not been caused like by being
stabbed. You know what I mean? Like um
like an injury, but not like that.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. I got my foot run over one time.
>> Yeah, I think my my bro my worst pain
was my foot. Remember I told you I
couldn't walk for 6 weeks cuz I banged it,
>> bro. No, that was worse than the two.
>> I got I got my foot ran over one time.
No, that's that that hurt.
>> [ __ ] that, bro. Well, your bone cracked and that.
>> No, no, it didn't it didn't break
anything, but it just was really um
what's the word?
>> Bro, I I fear that, you know, sometimes,
you know, I'm walking it happened
quickly, though. It didn't stay on my
foot. It just happened quickly. Like
someone was driving and it just it just
happened. It was my fault. I think I was
drunk that time. I was in the road.
>> And how long could you walk for? Or could you?
>> Yeah. A couple weeks. No, I was limping. [laughter]
>> I didn't go to a hospital though. I
didn't go to hospital. I didn't go to
hospital or anything like that.
>> But when I had my foot thing, it was
waking me up at 4 in the morning. Was
thumping, bro. I think I banged it in my
sleep or something. I don't know. I
couldn't walk for 6 weeks. I was limping and bro,
>> bad, bad, bad.
>> You're not going to fight no one. No. I
fight you in the ring
>> coming in today. Yeah.
>> No, you have to book it. No, you have to
you have to book me, bro.
I'm a I'm a busy man, bro. [snorts]
>> No, I'm a busy I'm a busy man.
>> Where's Where's the name?
>> Why would you lie? Why do you lie about
a lot of things though?
>> Like what?
>> Like you said you said your birthday was
something before and it wasn't.
>> Because the thing about you Yeah. is
when I give confidential cuz I have gave
some confidential details to to not just
you but to Jane before like I told Jane
what my mother done as a profession yeah
just to just see that it's minor and I
wanted to see what's going to happen and
when she was angry at me she she dulged
that information to these people now
obviously I don't think these people
remember it but she told these people
and I just thought oh okay like you know
what I mean only listen I keep people
diss Natalie on here all the time yeah
but let me tell you something Natalie
keeps secrets. That girl. Yeah. She
ain't put she knows some she even knows
my first name. Everything. Yeah. And
she's never put it out there. Never. No.
>> Thing I would I would never trust a
woman on YouTube. Like this is the
thing. Yeah. Listen what?
>> Yeah. A lot of people told me don't trust her.
But I can be honest. She's never ever
ever gave anything out about me. Her
green's never gave anything out about
me. And uh what's it? And and Bendy's
never gave nothing out about me as well. Them three.
>> Yeah. But Bendy's a troll, bro.
>> Yeah. No, no, but but he's never gave
anything out about me because I would
know. I would see it. I would see it in
one of his little troll accounts saying
something. Yeah. And obviously he's not.
>> What about Rick's mates? You didn't tell
him anything though. That
>> he was on He was on my social media at
one stage actually, but then he went
around telling people I was white and
like trying to troll me. [laughter]
Yeah. You know what I'm trying to say? Like Yeah.
>> Funny, is it? It's not really funny to
be honest with you because that's partly
the reason why everyone makes up their
[ __ ] about me nowadays because of
because of him to be honest. But you know cool.
>> I even I even recommend you a good
horror film the other day and you didn't
even reply to me. You can't
>> Oh, I didn't see it.
>> Well, I emailed you.
>> The only email I saw Yeah. is from um
someone messaged me what's it about um
Jane's teeth and I saw that on Vinnie's
vids or whatever. I saw it the other
week. I was crying. [ __ ] hell. >> Yeah.
>> How did How do Can I ask something? How
did people even allow their teeth to get
to that type of level anyways?
>> They don't brush them obviously.
>> No, but it can't be just that though.
>> I mean I mean look at look at look at
look at nom steaks. He's missing teeth.
And I'm not even trying to get you to
start on him. But you you talk about
cheap. Yeah. He's actually missing teeth
[laughter] in it. Am I lying? I'm not
even lying. You bought it up teeth.
Yeah. What? What the [ __ ] Timmy's
missing teeth as well. >> Who?
>> Timmy's missing some teeth as well.
>> Is he?
>> I think he's he's got he had a few
knocked out to be fair.
>> Oh yeah. No, no, no. That's different.
If you get them knocked out and you
like, you know what I mean? That's
different. But to actually use them to decay or
>> something nonsex is missing teeth. >> Yes.
>> So that must be like what? Like not
brushing them and that is it.
>> It's got to be more than just not brush.
You have to be eating the worst [ __ ] on earth. The worst. >> Yeah.
>> So, when's it when So, when's the next
time you're going to start kicking off
again? I need to I want to start tuning
in, but I don't want to tune in regularly.
>> I don't want to kick off. I just want I
just want this dough to keep me keep my
name out of his mouth.
>> To be fair, look. You see, today I
didn't even know it was about him. Yeah.
>> But I don't see him. He's not one of the
people that I actually see trolling you. So,
>> I put No, no, no. But he does. No. No.
But he does know because he talks [ __ ]
behind people's back. Listen.
>> No. No. No. But you see when you say you
want to know something, is it that he's
telling the truth and you don't like it? What?
>> Grievy tells the truth. Grievy disagrees
with me on loads of things. >> Cool.
>> I don't sh on him.
>> Right. So you see when you say he's
talking about you behind your back.
Yeah. Like because I don't see him
trolling that actively. He's not like
Bomb. Like Bomb used to come on to wind
you up. Yeah. I don't see that guy. He
trying to troll me on his channel by
like putting up like gambling wins when
they're like fake wins to try to get me
g like he's bro his channel's dedicated
to me like you should know
>> what he's trying to get you to gamble
with lose your money.
>> Yeah. Like what he's doing is he's
showing like but all he's doing is
putting his own money in and taking his
money out making it seem like
>> take accountability as a man. Yeah. How
could someone put up videos of gambling
and trying to get you to gamble? See
even how you saying that
>> you don't understand. His channel is
dedicated to me bro. He does community
post. It's dedicated to me. Do you understand that?
>> I need to see it.
>> It's indirect. You don't understand. He's indirectly
trying to get at me. Don't you get it?
>> So, wait. Oh, so
what is it? He's winning. He's winning
some things and he's saying that you
can't win or something
>> in indirectly. And he's post and he
posts stuff about me as well. He posts
things. Do you want to see your channel?
>> Just Just tell me. Talk me through it.
>> No, I can't I can't explain it. You're
going to have to go on it.
I'm not that interested to really, you know, remember.
>> Well, he's just he's just indirectly
directly trolling me in it.
>> Yeah. Hey, do you know who's got the the
best content now? I seen I subbed to the
other day Smokey Beat. He's got the best content, man.
>> Sad bastard.
>> No, that [ __ ] was funny, man.
>> He's a sad bastard.
>> You had problems with him yourself before.
>> I've never Listen, I don't know where
you even got that from, you know, when
you said this to me before. I've never
ever ever ever had problems with. And
you said where's he from? You said he's
from a Milton Kings or something. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I've definitely never had no
problems with him. Milton Kings is
basically like just on the outskirts of
London. It's like, you know,
>> I call him I call him Want to be London, is it?
>> It's actually It's actually a new place
that Milton Kings, you know.
>> It's been going years about, bro. >> Huh?
>> I went when I was 17.
>> Yeah, but I mean it's relatively new.
It's a new I don't know if it's a town
or whatever. It's not a city, is it? But
um yeah, it's new.
>> Yeah, they sound weird there, isn't it?
>> Not really. Sound just like us.
>> So what? They're cockneys,
>> I believe. So some of them probably are.
It's like it's like London. It's a
mixture of different. You get some
cockney, you get you get different accents. [laughter] No,
>> that's that's be a keyboard. Is it? >> Why?
>> He just isn't it?
If you give people the chance to meet
you, I guarantee they'll show they're
not keyboard warriors.
>> Like who?
>> Like him. If you was to go to his town
or something, I guarantee you he'll show
you he's not a keyboard warrior.
>> I think I think I think about you make
some mad assumptions about people based
on based on their YouTube name or something.
>> What about What about Okay. What about Terry?
>> Terry met you the first time, didn't you?
>> But he he told me to meet him again. He
>> That's true. Okay. All right. All right.
That's true. That's That is true. The
second time. Yeah. And he did all
>> He still comes on. He still comes on.
>> But the first time But the first time,
but the first time you was running for
him, we saw that on camera. And the
funny thing is, yeah, from your point of
view, when you done the video work, you
tried to make it out like you want. But
then, see, this is what I'm saying about
with you. If you people don't record
[ __ ] with you. Yeah. It's easy for you
to just change and make people believe
whatever. Because first, he didn't even
put out the video. I remember you put
out the video first year. It made it
look like that you was get like, you
know, it made it look like you wanted
some with him. Yeah. Then he put out the
video and he see and you can see that
you're running for him like the whole time.
>> I can't even remember, bro. I can't even remember. But
>> yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I've seen it. I remember.
>> I can't remember though. [laughter] I actually
>> I remember I remember.
>> Yeah. But so what would you do if I beat
that prime up? Would you Would you give
me a W?
>> I would I would say Yeah, of course.
>> If you beat anyone up, I would say I
don't Listen, I'm not I'm not biased. I
would say I would say if you beat Do you
reckon Do you reckon that Prime would
actually meet me though? >> No. >> Yeah.
>> I don't think
>> TJ I'm not being funny. Listen, I don't
know what you think.
>> I don't know. How long ago was that? Two
years ago in it. Two years.
>> Maybe 2, three years ago.
>> I don't think you would win now. I don't
think you'd win now.
>> Listen, PJ PJ PJ PJ,
>> I'm not trolling you. I'm being dead
serious. I've seen you. We've seen you
struggling with a old tiger. I'm not
disrespecting him because he tried and
obviously he's a bit unfit and stuff
right at his age, but I've seen you
struggling with him. So, if you're going
to struggle with a small guy like that,
then you're going to struggle with the
majority of people. And if someone got bit
of size to than than you, then you know,
I feel sorry for you.
>> Yeah, but I'm probably I'm probably
bigger than prime now.
>> What in in in fatness?
>> Just like like I don't know. just
they're generally bigger, is it? I don't [ __ ] know
>> what you're definitely You can't Well,
you're not taller, are you?
>> I don't know. Maybe now.
>> Yeah, you're not.
>> I can't remember. I can't remember. But
he wouldn't be
>> He might listen Listen. He might He
might not be able to fight.
>> He might not. He might not. You're
right. But you Exactly. He might not be
able to fight. In fact, nobody on here
might not be able to fight. But guess
what? You don't give them the chance, do
you? Because you're too busy trying to
squeal out and run off. So, you know
what I mean? So even if nobody else can
fight, you're not giving people their chance.
>> You think it was cowardly what he done prime? >> No.
>> Think about it. Think about it. Think
about logically. That's what he had to
do. He had to trick you to meet you
because if he had said to you he wants
to fight you and to meet him there and
then at the same location, you wouldn't
go. You wouldn't. You wouldn't have went.
>> You said you No, but you said if if if
you' done that to me, people would say
you done nothing. So of course.
No, but No, but I know they don't really
mean it. See, the difference is, yeah, I
know when they saying stuff about me,
Yeah. they don't really mean it. They
don't really mean like that, oh, um, I
wouldn't have done anything. All it is
is they want me to do it. They want me
They want me to be in that position to
do something crazy. Yeah, but I know
they don't really mean it. That's the
difference with with you.
>> I told you when that prime thing
happened, didn't it? I said, "Get your
ass down." Is it?
>> Yeah. Did it happen?
>> No, you should have.
No, you didn't have the funds to give
me. I said you have to give me funds.
>> Yeah, but you was near ready anyways. Well, yeah.
>> I don't think during that time I wasn't,
>> you know.
>> Are you Are you Are you going to behave
yourself this year now?
>> Yeah, I am.
>> Yeah, that's right.
>> You got to behave yourself, man. Because life
>> Yeah. And as I said before, I was your
age when I joined I was I was your age
when I joined the sector.
>> Actually, I actually do want to get off,
but that they need to stop reeling me
in. I'm being serious, bro.
>> How about How about Yeah, you just uh
what's the word? How about you just behave normally?
>> You don't see.
>> No, no, no, no. One's saying you even
have to go. No one's saying you have to
go. How about you just behave? Try to behave normally.
>> How about you stop doing weirdo [ __ ]
Yeah. Like uh going to Peppa Pig and
meeting going to cinema, watching Peppa
Pig, and then telling everyone about it.
Like and like you see this little stuff
like that when you're doing stuff like
that and you expect people to treat you normally.
>> Oh, I can just leave like Ant-Man, is it?
>> Yeah. You don't have that in you to do that.
>> Well, Ant-Man done it.
>> Yeah, that's him. But you don't have it
in you to do that.
>> He said they're all retards on it.
That's [laughter] what he said.
>> You big you big him up for leaving,
isn't it? Um yeah, like well he is what
he is, but I mean [ __ ] if he if he's got
Yeah. Because basically it shows that
he's got um something else outside of this place.
>> Like don't you get it? Like you see you
see when I've sat around and I've I've
watched you for too long. Yeah. It makes
me feel what's the word?
Like it it's I don't I can't explain it.
Like it just
>> when I watch it's like when I watch L J.
Yeah. I get brain damage. I can't watch
it. like the live streams, you know, the
live streams. [clears throat]
>> As far as
>> Oh, yeah. Let's talk about that one.
Yeah. Yeah. Cuz now I'm on now. Yeah.
Because it's hard to type when you're
arguing me about this, right? So, you
said Yeah. You said ages ago that um he
done nothing. He hid behind a gate, right?
>> Listen, I'm keep it real. I'm going to
keep it real with you. Listen, let me
just be real with you.
>> Let me be real with you. You know, you
are the only person and I've and I've
showed the the video to many people and
shown it, right? You're the only person
that believes that you're in the right
in that situation. This is what I'm
trying to say about no point working with you.
>> I didn't win. I didn't win, but neither did he.
>> But he did win because he listen
to No, no, no. Listen, listen. Before
all of that, let's go through the
backstory first. You said all that about
his kids, all the madness, right?
>> [clears throat]
>> He came. He told you he was coming. He
came and he wanted you to say it in his
face and you know to to stand on your
business. You know how he was going on
online. He wanted that to happen in
reality. You didn't do that in reality.
And then you now you expect him No, no,
listen. Now you expect him to kick your
door through and to get himself
potentially in trouble just because you
said a few words online. Even me. Yeah.
I'm I'm actually I sit here and I'm
embarrassed to myself be that like I've
had to do extra. I I I traveled to him
before he left to go back.
>> Yeah, but I'm talking about the I'm
talking about when he's knocked on your
door and your mom's had to witness that.
My mom would never have to witness any
[ __ ] like that. I promise you. Cuz
I'm I'm I'm not It's just not going to
happen. I'm not going to tolerate this.
Don't you see? We're just raised
different because there's certain
things. Yeah. That's just not
>> I didn't have to open the door. I I
literally didn't even need to open the door.
>> You should not. You You was better off
not opening the door. You made it look
even worse. You'd better off not open
the door because you said you're going
to come down. He asked you going to come
down. He said, "Yeah, you came down.
Then your mom's there." Number one, my
mom wouldn't be there. Like my mom will
be in the house somewhere and then I
would have to hurt someone for even
being that brave to come to my mom's
house. Do you know what I mean? I would
have to. And then your mom's giving you
a hammer. You should have took that
hammer to I'm just keeping it how what I
would have done. Yeah. If your mom's
giving you should have took it like no
one you don't need Listen, this is the
real world. Yeah. You don't need to give
someone a fair fight if they're coming
to your mom's house. Yeah. And you were
scared. You didn't You didn't come out.
>> I was I was not scared. No, I wasn't.
>> Listen, I'm not kidding. Listen, he
asked you. He asked you. He was being
respectful to listen.
Yeah. Yeah. I didn't need to madness
about his kids at all. He was being
respectful. He was being respectful by
telling you come outside of the gate so
we can have
>> I didn't need to. I didn't need to. I
>> He did not come outside. And then when
he left the door in my face, the door
went closed. The door was closed. The
door went closed. The door went closed.
I was not scared about saying that he
has to I didn't need to open that door. >> What?
>> I didn't need to open the door.
>> Are you listening to yourself? You're
basically making it You're basically
saying that he has to do the extra stuff.
>> Well, he come all the way here. Well, he
Well, yeah, he does cuz he came all the
way here. So, finish it. Yeah. Yeah. Do
the extra stuff.
>> Wait, hold on. Hold on. Yeah. Yeah. Do
all the extra. Let me let me tell you
something. Let me tell you something. Do
you know if he had done something more
and say he did kick that door and he hit
you and he bashed your mother or
something like that and you not run to
the police cuz you have done run to the
police a few times.
>> Okay. And what if I get in trouble? Do
you know what he will get in trouble for?
>> No. Listen to what I'm saying cuz you
know listen. Do you know what he'll get
in trouble for? He will get in trouble
for not only is he um that's that's
aggravated. He'll be aggravated assault.
No, I'm not. I was not at all.
>> Can I can Can I just explain the
difference between aggravated assault
and normal common assault? Now, if
someone sees you on the street and they
punch you in your face, that's common
assault. Yeah, that is not as bad as
aggravated assault. If you aggravated
assault means that you've planned and
you've come there with a plan to to
punch you in your face, that's 10 times
worse. Do you know the type of birds
that you get for these type of sentence
for things like this?
>> Do you know?
>> I know the law. I know these things.
It's like, you know, why do you think
I've been hesitant before to really
like, you know what I mean? Cuz I know
what this is and I'm not going to get I
don't really want to get myself in
trouble for stupidness. Like if you if
now if you're willing to come outside
then that even if I did get done by by
the old bill, it'll be common assault.
It'll be maybe ABH or something like
that. Anything to do with aggravated AB
or aggravated assault. Yeah, I don't
want it on me. No thanks. No thanks. So
that's instantly comes with 10 10 years
and I ain't got time for that. For what?
Just to prove something on YouTube. [ __ ] off.
So that's what I'm saying. If I was him
in a way, I don't know, but I'm a bit
more hotaded because I probably would
have gave you what you wanted and kicked
that door. I'm not going to lie. I
probably would have, but it's stupid. At
the same time, it's a stupid move to do.
I would have done something stupid. Just
like when I had to break into your house
twice. It's stupid. Do you know what I
mean? Realistically, when I think about
it, I think to myself, I'm lucky because
I got away. But that's that was a stupid move.
>> But at the same time,
I told him I told him to [ __ ] off. I
weren't scared of him. I was stood in
front of me when he's asking. So, why do
I need to explain this? See, if I if I
explain this to my oldest son.
>> Okay. So, why didn't he put his camera
on when I was in the same location as
him then? Why didn't he put his camera on then?
>> Okay. Okay. Why didn't he I went to the
same loc Why did he put his camera on then?
>> I don't know. You'd have to ask him about that.
>> I'm asking you, bro. Like, he me and I
and I traveled before he went back to
cuz I weren't going to let him like have
the last half.
>> I remember. I remember
>> you was there yourself. You was out
>> I remember. I remember. But what I'm
saying is though, but I can't answer for
that. I just know I just know the first
bit that he's on camera and he came out
[laughter] and as he was walking away
then that's when you done what he wanted
you to do the whole time and that's when
you come and you left your your uh the
front yard but then when he's when he's
turning back then you walking back into
your house again. Do you know what I
mean? It's it's like some little kiddy
games. You know when you're agree
just pushing each other the whole time
punches. He could never do that again
though. He could never do that again.
And you know it could never say that
because now you know he's over there and
if he did come back again. No actually.
What are you talking about? He could
never listen when he was when he did
come to Heath or whatever.
Did I not put up your voice notes? He
was literally crying to me
>> because you wanted to meet him. Because
>> No. No. Don't use me as an excuse. Don't
use me as an excuse. Yeah. I didn't even
know that he was coming. That's how
that's how bad it was. You just randomly
randomly Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I had a
discrepancy with him at around that
time. Yeah, but I didn't even know he was coming.
I remember it was early in the morning
at work and you said this guy's coming
blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah
blah. Right. And then I said why you
telling me for handle your business like
you've made him come handle your
business. That's what I told you. Then
you said then I remember you then said
to me and I said to you I'm at work
anyways. What can I do? Then you said oh
yeah but you can get boys to go and do
stuff though and whatever. Then you're
not saying then you said then you said
you give me £500. Huh?
>> Yeah. Because you wanted to meet him yourself.
>> Listen. But so that's your thing. You
get into problems with these dudes.
Yeah. Then if they come, then you just
instantly try and palm it off for me. Listen listen.
>> When Lord J come the first time, you
wanted him yourself. You wanted me to let go. >> Yes.
>> Did you not?
>> Yes. But I'm talking about the reason
why he he comes for you. He don't he's
not coming here for me. He's coming for
>> You wanted him. But you wanted So wait,
hold on. So So isn't that easy to do
then? Isn't that easy to do? So you wind
him up for him to come for you, right?
And then now you can just stay out of it
and then get me involved because we know
that me and him had a discrepancy
before. So now no, you can't do that.
That's not how it works. You can't do that.
>> But you cannot do that. That's childly.
See, this is what I'm trying to say even
this. Why do I have to explain this to
you? You made him come. Yeah. It's for
you. It's got nothing to do with me,
>> you know.
>> Yeah. And then and then you're trying to
you're trying to put me ahead of you.
And then you know the funny thing is
even if I did like do something and we
me and him got into it or whatever.
Yeah. You'll be saying stuff like a few
weeks later you'll be chatting [ __ ]
about me again anyway. So why
>> Yeah. Yeah. Cuz that's how you that's
how you work. That is exactly how you
>> He could never come back here, bro.
>> He He could.
>> He [ __ ] couldn't. He [ __ ] could not.
>> Someone. Tell him to come back then.
>> Is it worth coming? No. No. No. He
could. Is it worth? It's not even me. I
can I can easy come today. I can come
with Listen, I can easy drive to Essics
now within an hour and a half. Can I be
bothered? Can I be bothered to get the
same result? Burn my petrol. Can I be bothered? No.
>> Well, he's got all of these friends on
YouTube in it. So, yeah, it is worth it. Why not?
>> What you not to come out again for you
to only do the same [ __ ] again? Listen,
people's gave you enough chances on
here. Yeah, we've seen the same [ __ ]
repeat like it's it's endless. Do you
know what I mean? So what's the point?
>> But he would never
>> I personally wouldn't tell anyone
outside far out here to come and waste
their time with you. What is the point?
Now if you are that seriously
>> there was no point they coming here as
well cuz you just stood behind the gate
and done nothing. [laughter]
>> There was no point.
>> If I went to America listen if I went to
America I would not be hiding behind the
gate. I would not be hiding behind a
gate, bro. I'd be breaking in the house.
>> Number one, you wouldn't go there
anyways. So we
>> Bro, listen. If I was to go that there I
was supposed to. I wouldn't hide behind
the gate. I wouldn't leave my temple to
hide behind a gate. Bro,
>> it's easy to say when you wouldn't do it
anyways. It's easy to say.
>> I gave you Mark Samson's address before.
You didn't go there.
>> Why? You kept calling the police on you.
So why do I why, [laughter] bro? I went
to meet him. Did you come out? Why do
you have to go?
>> I got an excuse for everything. Huh?
>> Why would I go to Mark's address? I
tried to meet him twice.
>> So why why do you want me to go?
>> And and guess what then? And then so
Lord Jay can say that excuse as well.
He's tried to meet you. He tried to meet
you and you didn't and you bottled it.
Why should he have to do it again? See,
>> cuz he tried meeting Timmy several times.
>> Oh, I know about it one time.
>> Yeah. And he tried again and he kept
threatening to go back. So, I mean, you
know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> Why do you Okay, so why did he keep
trying to meet Timmy then?
>> I don't know if they ask him. >> Well,
>> probably to scare him. Probably to scare
him to be fair.
>> Yeah, but you know he bottled out of
meeting you. I'm not even trying to stir
[ __ ] I'm not even I am not even trying
to stir [ __ ] I'm being real. You know,
he he did.
>> Listen, PJ, man, I don't really care to
be honest. Like, you know what? You see
all this you see all this stuff here.
Yeah. Like, it doesn't live in my head.
Do you know what I mean? Like, if I've
had a problem years ago with somebody
like even fruit king, I had a problem
with him, whatever. He didn't turn up.
Do you think I I don't care? Like,
whatever. If I see it now, I'll just
block him. Like, do you know what I
mean? Cuz I'm not going to keep That's
the thing about me. Like, I'm not going
to carry on. If you didn't meet me or
whatever, then I don't have nothing more
to discuss. I'm not going to get into
this battle with you. I'm a man. Yeah. I
was raised I had a father in my home
growing up. Yeah. So I was always taught
like my my dad used to make us all wear
boxing gloves and fight each other in
the garden. Me and my older brothers
and Do you know what I mean? So that's
my thing. Like you know what I mean? If
I get angry with someone that's why I
don't like this internet stuff as well,
but I'm slowly adapting to the way how
it is. There's a lot of nerds that run
the internet. Yeah.
>> Okay. So if I listen, if I if I went to
meet that JF today, would you turn up,
do you think?
>> Yeah. And what if he
>> if he wouldn't I'll be the first one to
say he wouldn't
>> but then it would but then it would
continue with other then other it would
continue with other people wouldn't it
>> listen he said on there that he would
turn up and I think he would to be
honest with you why wouldn't he Listen
I'm not being funny here listen I'm not
I'm not trolling you but you turning up
to somewhere that's like the easiest
[ __ ] that's the easiest victory for
anybody think about it
>> why didn't why didn't loads of people
come out when I've done it before then
>> oh because probably they don't I don't
know they haven't got some some people
do you know some people just don't want
a confrontational they actually let me
not make excuses some people are just
not about that like do you know what I
mean [laughter] just keeping it some
people just not about that
but I'm just saying to any normal to any
normal person that's had a fight in
their lives or anything like that yeah
like you you don't pose a threat like
that like especially after seeing the
thing with the 12year-old and you're
seeing t the tiger thing it's like come
on this could be done very it could be
done very quickly. Like you see we Have
you ever seen someone just get knocked
out instantly from one punch? >> Yeah.
>> I I reckon I reckon the majority of
people could do that to you in this place.
>> It doesn't matter if they know how to fight. Huh?
>> Do you think you could take on most people?
>> But it's I tell you I tell you one thing
about me though. Yeah. Like I came from
where I come from and stuff like that.
Yeah. I was I was I'm used to fighting
like from when I was young. I've always
had fights and stuff like that. So
that's why I'm not scared. Even if I
lose or whatever, I'm not scared to
lose. Do you know what I mean? But I
know that I'm going to give it to I know
I'm going to hurt someone.
>> You take Do you think you could take
like Ed Matthews or Noah? >> Huh?
>> Do you reckon you could take Ed Matthews
in a fight?
>> Could you take Ed Matthews in a fight?
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah, I think I'll slap him up. That's
>> But he's a boxer.
>> No, but because he said he's done
kickboxing. I've done kickboxing since I
was 6 years old.
>> It's not childish. I'm just asking,
isn't it? Like
>> Yeah. But you know what though? It all
matters on the day, isn't it? Cuz you
never know. I could slip over by
accident. I could, you know what I mean?
Anything can happen.
>> Or you or you or you a big boy.
>> Even Even with you, you know, you know,
you know you could actually get lucky. I
think you have a punch chance. No, no,
no. You know when you saying
>> you know when you were saying yeah this
is still going on. How many times have I
said yeah me you Mark Samson and Timmy
Terry we all need to meet for piss up
and you meet >> what
>> I have said I've said Triple H me LT
yeah Mark Samson and Terry should meet
for like a piss up in a like clubbing session.
>> No one meets bro.
>> What do you mean no one meets? PJ I
would meet you anytime you want. What
are you talking about?
>> We can all go for a drink. I would meet
you anytime you want. Look, I'm even
Look, I've been in London since Monday.
I would meet you any I'm free. I'm free
until Sunday. I will meet you anytime
you want. Anytime you want. There's not
a time in a day that's too late for me
or anything now. Like, you know what I mean?
>> Can we meet Terry and Mark as well? Then
>> number one, Mark's got anxiety. Yeah.
Just as words from Jane. Jane told me.
Yeah. He don't go out anywhere. So,
that's that's off the cards.
>> Um Terry, I think Terry will meet you.
Terry will make
>> I think you'd have to go to him though.
I don't think he's coming to you.
>> What? Like last time he showed up. Yeah.
>> Yeah, I know. That that time there.
Yeah, I know. I can't even Yeah, that
was a let down. I'm not going to lie.
>> And he told me to come. He kept banging on come.
>> No, that that was a let down, man. I
can't believe he done that. But yeah, I
reckon he might he might just meet you
though, to be honest.
>> Should I for just go for a drink like
for the new year? Just squash it in the new year.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Come then. Let's do it today.
Yeah, Mark. Yeah, but Mark Samson Terry
has to show up as well.
>> I forget them cuz like forget them. Just
me me and you should just meet up.
>> We can all do cocaine together.
>> I don't I don't do that. But yeah, me
and you should just meet up to be fair.
Come on. It's been years now as well.
It's been It has been years. Come on. [laughter]
>> Yeah, it has been years. It has.
>> It has been years, isn't it? Come
>> and Fruit King can come as well, isn't it?
>> Yeah, he's in Liverpool. Yeah, he can
come to London, isn't it? So what? Come
on. You remember what I said before?
You, LJ, all of you should squash it and
all laugh with each other. [laughter]
>> You can laugh mean you should squash it.
Why don't we just meet up today?
>> You can laugh. You can laugh all like
you can all laugh like one big happy
family, ain't it?
>> Come. I'm free, man. Let's go. We're
somewhere local. I'll come to you. I'll
>> No, I can't I can't I can't meet you by yourself, bro.
>> Where? If Terry and Mark Samson does, I
will 100%. On my mom's life, I will.
>> No, you wouldn't. Why can't you meet me by myself?
>> It's too dangerous.
>> Why? So, you'll meet everybody else.
Yeah. You meet Monty and all these
people. Yeah. Not me. You done matters
to Monty and you still meet him and and
Fraser and and and but you you'll meet
them and not me. Why is that? >> Yeah.
>> Cuz you're you're too dangerous, man. >> How?
>> You just are too dangerous.
>> I'm not. I'm actually a nice friendly
guy, you know, deep down.
>> But you breaking people's houses and that. [sighs]
>> Yeah, but you should have talked about
my kids then, isn't it? Or my or my kid
at the time.
>> Yeah, but you started it.
>> Don't matter, man. You didn't have to
You didn't have to start saying all that
barbaric stuff, did you?
>> Yeah, but you you even said you was
going to kill me, is it?
>> I never I never told you them words. You
assumed them. You assumed.
>> You said I was going to wake up to a
hide, didn't it?
Yeah, I said he's going to wake up to
violence and that's definitely true.
That's why I stood I stood over your
tenant. I thought it was you. He I swear
he was built like you and everything. I
thought I hit the I'm not going to lie.
I thought I hit the jackpot. Yeah, but
then he I I took over the um I took off
the covers and the guy was naked in your
bed and it was like a single bed, isn't
it? You know, I'm not lying, right? He
was wearing a single bed.
>> I was one I was one step ahead of you in it, Taylor.
>> I was one step ahead in it.
>> You have to admit. No.
>> Why was he naked though? I don't know.
That was his run.
>> That's mad.
>> Well, so you saw what he saw his [ __ ] at.
>> No, he had like like he was laying um
how do I say it? Like he was he was
laying with his ass in the air instead
of his [laughter]
>> You just walked out of there.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I just Yeah. I couldn't
believe Yeah. I went into your room.
Yeah. I went into your room and I was mad.
>> What did it smell like?
>> Yeah. I told you. You want me Oh, you
want me to actually You like
embarrassment, don't you? Oh, I told you
before. It's I'll be honest. It smelt like
>> like uh cheesy feet like a musty ball.
>> It's No, it smell like cheesy feet.
Musty balls. Yeah. You know when you
like I don't know. Probably didn't wash
for like three or four days or whatever.
Like musty balls and like a It's like a
strong uh how do I put it? Like um like
a curry smell as well mixed with like
you know what I mean?
>> At least none of the neighbors knew
about it. Is it?
>> Huh? At least none of the neighbors knew about it.
>> Yeah, they did.
>> Why didn't they go on the door then? Why
>> The neighbor opposite your house yet
installed a security camera with the
light because of me? [clears throat]
>> Because it kept Yeah. Was that not
because of me?
>> I don't know. It was because of
>> Yeah, it was cuz
>> when you smash the window like you saw
lights go, is it? >> Yeah.
>> So, you won't be brought by smashing the window. >> Yeah.
No, that's bad.
>> Well, it didn't happen once though. >> Huh?
>> It didn't happen once. It happened
[clears throat] a few times.
>> Well, they all they all looked, didn't it?
>> When it's meant to be saved.
>> Yeah. And then you say you got money and
all this stuff. Yeah. You didn't even
fix those windows. Not one of them. You
didn't even fix it once.
>> I got it boarded up.
>> How long did it take for you to get it boarded up? >> Um, >> months.
>> Months? Yeah, I remember. Cuz I was
going there. It was months. You You had
people staying in there with a cracked
window like wide open like that. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, come let's meet today then. Come.
>> No, I can't. Unless Mark Samson and
Terry Well, get Terry to meet and we
I'll meet I'll meet
>> Not meeting me. I've tried.
>> You haven't tried, bro.
>> I've months ago like or maybe a year
ago. I've tried. He He won't meet me.
>> There was a time when you were supposed
to meet him um in Green Lanes or
something. Yeah. And I went there like
about a year ago. >> Mhm.
>> We're waiting for him. We're waiting for
>> No, no, no. You said you was coming and
you were still in your still in your mom's house.
>> Why do you do that? Like you do that all
the time. You arrange things with people
and then you you just won't come and
then you'll come out with some
ridiculous excuse. Oh yeah, it's because
uh he's meant to meet you first and then you'll come. [laughter]
>> What the [ __ ]
No, you're mad. You
>> You're nasty, man. You went with [ __ ]
You went with Fraser's girlfriend, man.
>> I'm going anyways.
>> Why? Cuz you know, ain't it?
>> No, I'm just going like I don't like
when you even just do that. Like, why do
you even need to mention certain things,
>> bro? Someone already told people. It wasn't me.
>> Yeah, but that's that's what I'm saying.
So, why that's what I'm saying. Why
would I tell you stuff? I tell you
something basic like that. Yeah. And you
just put it out.
>> People already knew. Cuz people already
>> No, they didn't know cuz I didn't tell nobody else.
>> Jane. Jane told people.
>> Yes. No. No. No. I told you years ago.
Yeah. And I told you the only reason why
I did that is cuz the little [ __ ]
Yeah. was talking crazy about me and
then he didn't want to let me meet him.
So if he don't let me meet him and at
the time when you doxed him, you said
that you knew his girl. Yeah. And he and
his girl's information. So I said, "All
right, give me his girl's information."
I added her. I added her and I done it
my own way. I didn't She I didn't even
tell her. She doesn't even know. She
never knew. She never even knew.
>> Yeah, cuz he was troll I doxed him cuz
he was trolling me.
>> Yeah, I have no problems with that.
That's what I'm saying. But then Yeah,
she she doesn't even know that I knew
any of you guys or anything like that. I
just done it off my own back because Yeah.
>> No, don't don't come on here try to
troll me and try to get away with it.
I'll I'll find a way to get you back.
>> Yeah, true, true.
>> You still fancy my sister?
I never really fancied her to be honest
with you, you know. I was only just joking around.
>> N you wasn't. [laughter]
>> I was joking. I was joking around.
Honestly, she follows me. She follows me on socials.
>> Oh, really? Then when Okay. When I next
see her, I'm going to I'm going to
go on every single one. I'll go on every
>> Oh, [ __ ] Why do I talk? [laughter]
>> I'll go on every single one and I'll
know it's you in it. I I'll know it's
you in it. Yeah.
>> No, I'm joking. But if you keep Hey, I'm
I'm going to I'm going to take off my
thing now. Anyways, thanks for telling me.
>> Yeah, but I can get you another way,
bro. I can just get like a random woman
like with loads of followings to follow
you again that way, mate.
>> Yeah, but you you don't know what my
thing is. I change my handle all the time.
>> Yeah, but I'll find it. [snorts]
I'll find it in it.
>> Oh my god.
>> Why did you go to that boxing thing?
>> What boxing thing?
>> The boxing fight. Uh what was it? Last
month, the month before that.
The last boxing fight I went to is in
Tottenham with Eubank. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Tickets to go there.
To go there, but I didn't go.
>> Yeah. I went I went to both of them. I
went to the first fight as well. >> Yeah.
>> Someone bought me tickets. Someone
bought me tickets, but I didn't go.
>> That's a waste.
>> It was They were like 30, it
>> is much you pay for it.
>> I didn't pay for it. They were bought for me. >> No.
What? What? How much was your tickets?
I got him for free.
>> What were they from? They weren't front row it.
>> They weren't from what?
>> They weren't front row, were they?
>> No, no, no, no. Of course not.
>> Were they all the way in the back or
>> No, it was um like in the middle.
>> It wasn't like Yeah, it was like on a on
a second deck or something.
>> Road tickets for like what 5 10 grand or
something I heard.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You you'll pay them
type of prices. Yeah. I didn't get that.
>> Especially if it's free as well. Yeah.
No. No. Because like obviously I know I
know people has got links to all
different stuff in it. So it's just like
a runaway thing. But the first time I picked up >> really >> Yeah.
>> So you calm down now. No more fights,
>> bro. I just want these people to leave
me alone. I don't You don't understand.
They've been at me now for years.
[ __ ] at me. You know, do
>> you know what? I I think that um this
would all be resolved. Yeah. If you just
met like the biggest person you see like
the biggest trolling one that's that
bothered you on here. Yeah.
>> If I if I can meet if I can meet anyone
Yeah. on here. Yeah. It would either be
Oh, it's got to be Prime or Red Star,
bro. It has to be in it.
>> No. No. Yeah. Yeah. You got to avenge
that Prime one. But you're not going to be
>> Yeah, but I'm not scared of that.
>> That That would have to be the one that
you'd have to avenge now. That That is
the one out of everybody.
>> I don't think I don't think he would meet though.
I reckon. No, I reckon he would.
>> It depends. If you went to him, I think
he might might do it.
>> Where Where was he?
>> I don't know. I'm just saying wherever
you met him before or whatever. Right.
>> Yeah. Nubber.
>> Yeah. Is that where he's from?
>> It's dead.
>> Yeah, it is dead to be fair. It was
dead. I I thought I was meeting someone
for a piss up and he just grabbed me. He
says, "You're meeting me." Do you
remember that? Don't you? Yeah. But
again, see that's what people have to do
to meet because if someone organized it with
>> I didn't say anything about him. That's
why that's that's what you don't know.
He's probably under different accounts
and stuff. You don't know. You don't
know. See, that's that's another thing.
See, haven't you learned your lesson
from that? Yeah. You know, when you just
calling like see these random accounts
like Jo and you don't know what they
sound like or anything like that and
you're saying madness to them, bro.
Don't you know that these these could be
people like crying behind their things
and they'll just come and meet you
randomly? You know what I mean? So if it
say say say say say say say say say say
say that happened to you yeah like he
grabbed you and he walked off like you
would like say it happened
>> to me I promise you I promise you right
now right right now one up yeah when if
it's oneonone yeah that's definitely not
happening to me definitely not it's not
I don't care who it is it's just not
you're not going to get you're not going
to have a camera in my face and hold me
in the other hand no one's doing that I
wouldn't even expect to do that to a
normal person forget me I'm saying I
wouldn't someone that's other than
yourself yeah I mean I could do that to
you but I I mean, I wouldn't expect to
be able to do that to somebody else.
Hold a camera.
>> Do you reckon it would? Do you reckon it
would happen with non legs? Yeah.
>> Yeah, obviously.
>> Well, where he's made to say sorry? Yeah.
>> Yeah, I reckon. Yeah, I reckon. Yeah, he
will be one to say sorry. But he's not
stupid enough to get caught like that, though.
>> I could catch him if I really wanted to.
>> No, you can't. Cuz if you did,
>> Yes, I could. Yes, I could. >> Oh,
>> is he, bro? Ham.
>> Cam, I could just camp outside the train
station, wait for him.
>> Okay. Well, hold on a minute. One
second. So, if if you was me in that
situation, what would have you done if
you was me? Like, and it already
happened just like he wouldn't even have
a chance to be talking. This Listen,
human reaction. Normal human reaction.
Yeah. If someone grabs you, the normal
human thing to do is to get them off of
you. That is my reflex. No, no, no, no,
no. We're not going to go into that. My
reflex is Yeah. If someone grabbed me,
which they wouldn't because it's not I
don't get into these type of situations.
Someone Well, I had before when I was
younger, but if someone grabs me, the
first thing that I'm going to do is grab
like you're getting off of me. Like, do
you know what I mean?
>> Smack to the chin. Smack the chin. I've
[laughter] had situations where people
have been too tough for me before, you
know, and guess what I've done? I've
escaped. Not escaped, but you know what
I mean? I've got out of it. I've looked
very close to me. I've seen a bottle,
picked it up, launch. That's it. Like
that's all you have to do. Like
>> this is the real world. Yeah. This is
how the real world works. I don't know
how people think that it's, you know,
it's like a boxing fight or something
like oh oneonone and everything fair and
let people get up when you knock them
down. No, no, no. This is the real
world. I'm a D.
>> So listen, so when that happened to me,
So when that happened to me, Yeah. when
it had already happened and he walked
away, what would you suggest to get some
bottles and smacking in the face with
him when he walked off?
>> Yeah. But I don't think he would have
had the heart to do that because he was
already squealing. I wouldn't be
squealing. I would do it now if it happened.
>> It's easy to say, isn't it? But it's I
don't think you've got any There's
nothing wrong. Listen,
>> PJ PJ PJ. There's nothing wrong with you
see my son. Yeah. My oldest son, there's
a reason why he he was not born in
London. He wasn't raised in London or
anything like that cuz I don't want him
to be anything like me or my brothers or
anyone that I know. I don't want him to
be like that. My brother, my my son is a
square. Like when you know what I'm
saying when I say he's a square. Yeah.
like he he's one of the guys he probably
looks like he's bad already.
>> But here's the thing. But here's the
thing. You know that
>> listen to me. You know that
>> there's nothing wrong there's nothing
wrong with being a good boy. But the
problem is with you is you like to run
your mouth here and then act like you're
like this guy and
>> Yeah, but he's not about it. He only
know he could win against me because he
was bigger. He He knew that he would
never meet me now. He would never meet
me now. He would never meet me now.
Ever. Never again. I promise. This is
what I'm saying. Why do we have like
debates about these things? You're there
running your mouth to people. Yeah. This
is not even you come. Listen, how did I
first get hold of?
>> He arranged to meet me. I would have
went there and I would have bodied him.
If I knew I was getting into a fight, I
would. You would not. You would not.
>> Yes, I would have. 100%. Yes, I would.
>> You would not. That's why he had to
trick you cuz you everyone knows you
wouldn't have went there if it was like
an organized thing. You
>> I also went to Birmingham with Monty and
he kept quiet. That's another thing. He
kept quiet last time I went Birmingham
>> which was
>> Yeah. Okay, cool. I I don't know too much about
>> But listen, but listen, bro. If I met
him again, listen, bro. Listen to me.
What I'm saying, if I met him again, I'd
have to do more than beat him. You know
that I could I could just if I That's
not good. Beat's not good. You'd have to
rob You'd have to violate him, bro.
Like, and I mean violate,
>> of course.
You'd have to You can't just beat
someone. That's not good enough, bro.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that's true. But you haven't
got that in you,
>> you know?
>> Yeah. Obviously, a normal person would
have to do that like to really get them
to get over them. But I You haven't got
that in you though. So
>> So what? like take his phone and piss on
like strip him and that in it. So
>> you know that you haven't got that in you.
>> You know you haven't. I don't know why
you say these things.
>> So if it happened then so what he done
wouldn't matter then if I done that.
>> If you done that yeah everything what he
did was void.
>> Are you sure?
>> Listen listen. You see I've listen um
one of my friends here when we was
younger he got robbed.
>> He got robbed here by like some people
that we had beef with. Yeah.
>> He got he actually got like got he got
robbed when he was by himself. He got
robbed for his chain. Got robbed for his
moped. everything like that. Yeah. Manto
man, right? And that's because they they
they they set him up and there was a few
of them and they they took his [ __ ]
Yeah. And whatever. >> Yeah.
>> About say about 8 months later, he
caught he caught the main corporate and
he and he stabbed up the main and he and
he and he stabbed up the main corporate.
So every he stabbed up the main
corporate and he made sure he stabbed
him in his bum as well. Yeah. Which is
like a dis which is like a disrespectful
thing. Do you remember when I was saying
that I'll do that to you as well? Like
it's like a it's like a sign of
disrespect. Yeah. and he made sure he
stabbed him in his bum as well. Right.
And do you know so the time where that
he got and we used to clown him for
getting robbed but at the same time we
was only just clowning him like it could
happen to anyone now
>> everything that happened before that
where he got robbed and all that it's
it's now void because he he got the
upper hand because he went back by
himself and he done he done his works to
that guy and now and that person didn't
want anything after that when when he
when he done that to that person that
person actually called him called him up
and like wanted to squash it after that.
So, you know what I'm saying? Like, it's
I don't listen, I'm not advocating for
that. I'm older now. I'm not advocating
for any stuff like that. I'm not
glamorizing it. I'm just saying.
>> So, if you had done something more to
I'm not saying you need to do all that.
If you just like you you smacked him up
like like beat him up in a normal fight,
>> you don't even have to rob him. If you
just beat him up in a normal fist fight,
like proper beat him up, then I guess
that you would uh you would avenge some
type of whatever you had with him. He
doesn't come on him anymore really.
>> Well, there you go. Probably got a life, PJ. >> Yeah,
but he could he would never beat me
again. I could promise that.
>> You can't promise that.
>> I can actually promise that.
>> So, what happened? Uh, wait. Just a
couple months ago, he was uh wasn't he
coming to London or something? You
>> he said he went Crystal Palace, but did
he actually did he show him there? No, he never.
>> Yeah, he went Crystal Palace. Yeah, that is.
>> Yeah, of course. It's South London.
>> Yeah, he said he went there, but he
didn't show he was there.
>> He's the one that he's the one that he's
the one that needs doing him badly in
it. Like, he does definitely in it.
>> He's the what?
>> He's the one that needs doing him badly
out of everyone. I think
>> not really, you know, he's not even that
bad. Like, when I think about like he's not.
>> No, he is bad cuz who does he think he
is thinking to grab people cuz he knew
he can win? No, no, no, no. Who does he
think he is, bro?
>> Think about that.
>> Who do you think he was? Who do you
think? See, you don't take
accountability. Who do you think you are?
>> You know,
>> who do you think you are? You sit on
here. Yeah. Calling everyone fat. Uh,
everyone's skin, everyone.
>> And then simp
who who is he need to like start doing
that, bro? Like, think about it. Who is
he to start if you know what I mean?
>> I think he need I reckon he needs to get
knocked out, bro. I reckon he does like him.
>> I think he does, you know, bro.
>> It sounds good though, isn't it? But
you're not going to do I've actually
know I've been thinking about it like
like I haven't brought up and that I
have actually thought about it like listen
I know the thing about you right you
probably felt the strength in his in his
arms here when he's grabbing you up
that's why you listen I've never seen
Listen you know even my dad yeah the
last time I've that's happened to me
that type of [ __ ] has happened to me
when I was like a little 9year-old kid
or something my dad had to grab me up
for talking crazy to my mom one time my
dad had to grab me that's exactly how he
grabbed you just like that you see
that's how I was that's exactly how I
was acting like with you. You see, you
see, you see how you was acting? That's
exactly how I was acting to to my dad
when he grad
like that. I was I was turning my face
cuz I thought he was going to punch you
in my face, but he didn't know. But I
was I weren't expecting it.
>> Listen, PJ PJ, you had enough time. He
he was sitting down at first. Then he
got up. Then he grabbed you. And
>> he wasn't sitting down. He was stood up
this whole time.
>> All right, fine. I got that wrong. And
then and then he grabbed you and then
the first thing you said was, "Why you
beating me up like a little bitch?" >> Yeah.
So yeah, but I'll make but he will never
do he could never beat me now cuz I'd
make him my [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but you said why you beat him?
>> Those words would never leave my mouth
>> at all.
Going to win. Hey, listen. Listen to
what I said. You knew he was going to win.
>> Someone was too strong for me or
whatever. I think I'll probably just
prefer you just getting beaten up. Yeah.
Before I start acting up like that, I
would never know what I should have
done. No, I should have just spat in his
face. That's what I should have done.
>> Yeah, but you didn't have the heart to
do it. He was obviously scared. That's
why you run off. You obviously caught me
off guard. He caught me off guard.
>> He never listen. You keep saying that
[ __ ] You had enough time.
>> Okay. Okay. Do you think Okay. Listen.
Okay. Let me ask you this question.
Yeah. If I was a lot bigger and do you
think he would have met me? You reckon
he would have done that?
>> I know small guys fight. You know, I
know small guys.
>> But I'm saying, do you think he would
meet me if I was bigger and stronger then?
>> I don't know.
>> I don't know cuz you you you would
assume a lot of things. You would assume
that I wouldn't try and meet you or
anything if he was a lot bigger or
whatever. But then again,
>> we're talking about Yeah, maybe. But
we're talking about him. What do you think?
>> I don't know. I don't know him. I don't
know. I don't know.
>> Okay. What if you What if you had the
physique of The Rock? Would you want to meet you?
>> What if he was John Cena? Would he want
to meet you?
>> No, you're asking me flipping playground.
>> It's picking target. It's No, cuz people
It's very easy for people to pick
targets. Do you understand?
>> Listen, as I said before, you need you
need to be accountable for your own
actions. Yeah. You're on here mouthing
off to people. Yeah, you will come to my
mom's house, bro. Yeah, come to my mom's
house. I've heard you many times doing
it. Not just to me, to everyone. Come to
my mom. Yeah, come on. You know the
address. You know the address. Why are
you bringing people to your mom's house?
I've told you this before.
>> Listen, Dusty, if Dusty, if someone
grabbed you up, you would do nothing.
That's what I hate about here when these
Do you know what I hate about this this place?
>> How do you know you would do nothing
though? See, you're just assuming again.
Listen, PJ, not everyone. Not listen.
You don't have to be the strong guy or
anything like that. Yeah. Not everyone
is just going to tolerate people putting
their hands on them. Like for instance,
look, if the guy was super strong and
the instant human reaction, if a guy if
another man grabs a man, right, the
instant reaction for that man that's
getting grabbed is to get him off of him.
>> Yeah. Your instant reaction was a lot
different. Your instant reaction was,
"Why are you beating me up?" Your
instant reaction was turning your head
because you you know what I mean? That
was your instant. See, look, there's
there's people there's two different
types of people. men out here. Yeah,
there's people that run and there's
people that would rather just get hiding
if they're going to lose or whatever.
Oh, I'm not even I couldn't even lie. I
punched on Timmy. I beat Tig Timmy and
Tiger. What are you talking about?
>> Yes, I did. I punched Tiger, bro. Tiger would admit
>> I saw the video myself. How you going to tell me?
>> I punched him on the ground when I got
you into that mattress, face platter
if you slip. It's a fight. It's a fight.
I got a fight. It's a fight. It doesn't
matter if you know I got up and doesn't
matter if you slip. It's a fight. No
more of it.
>> It's a fight. It doesn't matter.
>> It doesn't matter if you slip. It
doesn't matter if you slip. That's
That's what That's what a fight is. I
know for a fact I know for a fact if I
went on one of these people's doors in
this community, they're not opening the
door. That's what makes it funny. Like
that's what makes it funny. You
>> want me to give you I'm at my parents
house right now. Do you want me to give
it to you? Do you want me to give you the address?
>> Bro, listen. I'm talking about these
people in here.
That's why I did give you Mark Sansson's address.
>> Listen, Jake, if I went on your door,
you wouldn't even open it.
>> So, I don't know why you're like, you
know what I mean? You wouldn't open it. >> Oh,
>> you would not open it at all.
>> PJ, listen. You know, you know the
funny. Can I be honest with you? If it
was like a normal, if it was like
another person saying stuff, Yeah. then
we might be like, "All right, yeah,
that's true. That's true." But it's you,
PJ. you. We see you run from 12y old
with your knees running high to your chest.
>> Well, this is pretty good.
>> It doesn't matter.
You I don't give a [ __ ] mate. Cuz I'
I've never done that.
>> I don't care. Listen, if someone's kid
Listen, can I tell you how how I would
reacted if I don't care if another if
another person's kid thinks that me and
them are size and thinks that they're
going to try and chase me anyway, I
would stand there and I would mash that
kid up. But I'm not even joking. I would
because who are you? like you're not
you're not me and you're not s the [ __ ]
you think you can stand up to a grown
ass man and think you're but you left
your you left your own mother you left
your own mother you run off
>> knees touching your
>> chest people but these people would run
that's what they they would never meet
anyone but what makes me laugh is the
people in this community are worse than
me that's what makes the whole thing funny
>> why I've never seen anyone listen I've
seen Rick Smith take some L's on here
but I've never seen him like doing all
this like running away [ __ ] even
He got He got He got
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But I've seen
him I've seen I've seen him fighting
people and stuff. I've seen him
>> when the guy come when the guy come down
>> Yeah. Okay. Okay. Okay. Oh, yeah. I did
see that actually. I think I did. Yeah.
>> Yeah. That's
>> He started He started like like like
um taking back what he was saying, isn't it? >> Huh?
>> He was taking back. [laughter]
>> He was laughing at it.
>> Yeah, I remember that. I know it was
years ago, but yeah, I remember that.
>> What about the one with the guy with a
bottle? Was that an L?
>> What guy with a bottle?
>> No, but he was like the guy like screaming.
>> Was that an L?
>> I don't remember.
>> You do remember. You told me about the fat guy.
>> He was like, "Oh, he's got a knife. He's
got a knife. He's got a knife."
>> Are you talking about the guy? You
talking about the guy at the bus stop?
Yeah. Where um he was like, "Don't smoke
that." I think Rick was smoking weed or
some [ __ ] Yeah. And he was like, "Don't
smell that around me." And then he end
up Rick's men up putting him on his
backside. He put that old guy.
>> The other one where he's like, "Oh,
where the fat guy was like he's got a
knife and he was chasing him with a
bottle." The recent the most recent one.
>> Oh, what? And um what? And he's running. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yeah. But even still though, he ain't
taking no L's like you though.
[laughter] He ain't been made to say
sorry and all that madness. Like you was
made to say sorry.
>> Yeah, but Rick Mace would be made to say sorry.
>> Listen listen. He's a jail guy. Yeah,
he's a jail guy. I reckon he's a type of
person he'll probably rather get beaten
up than go out like that and then say sorry.
>> Rick is a [ __ ] bro.
>> If he was a jail guy, why has he took so
many L's from [ __ ]
>> Listen, let me tell you something. If if
a man is a jail guy, it doesn't matter
if you think he's a [ __ ] or not.
There's a certain code of conduct here
that they they uphold, isn't it? And to
go out screaming like a [ __ ] Yeah.
Saying sorry and all that. It's a no-go.
You'd rather get beaten up and get hurt
badly than then go out like that. Do you
know what I mean? I'm not going out like
that. I don't care if there's a whole
army in front of me. I'm not I'm not
crying or nothing. You're just going to
have to hurt me badly. Like, do you know
what I mean? See, we're two different
Okay. It's like this. It's like when I
was younger. Yeah. I told you that time
when I got chased down in Beckham. Yeah.
I was by myself. I was slipping. I just
come from a girl's house and I was in
Beckham B6, E6 or whatever. And these
guys saw me. I just walked around the
wrong the wrong the wrong uh turn in the
road cuz I trying to find the main road.
>> And there was a bag of guys, a bag of
goons just there. And they was instantly
on my case straight away. What happened?
They chased me cuz I was off cuz I knew
what time it was.
>> And when they finally caught up to me
and they tried to rob me and everything
because of my pride and my ego and
everything, it's like no, I can't. I
don't care. I rather get beaten up. Like
I'm not giving away. I'm not handing
over my phone. You're not running my
pockets and taking my [ __ ] Do you know
what I did? I took my phone out. At the
time it was one of them lemon phones.
Remember them knocking lemon phones? The
tear drop phones? I took my phone out. I
threw it on the floor and I stumped on
it. Yeah. So that means you're not
robbing me. No one gets it. [ __ ] it.
Like do you know what I mean?
>> Listen. Why do you think I've took the
most L's on here, bro? Because I've put
myself out there unlike a lot of you
people. You can't You don't put yourself
out there to ever be in a situation
where you could ever take an L. That's true.
>> How did you put yourself out there? like
these people on here like to meet people and that.
>> Listen, as I said, time crime had to had
to trick you to in order to meet you.
You thought it was a friendly thing,
right? So, how did you put yourself out there?
>> Well, when I've tried to meet Bomb when
I've met Terry, I put myself out there.
What are you talking about, bro? I put
myself out there.
>> You put yourself out there, Terry? Yeah.
Yeah, I'll give you that. Yeah, you did.
But then you
So, Jake the Snake. Jake the Snake. How
can you take L's when you you've never
even met anyone? You're just a keyboard warrior. I
>> ran you you ran with with the Terry one.
Like we seen that on camera. You ran.
>> But he didn't beat me.
>> You ran and when you was tired and you
couldn't run anymore. You were
screaming, "Get off of me."
>> But who won in the end? Me.
>> No, you didn't. >> Okay.
>> You only
the second time.
>> No, I'm not being No, no, no. Don't try
to ever say I'm being biased. I'm
calling it how I saw it. When When
>> a black guy got off his pedal bike to
stop the fight because he could see that
you needed help. Yeah, cuz if you didn't
need help like that, he wouldn't have
intervened. But you needed help. It
looked like you was being the victim. So
he he he stopped Terry because Terry was
the aggressor. So that's why he stopped
Terry and he was grabbing Terry off of
you. He never grabbed you off of Terry.
He grabbed Terry off of you. Then that's
when you saw a little like you saw a
little saving grace there. And that's
when you gave him a little pony kick.
You know what I mean? Yeah. All right.
You gave him a little pony kick when you
saw that he was getting told told to
move away and stuff. Right. All right.
And then the second time he called you
out and you went there. All right, I'll
give you that. I'm I'm not going to sit
here and lie to people like Yeah. Okay.
Yeah, that did happen.
>> But he called me out.
>> Yes, I know.
>> So, it doesn't make sense, does it?
>> Yes, I know. And Mark Samson's called
you out plenty of times as well and you
and you have actually turned up for that
as well. I'll give you that.
>> But to be honest with you, yeah, none of
this stuff really matters anymore. The
way I see it, you know.
>> Of course it don't.
>> It doesn't.
>> That's what I've been trying to tell
you. Of course it don't because
>> isn't it? So
>> yeah, but but until until you get upset
again and then a week later you're still
going to be saying the same old tune.
You're still going to be saying, "Oh,
Lord J hid behind a gate." Yeah. Cuz
I've noticed that even when I've
corrected you over the years in private
and I've corrected you in over the years
about you taking these L's. Yeah. You
you you understand for that brief moment
and then I would hear you later on when
you're angry again with these people.
>> We should we should stop this [ __ ]
Yeah. Like was it We should We should
just have part two, bro. Yeah, [laughter]
>> I think it's not part of team
yet to anything. There isn't going to be no
>> It's like It's like a It's like a
wrestling match. Yeah. One wins, then
the one loses. Like, bro, we need round two.
>> Yeah. There isn't going to be no damn
round two because you're not going to
agree. You're never going to agree to
that. There's not going to be a round
two, man. There's never going to be a
round two of you. Never.
>> It's all pointless, isn't it? Really?
>> Yeah. There's never going to be a round
two of you. What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah, it will. How would there be a
round two of you? Like how? Well, okay.
Okay. Who would you have a round two with? Terry.
>> Uh, you know, Terry, you know, Prime
will be the first one. I'd have to go
back, I think.
>> No, let's say let's say Terry, cuz
Terry's more closer. Yeah. I would
actually, you know what? I will give
Terry money and I'll give you money. I
know he's damn I know his details
anyways. His full name and that, so
that's not a problem. I will give him
money and I'll give you money just to
see that actually happen just so you
can't. And I want it in a park as well.
Yeah. [ __ ] this. Say, so say if me and
Terry met yet and you had to put a bet
on, who do you think would win?
>> I'm not putting down any bet. Yeah, I
think Terry would win. I'm not putting
down a bet, though. But I think Terry, [laughter]
>> right? [clears throat]
>> I think Terry would win. I think Terry
would win. I think he would win. To be
honest, just because I saw him with the
first time, uh, he he was the aggressor.
You wasn't the aggressor. He had
>> But have you noticed? But listen listen
but Yeah, that's true. But have you
noticed these people kind of step back
when you retaliate? Like if you think
about it in a way, it's true, is it?
When did you retaliate?
>> When I stopped and then I gave him a
little bit back. That Terry did it. It's still retaliation.
>> When you gave him a little bit back.
What you talking about? When you gave
him a little bit back, that's when the
uh the the uh bystander was holding him
back because he was the
>> Listen listen listen to this. This is
why I don't want any street fights like
on the road and stuff. Do you know why?
Because if you have a street fight on
the road, nine out of 10 times someone's
going to get involved and they're going
to try and stop it and it might, you
know what I mean? And then it's not
going to be proper. Now I think
somewhere there's going to be one winner
and you can clearly see it. Go.
>> You saw a Monty and a rice thing, isn't it?
>> Yeah, that see even that
>> Monty. Yeah, but Monty won in it. Monty did win.
>> Yeah, of course. Of course [laughter]
>> he did win.
>> Yeah, but even that that's not a fight
to me though because number I didn't see
no clear. I don't know.
>> I don't think you guys have any fights before.
>> You know, you know, you saw it in it.
Um, when Tibby met Monty and Mike when
they all met up in it, Tibby Monty was
getting a bit scared. Did you see it?
>> You talking about years ago when they
met in a bus station like a couple of
months. No, no, no,
>> no. I didn't I didn't see that. I didn't
see it on the Great Guys channel.
>> I didn't No, I don't even know who that is. Yeah.
>> And he said and and and Money might
said, "Do you want to go for a drink
with us or do you want to do it dirty?"
You know what I mean? Doesn't it? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Money was getting a bit scared.
But Monty actually turns up. You know,
you have to give it to Monty. He does
actually turn up.
>> No, I know he does.
>> I think it's because he's thick, though.
I don't even think it's a brave thing. I
just think he's thick. That's why that's
why he does it.
>> Well, like that's why he doesn't get
scared, is it?
>> Yeah. [laughter] He doesn't. Yeah.
Because Yeah. You know, normal people.
Yeah. They have like a a six sense or
whatever. Like they weigh up their odds.
You know what I mean? Anything could go
wrong, right? I don't think he's got
that. I don't think he's really
programmed with that to think, okay,
like I don't think he's street smart,
you know what I mean? Like something
could go wrong here. So, he just does
it. It just meets up. [laughter] >> Yeah,
>> I'm book smart. I'm book smart and street smart.
>> You're definitely not.
>> Yeah, I'm street smart. Yeah,
>> you're you're definitely not.
>> I am.
>> You're definitely not because that time
when I came to the house. Yeah. Your mom
understood straight away what was going
to happen. But you didn't understand cuz
your mom said it straight. And I agreed
with her going to end in the house.
>> Yeah. Yeah. She knew. She knew straight
away. You didn't know that, but she knew.
>> Yeah. But you don't understand. If you
what would have you done if you broken
the house and there was seven people?
You would have got [ __ ] up. You was
not You wouldn't win. You was against
seven people. You know that it
>> someone would have got badly hurt. I'll
tell you that now. Do you
listen PJ? I'm going to be honest with
you. Do you not think Yeah. that I plan
with I I plan having a plan B. You know,
I don't just go like I'm not Do you know
who King Von is? I'm not stupid to just
gohead. I' I've been hurt before like
badly. Do you know what I mean? I'm not
stupid. I know what I'm doing. I have
plan B and plan C. Even when I come to
your house, you have change of I
shouldn't even say all that. But anyway,
>> yeah, but like what if my army friends was there?
>> Someone was going to get
>> I guess it I guess it will turn it will
go left and it will turn into something
else then. It definitely would because
I'm not coming out of there like
>> you would defeated it.
>> Even if I got defeated, someone's going
to be with me in that defeat. [laughter]
That's just that's what is that's what
I'm trying to tell you. It would have
just went left then, isn't it? Like it
would it would have went it would have
escalated into something else.
>> Okay. What about when I stood up to that
um gay neighbor and he didn't want any of it.
>> Well, PJ, that's what you say. I don't
even believe that.
>> Okay, bro. I don't believe it then.
>> You can ask your friend Paul then. He'll tell you.
>> But wait, but wait. Yeah.
>> I mean, when when you say you stand up
to people. Yeah. What? cuz you you you
talk up for yourself because there's
your neighbor that he lives uh next to
your mom's house, right?
>> And uh I remember one time he you he was
pissing him off and he was getting
annoyed cuz he can hear you through the
walls, right? And he came to
>> Yeah, but even that situation, what did
you do as a man? Do you think another
man listen? How could I do anything when
my mom when my mom
>> 20,000 excuses? Let me tell you
something. I don't care. That's not even
running. Listen, but PJ, that's what I'm
trying to tell you. That's not even
running in my brain. If someone comes to
my mother's house, I don't think we're
just raised differently, but if someone
comes to my mother's house and starts
talking any type of disrespectful
anything to my mother, my mother's got
to witness that or anything. Mom, you
know, my mom's the type of person that
she probably wouldn't even tell her
three her three sons. She wouldn't tell
her three sons. You know why? Because
she knows she probably wouldn't even
tell my dad, her husband. She probably
wouldn't even do that because she knows
just by her even mentioning that it's
going to it's just going to be peak.
It's just it's going to be crazy.
>> I'm not going to accept it
>> under any circumstance. I'm not going to
accept it. That means I've [laughter]
got to throw away my life or whatever
the nicest way is.
>> What if a fight Okay, then what if a
fight Okay, then what if a fight happens
and then they start um complaining and
I'm trying to tell you
are built different because I'm a type
of person. I I'm sometimes Yeah, I do
stupid reactions, but we're just built
different because I'm I'm just going to
have to go through the consequences
then, isn't it? I'm just going to have
to go through that's what I'm trying to
say. I try my best in life here to not
put myself in these type of situations.
But guess what? If they did occur, I'm
sorry, but I'm just going to have to
throw my life away or whatever, isn't
it? Because I'm not going to tolerate my
mother. It's just like I'm not going to
to you know, I just pray to God one day.
Yeah. But you see how when you're
running around in London, you're
mouthing off to these females. I just
pray to God one day that's not a female
that I actually know. I honestly do.
>> I mouthd off to two women and two guys.
You saw that?
>> Yeah, I know. But that's what I'm saying
is that's what I'm saying. I'm just
praying that it's never somebody that
did someone I know. Huh?
>> Did I lose with that one as well?
>> What? When?
>> When I was mouthing off to them two the
two guys and the two women that were sat down.
>> What? The security guard. >> Yeah.
>> You did lose to them.
>> See, that's what I'm saying. You just
make I told them to [ __ ] off back to
Newcastle. I stood up.
>> Oh. Oh, that that one. Okay, that's a
different one. Wait, wait, that's a
different one. That's a different one.
But then you're just acting like
>> security one. Do you know cuz they got
involved? No, no, no, no. I tell you
what happened. They was like, "Oh, knock
him out. Knock him out." They got
involved. I said, "They're not going to
knock no one out. Mind your own
business." They They actually buted in.
>> You do. You know, Do you think that what
you're doing? Yeah. When you're going
around, do you think that's what like
normal people do? [laughter]
>> Yeah. But you saw it in it.
>> I just think you're a jackass. Let me
tell you something. Do you know what?
No. No. Let me let me keep it real. I'll
be honest with you. You see girls
nowadays Yeah. in this modern era, do
you know they're very, you know,
sometimes when they're saying all this
extra stuff online and saying, "Oh,
yeah, these guys are very dangerous and
they're misogynistic and all that." Do
you know why they say it? Cuz I used to
think to myself, "How are we dangerous
and all that?" And I think now you're
just overreacting. You're the same
things. That's why men are not
approaching you anymore. But then when I
think about it, there's a lot of PJs in
the world. There's now now I think
people have got a big mouth as well.
>> No, no. Let me tell you something. Let
me tell you something. Big mouth. Let me
tell you something. Let me tell you
something. I'm I'm I was born in the
early '90s. Yeah.
>> But I think people every single person
that was born after 96. Yeah.
>> They've got like I don't I don't know.
They did this a bit weird in their head.
Yeah. Where now every girl that like the
reason why girls are saying these things
is because there's a lot of youth got in
the world now. This wasn't a thing when
I was I promise you this wasn't a thing
when I was young. Like I didn't see
>> if they stop if they stop running their
mouth then people No, let me give you an
example. Hey, did you see that thing on
the train with that woman? With me and
that woman. I'm sorry. Sorry.
>> She thought she's lucky I didn't knock
her out, bro.
>> PJ, you PJ, she
>> No. No. Hold on. Hold on. One second.
One second. One second. One second.
Listen. Listen to me. Listen to me.
Right. You're talking about women saying
this, brother. She was running her mouth
like she was bad and I had to tell her
about herself three times. Who is she,
bro? You never told her about herself, though.
>> I said she's an ugly crackhead. I said
it three times.
>> Yeah, that's cool. But then she was
ethering you by telling you how your
food is stuck in your building. And then
we saw the problems on the little jogging button.
>> Okay. One second. One second. Jogging buttons.
>> If you do it to another man and he
knocks you out, you're going to moan
about men. So why you acting bad? Stop
acting bad then. Don't act bad.
>> No. Yeah. I mean, yeah, that's true.
Because I do you know what? How my
sister is raised. Yeah. We do.
>> You didn't say no. No, but listen. See,
>> me and my brother I tell you I tell you
one thing. I tell you one thing. Even
Even Listen, my my children's mother and
my sister. Yeah. like like how how we've
raised my sister. Yeah. We've always
told her like if a guy is trying it on
with you or whatever, yeah, just be
respectful to him or whatever because at
the end of the day, if you start being
rude to him and he hits you or does
something crazy to you, we don't want to
get a life sentence because we kind of tell,
>> you know what I mean? So,
you're kind of right in that regard.
Women shouldn't be dumb. Don't run your mouth.
>> All she had to say, all she had to say
like, "Oh, can you just like move the
cows?" I I would have been fine, bro. I
swear to God, I would have been fine.
And she just started like saying
madness, bro. And then some guy got
involved. He got his head crushed in the
door as he walked out. His head got
crushed in the door, bro.
>> And there and there's too many white. Listen,
let me tell you something. Let me tell
you something. This is You know this
>> there's too many white lights. You saw
it in it. You saw it. There's too many white lights.
>> Let me Yeah, because listen,
>> this is London number one. Yeah. You
need to stop that behavior. This is not
flipping um you know there's certain
places you can get away with this [ __ ]
like in Wales or Coventry or this is
[ __ ] London. You need to stop. I'm
telling you good. Listen to me. Listen
to me. I'm telling you for your own
good. You need to stop that behavior.
Yeah. Because there is Don't you know
this is not essential around like
there's there's people that may you may
think they look like [ __ ] or
whatever. Yeah. And they will hurt you.
>> They would hurt you. It doesn't matter.
I'm not saying I'm not saying they're not.
>> Yeah. So you need to kind of just like
fall back with like running like just
doing all this craziness like
>> online is one thing but then you're
doing it in real life now because this
online stuff is making you grave. So now
you're you're actually mouththing off in
real life now. I'm seeing it a couple
times and I'm trying to let you know
like for your own good for your own
health. Yeah. You need to stop it
because there is some [ __ ] out here
that you may think they look like idiots
or whatever and they might just hurt
you. Now what if that girl Yeah. Because
you know we've got um internet on on
them undergrounds and stuff. Yeah. What
about if that girl decided to call one
of her because I assume she was like,
you know, she's she's an active uh what
do I like to call them? She's a she's a
hoodrat. Yeah, I assume it from how she
was talking. So, I'm saying what about
if that girl decided to call one of her
people to come and meet you at the next station?
No, but you would have shot it and you
would have been running.
>> Yeah, but they would have got there in time, bro.
>> Oh, you never know. You never know.
People could be meeting people. You
don't know. People do different things.
You never know. But did you hit that
that guy on the train? He was a white
knight in it. 100.
>> Not really.
>> Say I should respect women. I said she
started it. Mind your own business.
>> Yeah. Because he
>> good for women.
>> No, no, no. It's like it's like this. If
you see a man aggressive, it's just
you say, "Look, we need to redefine."
No, no, no. But she was
>> We need to redefine what S means and
what white knight means. Yeah. If I'm in
a public place and I'm seeing a man, I
don't care what arguments about. If I'm
seeing a man,
>> both of them. Tell both of them then.
>> Yes. But the difference is we've got
certain uh what's the words? Strengths
about us. When you see a man naturally
being aggressive, a fully grown man with
remember remember what you look like.
You don't look like a little boy, you
know. You a fully bearded out guy. Yeah.
You look a bit crazy at times, right? So
when they're seeing a man like you
talking to maybe I don't know, maybe the
girl was a little girl, you know, like a
little woman or something.
>> Normal. Yeah. Just like normal.
>> Yeah. That's what I'm saying. So when
they're seeing [ __ ] like that, they're
like, "Let me step in to either diffuse
the situation so you don't do nothing
crazy." Like that's just all it is.
>> I'm trying to let you know like
>> because sometimes what how you how you
um comprehend things. It's just it's
crazy to me how you you seem to think that
>> But then he could but then they could
get up end up getting hurt by doing
that, couldn't they?
>> Yeah, they possibly could. But you But
you're not that guy to do it, though. I know.
>> But they don't know that. They don't
know me. Yeah. Yeah. But that would be
that would be a lesson learned for them
if that was the case.
>> Well, try to look good for women, didn't it?
>> Yeah, that would be a lesson learned for
them, [clears throat]
>> bro. There was this woman on a train
here months ago and she was like
mouthing off. I mouthd off back and then
this black guy, he said, "Oh, can you
both stop it?" He said, "You and you." >> Yeah.
>> And that's it.
>> And they shut up. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Then cool. He said you and you.
Cuz a lot you know what I mean by a lot
of them bad o these women. Well some of
them bro she was acting bad in it. Bro
you can admit that.
>> I know I know your behavior as well
though. You forget that though. Like I
know your behavior. And I'll never
forget that one where that girl was on a
log and you felt like you were so
entitled to get her little pun tang.
Yeah. That you started
>> like you started shouting at her and
blaming her for every other female when
they've done [ __ ] to you. And you like
she was actually feeling scared. I felt
a bit bad for her. You know,
>> and you could clearly hear it was an
accent. She's not even from London.
>> I wasn't calling her fat and ugly, was
I? Did you remember what I was saying?
>> Doesn't matter if you was calling her
that, but she felt scared. You felt
>> in your little stupid brain. Yeah. Like
you honestly think, oh yeah, it's just
it's just me. There's no reason for for
you to be scared like type of thing.
Another person to be scared of you.
Yeah. But you don't know how you're
perceived by others that don't know you.
She don't know you. Like just like with
Morgan. Yeah. She didn't know you. She
actually genuinely thought that you was
a nutcase. Yeah. And then I had to
school her and let her know that now
you're really just a harmless person. [laughter]
>> Yeah. Well, you shouldn't act bad, bro.
Like, some of these people need to stop acting bad.
>> Not acting bad. She she she she saw me
for a couple hours and then she
disappeared. She She like, you know what
I mean? She gave you false hope. She
gave [laughter] you false hope. So what?
Get over it.
>> No, that's another thing. Any normal person,
>> just do the respectable thing. Just be
respectful, you know? That's all I ask.
>> Why are you respectable? Are you are you
respectable? Are you respectable?
>> Boasting is disrespectful.
>> Yeah, but are you respectable?
>> Yeah. Even people, bro, even when I've
gone to the toilet and walked out on
people, I think, you know, I gave an
explanation, you know, in the end. You
do, you know, you do.
>> But you're not a respectful person,
though. You're definitely not. You eat
with your mouth full. You don't even
have normal etiquette. Your room smell
like [ __ ] Yeah. Like, how are you a respectful person?
>> You're an idiot, bro. You're You're an
idiot. Don't be.
>> You're an absolute idiot. Is it?
>> So, you just you just you Yeah, I had to
warn Jane that you're just a harmless
person as well. >> Huh?
>> I'm going to warn Jane that you're a harmless person.
>> Yeah. Go on.
>> See what she says, isn't it? You're harmless. [laughter]
>> Go on.
>> Yeah. Go on.
>> Yeah. It's funny, isn't it?
>> Go on. Yeah. But the the difference is
I've never once said I'm going to beat
up J. That's the difference. See, she
actually, you know, I I would say that
she would tell you herself, but because
she's an actual liar and she run around
telling people that I'm a rapist and all
this madness. Yeah. Like I would even
say that she would tell you like Yeah.
Yeah. So, yeah, you're right. [laughter]
>> I don't I don't sit I've never sat
around aggressively doing what you're
doing and and start like saying I'm
going to beat you up.
>> I don't do nothing, bro. Huh?
>> I don't do anything. I just mind my own business.
You've done it to your own mother. I've
heard you even tell your mom like years
ago though. It was years ago, but you
said, "Yeah, I'm I'll punch you in your
belly and all this shit." Do you remember?
>> No, I don't remember that.
>> It's on one of Young Clipping channel
thing. Uh PJ,
it's on one of your little um fan pages.
>> Yeah. What? Laney, is it?
>> You're not like Leave Laney out of it, you bully.
I I wouldn't do nothing to her.
>> You would?
>> She's She's She's uh She's getting on
now, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Your mother is as well, isn't it?
>> No, my mom's nowhere near your mom's
age. How old is your mom again? 70 something.
>> How old your mom?
>> 60 something.
>> Oh, okay.
>> Then how old is your mom?
>> 63. 63.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Is that similar age? >> Yeah.
But, you know, Monty done the right
thing. I hope he doesn't come back on
it, you know.
>> Where is that guy?
>> I don't know. Like, he he should have
got off. He he blames me for getting him
on it, but I tried to get him off here multiple times.
>> What do you think?
>> Is he still with Natalie? >> Yeah.
>> Do you think channel? I want I want to I
want to watch her like she still know
her channel to be fair. Does she still
does she still do live streams and that talking crazy?
>> I don't I don't watch her. I don't have a channel.
>> You know what? She's a f She's cool. You
know, it's until she gets the bloody
drink in her system, man. She starts
going bananas. But she's actually cool.
>> No, I heard I heard she's got black flaps.
>> I don't know.
>> Listen, listen. But you know, if you was
Monty, would you blame me for getting
him on here? Cuz I tried to get him off
in it. [clears throat]
>> Everything's always your fault.
>> [ __ ] off, bro. You always blame. That's
what it is with you people always
blaming someone else. [ __ ] off.
>> No, it's your fault. It is. Everything
on here is your fault.
>> Oh, look. Nons is on here. Look. Typing. >> Yeah,
>> he's actually sick. You know, he's join.
Let him join. I guess he wants to join.
>> No, he's not joining.
>> No, let him join.
>> He's typing. He's typing.
>> It's a new year. It's a new year. Put
the link out. Let him join.
>> No, he's he's a nons.
>> All right, but let him join.
>> I've got I know a lot. Do you know, bro?
I've put up so much [ __ ] about this guy
and his stepdad. and everything.
[laughter] You know that?
>> Oh, you know what? I think that's the
period when I put you um when I put turn
your notifications off, so I didn't see it.
>> No. Yeah, he's got this [ __ ] um his
stepdad, you know, the one that used to
beat him from leads, David Campbell. I
met Bro, I messaged him and everything. >> Yeah.
>> Well, I know so much.
>> Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold
on. Ain't you the one that's complained
to me before when they're putting up
your pictures of your dead brother and
that? Yeah. And then now you're still so
you're messaging just you're not only
messaging Morgan's family, you messaged
his family too and other people then.
Yeah. So you kind of deserve it. You
can't really complain.
>> I didn't I didn't message Morgan's
family. That was my dog.
>> So when No, no. It's cool. No, no, no.
But this I'm just trying to make you
understand something. Yeah. Because you
always seem to think that you're in a
right that people just go out of their
way to do all this madness to you.
>> Her dad needed to know her dad needed to
know what her daughter was doing. Like
>> you messaged you message people's
family. So, it's only fine if they start
[ __ ] with yours too then, isn't it?
See, I don't mess with people's family,
but you do.
>> I mess with your stepdad. I mess with
>> Yeah. So, then you can't really complain
if it just keeps on going on and on from
from both of you, too, cuz you're both
never going to meet each other. So, you're both
one second. One second. I've tried to
meet him, bro. How can you say that?
>> Yeah, but I mean, you're both never
going to meet each other because he's
not going to accept it.
>> Yeah, he's never going to meet me. Yeah.
So, it's saying like he's never going to
meet me then, bro. Put it that way, is
it? Yeah, but you're not you're also not
going to meet many people that would
like to meet you on here. So, it's like
a vicious cycle, isn't it?
>> You know, I I've tried to meet him three
times. You know, you've seen it.
>> He will never meet anyone.
>> He's just going to carry on on YouTube for years.
>> Let him jump on. Let everyone jump on, man.
>> No one's trying to join. He's going to
continue being a
>> fantasy stories join. Did you say that
he was trying to join earlier?
Uh, no. He typed. We weren't trying to
join. And it's like, bro, [ __ ]
nonlegs went to Amsterdam just cuz I
went LT. He's a
>> That's another thing. You see, this is
how your childish brain thinks as well.
Yeah. I'm not Listen, I'm no way I'm no
way trying to stick up for the dude. I'm
just going to keep it real. Yeah. This
is how you're another way your childish
brain thinks. Listen, mate. If if he
followed you because you went uh because
you went to Amsterdam first, then that
means that you followed millions and
millions and millions and millions and
millions of other people there because
I've been there several times.
>> One second. One second. Can I can I say
something? It was this because it was
the first place he went, bro. What's the
chances? You went abroad. So you went
abroad, right? Yeah. So you go abroad
the first time. What's the chances that
you have gone to the same country in the
same city as as someone else?
>> Bro, I suppose I'm just guessing. I
don't know. But he probably done it
properly though when he went over there
cuz he I'm I'm just assume that he
didn't spend a day there. He spent spent
more time there. Yeah.
>> Well, I was in Amsterdam for 3 days.
>> He was there for two days. PJ,
>> I was in Amsterdam for three days. Bro,
>> you went on like a Friday.
>> He went to Amsterdam. He went to
Amsterdam for a week.
>> Yeah. Well, yeah.
>> I've never I've never been there. I've
never been there for a week before. I've
been there for like four days max.
>> Yeah. He's a copycat. He copies people.
You definitely copy.
>> Someone's copying because of that. It's
like this. Yeah. I take recommend I take
recommendations. Like for instance, one
time I went to Magaloo. I went to
Magalof. I went to Magalo when I was
younger. Yeah. I didn't know about that
place as such, but I got told about
Yeah. Yeah. It's a it's a it's a proper
spot. Blah blah blah blah blah blah.
This was like 2010 times. Yeah. And then
based on that from what what my friends
and all that told me, I went to Magaloo
the following year or a year. He's also
he's also put like
>> he's al he's also put celebrities on um
pedestals to copy. He's done that as
well. He's put
>> I heard you saying that [ __ ] as well.
Yeah. Yeah. The Cheryl Cole. I saw you.
>> That is copying. That is definitely
copying, bro. When I used to meet him.
Yeah, that is copying.
>> I mean you guys arguing about Yeah. Some
mad childish dumb. I don't care. I'm not
even going to [ __ ] like all I'm
saying I don't care. He just didn't want
to feel left out. I don't care, bro. You
know, some people like to fit in with
the crowd for an easy life, ain't it? I
don't give a [ __ ] bro. It's not, you
know, it's what it is.
>> The [ __ ] they used to argue about.
>> Do you know anyone? Do you know Do you
know anyone that's been Amsterdam? The
first holiday they've been on, but me.
>> Listen, people go different places for
their first time.
>> I'm asking you. I'm asking you. You
>> I'm sure one of my friends if I can
probably think, but I'm probably sure
one of my friends that was their first
spot. Yeah. What the [ __ ] Listen,
>> everyone's privileged to just get stuff,
you know. I know people
>> No, it's not made up. Not legs. No,
that's not made up. Go on. Sorry. >> Sorry.
>> No, I'm saying. Yeah. Not everyone's
like you see me. Yeah. Not everyone's
fortunate enough like like me um like my
my child, my youngest child now has been
fortunate enough to to to come to
Jamaica the last year. Yeah. But that's
what I'm trying to say. Not everyone has
these type of things. And then by the
time when they're old enough to get
their passport and do their own thing
and get their own money and stuff, they go somewhere.
>> Do you know what I mean?
>> Yeah, I get I get that cuz he couldn't
afford it until he was 30. He didn't
have the funds,
>> you know. That's fine. You know, it's all right.
>> But even if that's the case and you
eventually look, there's people that
there's people that are born and then
they die and not have um they've never
had an experience like that to go
anywhere. So, do you know what I mean?
Even if he took him to age 50, it's I'm
not saying it to him. I'm saying to
anybody if it took him to age 50 to go
away for the first time. Look how Okay.
Okay. Okay. You're cussing him about
being age 30. Yeah. To go to his first
place which was local. Yeah. Okay.
>> How old was your mother when she took
her first holiday?
>> I know this.
>> My my mom went abroad when she was a
kid. Three times.
>> No, that's not what you told me, mate.
>> No, no, no. She did. She went when she
was a baby.
>> You told me that the holiday to Spain
was her first time
>> in in 47 years. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, was it? Okay, maybe. Yeah, she went
she went when she was a baby and a
teenager and again she went three times
as a as like a very young but not like
>> Okay then or was it one of your sisters?
Was it one of your sisters that didn't
go somewhere then?
>> Yeah, my sister hasn't. I think she's
been to France with the school. Um
>> Okay. So So it must be that I'm talking
about she hasn't been anywhere.
>> Yeah. So you know I mean it's just
different strokes for different folks, right? >> Yeah.
>> Do you know what I'm saying? So
>> he he took the ferry LT.
I've taken I've taken a ferry. [clears throat]
>> I've taken a ferry as well. Taken the ferry.
>> I've taken a ferry before as well, but
No, no, not to not to um Amsterdam. To
France. I've taken a ferry to France cuz
I was driving.
>> Yeah, he he he took the ferry. >> Yeah.
>> Have you ever been on a cruise? They
look good, you know.
>> They look good, you know.
>> Oh, that's that's for old people. I
wouldn't do that [ __ ]
>> [ __ ] off old people, man.
>> Cruises are for old people. That's for
people that's retiring and [ __ ] What?
Bro, there there's the [ __ ] am I going
on a cruise board to live on a ship? The [ __ ]
>> There there's cruise videos. Yeah. And
them cruises are are massive, bro. Like,
>> listen. Listen. You'd have better time
just getting on a plane and going,
"Yeah, I know about cruises and stuff,
but that's for retired retiring people."
Um, my nan from Ireland. Yeah. She went
on a cruise like years ago. I remember
that like 20 years ago or something when she was
>> My mom's not 75. My mom's 65. Get right.
>> Yeah. I think I think it's the arthritis
that makes her look older.
>> But at least at least I ain't got a nons
[ __ ] parent. Your dad's a [ __ ]
nons. Your dad was 42 when [ __ ] he
met your [ __ ] mom. He was 12. You
dirty pedo. That's not even a joke, bro.
That is that is
a proper pedo. He's not trying to trying
to join. He's not trying to join.
>> Come on. Yeah. Let him win.
>> He's not trying. No one's trying to join.
>> I told him to join, man.
>> Yeah. Join, you [ __ ] skint virgin. Come on. >> [laughter]
>> You know what I mean? [ __ ] skin [ __ ] Do
>> you know you you both of you are such
idiots. Yeah. But it's quite funny
though. Like you know what I mean? When
you've not Trust me when I
>> I tell anybody. Listen, I tell anybody.
Yeah. Give this place a break. Give this
place a break for a while. Turn off the
notifications to people that you're sub
to. Yeah. And then come back and then
listen to the dumb [ __ ] again. Yeah.
It's actually quite it's quite amusing.
That's what I've got time for today.
>> You know, do you know do you know his
New Year resolution should be to get a
little part-time job? Get him some extra
money, you know.
>> What about you?
>> I've got I don't need I don't need a
part time job.
>> What normal person say they don't need a job? What?
>> Yeah, but he need he need
>> remember when I was doing two jobs at
one time. Go on,
>> dude. No, just a little part-time job.
You know, never hurt anyone. LG, a
little part-time job.
>> Listen, there's not enough money in the
I need more. Like, it don't matter.
Like, you know what I mean? I always
need more more more more. Do you know,
let me tell Can I Can I give you some game?
You know, you could be making money. You
see, you see, let me tell you something.
You see anyone that's into this little
trolling [ __ ] Yeah. You're not going to
make money off a trolling. Like, anyone
that's involved in any type of like
trolling content and stuff, you're not
going to make no money. If you want to
make some money, and I'm telling you
some game, jump on Tik Tok or jump on um
on those kick streams and all that. Then
you can make money. Do streaming and
stuff like you can make money. You could
talk mad [ __ ] as you well within the
rules and you can you can actually make
money off of it.
It's hard to make money on YouTube, you
know. It's very hard unless you're going
to get like a genuine following that's
going to like um send you donations and
stuff like that. But yeah, I'm just
giving you a game, man. I'm let you know
cuz my son, my oldest son makes money on
Tik Tok. He makes just from doing just
from doing football skills on it.
>> Listen, the the times for making money
from YouTube is over, bro. Like that was
like, you know, listen to me. You know,
when like let me tell you something. You
know, when like KSI and them lot done
it, bro, they they've done it years ago,
bro. Like all people No, no. People
still make money. But what I'm saying is
if you're doing this type of content
where it's just trolling and just
[ __ ] you're not no one's going to
make any more money.
>> For me, listen, for me to be
>> have some real content, man. Do some
videos. I do. Go on.
>> For me to be allegible. Yeah. When I
went on on my old channel, for me to be
elleible, I needed 10 million public
short views to be allegible. That's easy.
>> That's not easy, bro. I No, it 10 million.
>> 10 million.
>> No, no, no, no, no. They asking you for
watch hours. Watch hours. No, it was
viewers, bro. I promise you.
I was cuz it come up on the bar and I
was nowhere near. I swear to God, bro.
And I had I had like gambling.
>> It's not just shorts. If you just done
normal videos. Yeah. Nor, you know, like
what you was doing before your normal
content videos of your gambling, all
that [ __ ] and you just done and you
just kept them up and you didn't lose
them. You didn't lose your channel,
anything. You have
>> I was know I wasn't I was noeligible.
That's what I'm saying to you.
>> I swear to God, bro.
>> I wasn't. The reason why I say that, the
reason why I say that, cuz I know I know
people, yeah, that literally had like
400 subs at first and now they have like
uh 12,000 and they start making money
now. Like these are these are
bodybuilder fitness guys. Like, do you
know what I mean?
>> 20 years ago. 20 years ago.
>> No, not recently. Within the last year,
I've watched people literally start
their channels to show you.
[clears throat] I swear to God, bro, I
did try. But then but then what they do
is they tie their YouTube with their Tik
Tok now the cuz that's how you have to
do it now. You can't just rely on
YouTube because even me why do you think
I've tried to get away from these people
in it? Because anything to do with this
trolling and [ __ ]
>> You know you know you're laughing on
this now. Yeah. If you stayed on it for
another 3 days you wouldn't be laughing bro.
>> No but I wouldn't though. That's the thing.
>> Yeah. Common sense. See that's the
difference. That's the difference.
Common sense. I'm bored right now. It's
the festive season. And I've been off
work here for the past what nearly what
2 weeks. Yeah. So I'm I'm I'm at the end
now where it's like I don't even know
what to do with myself now. I just like
that's why that's why I like being
productive. I like having stuff to do.
Yeah. Because when I like the first time
you get the time off work, you know, the
first few days and that like it's it's
nice, you know, you can wake up and
>> it's it's different, right? But then
after a while because I'm so programmed
and so used to it yet, I start feeling I
don't know what to flipping do. Like I'm
I'm literally bored. I want something to
do. That's why I kind of borderline kind
of wanted some trouble with you today.
I'm not going to lie. I'm not I kind of did. [laughter]
I'm not going to lie. I can like That's
what I'm trying to tell you. Huh?
>> I I've unblocked you, you [ __ ] skin
virgin. You're not blocked. I've just unblocked everyone
>> for what? To to join.
>> Yeah, you skin virgin. I've just unblocked everyone.
>> What? Did you put the link up? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. The [ __ ] skin virgin ain't enjoying it.
>> I I low key would all the madness today.
I'm not even going to lie. I'm so bored
and [ __ ] Yeah. Like
>> what do you reckon would happen if you
stayed on it for a week straight? You'd start getting
>> I wouldn't do that. I wouldn't do that
to myself. Do you know the funny thing
is Yeah. I told you as well. I've never
unsubed from you. Like I'm subbed to
you. Yeah. But I turn off to
notification so I don't have to see
anything. Like nothing pops up on my
phone for a while. And it was like that
for a good week, few weeks. That's why I
disappeared. Listen, if I took a break
like you and I come back, I'd be
slagging off everyone lo. I'd be
slagging off every I don't like them, bro.
>> What's the point? I don't think about I
don't I don't live like these people. I
don't like sit around contemplating
what's going on there. Like I don't It's
none of my business. All I care about.
Yeah. I listen,
>> there was a time for me to be young and
there's times when I've even reflected
on my own behavior and I'm kind of
embarrassed about like letting people
being able to get to my emotions like
that. Do you know what I I'm kind of
It's kind of embarrassing when I've sat
down and I've I've reflected upon upon
my behavior. Yeah. I'm 34 years age
years of age. Do you think Yeah. that I
should be doing the same [ __ ] [ __ ]
that I was doing when I was younger?
>> You're an old You're an old man, bro.
>> Yeah. Like, yeah, I can probably say
that now. Cuz when I was your age, I was
calling people my age old, too. So, yeah.
>> You're like you're you're uh like you're
like two years off 36. Think about it. I'm basically
I'm this year this year I'm going to be 35. So
>> yeah, you're getting like you're going
to be like before you know it, bro.
>> I'm I would never be nothing like that,
dude. Should I tell you why? Because um
even I should even be saying this, but
my plans are Yeah. Like my first son was
trial and error. Yeah. My first son was
trial and error. He turned out good to
be fair. But my second son, I'm like me
and his mother is going to invest into
him and [clears throat] we're going to
try our best.
Your girlfriend's [ __ ] 34. Nods legs.
Jesus Christ. Your girlfriend's 34.
That is [ __ ] That That is old, bro.
Is it for me? That is old. Yeah. For woman. Yeah.
>> Hey. Hey. I don't know what you're
saying. Yeah. Cuz you're going to get
here to I told you I was your age when I
first joined this sector. I was your age.
>> No, but she's old. She is. She's
>> when I think about it now. Yeah. I was
your age. Yeah. And look how immature
you are. You make your little stupid sounds.
You sit on here.
Hopefully this year, nonsex, he gives
you some sex. Hopefully she gives you
some sex this year, lad. [laughter]
>> Do you do you know you're a funny guy?
Do you honestly think that's not happening,
>> mate? He's a [ __ ] virgin. He's never
had it in his life.
>> Do you know what? Do you honestly think
that's happening? Not happening.
>> 100% he is a virgin. 100%.
>> You're nuts. You know that? Like just
the things that go on in your head. And
you know what? There's no point trying
to persuade you either. Like if you One
thing I've noticed about you yet is if
you believe something yet, there's no
point arguing with you. Just let you run with it.
>> I mean I I mean I've proved I've had
sex. He hasn't. So
>> when when do you prove it?
>> Uh I put a video of me getting a
[ __ ] I've been in women's bed.
>> That's not sex. Paid for that. You paid
>> You paid for that. You paid for that,
>> bro. I didn't When I was in What? When I
was in Sig's bed. When I was in the
women's bed in Manchester. When I was in [ __ ]
>> I'm talking I'm talking about the brain,
>> bro. It doesn't [ __ ] matter if I paid
for it or [ __ ] not. I still got it. [laughter]
>> Yeah, but I don't mean nothing. I don't mean [ __ ]
>> bro. But it means Well, I mean, he calls
me a virgin. So, I mean,
>> and he's got a girl, so and he doesn't
have to pay. So,
>> he has he has a girl that you don't have
sex with. Yeah. I've had sex. He has
>> Do you honestly, PJ? I don't know what
world you're living in. Yeah.
Listen. Okay. Okay. Okay. Wait, wait,
wait, wait. You've told me yourself ages
ago. Yeah. You've even heard your mom
getting rumpy pumpy. Yeah.
>> Okay. And what?
>> So what I'm saying is right is people
have normal relationships. Do you
honestly think that's not going on? How
do you think you were made?
>> He has never had sex ever. Never had sex.
>> Jesus Christ.
>> I'm not proved I've had sex. Shouldn't
[clears throat] you be saying this about me?
>> So wait, wait, hold on. Hold on. So
wait, hold on. Who's more? So what? He
has to prove it. No. No. I just want to
hear this. He has to prove it. And I'm
not sticking up for the dude, by the
way. But I'm just saying he has to prove it. Yeah. >> Yes.
>> [ __ ] off, PJ. [ __ ] off.
>> Okay. So, but you got no problem when
when he's calling me a virgin, you biased [ __ ]
>> I don't get I don't even get involved. I
don't even get involved. I just laugh
when I'm calling him a virgin. I've
proved [laughter] because it's ridicul
because he's got a girl. I'm saying you
honestly believe that. I'm asking you
honestly believe that,
>> brother. Brother, I've had one night
stands. I proved I've had sex. He
hasn't. So, [laughter] like I'm more
likely to not be you are. You've had one
night stands. You need to prove to
YouTube that that this happened.
>> I swear to the day that I need to do any
of that stupid clown [ __ ] Yeah. I swear
to God. Yeah. I I'll run myself of this place.
>> Something is not going on in the
bedroom. And you've never seen Have you
seen Have you been in the bedroom? Have
you seen him have sex? >> No.
>> Well, there you go then. So,
>> I'm just making an assumption. A normal
man of age. And the reason why I say
a normal man of PJ PJ,
>> he's not a normal man. He's a skin virgin.
>> All right, cool. That's fine. But I'm
saying a man of a certain age. Even
Listen, PJ, I know you're going to find
this to be a fairy tale or whatever.
Yeah. But I I don't really like putting
my business out there like this or anything. But
>> So why does no one say anything when he
calls me a virgin then? Can I ask you
that question? Cuz I've been asking
>> I don't get involved. I don't get
involved in all that. I just laugh.
>> One second. One sec. No, no. Let me just
let me just
>> I don't even necessarily believe it to
be honest with you. I don't necessarily
believe it. So I just laugh. It's just a
joke to me.
>> No, no. I'll bring this up. Yeah,
because this has actually been going on
for the past 3 weeks.
>> I don't even care.
>> Wait, hold on. The bias. I'm
>> no this is this is what I'm trying to
say. How your brain operates. This is
how small your small minded your brain
is. Why do you even care? Do you know if
someone even calls me that, the first
thing I'll do is I would laugh. Like I
won't [laughter] even care.
>> I don't care. But I'm saying why are
people so um fast to stick up for him
when I'm calling him what he is the
virgin. But then when people call me it,
no one's anywhere to be seen.
>> It's because you're a crybaby. There's a
difference. You're you're a crybaby. We
hear you all the time coming on here
winging crying about everything. And
then you'll tell us all that you get
more [ __ ] than us. You get more better
girls than us. You live a better life
than us. We're all [ __ ] bald, fat,
skinn, uh what's the other one? Uh reclusives basically.
>> Yeah, most of the people here are. [laughter]
>> They are though. What are they not?
>> I don't know, man.
It would appear, >> huh?
>> Yeah, some of them are. It would appear
some of them are, but I don't think all
of them are. No, I think Listen, I think
the normal people that has kids and that
Yeah. How could you? This is impossible.
You know, you know if you have kids and
that yet you know it's not a cheap
thing. I'm just going to keep it real with you.
>> You know, you know, you know, have you
ever seen that account? How hard can it
be? He's actually a cool guy. You know,
he goes on Lord of J. That's the guy
that come my door.
>> Ain't that the one that met you before? Yeah.
>> Yeah. He's cool.
>> Yeah. So, when I'm saying that these
people are jealous, bro, I don't think
I'm better than anyone. I'm just going
off by what they do, bro.
>> Jealous of what? PJ,
>> bro. I'm younger. I'm better looking.
I've got a better life than them. I can
go out drinking. I've got
>> PJ PJ PJ PJ PJ.
>> Okay. PJ PJ,
>> you are not 21 years old. Okay, stop
saying this young [ __ ] Yeah, you
you're in my category now. My age range
now. No, no, no, no. You're in my age
range. Yeah, don't get [ __ ] not in
your age range.
>> Yes, you are. You're 16 years younger
than me. Exactly. Okay, this way. Put it
this way. When I'm 30 When I'm 30,
you're almost 40, Rob. >> What?
>> Put it that way. When When I'm 30,
you're going to be almost 40.
>> No, no, no. When you're 30, I'm 36.
>> Yeah. Which is almost 40. [laughter]
Yeah, if you want to say that. Huh?
>> Yeah. Well, 36 30.
>> There you go. And then I just turned 30.
>> when I told you my money, you're close
to 30. Yeah. You say I'm near 30. So you
just Okay. So yeah. No. No. Because
you're right. Yeah. You're right. Let's
round it up. Yeah. Yeah. Let's round it
up. Yeah. I'm more close when I'm 36.
Yeah. I'll be more closer to 40 than I
am to 30. But right now I'm more closer
to 30 than I am to 40. So And you're
close to 30, too. See? See? See what I'm saying?
>> See what I'm saying? I'm all close to 30
and you're close to 30. So, we're in the
same age range right now.
>> You know,
>> not that I care in it. Like, because at
the end of the day, I've lived my life.
I've done I've I've done all the stuff
that I'm supposed to do. You know what I
mean? I could have done more probably,
but like, you know what I mean? When I
look at some people, I think I've stuck
they don't believe nobody as well
because you've lived like certain way.
Yeah. And you believe that everyone else
is just lying and stuff like that. Like
when I tell you stuff that in my early
20s when I was in university and I there
was a skint days by the ways. Um I've
done all these lads holidays type of
things. I've done it. I've gone to
weddings man. I've I've gone to what do
you call it? Stad do and all that type
of [ __ ] [clears throat]
>> Have you done anything?
>> I'm I'm closer to 30 than 21. Yeah. And
how old are you?
>> Okay. And how old are you then?
>> Who? Me?
>> No, I just start typing. Okay. And how
old are you then?
>> Who's typing?
>> This guy? Yeah, man.
>> Do you think it's pathetic L begging for
money on YouTube?
>> No, I'll do the same. To be honest,
>> I could never lower myself.
>> No, no, no, no. I don't care.
>> Let me talk. Let Let me just put this
out there. Let me just put this out
there. Listen, let me just put this out
there cuz you know I'm a business type
of guy. Yeah. I'm a capitalist. Number
one. Yeah. Anywhere you can get money.
Yeah. I don't care. Just have multiple
streams of income. Do it. Do it. Yeah.
You're an idiot if you don't do anything
but you're an idiot if you don't do it.
You see me, didn't I say this earlier? I
said there's no
>> there's never enough time yet. Like I
don't care if I've got two jobs. There's
always a way here. Listen, I can have
two jobs. Listen to me. Listen to me. I
can I can There was a time when I had
two jobs and even now I'm sponsored by something. Yeah.
>> If there's another way for me to get
money for something else, I'll do that
as well. Do you know what I mean? If
someone's got begging.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Do you know why?
We're not begging. Money gives you a
much more freedom in life to do stuff,
to maneuver, and to do things. Do you
know what I mean? That's the honest
truth. You know what I mean?
>> I would never I would never
>> I can never remain I can never remain on
the same level. I have to keep going up.
>> Yeah. I have to keep going up.
>> How when I first entered this when I
first entered this little sector here,
Yeah. I was I I've been promoted twice
since then. So,
>> money doesn't Money doesn't bother me at all, bro.
>> Money don't bother you. That's cuz
you're not ambitious. I'm [ __ ] ambitious, man.
I'mious. Do you know why I'm ambitious?
Do you know why I'm ambitious? Because
I've got I've got stuff to live for.
I've got children like two I've got a
young one now. Yeah. And my younger one,
I want to give a better life than what I
gave to my older one. My younger one, I
want him to go to private school. So,
yeah. Like, I'll do everything. And I'm
not rich. I just need to stop thinking
that he's better than people and have
money when he's
>> think he's better than people. I don't
know. I don't watch him. How does he
think he's better than people? Explain.
>> Because he's calling people skin when
he's skin himself every day. Hey, and
it's not even just me.
>> No, no, but you forget this in this
little [ __ ] sector here. Yeah. Having
just basic minimum things is a flex to
some people. Should I tell you why?
>> Yeah. Of course you don't live with your
mom, bro. Of course you don't live with
your mom. You don't have no family.
>> Yeah. So, [clears throat] of course you
don't live with your mom. You ain't got
no family. So, how would you be living?
>> Do you remember all them years ago when
I put up like my praas and see when I
saw how much people were [ __ ] hating
and just chatting bad [ __ ] Yeah. I
thought to myself, wow, like in where
I'm from, you know, in London, it's like
a it's like a a fashion show in London.
Yeah. I just thought like that's just a
normal thing. Like, but when I come in
this sector and I realize that there's
so much people that are wearing busted ass trainers,
>> I'd rather live.
>> One thing about myself is I take pride
in myself. Yeah. You would I wouldn't
even come out my house if I'm not
looking [ __ ] sharp. You know what I mean?
>> I'd rather live.
>> I remember when Bomb said I remember
when I remember when Bomb said that he
got got haircut every week. Yeah. I
actually agreed with him because here in
London that's just quite that's a normal
thing like you have to get a shape up
every week. That's just normal. Do you
know what I mean? Or two weeks maximum
or two weeks maximum. When I saw when I saw people
>> I wore my haircut for ages.
>> Yeah. But that's you isn't it? Like but
I'm saying if you're
>> if you're some not even a somebody but
if you're just around people or you you
know you've got a social circle and that
like I thought that's is normal. I don't
know about like white guys and that
because I know that their hair grows
different and stuff. Yeah. But like for
for black guys and that that we have to
get our [ __ ] done every week or two
weeks maximum. That's just normal here.
But then we don't pay as much. We don't
pay as much as
cuz my white friends Yeah. One of my
white friends, he pays like um 60 quid
for his hair. Yeah. And but he gets it
he gets it done like every four weeks or
something. Whereas me I need to get it
done every week or two.
>> Yeah. I get the full service at the
barbers. I get like face waxed everything.
>> You get your eyebrows done. I see. I'm
not a hairy person. I need my eyebrows
and all that [ __ ] done. I don't even
have a beard like that. Like, you know
what I mean? And even >> Huh?
>> Yeah. Nothing. No, I'm just saying I get
it done every month normally.
>> Do you know the funniest thing? Yeah. Um,
do you know I change my look, you know?
Uh, you Yeah, I change my look. I I've
cut my hair like I've got a taper now.
>> Oh, you're a copycat, bro. You're a cop.
I go through different phase. I go
>> You're a copycat. You're a copycat.
>> Have you got a taper?
>> Yeah. When I go and I get a tape, you're a copycat.
>> I didn't even know that.
>> Yeah, you do.
>> I go through different phases. I go
through different phases. I grew my hair
like around lockdown times. I grew my
hair out a bit and I even had braids.
Natalie saw it. I had I had braids for a bit.
>> Bro, you're a big fat stinking copy. >> Why?
>> I I [laughter] get I get a taper. >> Oh,
>> so you're a big fat stinking copycat.
>> I didn't know.
That's funny, isn't it?
>> But I'll probably um Yeah, I'll probably
like I'll do something different again
though. But yeah,
>> like again afro is in it or dreads. >> Nah.
>> Oh, I was speaking to some I was
speaking to some black guy. Yeah, he's
from Belgium. I just call him Belgium LT, bro. >> Where?
>> I don't know, bro. He's got like
dreadlocks in it and he I speak to him.
He speaks English and that is it.
>> I'm wasting my best years, bro. You've
already wasted your best years. You're
in your 40s and you know PJ PJ PJ I
don't even think
>> I have done I've done more than you in
my in my whole life than you'll ever do.
And [laughter] I can tell you everything
that I've done as well. I have You can
laugh at it, but it's the truth. What
achievements what have you accomplished in life.
>> I can tell you, bro. I have done.
>> Listen, this is not a trick question
yet. I can just I can tell you just
things just off the If you was to ask
me, I'll just be able to just list them
just out. I've absolutely done more than
you. I used to go out three times a
week. Oh, bro. Trust me, I've done more than you.
>> That's normal. What the [ __ ] People do
that when they 18 or 19, PJ. What the [ __ ]
>> You know what I'm saying, bro? Yeah.
>> People do that when they're 18.
>> Let me tell you something. Let me tell
you. Let me tell you something right now.
>> It's not even experience.
>> Let me tell you something right now. Let
me tell you something right now. Yeah.
From 23 to 26, not one of these people
had my life. I can tell you that. [ __ ]
off, DJ. Man,
>> I had more money. No, no, no, no, bro.
Bro, bro, right now, listen. I had more
money. I was going out more, bro. I'm
being I'm being serious. I'm alive. I'm
>> going out there's not even that's
nothing that's what normal people do in
in in their teenage years and and early
20s that's what normal people do you
start going out late in fact cuz I'm the
one you forget I'm the one that put you
on to some of these places
>> you don't need to feel sorry for someone
younger and better looking than you bro
feel sorry for
these people I'm the one that put you on
to short ditch in these places like I
cuz I've been there
>> yeah when I was 23 yeah
>> yeah you would have doing that [ __ ] when
you was [ __ ] 16 I've been doing that
[ __ ] when I was 16 too young to get
What are you talking about? >> Huh?
>> I never said I was.
>> Oh, but I'm saying this is when you're
saying stuff like that's normal behavior
for the average person that's like a
teenager or or early 20. That's normal
behavior to go out and [ __ ] get [ __ ]
wasted and do all that binge. What's it
Have you ever been on a bender? See,
you've not done that before. I have.
>> Yeah, I have.
>> You've what? You've done a free a free night bender? >> Yeah.
>> In In what? In nightclubs. What
nightclubs have you gone to? Go and tell me.
>> I have. Well, it doesn't matter what nightclubs.
>> No. No. Come on. Come on. Come I know
all of them in London. All of them in
London. I know them. So go on, tell me.
>> You know, it doesn't matter, bro, what
ones I've been to.
>> You ain't never been to Scar or
Gilgamesh or any of these type of
places, have you? You ain't even been Go
on. Go on. Do you even know about us in
Enfield? Well, it's not there anymore.
>> I've been to Simmons. I've been to the
Swan. I've been
>> Simmons ain't even a nightclub. Simmons
ain't even a nightclub, mate. You're
talking about little [ __ ] bars and
that turned into a grub. It turned into a grub,
>> bro. It's not like an aquarium or
something like that, though. Is it,
>> bro? I can chat to you about women.
You've never had a girlfriend. I've had
more women than you.
>> Oh, I can talk to you about women every
day of the week. I've had more of them
than you. And I've proven it. See, all
of the things these people talk [ __ ]
about, I've proven it. More money, more
women. And you still are.
>> You see when you're saying you prove it?
>> No. No. But you see when you say you
prove it. Yeah. Do you do you know how
this guy is so childish? Listen, you see
when you say you prove it, right, in
this life to prove this type of I can
talk about women as much as I want cuz
I've had more women than you. You've
never even had sex. See, this is what I
mean with these people. It's just self projection.
>> Oh Jesus, man.
>> Listen, I can I can talk to you about
women every day of the week. Even can't
get a woman. Even Even L can't get a
>> None of these people can get a woman.
The man's got kids, man. Listen,
one second. One second. One second. Have
you seen these kids? Have you met these
>> Let me let me say something to you.
>> One second. Let me tell Let me tell you
something. Let me tell you something.
Let me tell you something. For the
average person, yeah, you see when
people have kids, do you think that was
their first rodeo with that woman or
something? Do you think that was their first rodeo?
>> What's his kid's name? Cuz you said that
he's got kids. You know him. How do you
know his kids? I'm
>> these kids on the thing. You always do
this. Listen, listen, listen. I take
people at face value. Most normal people
are not going to lie about having kids.
normal people. Yeah. And I've heard I've
heard the child come on when he was on
earlier. Did his child not come on and
call you a stinking
>> M? Bomb has lied about kids and he's kid.
>> Yes. Because he's pathetic. Yeah. Yeah.
He's pathetic. But I'm saying the most
normal normal person is an Irish M.
>> Yeah. PJ,
let me let me say this here. I just
heard you were talking about nightclubs.
PJ, remember me and B were talking about
nightclubs to you in London and you
said, "Yeah, I've been to the ministry."
And then you looked it up and you said
it's only open 9 to5 because you looked
up the Ministry of Defense cuz you're a [ __ ]
>> I'm a [ __ ] Really?
>> Minister of Castle.
>> All right. Tell your Tell your Tell your
kid. I said that it's [ __ ] ugly and a
[ __ ] Dad's going to do nothing about
it. And daddy's going to do nothing. Say
those words. Say those words.
>> Bro, you you went to my door and you
stood behind the gate. You done nothing.
Stop repeating your door.
>> Stop repeating. We're over this. We've
been over this. We've been over this.
We've been over this. We've been over
>> I'm saying I'm saying that
I'm saying that your kid is bastic and
it's daddy's going to do nothing. PJ say
it to his face and you didn't
I said I told him to [ __ ] up my face.
>> I told him to [ __ ] off to his face
when he was halfway down the damn room.
I told him to [ __ ] off the corner
the corner and he shouting come back
come back and I walk around the corner
and he walked back into the house
and you wouldn't you wouldn't even
>> you wouldn't even put your camera on
you 26 and I'm saying that your kid's a
stinky dirty ugly mug and daddy's going
to do nothing
when your when your neighbors when your
man's neighbors get the letters you're
going to be homeless
>> yeah okay [laughter] you keep telling
yourself that you bro the neighbors the
neighbors already know everything
>> you know what I'm saying huh
>> you need a shrink
>> no bro not at all you come in the door
and you done you come in the door and
you done nothing
is for you to go outside and be a man
listen why do I need to explain this to
you because you supposed to be a man and
go outside because you are supposed to
be a man and go outside and have your business done
as well. You've done nothing.
>> DJ, you you know where I have a house.
Why haven't you been at my door? You stood behind
the door. What was the point? No. What
>> You might as well just start saying he
hid behind his mother. Man, you might as
well see that.
>> I was in front of my mom. I Well, I was
in front of my mom, so
you stood behind. You behind your mom and you
I behind lady. I was in front of my mom.
I mean, I was in front of my mom trying
to get me.
>> I was in front of my mom. Okay. And you
weren't about it.
>> You stood behind the gate and you done
nothing. You wasted Barquest's money, [laughter]
>> brother. You You were stuttering. You
stood behind the gate and you ran off.
>> Was it your front door?
>> Yeah. And you stood behind the gate and
you could have kicked me a million times about it.
Listen. Imagine you through the letter
box. Listen. I was on YouTube. I was on
>> Imagine your front door and I opened the
door. I opened the door and I told you
to [ __ ] off and I told you I told you to
[ __ ] off. I opened the door and I told
you to [ __ ] off. I didn't need to open
the door. Listen, if anyone was scared
of you, why did I open the door and tell
you to [ __ ] off? Why did I get cheeky to
your face though?
>> Did you,
>> brother? Listen, he [clears throat] he
had to talk to crazy.
He had several chances to kick the door
in my face.
>> That's what I said before. Why does he
have to do Why should he have to go to
the extreme? Why did you have to go?
What's going to happen is you and your mother.
I was more than happy. Okay.
>> I was more than happy.
>> I was your mother was calling the police
anyway. So why should he have to go to
the extreme to do something crazy,
>> brother? You come in the door and you've
done nothing. It's not even a W. It's
embar Okay, come back now then. Come
back now. I'll send you the money and
come back now.
>> Here we go. Go.
>> You stood you stood behind the gate and
done nothing. It's not a W. I would not
go to America and hide behind someone's
gate. I would not and I'm telling you to
and I'm telling you and I'm telling you
I would not go to America to hide behind
someone's gate saying I would not go and
hide behind [laughter] someone's gate.
Listen listen brother he didn't damage
my property. I was happy.
>> Why should he? Because he didn't do
anything. Okay. Okay. Fine. And I
damaged your property and you still
didn't come out. So now what?
>> He didn't do anything. >> Okay.
and you still
everyone that's listening, if PJ sends
me the money, I'll come.
>> Yeah, you come and I'll send you the money.
>> No, you just said I'll send you money
and I'll send you the money.
>> I told you about it. You didn't say that.
>> You stood behind the gate and done
nothing. Stop. No, that's an L. You're
not a winner. You're not a winner, bro.
Listen, you're not. If I played If I
went to another country,
listen, even you see all the trolls that
even back you. Yeah. Even they know deep
down in their head.
>> I don't give a [ __ ] I never Bro, he
stood behind a gate. I don't care what
anyone says. He had several charges to
hit me. He had several charges outside.
>> He had several chances to hit me.
Listen, let me show you something. Let
me tell you something. He showed more
respect than I did to to you. I tell you
why. Because he actually tried to do it
properly. He tried to be a bit more
respectful because your mother was there
and he said, "Come outside."
>> And he done nothing. And he done
nothing. And he done nothing. He done
nothing. Me personally, I like me
personally, I was at your front door.
Like I was standing outside. I already
learned from this.
>> If I went If I You would have done nothing.
>> I would not hide behind the widow with
you. I would not hide behind I would
windows and I would break nothing.
>> EJ, you would have done nothing.
>> I wouldn't do anything. Okay, bro. Okay.
Well, he done nothing then. Well, he done nothing.
>> Okay. But he came though, so I still won up.
>> He came and he done nothing. He came and
he done nothing. He still up because he came
to come and say all this madness and you
stayed inside. You played the victim if
I remember correctly. You victimity, bro.
>> Listen, you played the victim.
>> Okay. So, why did you play?
>> What was the excuse why he didn't kick
the door on my face again?
>> You turned into a Karen when he came to your doorstep.
>> Acting like you don't know why you're
dead. You acting like you don't know why there.
opened the door and told him to [ __ ] off. [laughter]
>> Re-watch the video, bro. Rewatch the video.
>> When he comes when he when he
>> This is how I know. Listen, listen.
>> I'm unbiased. Don't even bother trying
to say I'm biased cuz I'm unbiased and
I'm telling you what I saw. I would not
go and hide behind the gate. That is not
winning. That's not winning. That's not about it.
>> No one behind the gate in your own
little small little bra.
>> In your little in your little world, you
think that's a win, bro. Anyone can
knock anyone's door. You're not normal.
In normal world,
In normal world, in normal society, he
showed you that you're the big mouth.
That's what happened. Everybody on here
has showed you that you're the big
mouth. Everyone has.
>> What did I say I was going to do to his kids?
>> Harry has showed you
I'm sick and tired of hearing this [ __ ] from you.
>> What did I say I was going to do? [laughter] Absolutely everything.
Every time you take an L. Yeah. You got
an excuse. Terry does something to you.
You still think you won. Does something
you think you won. I have done something
to you think he won. Prime does
something to you and you say, "Oh, you
wasn't ready for it." J does something
to you. You think you won never gave me,
>> you know.
>> Yes, he did. Everyone has. Everyone need
to come outside and kill him. I Bro, we
go around. No one said you had to kill.
Listen, bro. Only in your world. You
think your boyfriend won. Only in your
world. No one said no one said you had
to kill your boyfriend.
He didn't have You told him to come out
and have a boyfriend stood behind the
go. in your world. You up in your little
brain. You weigh it up in your little
brain. Yeah. I would never go in and
hide behind the gate. So you go [laughter]
to me. I told him to [ __ ] off. It's
okay. I told him to [ __ ] off and he did.
I told him to [ __ ] up and he did.
>> Your knuckles are not built for the
punching power. So I understand.
>> At least I don't stand behind the gate.
Repeating myself. At least I don't stand
behind a gate. Even I've done more than that,
>> brother. He literally stood behind a
gate and he had several chances to hit
me and he never
>> The only time I saw you at that house.
The only time I saw you come outside
that gate is when he was halfway down
the road saying
the only time I saw it. That is the only
time I saw it. Yeah. Listen, I'm not
just making these things up. This is
[laughter] the video. Everything
everything I've just said now by the
video. See, that's why it's good to have
video. You know, I I say to people,
don't take your video. I'll put the
video. I tell people, no, listen. I tell
people all the time, yeah, if you want
to do madness on here or anything, yeah,
do not record it. But at the same time,
when it's PJ, you have to record it
because you say that you come in the
door and you've done nothing. I I'll
gladly record it.
Well, we're all
>> I will gladly play the video. I will
gladly play the video. I stood in front
of my mom and I told him to [ __ ] off and
I spoke about his kids. I'll gladly play
the video. I'll gladly play it.
>> Listen, for just your mom shaking alone,
you should have went out.
>> I stood in front of him and I told him
to [ __ ] off. He went nowhere near me. You went
forcing me. Stop force as strong as you
boy. Stop lying. You never told
>> Did you go outside? I said I was going
to rape a man's kids and he done nothing.
>> Elbow. Are you serious?
>> Are you serious? He literally done nothing.
>> Did you say to his face? Did you say to
his face? Did you say to his face?
>> I told him to [ __ ] off to his face and
he did. And I told him to [ __ ] off to
his face. Yes, I [ __ ] did.
>> He wasn't leaving that door frame, mate.
What are you talking about,
>> brother? The door was not shut two times.
>> Wait, wait. What's the excuse then? What
was the excuse then when the door
weren't shut two times? What was the excuse again?
>> My my my excuse for that is why should
he have to do anything abh no no no my
my I'll just explain to you my excuse
for that is why should he have to why
should he have to do anything extreme
and kick your door? Why should
[laughter] Why should any of us have to
do any of that?
>> Well, you do the door you travel you
talked about Yes. He talked about his
kids and I told him to [ __ ] off and I
told him to [ __ ] off and he didn't. He
came and then he [ __ ] off.
>> He came to test your temperature to see
if you're about that business as
>> I opened the door to [ __ ] off. I open
that stuff to him to [ __ ] off. I opened
the door and I told him
>> it's not for him. Listen, even if he did
kick that door through, as I said
before, you and your mom are complaining
>> cuz you're not about it. He's not about
>> You and your mom are complaining to the
police saying they're going to play the
victims. Bro, stop using
if you was worrying about the police.
>> If you was worried about you wouldn't
come here acting bad. Stop using the
police as you thought bad.
One second. One second. One second. Bro,
how many times have you people called
the police on me? I got nicked the day
before. [ __ ] out of here. Don't use that
excuse, brother. I got nicked. PJ, you
are no threat to me. I would never
listen. Don't even talk about police.
L's followers have called the police.
Yeah. Don't even try. I know they have,
but he has even try and use this.
>> Yeah, I got, you know, I was arrested
that that night before and you're
talking about Listen, he come in the
door and he done nothing. Done nothing at all.
>> What's he supposed to do, PJ? Huh?
>> Bro, he had chances to hit me, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Yeah. When he when he towards you,
listen, when he advanced towards you,
you were there trying to shut the door. So what?
>> Okay, bro. Okay.
>> You left it alone. Whatever. Okay.
>> Keep that door in your face and your and
you got hurt or your mother got hurt, guys.
because I'm right and you're wrong and
it's like trying to trying to explain
something to you right the door. He come
the door and he% right. Every single
person every single personally done nothing.
>> Every single person I have played it to.
>> He come the door.
>> He come in the door and he done nothing.
>> Every single person I played
>> and I never learned my lesson. And I
never learned my lesson either. Think
about it. I never learned your lesson.
We you you got shown to be a little boy.
You got to be a little boy. You keep
saying that you've never learned your
lesson. Listen, this is what I'm saying
to people out there. If anyone does grab
this guy yet, do not give him any mercy.
Cuz there's many times I've just felt
sorry for him and it's like, man, I
can't I don't
give this guy any mercy. This is what
you're going to come out with. When you
if you give him mercy, sometime he's
going to be humble for that second, but
then later on down in life, he's going
to be running his mouth again saying
that you didn't do something to him, you
didn't hurt him, and all this nonsense.
So, if anyone does eventually does grab
him, you you have to go fully in with
this guy. And to be to I mean
>> I hope it isn't me. I hope I never bump
into you to be honest with you. Like
what's the point behind the gate?
Bro, if I went Okay, listen. Okay,
listen. Listen. All right. You give me
someone's address. You reckon I'm
knocking on the door saying, "You got me
out. You got me out." HE DONE NOTHING.
He done nothing.
>> EJ, do you want me to give you my
friend's address? I've done that stuff
to your mom. Do you want me to give you
his address? Do you want me to give you
his address that I've done that stuff to
your mom? Do you want me to give you his address?
>> Okay, if you want to. Yeah, you can
email me. Yeah, I'll give you his
address right now. Yeah, you going to go
to his house?
>> I'm what?
>> You going to go to his house?
>> Listen. Yeah. And Triple H, it's another
thing. Yeah, I will. Yeah, go on. Email me.
>> You going to go to his house today? Yeah.
>> Triple H, if someone went on your mom's
door, you wouldn't even come out. You
wouldn't even open the door. One second.
>> That's a jail sentence for me.
>> Listen, PJ, you don't know me, man.
That's a jail sentence for anyone that I
know. You would not even open the door. Triple H.
>> It's not Listen, you don't have to be
big, bad, and tough. It's just any
normal [clears throat] person that was
grown up with their family or something.
Your mom is listen I grew up with my mom
and dad. Yeah. But if my dad can more I
would say my dad can more handle
himself. I wouldn't be angry. It's like
I would still be angry if someone
attacked him or something. But he's a man.
My mother gave birth to me. It's a
different type of love that I have for
my mother. Do you not understand? I I
would risk it all for my mother. You
know like it's it's different. It's a
lot different than you think.
>> If you are you're not built like that.
You wasn't raised like that. You wasn't
I can tell you wasn't raised like that
because you ran away from raising
my mom. I would have to die for my mom.
I don't care. Like I'm just being honest
with you. I would have to die.
>> If I went on anyone's door in this
community, they wouldn't even open the door.
>> EJ, I promise you right now
they would not open the door. They would
open person. I would open my door and
drag you inside and and
>> these people would never open their door
to no one.
>> You know, they would not. They're just
spastics. They're just losers. These
people are fat and ugly. They would
never open their door. They're in
wheelchairs, bro. Half of these people
in this community, [laughter]
>> they are though. They would never open
their door, bro. They would never open
their door. Never.
>> What for? For you? >> Anyone?
>> I don't think anyone they would be fair.
>> Why? What would they be so scared about
you? Like, what's so scary about you?
>> Because I'd be able to see their ugly
faces and expose them and [ __ ]
>> No, PJ. People just wear a mask.
>> Yeah, but I'll take a mask. I've got a
single ball of clavas in my house.
>> You know what I'm saying? Well,
>> I'll take the mask off then.
>> How are you going to do that when you're
not, you know, you're not physically
strong enough? If you're not physically
strong enough to do, there's only people
on here that's probably going to be
stronger than him. So, what the [ __ ]
>> This account is stupid. I can talk about
women as much as I want in this
lifetime. I've had more women than you.
>> It's the same argument with you people.
This is what I mean with you people.
It's just the same boring argument, bro.
You're just boring, bro. This is what I
mean. It's just boring. It's just the
same repeating [ __ ] Yeah,
>> PJ, you got to better your life, man.
>> These people need to better their life
on YouTube 24/7. No matter
>> I'm saying that. I'm saying that. Yeah.
Because generally speaking, Yeah. I've
listened to you for years now. Yeah. And you're
>> Okay. Prime showed One second. One
second. One second. One second. You
people knew my address, right? Before
that Prime thing, before the LT thing.
What was the excuse then, you little [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I remember the excuses. I'm not
even going to lie. I do remember the excuses. But
>> But still, no. Remember though, remember
that before you, before Prime, what was
the excuses then? You little fatty
[ __ ] What about then?
>> But but but listen PJ,
>> before that. No, before that, was it?
>> Listen, listen. Listen to what I'm
saying. You need to get out.
>> You need to find purpose. I'm being real
here now. Like, you need to find some
purpose in life, bro, because you can't
keep doing this. Is sending you crazy.
You don't understand.
>> I hate these people. I hate I want to,
bro. You know what I'm saying? I hate them.
>> Listen, listen to what I'm saying.
>> I [ __ ] hate him, bro. Like, I was
saying this to my sister. Yeah. I would
love 10 seconds and [ __ ] one of these
people up. You don't understand. I hate
them. I hate LJ. I hate these ugly kids.
I hate everything about them.
>> Why don't you put your energy into
something else, man? Seriously. Like
this is not this is this is not it. You
can't keep going on like this.
>> Ugly people. These little I hope they
all get cancer and die, bro. I hope they
die. All of them.
>> It means nothing. Yeah, you're just
angry. It means nothing, man. Shut up.
>> I hope they all die of cancer. And I
will say it calmly as well. I would say
this calmly. I hate them. I do hate
them. I hope they all get cancelled and
die. I hate
>> Are you gonna be the one that gives it to them?
>> But how's that possible, bro?
>> I'm just chatting [ __ ]
>> How How is that possible? No, seriously.
I'm actually I'm actually being serious.
I'm not even joking.
>> You know, you're saying stuff You're
trying to say stuff about me yet. Okay.
When you're trying to say stuff about
What about these people on YouTube 24/7?
>> Fat go live. Like I can't really listen.
They don't go live.
>> They don't go live. Yeah. I'm actually
taking time out my day because I'm
bored. Yeah. And I'm actually trying to go.
>> Normally, you know, normally I would
just normally I wouldn't even care to
even talk about any of this stuff or
even like sit and waste my time. Yeah.
I'll just I'll laugh a bit and then I
would disappear. Yeah. But now I'm
actually so I can go through this [ __ ] with you. >> Huh?
>> Yeah. But they go in other people's lives.
>> Yeah. But do they join and like
>> do they do they host live live streams
themselves? I don't think they do. Do they?
>> Yeah. But the thing is Yeah. You for for
a number of years you've provided
everybody with great entertainment
whether you like it or not.
>> Yeah, they have provided me great enterainment.
>> Somebody I wasn't watching. Somebody
texted me saying you're looking
addresses to go to. I'll give you my address.
>> Right. Shut up. We've already been
>> I live 43 Blackwood Street in Belfast.
>> Yeah, of course you do. Yeah, you give
your address on YouTube. Yeah. Yeah, of
course you do.
>> It got you. You would have to cross the
sea for that.
>> And you would do I'll give you my address.
Oh, Lenny was shouting at him.
>> PJ, you're not about
>> I've already Yeah, I've already crossed.
Yeah, I've already crossed the sea. when
>> Yeah, lad.
>> Remember, bro, you was in You was in the
airport biting your teeth. You're so
scared to fly. You was biting your teeth
before you went.
>> When did you cross? When did you cross the seat?
>> LT this I've already been on for I don't
know why you keep Yeah. Same argument, same bing.
>> You're afraid of flying. Sorry,
>> bro. Listen, you was biting your teeth
before you went on a plane. You're
scared of flying. Just cuz you went on a
short 10-hour plane ride to shitty Vegas
for five nights cuz that's all you could
afford. Doesn't mean anything.
>> Well, you go you go over there then if you flight,
>> bro. It's the same argument. You people
are so boring. You know that. You ain't
got nothing new to say. It's so boring. Is it
>> Wait, hold on. Hold on. Hold on. You're saying this?
>> You actually so boring, is it?
>> You're saying this
is no one makes no one quiet. Listen,
listen. Players, you was on YouTube
Christmas, you sorry ass loser with no
girlfriend, no life. Your sorry ass was
on YouTube Christmas cuz you got no
family. You and stop sucking L J's dick,
you [ __ ] lo. You know why you like L
J so much? Cuz you're lonely like him.
Lonely, ugly people on here. That's what
you are. Lonely, skint, ugly, no family,
no girlfriend life on YouTube Christmas.
I can put the video back up if you want.
I can put the video back up. >> PJ. >> Yeah.
>> You see Charlene, she was making some
curry go the other day. Did you see it?
>> Play. Yeah, I did. Players, why was you
on YouTube Christmas? Tell everyone why
you was on YouTube Christmas, you little
bully victim. Cuz you ain't got no
family. Why was you on YouTube
Christmas? You little bully victim. Tell
us. Tell us why you was on YouTube
Christmas. You absolute victim. Yeah,
you absolute bully victim. Why was you
on YouTube Christmas?
>> PJ, if you come to I'll bring my son.
I'll bring my 13-year-old son. He can
watch me beat you up.
>> I don't think that's fair that you let
Bro, you behind the gate. You were
shaking behind the gate. You're not beat
up or I'll let him beat you up. Either way,
>> I would I would
kid with one hand. I would come on Blackwood,
>> bro. I would literally re do you anyway.
I would be your kid's new daddy.
>> I say I'll let my son be your kid's new
dad. How about that? >> Tiger.
>> Yeah, please. You don't have a
girlfriend. You've never had a
girlfriend like Lord J. You've never had a girlfriend.
>> J couldn't beat Tiger. Tiger be a dirty markers.
>> Lord, Tiger done more than you. You
stood behind a gate and done nothing.
>> That's because that's Yeah, that's you
allow anyone to get hold of you.
>> Players. Players, where's your
girlfriend? You ain't got a girlfriend.
You're too ugly. You're probably still a virgin.
That's another thing as well. You assume
people haven't got stuff because they
don't want to do videos and put things
out on YouTube. Let me leave that to
you. You put things out for us to watch,
>> you know, cuz you're talking about
yourself. Oh, wait, brother. You don't
have a girlfriend. You're lonely. You
was on YouTube Christmas, Mr. Lonely on
YouTube. No family. No Christmas dinner
for you. Lonely. That was entertainment
for me, to be honest. Coming on like
Coming on YouTube Christmas, seeing
people like you without a family. That
was so entertainment. I loved it. No
family, no girlfriend. And you know, I
get to you as well. You know, simple,
bro. You people must be so bored on
here, is it?
>> New year, you're still doing this.
>> I've literally I've literally
>> You people must be so bored, bro.
>> I've literally come on today. Yeah. To
see the [ __ ] Yeah. And it's
actually it's it's quite fun. I'm not going to >> madness.
>> It's fun. It's fun. But I can't do this.
Is the thing that I couldn't I couldn't
do this like two, three days on a on a truck.
>> I'm trying to get away from them and
they won't leave me alone. This is why
I've told you before. I've told you
before, when you do something, when you
start doing getting productive and doing
something, you're 28. Yeah. How long are
you just going to keep doing the same [ __ ] for?
>> Bro, they keep drawing me out. These fat
ugly geeks other people. You have to
take accountability for yourself. Yeah,
>> bro. But you're on my live every day.
So, what does that say about you? You're
on my live. So, that shows that you've
got no life then. That shows that you've
got no life.
>> And it really, if you think about it, if
you're on my live every day, that must
mean you ain't got no life then, is it?
>> This is these people that are typing.
But in the
>> You know what I'm saying? If you're
going to say something, can you stop leaving, please?
>> Yeah. I'm going to say what the [ __ ] I'm
going to say. What's the last thing? Uh
oh, [ __ ] sake. I forgot what it was now.
I had something lined up there for you.
>> No, I forgot. I'll be back.
>> See, it's [ __ ] stupid.
>> PJ, look. What the I'm not calling you.
What you need to do is just just stop
getting so angry and calling people out.
Just stop it, man. Just behave. Like, at
the end of the day, look, you're not no
longer by yourself anymore. You're at
your mom's house. Yeah. Stop inviting
people to come to your mom's house.
>> No, they never they're never going to come anyways.
>> No, no, no. You can't say that. If it
does go wrong, I can say it.
>> No, you can't. No, you can't. Could you
say the same [ __ ] to me as well and just
try to wind people up to come?
You need to stop that because if they do
come if they do come if they do think
about this this is the last I'll say
about it you're always on nobody can get
a girlfriend everyone's a virgin Kenji
is one of the ugliest people they have
ever heard is awesome
>> we've heard this Kenji go on holiday
with Izzy or something you
>> and Izzy are together now
>> we all this before we've heard all this
>> is one of the ugliest people they've ever existed
>> we've heard all of this before
>> you lost a woman to him think about that
>> he we've heard all of this That's a moment.
>> This is 2026 and we've heard all of this before.
>> Kenji took Izzy.
My mom wasn't asking me why I'm on it.
I'm just saying because these little fat
geeky nerds won't leave me alone. No,
she's right. No, no, she's right. I'm
telling her that they literally will not
leave me alone. They will Your mom is
correct though. No, no, she is correct.
Like, just stop. Why don't you just take
just leave this [ __ ] man?
>> These dirty fat ugly [ __ ] will keep
drawing me out.
>> But look how angry you're getting. Yeah.
Why you just leave it alone?
>> You know what I'm saying? These fat,
ugly knees keep drawing me out.
>> Yeah, I had a conversation. They can
only draw you out because you're giving
them you're giving people power to troll
you out. That's why
>> I don't want anything to do with these
fat, ugly people. I've said it multiple
times. Why do they keep posting about me?
>> Listen, why don't you find something to
get into? Yeah, just do that instead
because this is not obviously it. Every
day you just keep going through this
[ __ ] for years and years and years. It's
not really good for your mental health
when I think about it. Like you're not
it's not good for anyone's
>> health like fat ugly people jealous of
you every day. And it is jealousy and I
stand by what I say.
>> No, people not jealous. No, it's not
jealousy. It's not jealousy. Okay, if
they're not jealousy, okay, if they're
not jealousy, it's not it's not
jealousy. It's entertainment. That's all.
>> Tell them to put Tell them to put their
cameras on right now then and prove me wrong.
>> EJ No, no, no. Listen to me. Listen to
>> Why is anyone stupid enough to do You
know what happens. No, but you know, you
know what happens when people do that?
They It become people become like you.
Because what happens is you put your
face out here. Yeah.
>> It's hurting my brain cells as well,
bro. It's 2026 and they're still repeating.
>> Listen, you you put things out on here
then what happens is Yeah. You just
>> It's a disabled community, bro. What do you
>> Just Google your name. Just Google your
name, please, and just see how much
[ __ ] comes up just on Google. Just
go and see it just for yourselves.
>> Tell Lenny that we're never going to
leave you alone. We're going to bully you forever.
>> You don't bully you bully yourselves.
You bully yourselves, mate. Listen, you
people are sat on YouTube with no family
and no girlfriend. You bully yourselves,
brother. You bully yourselves. Why do
you keep leaving? If you bully me,
brother, I bullied you and I bullied
your kids and you done nothing about it.
>> I bullied you and I bullied your kids. I
said I was going to rape your kid and
you done nothing about it. Stop that.
Stop that, man.
>> Bro, I said I was going to rape your
child, your little
What? Is a lady here listening to you say that?
>> Man said he was going to rape your kid
and you done nothing about it. You're
telling me about how you're bullying me.
Allow it, bro.
>> Why are you so Man, why are you so
triggered, man? [ __ ]
>> bro. I just don't like these ugly
people. I [ __ ] hate them. I hate these people.
>> So then listen. Well, then why don't you
find a purpose and do something else?
>> Was going to [ __ ] rape up your child
and you done nothing. You're telling me
how you'll bully me? Allow it, bro.
>> Well, PJ, he did do something cuz he
came. Yeah. He stood behind the gate and
he done nothing. Do you want to do it
again? Do you want to do it again, bro?
You want He came and you didn't want to go outside.
>> He came and he done nothing. He came and
>> You didn't want to step outside?
>> No. He came and he done nothing.
>> You didn't want to cross the threshold.
>> I didn't need to. He done nothing. He
didn't want to cross the threshold to see.
>> He done nothing. He stood behind the
gate and he done nothing. And I'm still
running my mouth and he will
continuously do nothing in 2026.
>> What are people supposed to do with
keyboard warriors though when you think about it?
Well, you can't [ __ ] kill them, can
you? You can't kill. It's
>> 2026 and he will still do nothing.
>> Yeah. And he will still do nothing. And
you don't bully me, bro. You and your
[ __ ] [ __ ] kids with learning
disabilities. Don't bully no one.
>> You know what I mean?
>> PJ, you didn't cross the threshold.
>> Even Even Even Laney would say that. Hey, PJ.