M
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Not even safe with them, are you? No,
not at all. Take that.
Well, they must have saw they must have
they must have saw the [ __ ] white man
coming. That's what I can say about
that, Brooks. I must have saw a white man coming. Yeah. >> Yeah.
Another bet lost.
That was only 20 pound as well.
I don't know how anyone else's bets went
on, but mine lost [cough] [clears throat] only
giving me them dirty stinky mood swings,
but obviously don't want to don't want to uh
pick off or anything.
So, I didn't do anything.
Wow. You're not even safe to do football bets.
That's a madness.
Just goes to show there's no gambling responsibly.
>> That was 20 pound. I put 20 on a treble
both score no draw and I got two out of three.
Yep. It just goes to show you can't
gamble responsibly. That tells you all
you need to know. I was out today as
well for hours.
You can't out the house today. It just
goes to show you can't gamble responsibly.
No, that's a thing.
There's only don't gamble. There's
there's no gambling responsibility.
There's no gambling responsibly. No.
No. There's definitely no such thing as
that. Definitely. Definitely not. No.
All I can say, lad.
I came back and I saw Timmy live and it
was the same people.
Strange. These people are supposed to
have jobs. They're supposed to have
friends. They come online hating on
other people every day. Strange to see
the same people on YouTube 24/7, eh? Yeah,
I lost this football bet. I don't know.
Treble both score no draw and I got two
out of three. They must have saw the
white man coming. Chico,
they must have saw the white man coming.
Yeah, I got two out of three.
They should give me some money for that.
You know what? That's hard to [ __ ] predict. Yeah,
two out of three.
Cuz I don't really gamble like that,
bro. This was only on football.
Well, it might as well been none because
I didn't win anything.
I didn't win anything, so it might as
well been [ __ ] none.
They should at least give you treble
your state for that. That was [ __ ]
hard to get them [ __ ] to get two out of three.
If I just done two, I would have won.
Yeah, but I'm getting mood swings. Yeah,
Obviously, I'm not going to do anything
obviously because my mom and [ __ ] and
I'm not going to ruin the whole day I
had. But yeah, I'm getting these dirty,
stinky mood swings again. Yeah.
So, I guess there is no gambling responsibly.
You know, they're not going to give me something back.
I mean, you definitely can get a
takeaway with 20. And it's not about the
money. I just don't like losing.
We've been over this a million times. I
mean, you definitely can get a takeaway
with 20 pound and I don't like losing.
Simple. I got two out of three. Both
score no draw. They should at least give
me 60, you know.
That's hard to get two or£50. They
should at least give you a bit double
your stake. That's [ __ ] hard to get
that, bro. I got two.
One was two one and one was 32 and the
other one was 1 nil. Dirty bastards.
It would have been £250, you know. But
you could have I could have done two teams, but
I could have done two teams, but then I
would have had to love money on it
and obviously I'm risking that kind of money. So,
well, not if I done both double both
draw, I could have put 80 quid on it.
That would have been like 600 pound, you know.
Well, yeah. Obviously, it's not a lot of
money, but I just don't like losing.
I just don't like losing, mate. Simple. So,
I went to the arcade today. I went to
Nando's. I actually went out today. I
done some stuff. I actually want a um I
want a toy.
Just gave it to a kid.
should have, would have, could have, but
I never and I weren't going to put 80
pound on it. So, yeah,
if I put 80 quid on two, I would have
probably got that 600 pound back. But yeah,
yeah, I went to the um
thing there's grabbing machines and
that. I actually want to play.
It was an all right day
despite the mood swings. So yeah,
I just don't know. Treble both score no
draw and I got two out of three.
I've got more money than everyone. Nah,
not me, bro. I'm skin. I've only got like £10.
I've only got£10, bro. I'm I'm skin
apparently. I'm just going to go by what
everyone says now because you you
clearly know people more than they know themselves.
And brother, it doesn't matter if if
you've got money or not. Losing is just annoying.
Why do you think you need to be skinned?
for it to bother you? That's a misconception,
you know, like that. You don't need to
be skinn like I could have a million
pounds and losing 20 will bother me cuz
it's just losing. I don't like losing.
Simple as that.
[ __ ] two out of [ __ ] three.
I got two teams. Yeah, we're two out of three.
Yeah, I went Nando today and yeah, so I
done some stuff today.
I don't give a [ __ ] if it's nothing. I
don't like losing.
Simple as that. I literally don't care.
I don't like losing. I'd rather it drop
out of my pocket. If it dropped out of
my pocket, that's fine. I just don't like losing.
Oh, only 20 pound. I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't like losing. Simple.
They must have saw a white man coming in
the betting shop. They must have saw a
white man coming. Yeah. Uh £250.
It was a both no draw and I got two out of three.
That was pretty good to get two. To be honest,
I can never seem to get three in
anything. It's so hard to get three.
Even if it's a normal both teams to
score, even three is so hard to get, you know.
No, I just put the football.
I I played on a grabbing machine today.
I won a toy.
I won a toy in the grabbing machine. The claw machine.
I don't miss. Yeah.
Yeah. Lucky you. I should have just put
80 pound on two teams. I would have had
like 600 pound back.
Ker from Winnie the Poo. >> [snorts]
>> No, I'm not Jewish.
It was a I still had mood swings. I just
tried to hide the mood swings. I wake up
every day with mood swings.
When I was 24, 25, 26, not really. But
now I literally have mood swings every day.
Every [ __ ] day, bro. It's so annoying.
So [ __ ] and annoying.
No, I gave it to I gave it to a kid.
Gave it to my nephew.
I was going to get E and give it to
Laney, but I couldn't get the E cuz
Laney loves E.
Lane's always loved E, but I couldn't
get the E or I tried and tried again.
It's too hard, bro.
Just bad experiences.
Bad experiences in life. bad experiences
with women, how the whole situation is [ __ ] up.
It's not good, bro. Really, really not good.
That's why I try to stay away from people nowadays.
I do. Well, I do stay away from people nowadays.
These dirty, stinky mood swings every
day, bro. It's [ __ ] annoying.
Oh. Um, I lost a football bet. I put 20
pound on three. Both score no draw and I
got two out of three. Yeah, I got two
teams out of three.
Yeah. [ __ ] man.
One game was 3-2, the other was 2-1, and
the other was 1 nil. So, the one nil one
[ __ ] us. [ __ ] us, Roy. Yeah.
So hard to get free.
So hard to get free in anything. Yeah.
It's just women, bro. I just hate them,
you know? I think about it every day.
They are absolute [ __ ] I was
dealing with one on Instagram earlier.
They're just all the same [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
Wake up every day. It [ __ ] puts me in
a [ __ ] dirty mood, bro.
Dirty [ __ ] mood. You can't even calm
yourself down anymore. It's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
[ __ ] [ __ ] annoying. So yeah,
it would have been nice to win that
football back, bro. But nah,
I was hoping it was 22 so I didn't
think, oh, I could have just done two
teams, but nah.
No, it's just too hard, bro.
anyone on two teams is too hard.
But I wouldn't have done a double. If I
just put 180 on two teams, it would I
would have won the first half.
Yeah, there was so many postponed to be
fair. I noticed that actually. I noticed that.
Wow. I put 20 pound on a treble. Both
score no draw and I got two out of three.
Yeah, I got two out of three, bro. [ __ ] me, man.
That was That was good to even get two
to be honest. They should give you
something back, man. They should give
you like 50 60 quid. I think they are
hard to get.
Nope, didn't know that.
So, yeah. One one game let me down for £250 basically.
That's a lot of money from 20. 250.
I don't know man cuz getting two teams
is hard, isn't it?
They used to do that. I swear they used
to. I swear if one team let you down,
you used to get your state back. I'm
sure that that was a thing.
No, it was Kitty Minister. It was the
Kitty Minister game.
The Kitty Fiddler Minister is what I call them.
Yeah, they [ __ ] me royally.
I reckon I could get a double both
score, no draw.
I'll put 150 on it one day. Just a
double both score, no draw. And then if
it wins, you'll have a lot of money in it.
Now pay maybe 1,200 pound from 150.
I would have won that in the first half
if I just done a normal race team to score.
But I'm not putting 150, 160, 180 on
[ __ ] triple bets.
I'm not doing that.
No, I'm not doing that, bro. Yeah. Yep.
Yeah. I just went Nando and had a day
out today while out ra
I was in JD. I was going to buy
something. I think, "Oh, what could I
buy?" And then I just realized I've had
all of this before. You know, clothes
and stuff, they don't bother me anymore.
They don't bother me. Like designer
clothes. As long as you've got trainers,
you know, nice pair of trainers, nice
pair of jeans.
I really don't give a [ __ ]
Like, I really really don't give a [ __ ]
bro, like about that stuff anymore. As
long as you got a nice pair of trainers,
nice pair of jeans. I honestly would
rather spend the money on a nice meal
or something else. I really don't give a
[ __ ] about clothes anymore, bro. I
seriously don't. I've got the money.
Easy. Could have spent5 6700 today. But
have I pulled a woman this year? Well,
considering I'm in England. Uh, no.
cuz they're all the same [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. Clothes, bro. Um, they don't
really bother me anymore. Clothes, you know, bro.
I don't know why. I've been there, done
it, had it, still have it. They don't bother me.
They really don't bother me. Like, if I
was to win more money right now, Yeah. I
would just well I wouldn't I wouldn't
even go drinking because of the women in
it. But I would probably go drinking if
I wasn't in this mood. Not today. I'm
just saying like like
uh normally like if I went to the
bookies and I won some money, I would
just spend it on food. Food and getting
drunk. I don't even [ __ ] about clothes anymore, bro.
To an extent. I pay good money for
trainers and jeans, but that's it. No, I
really don't give a [ __ ]
How do I know?
I'm weird, you know. Um,
I did get some trailer wipes today for
my trainers though.
Cost me £8.
I'd rather spend money on a nice meal.
Nice meal and drinks.
No, not drinks anymore.
I know loads of people have moved to
Thailand, is it?
It's disgusting. You have to leave your
own country to get women.
Should be illegal.
It should be illegal. That should
No, you do need wipes, bro. They're
special wipes. You do. They're special
wipes, bro. Trust me. I wouldn't bought
them. They're special wipes, you lad.
Special smelling wipes.
They're special wipes. And I've got
basic I've got brand new vapors, so it's
worth the investment. You know,
I like them wipes.
They're special wipes.
They smell nice, too.
The only one that's special was you, bro.
The only one that special was a lot of
these people in this community, brother.
I come back. I went on Timmy's. Lo and
behold, the same people again.
Still on YouTube, man.
They were on YouTube again. Yep. Yeah.
Yeah. It's a shame about the football bat.
Is a shame about the football. Oh well.
Oh well, man.
You don't really expect them kind of
bets to win, you know.
Imagine getting like a sixfold both
score no draw. Nah, it would never happen, bro.
Cuz I don't like losing.
Gambling fuels negativity as well.
You know, someone told me that 10 years
on this community, they're not on here anymore.
They said gambling fuels negativity
and that is the truth. It really really does.
I'm actually like, yeah, bro. I I can
actually see that. It does fuel negativity
if you lose,
even if you can afford to. I mean, bro,
I lost 100 pound on the first of January
and I spat on the machine. just spat all
over it and just walked out.
I mean, I could afford to lose 100
pound. I lost 100 pound. I just spat all
over it. I don't give a [ __ ]
I punched it and hurt my hand and I just
spat all over it and walked out. Yeah.
Yeah, that was global draw roulette
if you didn't know.
[snorts] I should have just done two
teams, man. Just a normal both teams to score. [snorts]
That's what I should have done. Uh,
why? When have I ever said that I'm wealthy?
When have I ever said I'm wealthy? Quite
frankly, my financial circumstances has
got nothing to do with anyone. And I'm
not the one that brings it up. Joe F is
Joe F is the one that brings it up.
Other people are the one that brings it up.
I'm definitely definitely not struggling
at all, but okay. Um quite frankly, like
I've just said, my my financial
circumstances have got nothing to do
with you or anyone.
Okay. I can't I can't afford to lose
£100. Okay, bro.
Whatever you say.
Okay. I can't afford to lose 100 pound.
Okay. Keep telling yourself that, bro. [snorts] Yeah.
I'm not struggling at all. I went to
Nandos today. I spent money today.
I contradict myself. How have I contradicted myself?
Yeah, they are crap mods to be fair,
but they're crap mods for a reason. Yeah,
just good enough. Yeah. Can you make me
a tea with two sugars, please?
>> I don't want to brush my teeth after. I
brush my teeth all the time now with
electric toothbrush. Um, how do I contradict myself?
Explain. If you're going to if you're
going to say something, back it up, bro.
No, I haven't. How do I contradict
myself? What have I said that's contradicted myself?
Elaborate. If you're going to say
something, at least back it up.
What? Because I spat on the machine cuz
I lost £100. That means I can't afford
to lose £100. Okay, bro. Whatever.
How have I contradicted myself? What
have I done?
No. Three. Both teams got I wouldn't say
that's that hard, bro.
Well, it kind of is, but I mean, it's possible.
No, you can pick three teams from the um
South the the the National South League
and I think you you'd get I think you
could get three.
I [snorts] reckon you could get three
if you kept trying. I reckon you could
get three. [snorts] Yeah, for
Horn Church, slow and Enfield definitely
I I reckon you could get three if you
kept doing it. I definitely think you
would get it. I don't know about both
score, no draw, but you'd get free both
teams to score. Yeah.
I'd afford both teams to score on Boxing Day. >> [snorts]
>> And I got a sixfold once.
I got a sixfold once. One pound returned
£75 when I was 19. I couldn't [ __ ] believe it.
I got all six of them. I couldn't
[ __ ] believe it, bro.
I couldn't believe it. I wish I had more on it.
Yeah. I got 16s once when I was 19.
I think I can remember every single team
it was as well. It [snorts] was 75 to1.
I got six 76 off of a pound.
And then yeah, even if I had 20 pound on
it, you would have been laughing
when you was 19. That's [ __ ] That's a
lot. That's I mean it's a lot of money
now. 14500 pound, but especially when
you're 19 off of a [ __ ] uh football bet.
No, I had a I had a treble. Both got no
draw and I got two out of three. Almost, Joseph. Almost.
And it was a both no draw. So I got two
out of three.
Almost, matey. Almost. Yeah.
Yeah. No one cares about that. Why are
you bringing that up?
Yeah. Yeah, I lost 20 pound.
All right. Um, Steven Howard, listen,
man. You can get three teams, both teams to score.
On the South League, you can.
I mean, it was I mean, I done a treble,
both score, no draw.
So, I mean, the chances I wasn't going
to win, was it?
If id done a double, both teams have
scored with a one in the first half.
Yeah, I don't mind you, bro. Reflecting
on old times. It's cuz you ain't got any
new stuff to say. I don't give a [ __ ] Yeah.
Why reflect on the past? Why not bring
up new stuff that's repeated, dude? Did you see?
[clears throat and snorts]
No. Who the [ __ ] goes on Mr. Bean's channel, bro?
What do you mean? What's the biggest?
What? From a small amount?
Well, it depends what you mean by
biggest. From a smallest amount, I bet or generally
I can do I can do a free both teams to
score. I would have wanted to say in the
first half, but I just didn't want to
lump that kind of money on it. Have I
just done two teams with 80 pound?
Um, £370 off 120.
I won a I won 76 off of a pound once
when I was 19, but I don't really bet on
football. Well, I' I've done it
recently, but I haven't done it over the years.
I've gone over a year without betting on
a football, so I don't really bet on it
as much as I did with the other things.
But yeah, 370 off um 120. Yeah, but I've
done it a couple of times. Oh, [ __ ]
bro. [clears throat]
I think it is. Yeah, I 176 off a pound
when I was 19.
1,200 off a pound. I wish you I bet you
wish you had more on it.
Always weighing it.
Yeah, I gambled 20 pound and one team
let me down.
And I I went to the arcade, Joseph.
Well, arcade amusements, and I won a
toy, and I gave it to my nephew
on the claw machine.
Yeah, I was out today. I went Nandos and [ __ ]
Oh no, I've been banned from Reddit again.
They love banning me on Reddit. Yeah,
[snorts] I I'll just make another account, Joe.
I'll just You know me, mate. I'll just
make another account.
So you you're right with LT now.
Well, I was trying to win the E off for
Laney, but I couldn't win it. So
obviously I won the tigger, so I just
gave the tiger to the kid, you know.
Yeah, of course Joe F only posts when he
wins. We all know that. [gasps]
So, are you right with LT now, Joe?
No. But it is still the race thing with
the bouncer. No, he is. No. No. No. Even
if you own the black guy fairly, he
would still defend the black person. No.
That it is a race thing.
No, that is definitely that is a race
thing. That is a No. No. That is a race
thing. 100%. That is a race thing. So,
no, it is actually a race thing. And the
only reason he's talking since is
because he hasn't been on here for ages.
He come if he stayed on here for three
or four more days, he would start
wanting to meet people again. He would
want to start meeting people again. It's
only because he's not been on here for a
while. So, he's like refreshed and he
doesn't care. He stays on here another 2
three days, he would start calling
people out again.
Just like, well, yeah. And and he would
be he would 100% he would. He actually
He actually would, bro.
No, but most of it was just the same
argument. It's just the same argument,
bro. I don't even know why he was
talking about that LJ that that LJ
thing. What the [ __ ] I don't give a
[ __ ] about that, bro. That was years
ago. That is that is it's so long ago
that it might as well not even exist.
Some of these things,
you know, it might some of these things
are so old they may as well not even exist,
you know, in 2026. I'm not I'm not even
joking. I'm not even like joking
really. Like I'm actually being deadly serious, you know?
What do you mean I don't know him? I
don't know him. I've never seen what he looks like.
I don't know him, bro. What the [ __ ] I
know him. I don't know his name. I don't
know what he looks like. So, I don't
know. I don't know him. Yeah,
I don't know him, bro.
You told me and LT to get oursel down to
waxy, isn't it?
Yeah, that's funny, bro. Yeah.
Same about that football bet, ain't it?
That is a shame that
yeah, there's no chance of getting four
far big. That would be very hard to get
a four both teams to score.
No draw. Sorry.
No, I don't think so. I think I need to
stay away from the public.
I'm a danger.
I'm I'm a danger to to society, bro.
I'm a danger to society.
So, I don't I don't think I should. And
I don't drink anymore either. I'm a danger.
I would literally meet a woman just to
[ __ ] them over, bro. I'm I'm a [ __ ]
nowadays. I'm a bit of [ __ ] I never
used to be like that, but I'm I'm like that now.
I'm a dirty bit of [ __ ] bro.
And I would be going out just waiting
for someone to start me.
That's what I would do. I would
literally just wait until someone starts
to me, you know, cuz you know, sometimes
when I go out, right, I'm and I'm in a
pissed-off mood, I'm just waiting for
someone to start. Just waiting. I'm just
waiting for that perfect excuse, you know?
Yeah. I could have took 40 profit. Yeah,
I know. But I never
Okay, so what's your point?
Why Why would I want 40 profit?
I would have took a 100 or maybe 150,
but why why would I take 40 profit to do what, bro?
I'm trying to win [ __ ] big. I'm not
trying I'm not going to take 40.
No. What the [ __ ] bro?
You're not taking 40 pound.
But yeah, I just want like someone to
start with me. Preferably a woman.
Like preferably a woman, you know.
Yeah. I mean, I won £40. Yeah. They gave
me £40 and it took £100 to get the next
spin. Yeah. I mean, they're giving you
little wins to get you more hooked.
You don't need to know that.
But you will see what will happen if one
starts on me again or or tries to act
cocky. You will see what will happen,
bro. That's why I don't go out. That's
why I don't go out drinking.
That's one of the reasons I don't go out drinking anymore.
Cuz you're already pissed off as it is.
You don't need some [ __ ] It doesn't
doesn't matter who they are, a man or a
woman. And trust me, I I will do something.
Trust me, I will do something. You know,
[clears throat] you don't need that
toxicity in your life. You know,
I was out drinking the other month cuz I
was forced to go out. Yeah. When was the
last time I went out by myself?
When was the last time I went out by
myself? Like two months ago.
Yeah. I went out by myself two months
ago. The last time I went out is cuz I
was forced to go out. Big difference.
Big big big difference.
Big big big big difference.
Well, guilt tripped into going out rather.
Well, yeah. That's what happens when
you've had so many bad experiences all
your life. Isn't that right? You know. Yeah.
I don't need to save, bro. I've got
money. I don't need to save. [sighs]
And that's it. I don't need to save,
bro. I don't give a [ __ ] about money,
bro. I really don't give a [ __ ] about money.
I really don't.
Some people go I don't, you know. [gasps]
So, yeah, that's why I don't go out.
[sighs and gasps]
Yeah. And I should have to go out. It's
not even just that. I should have to go
out and try again. I've already tried. I
should have to go out and try again. I'm
28 years of age.
I'm 28 years of age. I should be in this
position. So that's that's the way I see it.
That is honestly the way I see it. [snorts] So yeah,
you might think I'm being awkward and
difficult, but I'm really not.
No, I'm really, really not.
This woman was being a [ __ ] on
Snapchat as well um the other day. You
remember the one I met in Liverpool
Street, Steven Howard.
Yeah, just being another westernized
[ __ ] I saw some more approaching
videos today as well from this guy. Give
it a [ __ ] break.
What? It will never be different. If
you're talking about dating, it will
never be different. It will never be
different. it. No, it hasn't been
different the past [ __ ] god knows how
many years. So, it's not going to be different now.
No, of course it's not going to be different.
Why is it going to be different?
I hate double standards. I hate white
knights. I hate everything.
And basically everyone
if you actually think about it. I hate
white knights. I hate double standard. Um yeah. Yeah.
There's also a lot of [ __ ] in this
country as well. And I'm not even just
talking about women. There's a lot of
[ __ ] here as well. A lot a lot of
A lot of [ __ ] in this country, bro. I
think Nons's girlfriend fancies me. You
know, Dusty, I actually saw that short. Imagine
Imagine a couple being obsessed with someone.
That's a bit strange. Imagine your
sister and the [ __ ] Imagine your sister
and her boyfriend being obsessed with
someone on YouTube. Just wanted to point
that out. If anyone's got a sister or
anyone knows someone, it's a bit
strange, isn't it?
Because I can't leave Laney, matey.
I can't leave Laney.
That's so weird that he actually calls
me ugly when like I am actually better
looking than him. So don't you know
these people on here that don't show
their faces and they don't show their
faces so we don't know what they look
like. Okay, so we know what he looks
like and he is way uglier than me.
That is actually that's actually that's projection.
They're laughing at me, brother. I'm not
the one living in a bedsit. I'm not the
one with missing teeth. I'm not the one
that's never worked.
So, I mean, you can laugh all you want,
but you're just laughing at yourself.
You can continue laughing, but I'm not
the one in the bed suit. I'm not the one
with missing teeth. I'm not the one with
a nonsad. I'm not the one with no
family. I'm not the one that got beat by
my stepdad. I'm not the one with a
disabled arm. So I mean if you want to
keep laughing you can but I mean you are
laughing at yourself. You're not
laughing at me but you do you man. No
one can tell you what to do you know
and they are obsessed. They are
definitely definitely obsessed. They
have a YouTube channel dedicated to
someone. They're definitely
definitely definitely definitely
definitely obsessed. I mean one of them
definitely are obsessed.
They are definitely definitely obsessed.
What are you talking about, mate? What
the [ __ ] are you on about, man?
That's what makes me laugh. You know,
when you sit there and you say these
people laugh at me, Joe, I really I
laugh at it because we know that these
people in this community ain't got a
life. They're sat on YouTube 24/7 with
no interaction with the outside world.
So really, no one cares what these
people laugh at. They're so irrelevant.
You can laugh at what you want. You're irrelevant.
So at the end of the day, like no one no
one really cares. They're so irrelevant
that their opinion doesn't even matter
at you. And they don't have what they
have. I mean, yeah, I know. I don't have
what they have. I don't have a disabled
girlfriend. I've never been with a
disabled woman. I never have.
Um, a a disabled I would never get with
a disabled girl.
I've got more money than them. I don't
live in a bedsit.
They don't have anything. They literally
do not have a damn thing but a bedsit
and a poverty life.
That's all they have. You know,
if they were better than me, they
wouldn't waste their time on me. People
that are better than people don't waste
their time on other people. Um, that's a
fun fact. Um, if you if you wanted to
know, if you're truly better than
someone, you do not waste your time on another person.
Uh, hating and stuff. That's another
thing as then it would just make no sense.
Well, she definitely is disabled
and she definitely looks disabled. I
mean, she looks like a [ __ ] dwarf. I
mean, she definitely definitely is disabled.
So, yeah, people that are better than
you in life, they don't they don't come
on here and do this.
Uh they don't come on here and do this.
It's like that's that's uh
I mean, so you're Okay, one second. One
second. So, you're comparing watching
East Enders and Coronation Street to
coming on YouTube from the time you wake
up to the time you go to bed being
obsessed with someone,
bro. What are you on about? So, hold on.
Hold on. So, okay, let's get let's let's
let's use this as an example. So if you
watch EastEnders every day, which is
half an hour, that's the same as being
on YouTube all day every day stalking
someone and making videos of them all
day every day. Bro, that doesn't make any sense.
That does not make that literally does
not make any sense because they're more
than watching someone. They're being
obsessed with them. They're posting
about them. They're screen recording.
I mean, I would not do that to somebody
that I'm better than, but that's just
me. I mean, that that generally
generally is just me. If I was better
than someone, if I was better than
someone, I would just live my life, you know.
But they can't. So, that's that's
something, bro. That's something there, you know.
I mean, I've never been with a disabled woman.
I hate East Enders. I hate Comination Street. [snorts]
I hate that [ __ ] I hate that [ __ ]
[sighs and gasps]
It used It used to be all right years
ago, but I don't watch it.
I don't like that stuff. Yeah.
[snorts] And then [ __ ] fake cockney accents. Yeah.
No, I never.
Yeah. Danny Dier, he's uh he was born
not far from me.
Yeah, he was born not far from me.
Yeah, he's cocky. He is
Why did Nonsense lie to uh LT um
yesterday about the Chevel Cole thing?
He literally did say that.
He literally said if you don't like
Chevel Cole, you're gay. He did. He did.
He legitimately said that. What the [ __ ]
You literally did say that. You lit I
brought it up.
Yeah, I've been to Cannon Town. My
sister used to live there.
No, that was Holly Oaks. And it wasn't
it wasn't East Enders, it was Holly
Oaks. It wasn't East Enders. It was Holly Oaks.
So yeah, I know Canon Town, bro. I've
been there multiple times.
That self-projecting benefits in living
my mom. hypothetical, pointless,
self-projecting questions don't get answered.
Do you know another thing that I was
saying about these people earlier uh is
you have got nothing new or nice to say
about anyone, do you? This is another
thing with this. I don't give a [ __ ] if
you're jealous or not. I don't really
give a [ __ ] if you are, you're not. But
I've noticed on this community,
they they've got nothing new or
nice to say about anyone. They just slag
off people every day. And I'm not even
just talking about me. They've done it
to me. They've done it to Monty or they
they're always slagging someone off um
on this community. I've noticed that. Um
they're always like trying to bring
people down to their level.
Um that's another thing I've I've I've
noticed about these people on here. um
that they're just they're always like
slagging people off on this community
trying to bring you to their level. I've
noticed that as well. I've definitely
definitely noticed that and they've done
it with multiple different people.
I've seen that with with um multiple
different people. They want to bring you
down. It's a community trying to bring
other people down.
Uh, I don't know if you've noticed that,
Dusty, but I've definitely definitely
definitely noticed that they've got
nothing good to say about anyone.
No matter who it is, have you noticed that?
When the reality is these people are sat
on YouTube 24/7 with no life.
Um, which makes the whole thing just
contradictory, you know? But I've
definitely definitely definitely noticed
that even when they're talking about
other people, this person's skin, this
person's this, this person's that,
they're like trying to like demotivate people.
I don't know if anyone else has noticed
that they they've tried to like
demotivate um people. Um
even though there's so much evidence out
there that suggests that these people
have got nothing, there's literally so
much evidence. Like Stephen Howard, I
was on Lord Jay's a week ago. I was I
was sat there watching for about five
minutes and they were just typing to
each other and I'm thinking, "What the
fuck?" Typing, typing, typing, typing,
typing, typing, typing. And these are
the same people that try to bring other
people down every day. What?
How can I say what they have? I I can
answer that. I can answer that because I
have shown that these people on YouTube
24/7, time and time and time again, and
if they actually had something, they
wouldn't be on here 24/7. If they had a
life, if they had friends, they would
not be on here 24/7. They are on here
24/7. Um, when I came back earlier, I
went on Timmy's and it was literally the
same people typing their life away um
behind the keyboard. Um, I mean, you you
they literally have not got a life.
Like, I can I can actually say 100% that
they've got no life and they've got no
social interaction um with the outside world.
That's what I'm saying. Well, well,
yeah, that's what I'm trying to say to
you. They don't have anything. That's
what I'm saying. But then they're
constantly on here trying to bring other
people down. And we're not talking about
money. Wait, we're not just talking
about money, bro. We're not talking
about money. We're talking about
everything. We're talking about friends.
We're talking about a life. Um, we're
talking literally about everything.
The fact that they have to come on here
and do this shows they got no life.
Um, they can't have a life to for people
to be doing this. They can't have a happy life.
That is that is true though. I can tell
you that much that is 100% true. People
that have got a life, right, do not come
on here trying to bring strangers down
every day. It just does not happen. Um,
anyone that you idolize in in life,
yeah, does not come on the internet
trying to bring other people down. No
person that's got stuff going in their
in their life does that. No one does
that. Literally, not one person does
They're really really not. They're
really really not. Well, I I disagree
with that. So, we just agree to disagree. Um,
so yeah. And that's that. [clears throat]
Brother, it doesn't matter what a woman
would be impressed with. Stop defending the [ __ ]
Stop asking stupid questions.
Stop trying to stop bringing up the same
stuff and asking stupid questions,
brother. They're the problem, not me.
So, it doesn't matter what they're
impressed with or not. Stop being a s.
I've lived by myself multiple times before.
And I've lived by myself. I've worked.
So, stop talking [ __ ] bro. What you're
saying is irrelevant. I've worked. I've
lived by myself. [gasps]
So the whole what you're saying is just
irrelevant. Stop asking stupid questions.
Yeah. Yeah. Women Yeah. Women in this
stuck up Yeah. Women in this country are
definitely the problem. Yeah. 100%.
Yeah. Yeah. Women definitely are. And
you're banned. See you later.
Sorry. This is not a genuine person.
This is somebody This is somebody just
trying to troll. Um, they're not
actually being a normal person. It's
probably leave bomb be It's probably
bomb behind that account
again. No life.
They ain't got no life. They ain't got
no family cuz they wouldn't be on here, you know?
Well, here's the thing, right? When
these people get doxed Howard in 10
years, you can come back and tell me
that I'm right. Yeah. Cuz let me tell
you this, right? Every single person
that has done this that has been doxed,
how comes I was right about them?
Can I ask you? Let me ask that question.
Right. All of these people that have
done this in the past,
I was saying what they were like two
years before and it turned out they were
exactly that. Bomb atmusted
gray cat. Why was I right about loads of
these people that I made assumptions
about? Because it's obvious. You just
put two and two together and it adds up
to four. You put two and two together
and it adds up to four.
So why have I been right about all the
people that's been docked then in the
past if what I'm saying is not true.
Like bomb right? He come on here for
what years [snorts and clears throat]
talking about people's looks. I told you
exactly what he was and he was Pat
Mustard. I told you exactly what he was
and he was gray cat. I told you exactly
what she was and she was. You know, it's
easy. People that are
like that is the truth. Like I can tell
you people right now that's got a life
that's a family man. Yeah. I can tell
you right. I can tell you that that how
hard can it be even though he goes on L
JS. I've actually met the guy and I
actually think he is just a normal guy
with a job and kids you know because
I've actually met the guy and I don't
have no problem with him. He doesn't
like me anymore, but I've got no problem
with him because you can see you can
see, you know, even that Ben Fury's got
a life. Um, you can see like even with
like people like LT, you can see the
ones that have actually got a life and
the ones that ain't got a life. It's
fairly obvious to see.
And how hard can it be? Don't even like
me. And you know I'm saying that because
um and there's other people as well but
obviously those ones come to mind. So I
can say like yeah like they've got a
life. They just come on here and then
just come off of it.
But people like you know Smokey B uh you
know what's his face? Uh
what's his name now?
What's his name? Voice of reason. They
have got no life. They have literally
Wherever you go, they're there, bro.
Have I got a life? Well, brother, I
mean, I've I've told you that I'm saving
and I've given up on the dating game.
So, I'm I've kind of told you that I'm
not doing anything,
but yet these people still got more time
on their hands than me. But I've told
you that I'm not doing anything. And
I've told you why I'm not doing anything.
I've been having a life, bro, for the
past five, six, seven years.
So, I mean, I'm sat here chilling and
I'm not going out.
It's not hypocritical. It's not
hypocritical because I It's not
hypocritical at all. How is it hypocritical?
It's not hypocritical.
If I was out, okay, if I was Okay, say I
was going back to approaching and I was
going out drinking, I would not be on
here as much as these people are.
There's no way. There's no way I'd have
the time for it. You know, they've got
more time on their hands now. If I was
to going back to how I was, there's no
way I could be on here as much as these people.
There's no way, bro. There's no way.
There's literally no way. So,
yeah, they they are they are literally
on it all day, every day.
I mean, I've told you I've given up on
life, so at least I've actually got an
excuse. If I've said I've given up on
life and I'm on it, then that at least
I'm admitting it. But these people are
saying that they've got a life. These
people are saying that they've got this
and that, but they're on here 24/7. It
just doesn't make sense.
I don't know, bro.
Yeah. 28, bro. 28,
you know. Well, these people don't have a life.
So then why are you people on YouTube
24/7 then? That's what I want to know.
Why you people on YouTube 24/7?
That's what I want to know, you know,
cuz you are the ones that are slagging
off other people.
That's that's that's another thing. You
are the ones that actually slag off other people,
which makes the whole thing just contradicts itself.
So you're on YouTube 24/7 for entertainment.
Okay. From the time you wake up to the
time you go to bed. Really? Really, bro?
Well, you are very good at multitasking.
You are very good at multitasking.
It's nowhere near the same as East
Enders though, is it? It's nowhere near
the same as East Enders.
I done six hours yesterday and guess
what? You people was on here with me.
So, what does that say about you? I was
on here. It was actually 5 hours and 24
minutes. Who's counting? And you was on
here with me. You people was actually on
YouTube with me. Yeah. 28.
Nah, bro. That was me like 23 to about 26.
I'm kind of 27. Yeah. [snorts] No, bro.
I stopped going out regularly at 26. 26
and a half.
26 and A2.
Yeah, I was 26 and a half me no
I last went drinking like a month and a
bit ago in it.
I got a number and then they replied
back and just start being [ __ ] So
yeah, I think I broke the street now. I
think this is actually the longest I've
not gone out now drinking. [gasps]
Yeah, definitely broke the streak. I
used to do six weeks like a year and a
half ago, but now I've definitely broke it. [gasps]
It's too toxic for my liking, Dusty.
It's too toxic.
And you're making yourself worse as well
by doing it.
You're actually making yourself worse by
actually doing this. You don't actually
understand. It's for the best. You know,
you're just going to get more bad
experiences and you're just going to
keep going around in circles.
That's all that's going to happen.
Nothing else will ever happen. Trust me.
I'm surprised you thought it was [ __ ] money, Jo.
No, I had um I did have two beers on Christmas
at my sister's, but that's about it. I
was bought Guinness um like a present.
Um but yeah, I mean I drunk two beers on Christmas.
Then I fell asleep. I didn't go out New Year's.
Didn't drink New Year's. No.
So actually yeah, I did have two beers
Christmas. Oink oink. Yeah,
that's kind of cuz it was bought for me in it. Yeah,
but I didn't go out New Year's Eve. I
told you I don't give a [ __ ] about
money, bro. I've got money. I get money.
Money comes and goes. I don't give a
[ __ ] about money, bro. I was more
depressed when I had the house. But I
wasn't bitter. I don't think I was
bitter when I had the house. I was
depressed and then I'd like eventually
get over it, but I don't think I was bitter.
No. New Year's Eve is a Mugs game, bro.
New Year's Eve is a Mugs game.
Going out New Year's Eve is a Mugs game.
New Year's Eve. That's That is a Mug's
game. New Year's Eve.
That is actually a Mugs game. New Year's
Eve. Going out New Year's Eve. Going out
No, I wasn't, bro. No, I wasn't. I've
still got money. I've still got money,
bro. I can go out and do it now if I want to.
I wasn't loving life. I was I was I was
depressed. I was depressed. How do you
think I got kicked out of my mom's?
I was depressed.
No, I was depressed. I used to complain
to Sig all the time. You must have memory loss.
You must have memory loss, mate. Because
I always used to complain.
It doesn't change my moods, bro. Money
does not change my mood.
Well, yeah. Well, going out drinking New Year's Eve.
Yeah, that was years ago. Oh, well,
years ago. Yeah, years ago I did. But
I'm talking within the past year and a
half, two years.
I was that way regardless. But yeah,
you're talking [ __ ] three years ago, man.
You're talking years ago. What the [ __ ]
But not now, bro. [ __ ] that.
That's what you're supposed to do when
you're younger. And then when you're
this age, you're actually supposed to be
settled down with someone.
You're not dealing with immature [ __ ]
Yeah, I was. That was years ago, man.
That was That was actually years ago. [snorts]
I'm sure I still got mood swings. I'm
sure I did.
at some point. I'm sure I did.
Yeah, I'm sure I did.
I don't care about clothes anymore
either. That's how you know you got
older, bro. When you don't care. And
don't you dare [ __ ] say I can't
afford it cuz I [ __ ] can.
Even clothes don't bother me. If I got a
nice pair of trainers and a nice pair of jeans, nettled.
Nice two pack of Levi T-shirts. 30.
That's me done, bro. I don't really care.
Had it, still got it. Bors me, bro. Yeah,
but not like you, Joseph Ra. You wear 40 jeans.
I was in JD today. I could have bought
some new clothes, but nah.
I've still got a lot of clothes. I still
got some my Reese clothes as well.
Yeah. Well, times have changed.
I did have a carefree attitude. It still
bothered me. It still used to bother me.
No, it did still used to bother me.
That's why I used to keep busy. No, it
still used to bother me.
It still used to No, it did still used
to bother me, bro.
It's cuz I was too busy. I didn't get
time to sit and think about [ __ ] So, yeah.
Well, I've got 200 pound jeans
and I didn't I and I didn't use cler
either. I didn't use cler either.
I always used to moan to sig about being
depressed and [ __ ]
you know. [sighs and gasps]
So, I was still depressed even when I
had that house, matey. Trust me.
Not [snorts] when I was living in the house.
Not when I was living in the house, but
still make still making money for the
house. It still never bothered me. It
really still didn't bother me. You know,
I do I Yeah,
I think it's cuz where I live, I think
I'm worse because I live here with
Laney. Not with Laney, but I mean, even
if I live by myself, I think I would
still be [ __ ] depressed. To be fair,
I don't think it's a fact because
Laney's here. Even if I was by myself.
Yeah, but I had company in the house.
Well, it's not though cuz I can afford
200 jeans. I'm live I'm living beyond my
means. Doge Ferrar.
Yeah, Mike. I done a football bet today.
I lost 20 [ __ ] quid.
No, it's not a complete lie though cuz I
can afford 200 pound jeans.
Unlike people Christmas, you know these
people that done Christmas, you know,
most of them are in debt. You know, most
you know most people that Well, I don't
know about most people, but you know
loads and loads and loads and loads of
people that do Christmas. you know, they
can't afford it. They end up in debt in
it. That's why they've got no money this
uh the whole of January. No one goes out drinking.
They literally do Christmas, right?
And if and this guy was talking sense on
Instagram. He says, "If you can't afford
it, don't do it.
If you can't afford it, do not do it."
You know, and that's the truth. Like, I
I could afford it. I just chose not to
do it. There was a reason.
There's a reason. There's there's
there's there's a reason.
There's actually a reason.
Well, bro, there's a lot of Well, I'd
say most people couldn't afford
Christmas than could.
Why do you think the pubs are empty all
January up until March?
So, there most people are definitely
living beyond their means because why is
no one out January, bro? It is dead. is
dead. And trust me, I've I've
experimented with this time and time
again. So, they're living beyond their
means when they're doing Christmas.
There's more people obviously can't
afford it because why is no one going
out in January?
For what reason? If they got money, why
why aren't they doing it?
So, you know, there
most people can't afford Christmas that
did Christmas. I' I'd go as far as
saying that, you know. I actually would
go as far as saying that
my life wasn't a lie. Nothing I ever
said was a lie
to any of these people.
And no, she didn't want me. She was
being a [ __ ]
She was being a dicker and she was being a [ __ ]
But no, most people most people can I
mean I didn't do Christmas because
I learned my lesson basically. I bought
Laney the UG boots but obviously I
learned my lesson
um with someone else. I could afford it.
I could afford it but I just didn't want
to do it. Even if I had loads more other
money, I still wouldn't do it because I
just wanted to be selfish. Obviously,
I'll buy Laney. I'll buy Laney a present
and that um
and whatever, but I wouldn't buy um
anyone else. And there's actually a
valid reason for that.
And it is a very valid reason. And I
learned my lesson. So, yeah,
I was. Yeah. Yeah, I was.
You know, uh yeah, I was mate. It's not
a bad thing. If anyone can find if
anyone can find a loophole in the
system, do it. Do it. You know, I was
someone was telling me about their
mother. There, oh, my mom would never do
anything that's like not by the books
and whatever. But what it's good to be
like that, but a lot of these people
don't understand that doing things the
right way is not always it doesn't
always pay off, if that makes sense.
Like you might you want to try and do
everything the right way, but sometimes
that's not the way, you know? And I'm
not saying sell drugs or do anything
that's going to get you in prison. But
yeah, if you find a loophole, yeah, take
advantage of it,
you know, take advantage of it. You
know, if you can find a loophole in the
system to make you extra money, 100%. As
long as it's not selling drugs and it's
going to put you in prison, [ __ ] do it.
Anyone that can find a find a loophole,
do it, you know.
And that's that, you know, 100%.
What are you What are you saying, Dusty?
What are you saying, Joe? If you left
with a house that's going to make you
two grand a month for 3 years, you're
not going to do it. You're not going to
do it, are you? Really? No. Of course
you would do it. Anyone would do it.
Anybody would do it.
Any person in their right mind would do
it. Even with one room, why the [ __ ]
wouldn't they do it? And losing out on
all that money. Nah. And you can't get
nicked for it either cuz it's a civil
matter. So, no. 100%. No. Like, yeah,
it's illegal, but you can't go you can't
get nicked for it.
So, it'd be very hard for them to prove
that you're doing it. But yeah,
100%. Yeah. No, [ __ ] down right do it
if you can find a loophole in the system. You know
what? What are you going to do, bro? You
would do it. You 100% would do it.
Well, it never ever come back to me or
my mom. So, never did.
I mean, you can go to prison
technically, but I mean, it's very unlikely, you know,
and the only [snorts] one that would get
in [ __ ] for it is my mom, not me, cuz I
weren't on the teny.
So, I didn't even know about it. One one
guy said to me one time, he said, "Oh,
you know you could rent them rooms out
and get extra money." I said, "Really?"
And then I just done it.
I had I was living in that house for a
year by myself before doing it. I was
like, "What? Really?" So I've missed out
on all this [ __ ] money.
Then I done it. I was like, "Oh shit." Yeah.
Yeah. Missing out on money. [ __ ] yeah. [laughter] Nah, Facebook.
Nah, Facebook. Facebook,
to be honest though,
it it was annoying, bro. The
responsibility and [ __ ] It was
annoying. It wasn't, you know, it wasn't
even like he was earning loads and loads
and loads for the [ __ ] trouble that
it caused, to be fair. But yeah,
but nothing happened. It never come back. You know, they were
they were, man,
they were. So, you're telling me, Joe,
if you weren't left with that h if you
was left with that house, you would you
wouldn't sublet the rooms? Of course you
would. Anyone would do that?
Of course you [ __ ] would.
You're lying if you if you're saying
that you wouldn't.
No, it's pay as you go.
You would. You would, bro. I'm sure you
[ __ ] well would. Even if you were still working,
I think you would me. I think you
definitely definitely would me.
I should have grown weed in the [ __ ]
house, mate. I could have got a lot more
money, but [snorts] nah.
Then you actually could get nicked.
But you're telling me you would not
sublet any of them rooms if you could?
See, they should have just put that in
my name. I would have actually paid it.
I would have actually paid it every
month. I actually tried I actually tried
to get them to put in my name and I
would have actually gave them the money
every month, but they weren't having it. So,
they weren't having it at all, mate. I
would have paid the money weekly for that house. you know. [snorts] Yeah.
But they weren't having it at all. Now
it's just all boarded up.
Now it's boarded up and they're not
making money on it. It's going to be
like that now for years. Borded up
pretty much. It's [clears throat] pretty
pointless to be honest because they
could have actually made money from it.
But yeah, they're just [ __ ] idiots,
bro. Really? They could have been making
money on that house, you know, because
now no, it's going to take years for
someone to go in that house now cuz it's
all boarded up.
Yeah. [ __ ] madness that is.
You [snorts] can't reopen it cuz then
you would actually get nicked
if it I was actually thinking about
doing that, but no, you can't do that,
bro. you would actually get nicked. It's
all boarded up.
Then you would actually get nicked
cuz obviously they they've took it back
in it. So you're you're breaking in
their property now. You know, as soon as
they've won the court case, that's that
is it. [gasps and snorts]
No, you can't do that. Before all of
that, you can do it. Not let them in and
whatever, but you know, you can't, bro.
You get nicked. Yeah.
Why? Could you imag Hey Joe, could you
imagine non legs doing the Uber Eats delivery?
Like just just a little job. Nah,
[ __ ] kill him, mate. [ __ ] kill him.
It will [ __ ] kill him.
You would actually kill that [ __ ]
Yeah, that would actually kill him.
I can't believe that cunt's never had a little job.
Nothing wrong with a little job, Joe. Is it?
Nothing wrong with a little part-time
job for extra money. I don't I don't see
what the problem with that is.
What's wrong with a little job, you know?
It's nicer little job.
I was so happy to [ __ ] that woman over, you know.
She was a [ __ ] You know that one in
waxies? She was a proper proper [ __ ]
You know, trying to think that she was
better than me. Oh, bro. You know that
one in waxies? Uh, Dusty, the one I made
go to waxies on that. Yeah, she actually
deserved it. She did.
I don't need to tell myself nothing,
bro. I've already I've worked. I don't
need to tell myself I've worked.
I've worked me matey. [gasps]
I've been more independent than Oh,
[ __ ] I've been more I've been I've been
more independent than non legs ever
will. Went to the gym, worked, had a responsibility.
Definitely definitely more. It's not my
fault. [ __ ] you know um it's so
expensive the rent in uh London and
[ __ ] or Fredo.
>> Thank you, Captain.
Yeah. So, uh yeah, it's something my
fault about the rent in uh in London, you know.
I was more independent than that [ __ ] I
had a responsibility and I was working
as well. That [ __ ] doesn't know about about independency.
He doesn't even wash his own clothes.
I don't even think he washes his own clothes.
I think he goes to the uh he does wash
his clothes in the washing machine. I
know that for a fact.
I was a landlord as well. And I live and
I've I've actually lived by myself as
well. A couple of times.
I've actually gone I've actually lived
by myself a couple of times. Um
yeah, trust me, bro.
You're not independent because you live
in a shitty bed.
You're not more You're not more
independent than someone because they
live with a parent. I mean, most people
in London live with their parents if they're single.
That is a fact.
That is actually a fact. Most people in
London do. They either live in a box
room in a shared accommodation or they
live with their parents. Like, that's
not even [ __ ] bro. And you can ask
a lot of people.
You can ask a lot of people.
You know, they'll tell you the same thing.
living with a parent doesn't make you
any less independent.
I pay my bill. I buy my own food. I do
my own [ __ ] I do my own washing. And I
make my bed. Oh.
It is true. It is true. Most people in
London, they either live in a room, a
box room, or they live with a parent. He
doesn't live in London. He's just lucky
that he got a council beds [ __ ] If he
didn't live, he didn't live in that
council bed, bro. He would be living
with his dad.
He would be living with his dad,
you know. Um,
London is good. You can make money in London.
There's [clears throat] lots to do in London.
It is. It's good. London is good, man.
Have you ever had bills like council
tax, gas? I have had electric, gas. Yes,
I have when I used to live in the other
house. Yes, I did.
Gas and electric. Yes, I did.
Yes, I [ __ ] did.
Yeah, it doesn't matter, bro. I'm I'm
I'm independent. I've lived by myself.
I've lived by myself, mate.
You know what I'm saying?
You know what, right? I hope one day,
yeah, they take that cancel bedit off of
him just so he, you know, cuz he always
likes to tell people that they live with
their mom. Bro, the guy would be living
with his dad. If he didn't get a council
bedsit, he would be living with his father.
he would be [ __ ] Like he generally
generally generally would be [ __ ] You
know, people like that that get accommodation,
they should actually be thankful for it,
you know? They should actually be
thankful that they actually got given
something by these [ __ ] in this
country. They shouldn't stop bragging
when we all know that if you didn't get
given it, you'd be with you'd be living
with your dad. You actually would be
living with your [ __ ] father or
another family member. You literally would.
And that's a that is actually a fact and
I can actually say that. You know what I mean?
You know what I mean, bro?
So unless you have a partner,
you know, it's very hard to live by
yourself in London in in London. Really
depends how many people you live with.
I'd probably have to like rent a room
and shared accommodation if I was to
like live somewhere else
because I wouldn't pay rent. I'd have to
pay [ __ ] all of my money on [ __ ]
accommodation. [ __ ] that, bro. I'm not doing that.
Doing that at all. You know,
you know, it's not Middles, bro, mate,
where rent is £400 a month,
but you've never gone up, brother.
Listen, they do not give single men
Yeah. flats. You do, bro. Are you an
idiot? You know, you do realize they
don't help people anymore. I've already
gone through the process and they don't
help you. If you're a single man, they
don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah. So, uh I exactly know how this
works and I know exactly what they've
told me. So,
yeah, they do not help single men. They
I mean they'll put you in a hostel, but
I mean they'll put you in a hostel.
That's about it. Yeah. So,
no, not anymore. They don't. They told
me they weren't going to help me. They
offered me a hostel and then they said,
"If you don't go to the hostel, we're
not helping you. It depends where you
live. I mean, a part of it I mean, a lot
of it depends where you live and what
bubble you live in. I mean, but where I
live, they they they weren't interested.
And I tried and tried again. I got an MP
involved. They weren't interested.
It depends where you live, you know what
I'm saying? It depends on the B that you
live, but where I lived, they weren't interested.
And there was even an MP involved as well,
you know. So yeah,
you know, you it depends on where you
live, you know,
it depends. But they weren't helping me
and we tried and we tried again. Um
they won't help you. They'll offer you a
hostel. Unless you're a single woman
with a kid, they're not going to help
you, bro. Depends. Again, it depends on
the on the burough, you know. If you
live in Manchester or you live some,
they might help you. I don't know. Every
B is different, but you can't go into another burough.
You have to live some like you can't go
to You can't go to another burough. You
can't go to another burough. Um and then
you have to actually live and be
addressed under that burough. That's the
thing as well. It's [ __ ] up, bro.
There was a guy from Newcastle. He's
living in he moved from Newcastle. He's
homeless in London. And I said, "What
the [ __ ] you doing here?" He said, "Oh,
they wouldn't help him and shit." So,
he's around central London, but they
they'll offer you a hostel, but they
won't give you.
Oh, it's the same in Manchester. Well,
it's the [ __ ] same here. They won't help you.
So, you either live in a box room in
London or you uh you meet someone and
have a child. Seems to be the only way.
But you're not going to meet someone and
have a child. So,
yeah, if you applied years ago, it would have been
So, what did you do then? They said you
wasn't priority. So what what happened then?
So what happened? Did you
Yeah, they'll offer you a hostel.
Brother, I said it I I never said
Manchester is a B, you [ __ ] [ __ ] I
said it depends on the burough, right?
Yeah. And I said if you live in
Manchester, I never said Manchester was
a B, you [ __ ] [ __ ] I was talking
about bowers in London. So, you might
want to listen properly before telling
people that you're losing brain cells
that you literally don't have. You don't
even have any brain cells to lose. No
one said Manchester was a borrower. So,
it depends where you live and what
burough. No one said Manchester was a
bur, you [ __ ] [ __ ] But anyways, yeah.
Well, they didn't even offer you a
hostel. What the [ __ ] Yeah, they
offered me a hostel. Yeah.
You know, I would said Manchester was a
B. It's a city. One I've been to many
times. So, you might want to listen
properly next time. Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, bro. Knew him. Yeah.
they're bastards. New, bro. They're [ __ ] bastards.
They're absolute bastards.
And then they help women with kids. That's bad.
Which I don't understand why they help
women with kids cuz having kids is a
[ __ ] choice. No one's asked you to
[ __ ] have sex.
So that's why I think different to a lot
of different I think different to a lot
of people. I find women hypocrites. I
find the whole system is [ __ ] But I'm
very different to to like probably most
people the way I think. You know,
they should help people that are single
regardless if they're from this country. Yeah.
[snorts] I wonder what would happen if
you went homeless in Middlesbr, bro.
You reckon they'd give you some if you
went homeless in Middlesbrough?
Do you think so? You [clears throat]
know, you can actually rent out rooms in um
Middlesbr, bro. You can actually buy a
house. I think I was looking at it
before. It's like £140,000.
So you could actually buy a house and
actually rent the rooms out.
Obviously you wouldn't make as much as
London, but you could actually do it, you know.
Oh, maybe it was 70 something,000.
I can't remember, but it wasn't that
much. [snorts] And obviously you could
actually rent them room. You could
actually rent um them. That's what I
would do if I ever won big money. I
would buy a property.
I think it might have been 80 grand. I
don't think it was 14. It was either 80
or 140. I can't remember. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
I think it might have been 70,000,
but maybe in Middlesbrough they'd
actually help you. I don't know,
mate. Why don't you get yourself a job?
Same to you. Why don't you get a job?
Yeah. Why don't you get a job, bro?
Yeah. Same to you. Why don't you get
yourself a job
instead of being on YouTube 24/7? Same
same to you, bro. Same question to you. [snorts] No.
O, does anyone know how much it is yet?
Has anyone ever got a filling from a
private dentist? I heard it's like 150.
I need to go dentist on um the 7th, but
mine's NHS. But I'm just wondering how
much is it to actually get a fill in? I
think it's like 150 180 like a private
dentist. Anyone who's ever used private
dentist, how much has it been? I'm just wondering
the dentist I go on the NHS.
That's another thing. you know, if you
if you don't work, you get free um
dental um treatment.
I think it's like 150, 180, isn't it?
But I don't have problems with my teeth
anymore. I brush three times a day. I
cut back on sugar. I haven't had any problems,
but I'm still going on the 7th cuz I
booked it and I can't miss any
appointments. So, yeah.
I got a nice electric toothbrush that
lady bought me.
Lady bought me a lush.
What about you, Dusty? Have you been to the dentist?
Private? I assume it's private where you
where you went.
Yeah, they're uh they're a con as well.
I heard that them dentists. Yeah, they
do [ __ ] to your like teeth so you keep
coming back and paying more money. >> [laughter]
>> I heard that, man. I don't know if it's
true, but yeah,
but that's like Thailand. But the good
thing about Thailand, yeah, you can get
like a fill in for like £20.
You you pay for antibiotics. There's no
waiting around for anything there. Here,
you got to wait around for everything.
You got to fight for for [ __ ] in your
own country. The people are [ __ ]
The women are [ __ ] It's just a
[ __ ] country all around.
It's actually just a it's just a [ __ ]
old country all around is it really?
If the be if the weather was better and
you didn't have to fight for everything
and the people are normal, it actually
wouldn't be a bad country.
But it's just the way it's just
designed. It's just it's just [ __ ]
It's actually just [ __ ] you know.
>> Hello. All right, Timmy.
>> Why are you whattled over these [ __ ] trolls again?
>> All right, Timmy. I I lost I lost £100
um two days ago on that [ __ ] global
draw roulette that you play, bastard. I
got to 140 and I lost it.
>> PJ, you can't rely on gambling to be an
income, mate. You've got a chance that
you either win or lose. But with me, PJ,
I don't do what I used to do or you do.
I always keep a lot of money back in the
bedroom. So when I come home, I've got
money. Like I've had a nice Chinese just
a minute ago. I had a Nando today.
>> An Nando? [ __ ] That's [ __ ] [ __ ] That is
>> first time in months.
>> £15 for a little bit of chicken. You can
buy it for three quid from the [ __ ]
supermarket and do it yourself.
>> Yeah, but it's delicious, isn't it?
>> It's nice. But it's a whip off though. I went
for a whole chicken and £750 for a point
of [ __ ] beer. What a whip off.
Yeah, you you drinking gamble every day.
>> Yes, PJ cuz I've got a life unlike you
crying over [ __ ] trolls on YouTube
and like that god person in the chat
going on about people when he cries over
[ __ ] Darth Vader. We all know what
these people about on YouTube. Why cry
like a [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Have you won on that global draw roulette? Theund
>> [ __ ] what people think about me. You can suck.
>> Have you won Have you won on that global draw roulette?
Yes, PJ. I've had 100 to one a few times
on the max number. I've had
>> Yeah, but it's hard to try green, isn't it?
>> No, I've had max I've had 498 um and 50
something p I think it is on number
three. I've had it on. I've had it on
>> That's why I don't go there much
anymore, Dusty. I hadn't been in months.
That's what the last time I went to
Nando was the last time I went to Nando.
My sister paid for it in it months ago.
I don't go Nando.
>> But you [ __ ] skin mong anyway.
>> Yeah, I'm skinn bro. [laughter] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> My sister paid for it.
>> Timmy, you need you need to stop saying
Timmy, you need to stop saying that
stuff, bro. It's really
>> You're the one who's moaning about
[ __ ] Joe, moaning about [ __ ] Lord
Jay and that lot and you're telling people
>> No, but seriously, you need you need to
stop you need to stop the skin thing.
It's really boring.
>> [ __ ] 45 making out your life is great
and you've got the worst life on
YouTube, PJ moaning about trolls.
No, LJ's got the worst.
>> No, you have got the you have got the
PJ. Why don't you just stop? Why don't
you just do what I do? Troll people in
the chat and laugh at them. So the [ __ ] [laughter]
>> Timmy is an idiot.
>> I'm not an idiot, mate. I'm a troll. >> Timmy. >> Yes.
>> Are you skinn?
>> Yes, bro. I'm P. I'm like you, PJ. I'm a
virgin. I'm broke. I hate trolls. And
I'm going to cry.
>> Oh, I'm a virgin. Oh, okay. I'm a
>> Every [ __ ] knows you're a virgin. For
the past 5 years, you've moaned about
>> Oh, Jesus Christ. I'm losing brain cells again.
>> Man, you are. [laughter]
>> I'm losing brain cells again. Someone help me.
>> Well, it's not the end of the [ __ ]
world if you're a virgin. Who gives a [ __ ]
>> Oh, Timmy, you're you're making me lose
brain cells. Stop it.
>> You know that more women than you've had
[ __ ] hot dinners.
>> Yeah, I'm a virgin even though I prove
I've had sex.
>> You haven't proven you've had sex. got
his gay club. He's got false [ __ ] teeth.
>> Timmy, you do realize you're one of the
only people in this community that's
never been seen with a woman. You do realize?
>> Yes. Okay. I've never had I've had a
woman for 10 years that you come. She's
come on by said, "Shut the [ __ ] up and
come to give me sex and all this and all that."
>> There was two women that came toward you
before and you were blushing. I PJ,
you're absolutely spot on. You've got no
autism. Your name is Jesus Christ. There
was two women that came toward you and
you was blushing and you're calling me a virgin.
>> You are our savior, PJ. You are our
calling me a virgin. >> Okay.
>> Oh my god. I'm [ __ ] You're You're an [laughter] idiot.
>> Timmy, you do realize Timmy, you do
realize it. It doesn't wind me up. It
just makes you look stupid.
>> It doesn't wind me up. It just makes you look stupid.
>> No, it don't make me look stupid. You're the
>> It does make you look stupid. Calling
someone like me a virgin.
>> About [ __ ] trolls. You're the one
who's looking stupid, fella. Not me.
>> Calling calling me a virgin that you in
your mom's bedroom cuz you can't afford
to pay your own [ __ ] gas bill.
>> You're calling me a virgin? What the [ __ ] [laughter]
How does that even make any sense?
>> Electric bill.
>> Oh wow. This guy has really got
>> Hey, when are you going to move out your
mom's lad? When are you going to move
out your [ __ ] mom's?
>> When are you going to get laid?
>> I've already been laid just a minute
ago, PJ. Oh, just a minute ago.
>> Yeah, I had I had I HAD A GOOD
>> OH, REALLY? SO, just before you joined
the panel, you you had sex?
>> Yeah, I get I have sex every time. PJ
I'm Austin Paris.
>> Oh, really? >> Yeah. [laughter]
>> Oh, so you have sex every day?
>> Yeah. What's wrong with that?
>> Timmy, you're a big fat stinking virgin.
Something like that.
>> That's your opinion, PJ. But when we get
judged by God, you'll see that I'm a sex
god and you'll be classed as a lifestyle [laughter]
when I showed you money last last year
and I made you run away. [laughter]
>> Anyway, PJ, why don't you play some David Bowie?
>> Why don't you show me some money?
>> What about you show me you live on your
own and I'll show you some money, PJ?
That's the deal.
>> How much money have you got? your
[ __ ] moms and stand on your own two
feet and I will show you £3,000.
>> You don't have £3,000.
>> Oh, yes I do. PJ, why you jealous?
>> He doesn't have £3,000.
>> Yes, I do. PJ, I don't lie like you and
make I've got all this money and all
this and I never said I've got all this
money. I never said that with your mom
and you have to ask your mom for a loan
for chicken nuggets.
>> Oh, really?
>> Not really, PJ. It's the [ __ ] truth.
>> Mr. Bean owned you. Mr. B is a legend.
Me and Mr. B have a lovehate
relationship. But Mr. B knows deep down
that you are a skimp virgin Peter.
>> So, right. Is he Is he like Is he the
real Mr. Is he the real Mr. Bean?
>> Mr. B is a wide up. But Mr. Be
>> Yeah, but is he the real Is he the real Mr. Bean?
>> No, the original Mr. B was back in 2014.
>> No, I'm saying is he the one that got
that that you see on TV and that?
>> Oh, god. [ __ ] off, PJ. Of course, it's not.
>> Well, it says Mr. Bean and he's got his
picture. Yes, because anyone could copy
an avatar. You spaz.
>> But he sounds like Mr. Bean.
>> Well, anyone could sound like Mr. B. I
sound like Rick M, but I'm not Wick M.
>> No, I think that's Mr. Bean with the teddy.
>> Anyway, PJ, I'm going to give you a very
quick lesson in life.
>> How are you going to lose your card?
>> How do you pay the gas bill?
>> When are you going to lose your VC card?
>> PJ, when are you actually going to move
out your mom? Seriously. And stand on
your own two feet. Why Joe, have you
seen that account recently or not? [laughter]
>> PJ, you call everyone.
>> PJ, you call everyone Skid, but you
can't even afford your own W
>> that you have to move back to your mom's. >> Okay,
>> PJ, I I don't I've not lived with my
parents for over 23 years.
>> Oh, [ __ ]
>> Sorry. 22 years. [laughter] >> [ __ ]
>> You've You've lived with your mom all your life? >> Really?
>> Not really. Yes.
You've never had a job.
>> I guarantee if I order your mom a
takeaway right now, the doorbell would ring.
>> Timmy, you've never had a job.
>> PJ, I've had more jobs than you've had
sex. Oh, yeah. You haven't had any sex.
You're a [ __ ] virgin.
>> Yeah, I'm a virgin.
>> How can I How could I be a virgin
without proving I've had sex?
>> Someone please explain that to me.
>> DJ, you're not a stunt gun. You're ugly
as [ __ ] You can't You've admitted that
you don't brush your [ __ ] teeth, you
[ __ ] I brush my teeth three times a day.
>> Don't change your [ __ ] socks. You
can't brush my teeth three times a day.
Cleaner, you are nothing special, lad.
>> I brush my teeth three times a day. But
okay, Timmy, you've got missing teeth.
You said you said on YouTube, you've got
missing teeth. I'll put the picture up
that you don't brush your teeth.
>> Timmy, you've got you've got missing teeth.
>> Yes, because I had it knocked out when I
got mugged at a Cash Point, PJ.
>> Yeah. So, sort your teeth out before I
talk about I brush my teeth three times a day.
>> DON'T HURT ME. DON'T HURT ME. DON'T HURT
>> I brush my teeth three times a day.
>> You are a [ __ ] [ __ ] lad.
>> I've got an electric toothbrush.
>> So what? You got electric toothbrush?
But you didn't brush your teeth three
weeks ago, lad?
>> Well, I brush them three times a day now.
>> Is that because you're a virgin and you want sex?
>> Yeah, that's that. Yeah. Yeah. How did you know?
>> Do you know what, PJ? You will never get
laid. You're too desperate.
>> I think you and non-sligs are going to
die a virgin. Both of you. How can I die
a virgin when I've had sex? You [ __ ]
>> No, I think you two [laughter] I think
they're going to die a virgin. Me. I'm
as big as Mongol. You are. [laughter]
>> No, I think you you two are going to die of virgin.
>> You know what? You two know when you had
that meet up. You know, you know I
called you a Mongol when you had the
meet up. Twiggle D and Twiggle Dumb. Cuz
you're both [ __ ] thick as [ __ ]
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah. Twiggle D and Twiggle Dumb. [laughter] >> [laughter] >> Yeah,
you're a [ __ ]
>> So are you.
>> No, you really are a [ __ ]
>> You are a [ __ ] You can't even stand
on your own two feet and live by
yourself cuz you're scared that the
bogey man's going to come and attack you
in the night. That's why you live with your mom. >> Yeah,
Prime's going to break in and knock you
out, PJ. Is that why you live with your mom?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I can beat 51.
>> You can't do that, Tommy. I can hear it
in your voice. You're about to get rattled.
>> This guy's Could you believe this guy is
in his 40s?
>> Can you Can you please get rat ass off
and do some content on
>> Could you believe this guy's in his 40s?
>> Can you Can you Can you throw a chair at
your mom again?
>> You're You're in your 40s.
>> You're in your 40s and [laughter] doing this.
>> I know your I know your birthday. >> [laughter]
>> What the [ __ ]
>> I know your birthday.
>> Oh my god. You really are dafted, aren't you?
>> Anyway, why do you let this Joe F ru
your life? Cuz Joe F owns you cuz you
get rattled over some Yorkshire geyzer.
>> Yorkshire. What do you call him? A Yorkshire geyzer.
>> Yes, he's from [laughter] Yorkshire. I
called him a Yorkshire.
>> Oh, look. It's the fatty Autumn.
>> I'll leave Autumn alone. She's pretty. [laughter]
>> Just cuz you can't get laid a [ __ ] virgin.
>> Was it? He said that she's pretty. [laughter]
>> She's a [ __ ] for 35. I think she's
doing marvelous. She looks young.
>> She looks fat.
>> Unlike you, PJ. You look 50 cuz you
can't afford to brush your teeth.
>> She's a fat I brush my teeth three times
a [laughter] day.
>> PJ brush his teeth. Show us your teeth, PJ.
>> She's a She's a fat.
>> Show us your teeth cuz I don't think you brush them.
>> I brush my teeth three times a day,
mate. Well, show us your teeth then if
you got nothing to hide.
>> Go on. I don't need to show my teeth.
>> Well, show them again.
>> Show us your teeth.
>> No, show us your teeth and I'll show you mine.
>> Go wash your teeth.
>> I don't need to show my teeth. I brush them.
>> Yeah, I brush my teeth three times a day.
>> No, you don't. Stop lying.
>> Yes, I do. I'm going to brush them in a minute, actually.
>> I bet you haven't got an electric
toothbrush. I bet you're lying.
>> Am I really?
>> Show us your electric toothbrushing.
>> No, I can't show you it. It's cuz you
haven't got one. [laughter]
>> I wouldn't I wouldn't do you autumn.
You're a fat pig.
>> You are a lying [ __ ] virgin.
>> You're a fat pig. [laughter]
>> Do [snorts] you know what pig? I own you
cuz you're reacting to me. It's lush.
>> You're the one reacting to me.
>> I'm not reacting to you. I'm laughing at you. [laughter] >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. [laughter]
>> Autumn. So Autumn, why do you use
filters then? She doesn't use filters.
>> Yes, [snorts] she does.
>> No, she don't.
>> By Autumn, did you know that Timmy skin
>> that Autumn won't poke her [ __ ]
thingy at your dick cuz you're a virgin? [laughter]
>> Did you know that Timmy?
>> Did you know that?
>> Did you know that Timmy skin?
>> Yeah, I'm broke.
Show us the tenner. PJ, show us a tenner. [laughter]
>> Timmy skin.
>> I'm broke. I'm broke. Yeah, I'm broke.
>> You are.
>> You're going to show us a tenner, PJ.
You going to show us a tenner? >> No.
>> Why do I always have to show you money?
>> Because you're the one who goes on about money.
>> Can I see your money?
>> I will show you a tenner if you show me a tenner.
>> I've shown you £1,500 before. You ran away.
>> It doesn't matter. That was before.
That's not today.
>> Yeah, it doesn't matter. You ran away.
>> I use my bank card, PJ. I use called Mastercard. >> No.
>> Oh, yes.
>> Give me your skin.
>> Yeah, I'm skinn.
>> You are.
>> You got a credit. Have you got a credit card, PJ? >> No.
>> I have. >> Really?
>> Only a£500 limit, but I've got a credit card.
>> How did you get that?
>> It's called paying my bills. sometime
cuz I don't live with my mom.
>> So what? £500 a lot of money.
>> PJ, if you started getting after your
[ __ ] ass and moved out your mom's and
started paying your [ __ ] water
weights and stuff like that, it builds
up your credit rating, you dick.
>> You think £500 is a lot of money?
>> It's better than what you've got. You
can't even get a credit card.
>> No, I'm saying do you think it's a lot of money?
>> You You said to London Taylor yesterday,
I can't get a credit card.
Timmy's got £500 to his name,
>> mate. It's more than what you [ __ ] got. [laughter] >> Nah,
>> you have to lie that you got money cuz
you got no friends and you have to you
have to show off to a fiberactic cable
and make a load of make up a load of
stories. Your name is fat Dan. You are the split.
>> You know, you know that London Taylor,
he wants your mini He wants your Minnie Mouse.
>> I'm going to call you fat PJ Minnie Mouse. >> PJ,
>> he wants your Minnie Mouse.
He wants your Minnie Mouse.
>> He wants my Minnie Mouse.
>> I said London Taylor wants all Tim's Minnie Mouse.
>> London Taylor told you some good advice
yesterday and you took it out then you
and you took it through one ear out the mother ear. >> No.
>> Yes, you did PJ.
>> No, you're very autistic, PJ. You can't
handle the truth. You were left with [laughter]
>> Imagine. Imagine Timmy calling other
people autistic. Well, I am autistic PJ
only, but I'm no lefty autistic monkey
like you. You're Is nonsle autistic.
>> You are a [ __ ] baby. You are Is nonsle autistic?
>> Of course, I'm autistic PJ. But at least
>> No, I said is nonslegs autistic.
>> No, he's just a [ __ ] dumbo.
>> No, but he said that he's got autism.
>> No, he ain't got autism. He's got [ __ ] borism. >> Borders?
>> Borders means basically he sits in his
bed sit all day trolling you cuz he's
got nothing in life. You don't you hate
him in it?
>> I don't hate him. I just think he's an
idiot. Not you. I think
>> you both.
>> I think you're an idiot as well.
>> I think anyone who spends I I think
anyone who spends all day on YouTube
moaning over someone over a fiber cable
needs to grow the [ __ ] up their age,
[laughter] not the difference. But see,
with Joe F, he's not obsessed with you,
PJ. He's just having a laugh. And you
can't take the laugh.
>> I think Joe F is a [ __ ] virgin. He's
not a virgin, bro. He owns you in life.
>> No, I think he's a virgin,
>> bro. Right. There's a difference between
obsession having a laugh, right? Red
Star has a laugh, right? He put you wind you up.
>> Surely he's meant to obsess with you.
Joe, Red Star, they just wind you up. >> Yeah.
>> Red Star puts your [ __ ] pictures out
there because it winds you up. >> No.
>> [clears throat] >> upload
this and all this and all that.
>> Red Star is an absolute virgin though.
>> Don't you talk about my friend like
that. He's from Birmingham.
>> No, he's an absolute virgin.
>> Don't you talk about Money Mike that way
or knocked you out. We stars Money Mike. >> Yeah.
>> Yes, it is.
>> And Money Mike owns you, sunshine.
>> You dirty virgin. Money. Mike's not a
virgin. Like you,
>> you dirty virgin.
>> Leave my friend Red Star out of it.
>> Monty owns you.
>> Cuz you're going to do [ __ ] all apart
from Don't hurt me. Don't hurt me. [laughter]
>> Why? Money owns you. Is it?
>> Monty owns no one, mate. He punched me
and it was the most pathetic punch. I
went to someone punch him back and he
shat it. If it weren't for money Mike
holding me back, that guy would be in
the back of an ambulance. Lad,
>> no. PJ. He's He was like you, the backwards man.
>> You're an idiot.
>> You can't call me PJ. When I met you in
your road, you shout it. I've never seen
anyone run backwards so fast. >> Really?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Have you ever seen that
film? The Backwards Man. The Backwards
Man. What film is that out of? Um Oh, is it um
>> You're funny.
>> The Backwards Man. The Backwards Man.
What film is that out of again? Oh, [ __ ]
me. Um it's not Is it me, myself, and
that film? Oh [ __ ] Come back to me as a
film and he runs backwards basically.
They're calling the backwards man.
>> Uh the backwards man. The backwards man.
Everybody wants the backwards man. Oh what
>> do you like the great guys?
>> Do I like what?
>> You like the the five great guys?
>> Well the five great bacons. You mean
>> PJ? I don't mind.
>> PJ is YouTube. I don't mind them.
They're all right. that they can't
criticize others and they do exactly the
same [ __ ] mistake.
>> Jimmy, do you know what? Yeah,
>> listen. Yeah, I'm actually disappointed.
I thought I was going to come commoner
in 2026 and it was going to be different.
>> PJ, the internet's going to get worse. The world
>> No, I mean like people I didn't think
they were going to repeat themselves again.
>> PJ, Satan is working overtime. The lake
of fire is coming onto the earth as we
speak. If you think this internet, this
world's going to get better, then you
need to go to Specs Savers. All right,
Timmy. You said the people only repeat
themselves cuz they're autistic, isn't it?
>> Every [ __ ] person on planet Earth is
autistic these days.
>> It's the same. Yeah, but listen, Timmy.
Timmy, would you agree with this? It's
the same people on here every day.
>> Yes, PJ, but I don't go live going on
about it 16 hours.
>> The same every day, is it? >> Huh?
>> PJ, the difference with you and me. I
don't give a [ __ ] I just get on with my
life. I like to come on the internet
and Max Miller who get rattled over a fiberactic cable. >> Yes.
>> So how do you know it's the same people every day?
>> Uh because it's [ __ ] obvious. You dickfest.
>> What? So don't they leave the house?
>> Most of them I mean of course they
[ __ ] don't. You got Abby Ford
trolling all day on Buzz with his big
[ __ ] earphones on sitting in his
[ __ ] mom's bedroom trolling me and
[ __ ] [laughter] M. And that me laugh.
You got [ __ ] Mass Miller crying over
because he's a lefty [ __ ] [ __ ]
because I have an opinion and I'm the
scarier. [laughter] He's a
>> Mr. Remember LT yesterday?
>> You remember LT? Hey Mr. Bean, do you
remember LT the dangerous guy? [laughter]
>> You know what I mean? PJ, everybody on
this community, including you, is a [ __ ]
>> Wait, LT, Mr. Bean, he's a bugger.
Why is he a bug?
But PJ, seriously, I'm I'm going to say
this and this is the last time I'm going
to tell you this and get this through
[laughter] your head.
Stop giving a [ __ ] what other people do on here.
>> You're looking like a white trash.
>> Everyone laughs at you, Jimmy.
>> I don't give a [ __ ] I'm glad they laugh
at me. At least I give them a smile in
the day. Like you, you a boring [ __ ]
[ __ ] This person repeats himself. Oh,
this [ __ ] does this does this.
I'd rather get laughed at and be laughed
at and make someone smile and be a
boring [ __ ] is a slag. Autumn is a slag.
>> All you do is moan about [ __ ]
pointless [ __ ] PJ's a slag.
>> Can you not eat your mouth or you [ __ ] what?
I can't hear you. Hello.
Sorry about that, mate.
Oh, you're you're a slug. You're slag,
isn't it, Autumn?
You suck dick. You're a Willie sucker. All right. [snorts]
You're You're a little Willie sucker.
Yeah. You suck dick. Yeah. Yeah. [snorts]
You dirty [ __ ] [laughter]
Oh, Mr. Bean, you still there?
You're still there, Mr. Beam.
Oh, you look like a [ __ ] Oompa Loompa.
A poor [ __ ] Poor [ __ ]
I bust myself three times a day to me.
After these crisps and this cloak, I'm
going to bust them. I'm going to bust them again. Poor [ __ ]
that my body. Listen, firstly, I'm not
your mate. And secondly, that photo was ages ago.
That that [ __ ] photo was ages ago,
mate. I'm not even fat.
I'm not even fat. And that was ages ago.
You're the one using filters.
You're the one using the [ __ ] filters. Yeah.
Yeah. You're using filters. M. Yummy. breakfast. bless you
poor [ __ ] Do you remember that
account Steven Albert that said Peter
Belly, you can't leave YouTube. You
can't deprive Grieve. You can't deprive
Grevy of content. You poor [ __ ]
Oh, bro. I I'll never ever You're the
one that sucks dick all the time. Autumn.
You suck dick every day. You dirty [ __ ]
You poor [ __ ]
Remember that time to see him? Poor [ __ ]
I'll never forget that, bro. I was dead.
Oh, it looks like the virgin [ __ ] [laughter]
O, don't you remember that account?
It's disappeared. I haven't seen it for a while.
Nothing you can do to change your [ __ ] situ. [laughter]
And you know the madest thing is stupid
now. That account could be anyone.
It could be anyone.
I've had plenty of [ __ ] that weren't
paid for, mate.
Plenty of [ __ ] that weren't paid for. Absolutely plenty.
Plenty, mate. And none of them were disabled.
I've had plenty of free [ __ ]
Plenty of free [ __ ] Matey,
you're the one with dementia. Not me.
Poor [ __ ] [laughter] Yeah,
you must be the one with dementia.
You must definitely definitely uh be the
one with the venture. I've had plenty of
[ __ ] I don't need to wish
I don't need to wish anything, mate.
You don't need to know that.
You don't know that. [snorts]
Yeah, you don't need to know that.
You do not need to know that, man.
I've had plenty of free [ __ ] Is it
supposed to be a competition or something?
Can't beat the packet of crisp.
You don't need to know that.
You don't need to know that, mate.
It's a bit perverted. You wanted to know
that. Jesus Christ. [clears throat]
No, not at all. I was out. I was out today.
I was actually out today.
If I approach someone Joe and one and
someone says they've got a boyfriend to
me one more time, I'm going to push them
on the pavement.
I'll I'll push them on the [ __ ] pavement.
No, bro. [ __ ] that.
Never doing that again. No.
Hard to make money on YouTube now. No,
you can't make bro.
But I've already done stuff though, Joe.
So when you're saying you will do
nothing, that's just silly because I've
already done more than enough.
I've already done more than enough. I've
stuck it on people,
bro. I've already done more than enough.
You're lying to yourself when you're saying that [clears throat]
it's hard to make money on YouTube now.
To be eligible
is it's very very very hard
to be eligible to make money on YouTube now.
I've already done stuff. Do you not
remember the park incident when I had
that woman scared?
Do you, bro? I think you you're the one
with dementia, not me or lady.
I think it's definitely you. I think
you've actually forgotten [ __ ] I've
actually done in the past.
Uh, I don't know, bro. Probably never.
I'm just happy to stay in bed.
She wasn't scared.
She wasn't scared. Okay, bro. You keep
telling yourself that.
You keep telling yourself that, bro. She
was [ __ ] herself.
She was literally [ __ ] herself.
Oh, she was scared.
She was definitely definitely definitely definitely scared.
You was definitely definitely definitely
scared. But you like to twist things so
keep tell yourself that anyways.
No, bro. No losses for Joe. He always wins.
Joe never loses. Joe always wins.
Did you not know that?
Yeah, he always wins.
Yeah. And don't forget he won't go live
in a bookies because he doesn't want to get banned.
That's his reasoning for not going
gambling live. Huh?
Yeah. I'm saying it. Yeah. I'm in bed.
What do you want me to do, bro?
Yeah, it's a Saturday in January, bro.
No one's out.
I mean, firstly, it's January, so no
one's out anyways. Uh because they all
skinned. And secondly, Okay. And your
point is, what do you want me to do?
Thank you, man. What do you want me to do?
Go out to pubs and bars, but no one's in them.
I mean, what are you expecting?
Did he tell us what you expect him?
I'm in the best place. No more bad experiences.
[snorts and clears throat]
Yeah. I mean,
no. What do you expect me to do? Yeah.
I'm on YouTube on Saturday in bed in
January at 28. Yeah. What do you want me to do?
go out and get more bad experiences with
women and deal with toxic [ __ ] No offense. No thanks.
But I mean, it's dead anywhere in
London. Well, there's going to be people
out, but not many people. So, what do
you want me to do then?
Yeah, it's Well, it's actually just past quarter.
Um, yeah. What [snorts] do you want me to do?
You don't understand. I'm tired of it.
It is dead. It is dead.
Drinking environments are dead in January.
They are dead, bro. They are dead.
They are dead. Trust me. I've been out
in January, bro. It's dead.
It is dead. Well, I mean, there's going
to be people out, but it's dead compared
to what it normally is. And it doesn't
matter whether it's dead or not, bro.
I'm not going out regardless.
So, forget I even mentioned that because
I still wouldn't be going out. So,
I don't want to go out. I don't want any
more bad experiences.
Yeah. Prove me wrong. Yeah. Yeah. Go to
O'Neal's. Go to O'Neal's and and show me
there's people out.
Yeah. Go on, brother. I remember I went
to Stratford Westfield in January last
year and it was dead.
It was dead, brother. I know my city,
brother. It's dead. It is literally
dead, brother. I know the city that I
live. I went out I went to Westfield in
Stratford in January and it was pretty
much empty in January.
And I've been out in January, bro. I've
been out in January every year and it is
dead. It is literally dead. The club
that I went to meet Stig at,
it was dead. It was like I went at
10:00. I swear to God, I remember this
as well. And I actually messaged the
[ __ ] I went there at 10:00.
I was there for an hour. Still nobody
was coming in.
It was dead as [ __ ] I was like, "Why is
it so dead?"
Yeah. Go on.
No, it's dead.
And it doesn't matter anyways. I
wouldn't be going out anyways. So,
yeah, I have no reason to go out. And 28
is not 24, not 25. I don't need to go out.
What am I going out for, bro?
[snorts] No. Well, I was out today. I
went out today.
I tell you what's not good for your
mental health. Dating women.
I can't afford to go. Okay, bro. You
keep You keep telling yourself that.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that, bro.
Yeah. No money. Yeah, you keep telling
yourself that. Anyways, uh I was out uh
I was out today, bro.
Um I I've already been out today.
I don't want any more bad experiences. I
don't want any more I tell you what's
really bad for your mental health,
Samuel. Uh, welcome back, brother. I
tell you what's even worse for your
mental health is going out trying with
women. That's really bad for your mental
health. And that's why I gave up. I'd
rather be sat here and do nothing than
deal with them ever again.
No, no, no, no, no. That's even worse.
No, no, no, no, no, no. Hell the [ __ ]
no. Am I going near a woman ever again
in my life? You can get [ __ ] They're
all the same, bro.
Trust me, I'm on my last nerve as it is.
Nope. I ain't going out,
brother. I'm done with it. I mean it.
We've already broke the record. I mean
what I'm saying and I'm not going back
on what I say. I don't contradict myself. Simple.
I am dumb.
I am done, bro.
Been there, done it, won the t-shirt. Joseph.
Oh, yeah. He does know about that as
well. I need to tell her about that.
I need to tell her about that as well.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I need to tell her about that.
But listen, been there, done that.
Um, it's not busy. And anyways, Joe,
Joe, listen. If I didn't go out most of
December and I didn't go out in
November, why am I going to go out in January?
Okay, brother. Whether it's busy or not,
which I know it's not busy. Whether it's
busy or not, I'm not going out anyways. So,
I mean, I'm not going out anyways.
Whether it's busy or it's not. And trust
me, it's not busy. I know my city and I
know what month it is. Uh, brother,
listen, it's not busy. It's not busy.
Yeah. Anyways, we're not having an
argument about this anyways because I
simply don't give a [ __ ] Even if you're
right, I literally don't care. I've been
out in January and every time I've been
out in January, it's been dead. And even
if it's not dead this January, which it
is dead, I'm still not going out. So, [ __ ] off
there. I have been going out generally
for the past three years and it's always been dead.
It's been dead until [ __ ] like February.
It literally has been dead until
February. Yeah, there's going to be some
people out obviously.
I went out last January. It was so dead.
I went back home. I tried a few times.
And anyways, I wouldn't be going out anyways.
You know, even if it miraculously came
busy, I don't really care.
Nope. I'm not getting myself out there.
I'm completely done. [snorts]
You keep telling yourself that.
No, I just don't want any more bad
experiences with women. It makes logical
sense. Were you always sick of me going
out? You're sick of me going out coming
back and moaning about the same thing.
No. So, we're not doing it anymore. We
are not doing it.
We [snorts] are not doing that [ __ ] anymore.
We're not doing that anymore, bro.
What the [ __ ]
We're not doing it. We don't contradict
ourself on this channel.
I don't want any more bad experiences. I
shouldn't have to go out. Like I said to
you earlier, I shouldn't have to go out again.
I should have to turn out again. I
should have to go out again.
I'm not getting myself outside. Bro,
you're you're wasting your time with me.
I'm not going nowhere.
I don't give a [ __ ] if I'm 28. I've been
dealing with this [ __ ] for years and I'm stopping now.
I'm already on my last nerve as it is,
you know, holding it by a straw. So, I
ain't going nowhere.
I'm not going nowhere.
I'm literally having a shower in a bit,
brushing my teeth, and I'm going bed.
That's what I'm doing. Okay.
In my head, Steven Howard, I should have
to be trying again.
I said it to this guy earlier on Reddit
and this Belgium guy. I've had enough
bad experiences to last me a lifetime.
Oh, and I proved you wrong as well, Joe.
You said that I'd be going out in the
new year. Nope. I ain't going nowhere.
I am not going nowhere. So, I proved you
wrong. So, I proved you wrong. I proved
you wrong with that one. Yeah.
I honestly don't think I'll ever go out
again, bro. I'm I'm certain I ain't
going out again. Ever. Uh-uh.
H I proved you wrong.
You saw me back at it. [ __ ] that, bro. Uh-uh.
What? To get more bad experiences. Oh,
you're too young for me. You're too old
for me. I'm not dating you cuz you're a
Muslim. Oh, let's meet up at this time.
Oh, actually, I found someone. And I
have to start sending people my dick all
over again. [ __ ] off, bro.
And I have to start sending people my
dick again and get my WhatsApp banned.
Get the [ __ ] out of here, bro.
You must be [ __ ] Been there. You been
there, done it, won the t-shirt. They're
all the same. I've got nothing left to prove.
I tell you what, right?
One of these numbers meet me.
I'm unlikable. Oh, that's nice for you,
bro. Yeah. Yeah, that's nice. Really?
That's nice for you, bro. Do you do Do
you tell yourself that to go sleep every
night? Really? Yeah.
You know, nothing you say, no one really
cares about anything that you say. Do
you know that?
Cuz you're just a lavy bong. You come
from L J's channel.
That's why we laugh at you. That's why
me, Steven, and Greavvesy, we all laugh
at you because you come from L J's side of YouTube.
Yeah, man. We all laugh at you more than
you could ever at us. Isn't that right,
Steven? We laugh at him.
Yeah, we laugh at you, man.
Just like we laugh at him.
42, no driving license, barely traveled,
no woman, has to have phone sex with a
woman in [ __ ] America. We just keep
laughing, which is why you actually uh
>> [clears throat]
>> Thank you, bro.
That's nice for you. And what are you
doing on a Saturday? Watching me. So,
what does that say about your life?
So, you're watching me on a Saturday.
So, what does that say about your life?
What does that say about your life?
Yeah, your life is a million times better.
28 and you have nobody or nothing,
brother. You're just talking about yourself.
That's why like I'm not getting
triggered. I'm not asked. I'm not
blocking you because you're just talking
about yourself. But you're just a lot
older than 28. So they got the age wrong.
All you people do is talk about
yourselves for 15 years. You're boring
as [ __ ] Come on, bro. You need to step
your game up.
You're sat on YouTube on a Saturday
watching me. You need to You need to
step your game up, bro. Step your game up.
You're boring. Get a life. It's been 15
years now. Anyways, it says as an older person,
I know they're very obsessed. They're
very boring as well.
That's their life in it.
a red star. You never got any of my
money stopped. I've got more money than
you. But you keep telling yourself that,
bro. You didn't get any of my money
stopped. Not a penny of it. And I've got
more money than you. So you keep telling
yourself that, bro. Like Like I told
you, bro, if you keep telling yourself
that and that makes you feel better,
that's good. Like I'm I'm helping one
person. You never got any of my money
stopped. Never have, never will. I'm
still making money. I've still got more
money than you'll ever have. But if that
helps you sleep at night, you keep
telling yourself that and you're
blocked. See you later. And that's the
way to handle these clowns, bro.
That's the way to just handle these little idiots.
They don't get anyone mad. They're just repeating bastards.
Like, what does that say about their
life if they're sat on here watching me
on a Saturday?
You never got any of my money. Stop. Uh,
I do have money. I make money. I got I
have got money. Yes. And I make money.
And that's for me to know and you to
never find out. And I got more money
than you as well.
And it wasn't who got my money stopped.
None of you got my money stopped. I've
already explained the story multiple
times. But to answer your question, uh,
I do have more money than you. And I do
get more money than you. Yes. Um, I tell
you what I want you to know and that's
for me to know and you to never find out. Sorry, bro.
You still don't have
Yes, you have money and made money. I
get that. But you still don't have what
you have. What I had. You don't know
that. You don't know me.
You How much How much do I have right
now? How much do I get a month? Okay.
Okay. Okay. So, you know me and if you
get it right, I'll say, "Yeah, you don't
know how much money I get." You don't
know how much money I have.
See, bro, did you not learn your lesson
before when you kept talking about
people that you don't know and you got
embarrassed? You don't know how much
money I have and you don't know how much
money I get. I tell you what I want you
to know. Yeah. Simple. You're very easy
to play on this community.
I have more money than you. I've
explained this multiple multiple times
now. If that does not sink in your
brain, bro, then that's it.
Nope. Wrong again. I get more than 1.3K
and I've got more than 1.2K. Try again.
I'll tell you when you're I I'll tell
you when you're getting warmer.
I'll tell you when you're getting warmer, bro.
And it's not who got my money stop. None
of you got my money stopped.
The courts got my money stopped. You
never got any of my money stopped. You
ear dropped and you made up a story to
try to get a reaction. You're boring.
You share terror's allowance. Nope. And
I get more than 80 a week. Try again,
bro. Keep trying. I'll tell you when
you're getting warmer.
I get more than 80 a week. Try again.
And I don't share any of my money.
See? See what happens when you talk
about people that you don't know.
I would have thought you would have
learned your lesson being embarrassed
multiple times, but you don't seem to
learn your lesson, do you, kid? No, you
know, you don't know nothing about anyone.
But guess what? I know that you you wear
40 jeans. I know that you've got a 200
pound. I don't know. He's just he's just
jealous of me. Just like a lot of these
people, bro. A lot of these people here
were jealous of me. Uh, I don't know
why, but I mean Joe, it's like when you
say that I live in poverty, the only one
that lives in poverty is you. 40 jeans,
200 uh 200 um
200 jeans uh sorry4
uh 40 jeans, 200 phone. Bro, the only
one that lives in poverty is you.
Oh, it have been skin. Oh, okay. That's
boring. We've heard that for the past 15
years. Hey, bro. Listen, another thing
is Yeah. Um, you are the only one that's
living in poverty.
You're the bro, you do realize you're
the only one that's living in poverty.
If you want to go buy material things,
bro, he doesn't have nothing going. Bro,
I've told you they've got nothing going
for themselves. These people, I I
literally said this earlier before I
left the house. They've got nothing
going for themselves.
That's the whole point of it. That's why
it's funny. They're just fat, ugly
people that ain't got nothing that come
on YouTube 24/7. They haven't got
anything, bro. They literally have got
nothing going on in their lives but
obsession with people that they don't
know. Yeah. That's their life, bro.
They're never going to change. They've
been doing it for many, many years now.
That's why it's just very, very boring.
Just like them. Boring, you know? So,
they haven't got nothing. He's not the
only one. I've got loads of people
obsessed with me, bro. Loads and loads
of people obsessed with me.
He's not the first and he won't be the last
because they haven't got anything in
their life. That's why they're, you
know, they're on it.
I know. I know. It's mad, isn't it?
I know. It's a strange It's a strange
thing, isn't it? Iva. Yeah,
I think it I think when he talks to me,
he convinces himself things that makes
himself feel better, like poverty. When
he is the one that's living in poverty,
not me, mate. I've got money. I get
money. I've got designer clothes. I can
do what I want when I want. I There's
nothing poverty about me. That is self-p
projection. Oh, and he shows fake
gambling wins as well. I said to this
Joe guy, "Yeah, why don't you go live
gambling?" And you know what his excuse
was? Oh, I'm going to get banned from
the bookies. You don't get banned from
the bookies for live streaming. You
don't get banned going to the bookies
and live streaming. I literally said, if
you win all the time, live stream it and
you can't do it. Another excuse and
another excuse and another excuse.
Another excuse. Another excuse. Another
But you don't you do not get banned for
live streaming in the bookies. We all
know that's [ __ ] I've done it. L's
done it. We've done videos in the
bookies. You are full of [ __ ] If you
actually go live and you actually gamble
and you keep winning, then [ __ ] fair
play, you know, but you can't do that
because you're not always winning
[cough and clears throat]
because you're not always winning. I
mean, the thing is, do you know what's
so mad Iva? Yeah, he's got a ch his
channel is dedicated to me. He's another
nonslegs. He's another
He's another nonslegs.
He's another um he's another law J. He's another nonslex.
He's uh his channel is dedicated to me.
His channel is dedicated to me. That's that.
Yeah, but it's entertaining. I don't f I
don't mind that. Greg and Steven Howard.
It's funny. I don't give a [ __ ] It's
funny to me, bro. It's really funny to
me. I don't mind. I don't care. I don't
mind a wind up. Yeah.
And who's LJ's fans? People that will
never meet him. L will never ever meet
L will like LJ's uh fans will never meet
him. I mean, they're they're trolling
him. I mean, they don't even come on the
panel. It's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
community. What do What do you expect?
Come on now, bro. I have two bookies
around here. If I get banned, I'm
screwed. You're not going to get banned.
You are not going. And I can't tell you
to put videos up cuz then you're just
going to put winning videos up.
So that's that. Your whole channel is
dedicated to me. Are you sure you don't
want to bum me, bro? Since you don't
like the word jealousy. Like are you
sure you don't want me to open my ass for you?
Are you sure you don't want me to like
open my ass for you to put your [ __ ]
little dick in or something? Bro, you
seem like another nonslegs if I'm
honest. I know you don't like the word
jealousy, so we'll just call you gay for
now. You know, your channel's dedicated
to me, bro. And I'm the sad bastard.
Really, bro? And I'm the sad bastard.
Come on now. Stop it. Yeah. Go. Yeah. Do
that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He's
always got an excuse. He just shows
wins, bro. That's all That's all he
does. He just shows wins. And then he
And then when people And then when
people point it out, they're jealous.
When people when people sus the guy out, they're jealous.
What do I want? I want you to come on
the panel and talk. That's what I want
you to do. I want you to come on the
panel and talk. But that's never going
to happen. But then you're continuously
acting like the big man, yet you can't
talk. You act like such a big man, but
you can't even talk on a paddle. If
anything, you're worse than nons to be
honest. You're sat here acting like the
big [clears throat] [ __ ] but we all
know you won't even ever talk.
What a sad sad bastard. You really are a
sad bastard. You're a sad bastard.
You're a povertyridden bastard.
You want I don't want No, I don't want
you to show your face. I want you to
talk. And you judge men's looks. I mean,
you're the one judging my looks. So, you
must be gay cuz I've caught you on Red
Stars judging my looks. So, uh you must
be gay judging other men's looks. You
can never show your face, Joe. And we
know that. We know the reason why you
would never show your face. We won't get
into that. But we know exactly why you
would never show your face. Just like a
lot of other people would never show
their face. We all know the reasoning
behind that. But we won't get into that
because that's we all over that, bro. You know. Yeah.
We all know that.
You know what I mean? Yeah, man.
That's fine. You keep showing your face
and let us laugh. Brother, I'm better
looking than you and all of the people
that I quote laugh. You can laugh all
you want, brother. I'm better looking
than all of you that talk [ __ ] about the
way that I look and you know it. So,
whatever, bro. You can keep laughing at
someone that's younger and better
looking than you. Okay? You keep telling
yourself that. If that makes you feel
better about your life, bro, that's it,
bro. I I show my face and get laughed at
by a bunch of fat, ugly people, and then
when their faces have been out there,
they've always been fat and ugly. Bomb,
gray cat, Pat Mustard.
You know what I'm saying? Like, bro, you
people are are fat and uglier than I
could ever be. So, you continue laughing
all you want.
That's fine. That's literally fine.
I would be very very very surprised if
one of these people on here got doxed
and they weren't fat and ugly. I would be gobsmacked.
Like I would actually be surprised, bro,
if they were like young
uh decent looking. I'd be very very
surprised because it would never happen
that if you were the best looking person
on here, we'd still laugh
on here. People would still laugh. You
don't understand. Well, guess what, bro?
I laugh at you every day. I laugh at you showing
gambling things where you always win. I
I laugh at you every day that you
pretend that you got a miss, that you
you're in denial about the fact that you
live in poverty. I laugh at you every
day. So you can laugh as much as you
want. I laugh at you every day, bro. I
laugh at you. I laugh at Lord Jay. I
laugh at these house bound followers
that ain't got no life. I laugh at you
as well. So we get more laughs out of
you than you could ever get out of us,
you know. Sometimes I've I've guilty.
I've actually been there. I've actually
been on LJs in the past and just laughed
at them, you know, all sat on the
internet, all ain't got no life,
all ain't got no life, got no friends,
got no nothing. And they're talking
about other people. I laugh at it, you
know, to be honest with you.
You know, whenever I go on your channel,
I laugh at you. Yeah, it's funny cuz
you're so low IQ that what you're doing
is not working. I know what you're
trying to do on your channel cuz I'm
more intelligent than you'd ever be, but
it's not working.
I literally know what you're trying to do. You know,
do. Like I I sused you out a long time
ago when you started defending your
boyfriend Nons. I sused you out straight
away. than when you was putting the
gambling stuff up. Like, I sused you out
immediately. You're that predictable.
You know what I'm saying? You're
literally that predictable. Um, yeah.
And that's that. I thought you left. I
thought you left as well. I thought you left YouTube.
So, um, yeah, that's that basically.
So anyways, so why do you want me to go
out on Saturday? Anyways, today it's
Saturday today. What What's the purpose
of me going out, mate? What would you uh
what I don't know what you want. Why do
you want me to go out? Huh?
Oh, I see people getting a haircut
today, bro. What a waste of money.
This, you know, this time of uh year. I
actually saw it, you know. Yeah.
Yeah. So, why are you saying that I'm
sad for staying in?
Well, I will get something. I'll get bad
experiences and have to deal with toxic women again,
bro. I I really need to join this porn
thing, bro. I keep saying I'm going to
do it, but I'm just so lazy to even try
and do it to be fair.
Yeah, I will get something. I'll get bad experiences.
and [ __ ] with women.
That's what will happen. That's what
I'll get. So, I will get something. Yeah.
Yeah, I need mates to go out. Yeah, I've
got mates and I've proven I've got mates.
You people ain't got mates, though.
That's why you're on YouTube 24/7. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, I've got mates. You people ain't
got none, though. That's why you're on YouTube 24/7. Uh,
brother, you do realize
that you need to stop this now, bro.
This has been going on now for 15 years, lad.
And it hasn't changed your life once you doing this.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I, brother, listen. And I'm And I'm
telling you, yeah, I I'm saying London's
dead because I live in London. Yeah. And
it is dead. Also, you said to me,
"Dementia, brother. Why would I have
dementia, you retard?" You said to me,
You said to me, You said to me, "Oh,
well, I mean, yeah, nothing's going to
change in your life either. You're the
one sat on YouTube obsessed with me
every day. You're on YouTube obsessed
with a 28-year-old every day. Look at your life.
You know, you need to you need to look
at your life, bro. Your life's not changing.
You've been on it for years as well, you sad bastard. Yeah.
No, I never forgot what I said, you
[ __ ] You said to me, "Oh, why you why
are you on YouTube on a Saturday?"
Yeah, you people are bully victims. Stop
talking about yourselves.
Yeah, everyone owns me. Yeah, good for
[snorts] you. Anyways, uh you said that
you was uh you said to me, "Why are you
on YouTube? I'm sad for being um sat in
doors at 28 on a Saturday." And I said
to you, "What am I supposed to be doing?"
[ __ ] on doing back flips or something
like what the [ __ ]
you saying? I've got dementia, you [ __ ]
Get a life, Joe. Stop coming online
every day harassing people that are
younger and better looking than you. You
say you've got all of this money. You
say you've got this life. I don't see
it. I really really don't see it. Just
like what that guy said. I really You
just You just seem like another nonslegs to me.
You just seem like another nonslegs.
Just another little jealous bully victim
obsessed on YouTube every day. You're
just another nonslegs.
Also, why did you never talk about um
the women that I was in bed with when
Nonsense was calling me a virgin? Just
just throwing it out there. I don't
think I ever got an answer to that. Do
do I? Did I?
Cuz obviously you're impartial in it and
you say things how you see it and you
were just being partial impartial by
what you were saying. You never ever
brought up the pornos or anything, did you?
Strange. [gasps and sighs]
Bit bias, isn't it?
I said this to LT yesterday as well. He
was like, "Oh, yeah, he's got a
girlfriend." I was like, "I know, but
I've actually proven I've had sex with
multiple different women, and I've
actually had women and I've had women
Yeah, women don't like you either." I
know, bro. Women don't like you either.
And I can assure you that I've been with
more women than you have. Oh, bro. Women
don't like you either.
If women don't like me, they definitely
don't like you.
That's strange how you never brought up
uh me sleeping with the women. That's a
bit strange, isn't it?
H bit weird. Yeah. Women don't like you
either. I've been seen with women. None
of you. None of you have. Yeah.
So, anyways, why didn't you uh talk
about the pornos on nonsleges when he
was calling me a virgin? You never did
answer that, did you? You were so fast
enough to uh to defend him. I thought
you was being fair.
That's a bit strange, isn't it? Peas hammer.
That's a bit That's a bit strange. Bit strange.
You seem like a non-slover to me, but we
won't get into that.
Oh, these people would don't even have
the guts to leave their house.
It doesn't matter if I paid for a
[ __ ] or not. I've actually proven
I've had sex multiple times. I mean,
I've been in multiple different women's
beds that weren't prostitutes. And I
never saw you brought it up once,
which surprised me that you were so
quick to defend your boyfriend for
having a disabled girlfriend. He hasn't
proven he's had sex. I have. I've
literally proven I've had sex multiple
times. He's He's never proven he's had
sex. I don't give a [ __ ] if he's got a
girlfriend or not. He's never proven
he's had sex. I have. Big difference. I
mean, literally big difference.
Yeah. Thanks for mentioning it, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, I've actually proven I've
had sex. I don't give a [ __ ] if he's got
a disabled girlfriend or not. I don't
give a [ __ ] I've proven I've had sex
multiple times. Multiple [ __ ] times.
Even back years ago. But I didn't see
you there, Joe, talking about it. But
you were so fast to defend your
boyfriend talking about his disabled
girlfriend. Oh, he can't be a virgin.
He's got a girlfriend. You little
[ __ ] Kieran. Kieran also noticed that as well.
Kieran noticed that as well, mate. You
had a panic attack. You was like, "Oh,
how can someone with a girlfriend?"
Robert, that does not prove he's had
sex. I've actually proven I've had sex.
I don't care about a disabled girlfriend.
I literally don't care about a disabled girlfriend.
Joe was like, "Oh, he can't. He got a
girlfriend. He's got a girlfriend." He
was licking his ass for somebody doesn't
like you. It's so weird. He definitely
definitely is a lavry mong. I I knew as
soon as that he was just a lavry mong, you know?
Definitely definitely a lavy mong. That
[ __ ] skinned virgin has never proved
he's been inside a woman ever. I have. I
literally literally literally have.
Yeah, a few people's mentioned it.
A few people's mentioned it.
That is very strange, isn't it? And I
was saying the same thing to LT. I said,
"Brother, it doesn't matter if I paid
for it or I didn't pay for it. I still
had it. That doesn't mean anything.
Whether I paid for it or I didn't, it
still had sex and I proven I've had sex. So,
yeah, good point, bro. Good point.
They are very, very obsessed.
Yeah. Don't call them jealous, though.
Don't call these people jealous. They're
not jealous. They've got nothing to be jealous of.
These people have got nothing to be
jealous of, they say.
But they're on YouTube 24/7. They can't
take a day off of YouTube. And their
lives are better than yours.
I don't know, man. I beg [snorts] to
differ, to be honest.
Sat on YouTube 24/7.
They were on YouTube Christmas. [snorts]
I don't know, man. I would like to put
money on that.
What's their reason for being on YouTube 24/7?
What's their reason for what? Being on
YouTube or doing what they do? Yeah,
that's what I Oh, that's what I've
asked. If you're not generous with
someone, why do you do this every day?
They can't answer it.
They They say they do it for reaction,
but I mean, even if you don't react to them,
uh they still do it. But they're not
jealous of you, and they're better than
you. They've got more life than you.
They just sit and obsess over someone
they don't know. I mean, they It makes a
lot of sense, doesn't it? Yeah.
Cuz me personally, I wouldn't be
obsessed with somebody that I was better
than. But that's just me.
If I was better than someone, I wouldn't
waste my time on them. I wouldn't waste
my energy stalking someone every day.
But hey, that's just me. Everyone's
different. [snorts] What's right and
what's wrong? Oh, [ __ ] hell. It's
cold, isn't it, man?
Yeah. They're not jealous. They're not
jealous at all, bro. No.
[snorts] Do you know what makes me laugh
about it, Peas Hammer, is that they
judge you. Yeah. So, they've got their
opinion on you and then they say what
they want about you. Yeah. So, they say
that in it, but then it's like these
people are a million times worseer than
you, uglier than you, fatter than you,
skinnier than you, lonier than you. All
of the people that are judging you are
worse off than you.
That's the thing that makes it so funny, bro.
That's the thing that makes the whole
thing just so [ __ ] funny.
Um because they are literally worse than you.
That's the thing. And by you, I mean me.
I would explain why I do this. I prove
you bull cup wrong. And it makes me feel
good. No, my life isn't yours, brother.
Your life is worse than mine. You're on
YouTube sat there being obsessed with a
28-year-old every day. I assure you,
your life is worse than mine.
No. No. Your your life is is is
literally being obsessed with me. Nice
try, though, bro. Nice try.
Yeah. You're older than me. You're
uglier than me. You got poverty jeans.
You got a poverty vote. You got poverty
phone. and by the looks of it, you've
got a gambling addiction even though you
only show your wins
and your life is better than mine.
Please explain it. If you are going to
say something, can you back it? Can you
back um can you back it up with facts?
Can you elaborate and back it up with facts?
You've got a chronic gambling addiction,
even though you pretend you win all the
time. You're wearing 40 jeans. You got
200 phone. All you have to show is a
pension that's probably not even yours.
I don't think your life is better than
mine somehow. I don't think your life is
better than mine.
I really, really don't think your life
is better than mine somehow.
I really, really don't.
You also live in a location where
there's literally no opportunities
as well. I mean, there isn't really much
to be jealous of.
I don't really know what's there to be
jealous of to be fair.
I just don't know.
Oh, really? How do you know it was his pension?
Are you sure it was his pension? Mute.
You don't work. That's another thing.
You was telling me to get a job, but you
don't work yourself.
Uh, are you sure that was his pension?
Do you know him? What's his name? What's
his real name?
You should know all of these things if
you know him so much. Also, you tell
you're telling people to get a job and
you ain't got a job yourself.
You're another one as well. These people
have been on here for 15 years telling
people to get a job, but they ain't got
a job themselves.
Been calling people skimp, but they
skint themselves. Could you imagine? Right.
These people have literally been on
YouTube for 15 years self projecting.
Imagine that. And they're older than you.
That is that is that is mad to be fair.
That is mad, bro. Listen.
A pension. You can't touch a pension. Okay.
Uh one second, bro. You can't touch a
pension. Why don't you actually show
disposable money that you've got now?
I know. But don't forget, peas. I'm the
one that's living under poverty.
I'm the one that's living under poverty. Remember,
I'm the one who's who's living under I'm
the one who's living under the poverty.
I'm living under poverty. Me, bro.
Yeah. Really? Okay.
Really, really really really
funny, bro. Really funny.
Do you know what's so mad is this phone
that I'm on right now that's blacklisted
is still worth more than your phone.
That's how funny it is. This phone that
I'm on is blacklisted and it's still
worth more than your phone
and it's blacklisted. >> [laughter]
>> Do you know how mad that is? A
blacklisted phone is actually worth more
than your phone that's not blacklisted.
That's how sad it is, you know?
Yeah. I've got a lot of people obsessed
with me. Peas hammer. I've got a lot of people.
Why do you think they're so obsessed with me?
What's your opinion?
Do you think they may be I think they
may be gay to be honest with you. I
think that they could be gay these people. Yeah,
maybe they're gay or something.
Yeah. Oh, no. They're not jealous, bro.
Don't call them jealous. They're not
jealous. Don't call them jealous.
There's nothing for them to be jealous of.
No, don't call them jealous, bro. Jesus
Christ. Don't get into that again. No,
they're not jealous, bro. No, they're
not jealous. Nah, of course they're not.
Nah, they're not jealous, bro. Don't
call these people jealous.
No, they they've got great lives. These people
not jealous. They got nothing to be jealous of.
No, nothing. Nothing to be jealous of. Thank you.
>> All right.
What did you get? >> Yeah.
They've got nothing new and nice to say
about anyone. Peas hammer.
Mhm. They've got nothing nice and new to
say about anyone. [snorts]
They slag people off every day on this
YouTube. Have you noticed that?
They just slag people off.
Slag people off on the internet they
don't even know. 15 years
they don't have family love. Oh, bro.
Didn't you see them? Didn't you see them
two weeks before Christmas when they
were trying to say that my family hate
me and I'm going to be alone Christmas?
It was all self projection.
All self projection, bro.
That straw is [ __ ] All self projection.
Yeah, this was like two weeks before
Christmas. They were doing it every day,
bro. They were they were relentless. M
Yeah, I think Ronald Pump was right.
There was a guy on here before uh called
Ronald Pump Peace Hammer and he was
like, "You're better looking than them.
You've got more money than you more
money than them, and you got a better
life than them, and it kills them."
I think he was right, you know, bro. I
generally think that guy was right.
He said it kills them. He says you
should come, you should um you should
just leave this community and just go on
another channel and that and live your life.
I think he was right to be honest with
you. The amount of people that are
obsessed with me every day is mad. I
didn't get food, bro. I I went Nando
earlier, Reevesy. I went Nando.
My sisters hate me. I was with my sister today.
Um, and my mom loves me and I was with
my sister today
and my dad did not drink himself to
death. Try again. You must be You must
be self-reflecting your family life onto
me, bro. Cuz I'm pretty sure I was with
my sister today and I was with my sister Christmas.
Yeah, you're definitely self projecting that. [snorts]
Wouldn't be the first time. Uh yeah, I
went to Nando earlier and um yeah, I'm
having a banana milkshake. Mhm.
It's cuz you're younger and better
looking than these people. That's what
it is, bro.
By you, I mean me.
Look [snorts] at this. My sisters hate
me. My sister My sisters do not hate me.
I was with my sister today. I was I was
with my mom today. I live with my mom.
What the [ __ ] are you talking about, bro?
There's a sister that I don't talk to.
I've got two sisters. Yeah. I don't talk
to one of them,
you know. And I was live on Christmas as
an experiment and they were on YouTube
Christmas. These people was on YouTube
Christmas, by the way. Um I was live for
5 minutes before going to my sisters and
they were all on YouTube. So that proved
that all of what they were saying about
family hating people, it was them cuz
they were on YouTube Christmas. I turned
the phone on. I walked down the stairs.
I left the phone upstairs. I waited 5
minutes. I walked back up the stairs and
they were on YouTube. So all of that
[ __ ] what they were doing over the
festive period. It was all themselves.
Everything is themselves. Everything
that they say on here is themselves.
Else they wouldn't be on here hating
every day. That's my That's been my
point for years, [snorts] you know.
Yeah, they were they were they were bad
two weeks before Christmas, bro. Proper proper proper.
But on Christmas, these was without a
family and these were without a Christmas dinner.
They were out. They was with They were
without a family and they were without a Christmas dinner. >> [snorts]
>> Trust me, they were right.
Isn't that right, Grezy? Yeah.
But I've got another channel, by the
way. Um, Peace Hammer, where I put all
my approaches up. I've actually got another channel.
Yeah, I've got another channel. I've got, [snorts]
bro, no one cares whether it's your
pension or not. You can't even touch your pension.
You can't even touch your pension, you
pathetic old man. So, no one really
cares if it's your pension or not, you sabastson.
I said [snorts] it's probably not yours.
And even if it is yours, but listen, you
can't touch it, you know?
[clears throat] Yeah. 17 years. You
probably won't even be [ __ ] alive in 17 years.
Can't even touch a woman without paying
her. That's you talking about yourselves again.
again. Well, actually, you're not even
talking about yourselves to be fair. I
take that back because you people are so
ugly that even if you even if you even
if you paid a woman, you still wouldn't
be able to touch her. That's how ugly
you are. That an escort would probably
reject you. So, actually, no, I take that back.
I can't believe
these people live to hate people they
don't know every day. I don't believe
them when they say they've got a better
life than me.
I just don't believe it.
I really, really, really don't believe it. [sighs]
I have never ever said once in my life
an escort has rejected me. [snorts] I
know exactly what I've said. And what
you done was twisted the story as what
you you morons usually do. You like
twisting stories and making stuff up. I
never ever said an escort rejected me
ever in my life. I know exactly what
I've said. And you've twisted a story.
But brother, listen. You couldn't even
pay a woman. You fat ugly people have
been on the internet for 15 years
self-projecting cuz you're that disabled
and that low life. You ain't got nothing
going for yourselves. You're just wasters.
What's my plans for the future? That's
for me to know. and you to never find out.
Yeah, you are, man. Stop talking about
yourself. If you people, right, was
really intelligent, why do you come on
YouTube repeating the same [ __ ] every day?
I mean, people ask you to show your
faces. You can't show your faces. Oh,
I'm intelligent. If you're intelligent,
why do you come to the internet for 15
years repeating yourselves every day?
Just a question. No trigger, no shouting
over. You say that you're intelligent.
Why are you on here 15 years later
repeating the same [ __ ]
I'm just asking a question.
I'm I'm looking forward to the answer.
Every day from the time you wake up to
the time you go to bed.
Yeah, yeah, there's a lot of them 18
years old. They're old men. These people
behind these accounts are just fat, ugly
old men that just,
you know, and the thing is um peas
hammer, you know, when you're on here,
yeah, they actually give you a headache.
They actually you actually lose brain
cells and then you come off for two days
and then you actually feel better, you
know? They they just they're just old
ugly men that just sit on the online
talking about themselves every day.
They're just wasters.
They're literally just wasters. If you
have been bullied for 15 years, why are
you still on here? I can tell you why
I'm on here. Because you people don't
bully no one. You bully yourselves.
You are the ones with no friends. You
are the ones with no life. You are the
ones with no family. You simply don't
bully no one. You bully yourselves.
And that's and that's that. You love pro
you love you love proving you love
proving me wrong.
You love proving me wrong. Prove you're
not a fat ugly m. I'll put the link up. One sec.
Prove you're not a fat ugly m that's
scared to show his face.
I'm a bit drunk on milkshake right now.
Come on, join the hangouts and show us your face.
And that's one you would always have
over these people. And it kills them
deep down. Even though they'll say that
it doesn't, but realistically it does.
We know it all does. If you love proving
me wrong, prove that everything I'm
saying about you being fat and ugly is
not true. You should be able to do it.
You should be able to do it. If you love
pe proving people wrong that much, you
would love doing this. You would love
>> [snorts and laughter]
>> I mean, you said you love proving me
wrong, so prove me wrong.
Prove me wrong. Prove you're not fat and
ugly. Prove to me and all of these
people here that you're not fat and ugly.
You feel bad for me. You need to feel
bad for yourself, bro. You need to feel
bad for yourself. Sat on YouTube for 15
years repeating yourselves.
Yeah. You need to feel bad for your
disabled selves. You need to go get
yourself a life as well. 15 years on the
internet being wasters. Congratulations.
And all you've done is self project your
life in all of them years. But anyways,
listen. You said you said that you'd
love proven me wrong. So why why won't
weren't you show us your face? Why are
you scared to show your face?
Why are you scared to show your face? Come on.
Why are you scared to show your face, bro?
No, no, no. [ __ ] weighing yourself.
What you're going to Why are you going
to go to Boots and weigh yourself and
you can just come on camera right now?
All you got to do is join and put the camera on.
What's the reason why you won't do it?
Can you can you actually give a reason
as to why you won't do it? What's the
reasoning behind you not coming and
putting your camera on? Because you want
to try and prove people that you've got
money. You're you're trying to prove
yourself to strangers on the internet
that you've got money. Yeah. Right. So
why can't you show your face?
Why do I mean it doesn't make you bent
seeing another man's face. I'm not
asking to see your dick. I'm asking to
see your face.
I don't want to see your dick. I don't
want to see your [ __ ] I just want to
see your face. You said that you love
proving me wrong. Prove me wrong then.
The link's up there. Show us your face.
You can't do that. Why can't you do that?
It's a simple question.
Oh, people can easily find me. Don't
even try that excuse, mate. Bomb used to
use that excuse multiple multiple times
and no one ever found out who he was.
Don't even try with that excuse. Do not
even try with that excuse. Right. At the
end of the day, reverse reversing image.
It's not reverse pitch. It's actually
reverse image. Mr. De um dementia and
it's not accurate. And another thing is
Bomb used to use the same excuse and
guess what? No one's found him and no
one's found a lot of these other people
that's been doxed. So try again with the
next excuse because number one that
excuse doesn't wash. Try the next one.
Cuz the thing is right, I'm pretty sure
this Oreo man has never seen me before.
So, if I went on these Streamyards,
right, and these people were saying,
"Oh, you're ugly. You're this. You're
that." I would show my face. I'd have no
problem showing my face. You know, the
only people that would have problems
showing their faces is people that were
fat and ugly like you. And that's it.
So, if this doesn't make sense. So, yeah.
No one's going to know who you are from
just a picture. Stop being stupid.
Right. Have people found out Shagger?
There's loads of people on here that
shown their face.
There's literally so many people on here
that shown their face and they've not
been doxed. So explain that one then.
Shag has shown his face. Who else has
shown their face? There's loads of
people. Davy UK has shown his face. Um
Lim has shown his face. There's loads of
people that shown their face on here and
they've not been doxed.
You're just full of excuses. Mm-
You don't show your face for a reason.
And we all know what that reason is.
You know, it's not to protect your
identity. Stop talking [ __ ]
You know, it's [ __ ] You don't show
your faces because you're fat and ugly.
Simple as that.
There's loads of people that's shown
their face that's not been docked, bro.
There's loads and loads of people. So
yeah, you keep going, bro.
Nah, only people that are not fat and
ugly show their faces. That's your
excuses every time. Listen, bro. Every
time someone's used that excuse in the
past, you've all been fat and ugly.
Like, every single person that's used
that excuse that's been doxed has always
been fat and ugly.
So, no, I didn't get docked for showing
my face. People already knew who I was.
People already knew my name. No, I
didn't get docked showing my face. Ah,
so that's that. But all of you people
before that's used that excuse, you've
always been fat and ugly. Every single
one of you. So, I mean, read and what you will. Yeah,
people found a girl on the train.
Yeah, but that was a one-off, bro. That
brother. Listen, you're never going to
show your faces ever. So, stop using excuses.
Stop using excuses. You people on here
are fat and [ __ ] ugly. And all of the
people in the past that said they
wasn't, you always have been. Bomb gray
cat pat, they've always been fat and ugly.
Why have you always been fat and ugly?
Can I ask you that?
Can I ask you that? Why has all you
people that's been docked before always
been fat and ugly? Like you haters. I I
just want to know why that is.
All of you people that's been coming on
here before talking about people's looks
that's been docks. Why have you always
been fat and ugly
and ever normal and decent looking or
normal looking? Can I ask you that? I
find that very very odd. H
Why is it why have you always been fat
and ugly? I'm just I'm just wondering.
Pat, gray cat, bomb.
Um there's definitely been other people
as well. If you give me time to think,
why is that then? I'm just surprised,
you know, for people [snorts]
um to talk about the way people look.
You've always been fatter and uglier.
Very very strange, isn't it?
It is strange.
I don't think there's one person that
spoke [ __ ] about my looks that's
actually that actually looks normal. H
that's actually been normal looking to be fair.
No, I can't think of anyone that
actually has spoke about the way I look
that actually looks normal. Non legs
[ __ ] ugly as [ __ ] Pat Mustard ugly
as [ __ ] Bomb ugly as [ __ ] Gray cat
ugly as [ __ ] Why is it all of these
people are uglier than me?
Very, very strange, isn't it? I'll leave
you with that one overnight. You know,
may maybe you can figure it out.
It is very strange.
No, no, no. It's not about being models.
They are literally fat and ugly. No, no,
no. It's not about being models. They are literally
ugly as [ __ ] Bomb Pat Mustard. It's not
about being a model, mate. No one's
asking people to be a model. We're just
asking you people to look normal. You
don't even look normal. You people
that's been on here talking about the
way people look. You people that's been
doxed, you've literally been fat and
ugly, like not even normal looking. You
haven't even looked like something on
from planet Earth. I I would even go far
saying, you know, people that look
normal. Let me name you someone that
looks normal. Jake the Snake looks
Um, who else looks [ __ ] normal? Cory
Dak looks normal.
You know, mate, you don't even look
normal. [ __ ] [ __ ] being [ __ ] being
[ __ ] good-looking. You don't even
look normal. [sighs and gasps] So,
never offered money man Head. That's
[ __ ] Do you know why I've never
ever got into that? Because it's
[ __ ] So when something is [ __ ]
I just don't entertain it. You know,
think about it, bro. I I've never got
into that. That's been mentioned a few
times. I've never got into it because it's [ __ ]
So, you know, it's just [ __ ] and
immature and lies. So, that's why I've
never ever uh
got into it. So, why does none of you
people look normal anyways that's been
doing this for years that's been doxed?
I'm trying to get to the bottom of this
on on a Saturday night, you know? H
I really don't know. It's like L. He's
He's lost a genetic lottery. Four eyes,
bold, fat, ugly, disabled.
It's very weird, isn't it? It is very,
very weird. It's as if they don't want
you being better than them. It's as if
they like It's like I was saying
earlier, it's like these people are
trying to bring you down to their level
because they know that they got no hope
and they It's like that it's as if
they're trying to bring you down to
their level, if that makes sense.
What's with the hate every day, man? And
I'm not even just talking I'm not even
just talking about me. I'm talking about
um other people
like uh Monty. I just want to know why
you come on the internet hating every day.
I know it's boring because it's the
truth. Uh I want to know why you do it.
You sit on the internet all day hating.
Like you got better lives than me, you
know? You're better than me. you got all
of this money, but you just sit online
24/7 hating your life away.
Just want to know, you know, no one's
blocked. I just want to know. You you
you hate on people every day. You don't
know. And of course, it's boring cuz
it's the truth. The truth hurts. Sorry. You know,
do you ever maybe like
look in a mirror? You know when you know
when you're coming on here Yeah. and
you're saying that people are skinned
and people are this and people are ugly
and all of these things. Do you ever
like actually look in the mirror,
you know, and go down memory lane and
look at what you people have been doing
for 15 years on this community?
Do you actually like look at yourselves?
That's that's not even me trolling.
That's me being serious.
I don't know what you get out of it to
be honest. I don't know why you do it. I
don't know why you sit on here and do
this every day.
Strange, isn't it?
Coming on here every day trying to bring
people down to your level. That's what
I've been seeing.
[sighs and gasps] Strange.
Like, are you people depressed? Are you
um are you saving for a car? Are you
terminally ill? Uh are you housebound?
I'm trying to get to the bottom of why
why you do it every day.
You know, you're not disabled. You claim
that you're not disabled. You claim that
you're not skint. You claim you're
better than everyone else. So why do you
do this every day?
That's what I'm trying to I'm trying to
understand, you know,
to give them a good feeling.
Well, at the end of the day, but your
lives are perfect. You don't need you
don't need a good feeling. You don't
need to come on YouTube hating on
people. I don't need to do that. I don't
need to. I don't need to. I'm going to
court over YouTube. Maybe I'm not going
to court over YouTube. Try again. Um,
and that's made up. I'm not going to
court over no YouTube. Um, and another
thing is, uh, trying to deflect. I mean,
really, bro, I mean, at the end of the
day, if my life was so good like you
yours or claiming yours or I I wouldn't
need to come on YouTube to laugh at
people, you know? I wouldn't need to
come on a disabled community to feel
better. Make it make sense, Joe. If your
life was so good, you wouldn't need to
come in a community to to make yourself
feel better looking at someone else.
That does not make no sense. Do you know
what all when I when I next see people
again, I'm going to ask them, do you go
on the internet
and um uh use strangers to feel better
about yourself every day? And I I will
tell you the answer. I'll tell you what
they say to me. You know, I mean, again,
that says a lot about your life, you
know? YouTube has not ruined me. YouTube
has ruined you people. You have been on
here [ __ ] for 15 years now doing
this. Sat on YouTube hating your life
away. And that's all you've done is
hated your life away. You don't bother
me. You don't bully me. The only reason
I've I I reacted the past couple of days
is cuz I was pissed off anyways at
something else. No one's blocked. I'm
saying it how it how it is and you know
I'm correct as well. That's why you
can't say anything. You know
I could literally be considered a loser
to society. Yeah. Society could sit
there and tell me that I'm a loser and
I'd still have a better life than you.
That's how damn bad you are.
That's literally how down bad you are.
Is that I could literally be considered
the biggest loser and I'd still have
more than you.
People that sit on YouTube every day
because you people don't fit into
society. Why do you lie so much? You're
on bell. Um but think it's going bro
there's not going to be no cool case.
And why are you reflecting anyways? Why
are you reflecting? I'm ask I've asked
you a question and you can't answer it
cuz you know that I'm correct and now
you're talking about [ __ ] nonsense.
What the [ __ ] Cuz you know I'm right.
You know I'm correct in what I'm saying.
That's why you're changing the subject
and trying to deflect. You people on
here do not have a better life than me.
There is no way people sit on the
internet 24 hours a day from the time
they wake up to the time they go to bed
I've got a better life than me. There is
no way that is happening under any
circumstances. And you know it's true as
well. That's why you're deflecting.
Yeah, I'm still on bell over YouTube.
Well, actually I'm not. But you keep
telling yourself that. Yeah, you keep So
nice [clears throat] deflecting tactics
as well because you know I'm right.
You know I'm correct. That's why you
can't answer me.
And it's the And it's the third
generator. Guess what I've also done.
Sorry. Do you know what I've also done
that you can never do? I've took I've
took three weeks off of YouTube. You
people can't take a day off of YouTube.
You people literally cannot take one day
off of YouTube. You can't say the same
about me. I've took days off of YouTube.
I took weeks off of YouTube.
You literally are on YouTube every day.
You must be [ __ ] disabled in it. Most
of you on this community, you must be
You must be You must be fully fully
disabled in it. You got to be
You got to be fully disabled to do this
every day for years. You got to be
disabled in it 100%.
Yeah, you've got to be disabled.
Simple, man. You mean you didn't go live
in them days? Nope. I wasn't watching
and I wasn't live.
But you people can't even go without
commenting for a day. Why is that?
If YouTube never existed, bro, you're
just talking nonsense. What you're
talking doesn't even make any sense now.
Do you know what? You people really need
to get a life.
Like, you're saying that you're bullying
me, but all I'm doing is pinging you.
That's that's all I'm doing.
You know, you've still answered my
question. Why are you people on YouTube
from the time you wake up to the time
you go to bed hating? I'm asking you a
question. Why can't you answer it? You
people don't bully no one. You don't
bother no one at all.
Oh, did he? Good for him. Tell him to go
away. I'm not showing him nothing. The self projector.
So, really, you're still on YouTube, but
in your account.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. They live
these people live to hate.
This is what I'm saying. They they hate
they hate on they hate on loads of people,
but they've got better lives than
everyone, so they say. But they they
literally come on here every day hating.
I just don't understand it. I need to
brush my teeth now. Going to bed in a bit.
I don't understand it myself to be fair,
but I don't think we'll ever understand it
that I just said to that Joe piece
hammer. I just said to uh I just said um
peace hammer to that Joe uh you're uh
you come on YouTube every day to hate on
pe uh to laugh at people to make
yourself feel better.
Well, so that's a bit sad, isn't it? You
come on here to laugh to make yourself
feel better at to to other people.
That doesn't make any sense, but okay.
Yeah, I'm just about to brush my teeth, bro.
[snorts] Yeah, they they do, like I was
saying, bro, they've got nothing good or
new to say about anyone.
If it's not me, it's not, it's Seaside
Mark. If it's not Seaside Mark, it's
Monty. If it's not Monty, it's probably
some [ __ ] woman, you know.
Yeah, I know, bro. I know. It's a
madness. It's a madness. It's like they
just they just try to bring everyone
down to their level.
You know what I'm saying?
It's just negativity every day.
PJ, are you still a virgin? Stop asking
stupid questions. That's the answer to your question.
Yeah, I know. It's mad, isn't it? What I
think it is, bro. Like I was saying, I
just think it's a bunch of 40year-olds
that's just been bullied their whole
life. That's what I that's what I said
about these people. I just think they're
people that have just been bullied,
failed at everything that they've tried
and they got no hope, so they just come
on here. That's what I think. But you know,
that's what I think.
I don't know about you. I don't know. I
I think it's shade.
>> Yeah, exactly. It's not even like they
they're just doing what they're doing.
They're actually hating on other people.
That's another thing. They don't have
banter. They literally just hate on
people every day of their life.
That's another thing. There's not
banter. It's just boring hating and
repeating. That's that's all it is with these people.
You and PJ are the same. Well, brother,
I literally just explained to you that I
was with my family today and everyone
seen me have sex. So, yeah, you're self projecting again. [snorts]
Take not to hate. Yeah, I know, bro.
Every single day
I've ever been with a woman. Uh, mute.
The only people's family that hate you
is is you. Your family hate you. That's
why you was alone on Christmas. I
wasn't. And I've had sex with more women
than you ever will. Self- projection.
And this is what I mean with these
people. Peas hammer. It's just self
projection every day with these people.
Every day for about 15 years. They've
been doing this. Um they've been doing
this for 15 years.
Um just the same self projection from these wasters,
you know. And you know what's so mad is
that I've shown more women than them.
I've shown more money than them. I've
shown more everything and they still
continuously talk [ __ ]
They still continuously speak their [ __ ]
every day behind their accounts.
I mean, yeah.
It's mad, isn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. I'm going to brush my teeth now, bro.
I'm going to brush my teeth now. Yeah.
I'll be back in a couple minutes. What was that?
Sorry about that, bro.
It's so funny you say that my family
hate me, bro. That's [snorts] just self-projecting.
Hey, I'm just going to have a shower. Is
that okay with you, Greavesy boss?
Okay with you, boss, cuz I made my bed
and I don't want to get in my bed dirty.
Okay with you, boss.
What is it? [sighs]
Yeah, I need to have a shower, bro.
[sighs and gasps] Two seconds. Oh yeah.
I'll be back. Just having a little shower.
Oh, it's [ __ ] freezing, mate. [ __ ] freezing.
[laughter] It's freezing cold.
Yo, just come out the shower with your lad.
Oh my god, it's [ __ ] freezing.
It's so cold, bro.
Just come out the shower. [ __ ] there.
You still there? [sighs]
[snorts] Oh my god, it is [ __ ] cold,
bro. I had to have a shower. I'm not
going into a [ __ ] fresh [snorts] bed
with a dirty body. Yeah.
O, do you remember that when N's legs
kept going about shovel co
peas hammer? [laughter]
That was a fit in, wasn't it? He's a big
fat stinking coffee and he
[clears throat] they all used to copy
each other. I was thinking about this in the shower.
He didn't want to feel left out, did he? Listen,
you can't deny she's attractive. You
can't deny it. You can't deny she's attractive. [ __ ] virgin.
Bro, I'm ready for the nesticles. I'm
going to I'm going to sleep in my basketball shorts.
It's so cold. Yeah, man.
Yeah, I definitely won't be out drinking
this month. Like I said, pes time. I
don't think I'll be out drinking again.
Oh no, bro. [ __ ] that. Nah.
Don't see the point, bro.
I wonder how many times you'd have to go
out now. Yeah. To get a date. [snorts]
[ __ ] a million.
How many times do you reckon you have to
go out before getting a date now? Like 100.
Well, I don't know why people on Reddit
say that you're going to meet people. Peace hammer.
You're going to [ __ ] meet people.
That's what they say on Reddit. But I
don't I don't think so, bro.
Yeah, bro. I didn't go out New Year's to be fair.
I didn't go out New Year's.
It's a Mugs game. New Year's Eve is a
mugs game, bro. To be fair. Overpriced
drinks. Have to pay to get in. Full of [ __ ]
Nah, it's just overpriced. It's just overrated.
Overrated. Overpriced. [ __ ]
it's just [ __ ] man.
No, I was thinking of going somewhere
else New Year's Eve, but I'm not really
asked about New Year's Eve.
It's just [ __ ] overrated as [ __ ]
It's so overrated. I like going out on a
Thursday me in April. April, May on a
Thursday is the one.
I mean when I used to go out I used to
like Thursdays me
New Year's Eve. Nah, I have been out New
Year's Eve. Obviously
it's just a Mugs game
to be fair. Lad [sighs]
I like Thursdays. I don't know where you
live but I like I used like Thursdays. [snorts]
Yeah, I'm out of feel.
So, I hate lending people money, bro.
Trying to get the [ __ ] thing back.
I've got two towels on me, bro. [snorts] Oh, [laughter]
look at me, bro. Oh,
Jesus Christ. It's so cold.
I'm not getting up until I'm completely dry.
[ __ ] it's freezing. >> [snorts]
>> Oh God. [snorts] Uh,
right. One second.
to this Very well. cat.
Oh, we don't need that.
>> Yeah, I like [snorts]
that's literally what he started saying.
He's a copycat.
[ __ ] no mind of his own.
Is there any charge this?
Let me charge this thing. Let's see.
I love these electric toothbrushes.
They're [ __ ] lovely, bro. Copycat and I [laughter] It's freezing.
No, you're gay. You're giving all that. Oh [ __ ] Oh,
ready for bed.
Ready? Ready for the old nest of course.
Oh, that's lovely. Oh, that is lovely. That is
Oh, it's lovely.
Nice t-shirt, shorts. Oh gosh.
Thank you, [ __ ] for sending the money
back. Thank you, [ __ ]
I just say that in it. Thank you, [ __ ]
I'm going. Yeah, I'm going to go on Reddit.
See you in a bit.