being [ __ ] trolled again on this
stupid. You know what? Can't say cuz
these stalkers and that.
You know how it is.
Yeah, I saw Timmy was like, "It's the
same [ __ ] people on Timmy. Same
[ __ ] people straight on to YouTube."
What the [ __ ] I was on Timmy's earlier.
I was on the sofa. Why is it the same
people every day?
[ __ ] hell. Gave me [ __ ] a
headache. I had to click off of it. [snorts]
Yeah, man. It's the same people. Same
repeating people every day on YouTube. [clears throat]
Yeah, I had to click off of it, man.
Yeah, I had to click off of it.
YouTube change this change up, man. Seriously,
you need to change up. I went on
Timmy's. Yeah. [ __ ] you see the same people
doing the same [ __ ] What the [ __ ] bro?
Why don't anyone say anything different
on this community, bro? I had to click
off of it, man. Same repeating people. Same repeaters.
They try to call other people every day.
[ __ ] hell. Madness, isn't it?
Straight onto YouTube. You know
these people? Yeah. As soon as they open
their eyes, Yeah. they open their little
ys and they're straight onto YouTube.
Straight onto YouTube as soon as they
open their eyes. You know, I don't even
go on my phone as soon as I wake up.
Straight onto YouTube. What life could
these people possibly have, man? Like,
what life could they possibly have been
on YouTube all day? Seriously, man.
Seriously. Straight onto YouTube. when I
went on Timmy's madness.
These people need to stop talking about
other people, you know. They really,
really do need to stop.
If they never spoke about anyone, I
wouldn't say anything. They need to stop
talking about other people in this
community, man. They are literally on
YouTube all day, every day.
give you a headache in it.
Yeah, man. Reddit still giving me the
same advice. That boy,
they're giving the same shitty advice.
Yeah, they're giving the same shitty
advice as they always give.
Just mad, is it? Really, really mad.
They give the same advice, the same [ __ ]
you know? What the [ __ ] bro?
Um, they said that, oh, you you could be
uh they said that you could be mistaken.
Definitely definitely not mistaken.
Definitely definitely definitely not.
Um I told them multiple times it's been
going on for years. They still weren't interested.
No, this is not a phase. It's not a
phase. Do you know what a phase means? A
phase means like something that's um
like temporary. This is not temporary.
This has been going on for years now.
[ __ ] years, you know, absolutely years. So yeah,
I was going to go out, you know, today
for a meal, but then I thought that I
can't be asked.
Yeah, I might give you some content
soon, Grezy. I might go to Wales and do
that chicken ticker thing.
Chicken ticker, Donna.
Yeah, poor [ __ ]
Yeah, they are. Well, what do you
expect, bro? They're fat, ugly people in
no life. Of course, they're obsessed. Is
that Is that Is that It's nothing new,
bro. So what?
Who cares, man?
They're fat, ugly people that ain't got
no life. And what, man? No one cares.
Same as that, Jo.
I was going to go for a meal today, uh, Grievy, but
uh, yeah, I can't be [ __ ] to be honest.
Yeah, I'm just chilling under an electric blanket. So cold.
It doesn't matter what I'm doing, bro.
It doesn't matter what I'm doing. Worry about yourself.
Worry about yourself. And this is what
these people in this community don't do
enough of. They don't worry about themselves.
They just worry about other people.
Worry about yourselves, you know.
I think that's a fair point, isn't it, Grezy?
[ __ ] they slag off people every day.
They've got nothing new, nothing good to
say about anyone. [ __ ] hell. You
know, you know, even when you go on
Timmy's, yeah, they've got nothing good
or nice to say about anyone, these
people in this uh community,
you know, they have nothing new or good
to say about anyone.
Yeah. Okay. Yeah. I done my balls and
you keep telling yourself that. If that
makes you feel better, you keep telling
yourself that. You won't get a reaction from me. So yeah.
Yeah. Okay. You keep telling yourself that.
Yeah. Uh Greavves, I went to the um
what the [ __ ] do you call them?
I went to the arcade uh yesterday and I
won a tiger tie toy greasy. I was trying
to win um
I was trying to win um
e for laney but I couldn't win
it for Laney. Yeah, I'm skin. Okay, bro.
You keep telling yourself that. Uh no, I
didn't do a football bet today. I saw
most of the games got postponed though.
I could almost won a football bet
yesterday. I got two out of three. Both
score no draw. Uh both teams to score. I
done a three. Both score no draw. And I
got two out of three. Yeah.
But I couldn't win either. It was hard.
You know the you know the grabbing
machine, the claw machine.
Yeah. You keep telling yourself that.
You know the more you do this Yeah. the
more you call other people's skin, it
just goes to show that you are yourself.
So, um you know, when you keep doing
this, it just shows that you are the
ones that asking. You're not bothering
me. You're not getting a reaction out of
me. You're just talking about
yourselves. So, you keep doing it.
I've already proved I got money multiple
times. I'm not proving you anything. I'm
not proving it again.
I don't need to prove anything. I've
proved you wrong enough times. You still talk [ __ ]
Maybe if you want to, Do you know what?
I'll give you this. Yeah, if you if
you're actually serious about this. If
you actually want people to start um
proving stuff to you, bear with me,
Greavvesy. Listen to this. If you want
people to start uh proving stuff to you,
you might want to start giving them
credibility for what they've already
proven first. And then people might want
to actually start proving stuff to you
again. when you actually show credibility
what people have already uh give people
credibility uh for what they've already
shown then you should basically come
back to us you know is that right Grezy.
Yeah. And that's why we call it an autistic community.
That's why we call it an autistic
community, lad, you know. Yeah.
[sighs and snorts] >> [gasps]
>> You don't have 387K. If you had 387K,
you wouldn't be on YouTube all day,
every day. Stop talking [ __ ] [snorts]
What have I shown you? uh money, women,
food, friends, proven that I've had sex,
proven that I've traveled to meet people
for fights, and you've said nothing
about any of it.
Easy. I don't even have to think about
what I've shown.
If people show things that most people
spin to suit the narrative, no, I don't.
What have I Who have I done that to? Who
Give me an example.
But do Yeah, but do you know it's his pension?
But do you know it's his pension?
People show money. Who? Who is showing
money, bro? I never said anyone's money
was fake. Wait, what? Hold on, hold on,
hold on. You don't know that is Joe's
pension. That is valid.
When I've said, "Oh, that could be
anyone's." That's that's the truth.
That's not that's not anything to suit
my narrative. And I've never said
anyone's money's fake ever. I said non
legs was showing his daddy's life savings.
That's what I said. He was showing his
daddy's life savings, which he was. I
never said his money was I never said
the body was fake. That's what other
people were saying. So,
no, I never said Bob's money was fake. I
said it was less than what he was making
it out to be. I never said his money was
fake. And with that Joe thing, that
could be anyone's pension.
No, other people were saying it was fake.
Uh, well, considering the money was in
my possession, no, you you can't say
that. No, I mean, considering I bought
garments, considering I've been to
expensive restaurants, uh, no, because
that makes no sense. Uh, that pension
could be anyone's. Anybody can literally
go on a pension on the internet and and
put it up. No, that's completely
different. Um, I'm surprised you would
even ask that. I mean, that is the most
ridiculous thing I've ever heard about
in my life. So,
So, money in my possession. One second.
So, money in my possession,
even though I bought designer clothes,
that's that could be someone else's money. Really? Really, bro?
Come on, listen to what you're saying.
Well, show the money now, then. If it if
it's your money, then show the money
now. If you if you've got that kind of
money, why can't you show it now?
Because it's not your money. I mean, the
guy has literally admitted that it's his
dad's some a lot of it was his dad's
money. He's actually admitted that. He
has actually admitted that, you know.
So, no. [snorts] Anyways, because
somebody that lives, right, we're not
going around in circles. I'm not going
around in circles with this anymore
anyways. So, we're not we're not having
the same conversation.
We're not having the same autistic
conversation with I'm I'm done with it.
We're over this.
I'm ending this conversation now. I see
where this is going. So, yeah. Wait for
more people to join.
Yeah. The only one living under poverty
is yourselves. You are the ones that are
sat on YouTube. Maybe they're hating on
people. Not me. [snorts] The only people
that under poverty is yourself. Not me.
I've got designer clothes. I've got more
money than you. I've said that for the
12 millionth time now as well. It still
hasn't processed in your brain. So, you
laugh at yourselves on YouTube every
day. You know all about poverty living
in it. So, you know all about that
poverty life cuz you're the ones that
are living under poverty. And yes, I
said under, not in. You're talking about yourselves. Anyways,
anyways, moving on now. We're moving on,
right? Well, I'm moving on anyways. I
don't know what you're doing. So, yeah.
No, I'm ending the conversation because
you're not going to get through to
autistic people. Uh, autistic biased
people you're not going to get through
to. So, it's just a waste of time going
back and forth, back and forth, back and forth.
Um, because at the end of the day, I'm
going to be arguing with this disabled
repeating people and you don't get
anywhere with them. So, it's just easier
just to terminate the the um the compet.
Oh, triggered. That's repeating. Have
you people got anything new to say?
You've been on YouTube for 15 years
repeating. Have you got anything new to
say? Like, that's not even being
triggered. That's asking you, why have
you been on the internet repeating
yourself for 15 years if you've got all
of this money and this perfect life?
Please answer that question. I I asked
this question yesterday and you didn't
answer it. If you've got all of this
money and all this life, why have you
sat on YouTube all day every day for 15
years repeating yourselves and you can't
answer it because you know I'm right?
Because you ain't got nothing in your
lives. You're sat on YouTube hating
people that you don't know. That's what
you live for cuz you got nothing. I'm
not wrong. I am literally not [ __ ]
I am literally literally literally not wrong.
[ __ ] you sit on YouTube hating on
people that you don't know every day.
What the [ __ ] bro? Sad bastards.
You should stop trying to judge people.
You know that. You should stop trying to
judge people on here.
>> You should stop trying to judge people.
Oh, they're definitely skinn and got no
life. If they had if they had money, if
they had money, they'd have a life. They
ain't [snorts] got a life. So,
no, no, no, no. They want it from the
time they wake up to the time they go to
bed. They're definitely definitely
skinned. 100%. They're definitely
definitely definitely skinn
cuz they wouldn't be on here all day
every day if they had money. Simple.
Okay, one second.
And it's what you actually do on here as
well. It's not the fact that you're on
here. It's actually what you do on here.
So, I don't know any millionaires that
come on the internet every day hating on
people that they don't know for years.
I don't know one person that that would do that.
I do not know one person that would do that.
someone that's got all this money would
sit on the internet hating people they
don't know every day. I don't know what
person would do that but that's just me.
Um but yeah, so it just doesn't it
really doesn't make any sense.
Really really doesn't make any sense at all.
I don't know, man. They're all millionaires.
I don't know. But I don't know their
secret. They're all millionaires.
Yeah, they're all millionaires on here.
By has more money than me. Oh, really?
That's nice for him.
You want to start saying some different
stuff now, bro? It's 2026. Do you want
to kind of like change it up a little bit?
It's getting pretty boring now.
You know, it's getting pretty pretty
boring now. You want to maybe like
switch it up a little bit?
A triggered skin. We've been hearing
this for the past 15 years.
Yeah. We've been hearing this now for 15
years, mate. Do you want to maybe switch
it up a little bit? It's getting kind of boring now.
getting uh getting pretty boring.
Maybe some different words, you know.
Uh really, I do feel sorry for you
players though. You was on YouTube Christmas.
No, I've not been on here 15 years. I
just know these people have been on
there for 15 years. I've known about
this community for about 10 years, but I
know they've been on it since 2012,
probably longer. So, I I know that
they've been doing this for that long.
L Well, them three. Well, I don't know
about Triple H, but uh LJ and Jo
definitely don't have money,
but I don't know about Triple H.
You asked, you self projected. You asked
me where my girlfriend was when you
don't have a girlfriend. Yeah, I
remember. I remember. I remember you
were sat lonely Christmas day with no
girlfriend, no family, self-projecting.
I remember you was on YouTube Christmas
Day. Take that L. [laughter]
Take that L, bro. You was on YouTube
Christmas Day with no girlfriend and you
tried to put on me. You sad little
bastard. Anyways, [snorts] I'm banning
you cuz you're a lavry monk. We don't
have lovely Mongs on this channel. And
your band as well. See you later.
[gasps and sighs]
Sad, pathetic bastards. [snorts] [clears throat]
Remember when I robbed the escort? Bro, that's repeating.
Yeah, that's repeating, bro. Stop living
in the past.
That's repeating, bro. Yeah.
What the [ __ ]
Yeah. Okay, bro.
Bro, why are you living in the past? Why
are you bringing that up? Huh?
Why are you Why are you bringing that up?
Any plans? No, not really.
You got any plans, Greasy?
Don't know what to eat today, you know.
I said I said I've got no plans.
I ask you what?
You're laughing at yourself. You little
self projector. See you later. Love you.
Mong. Well, I just had to message someone there.
Yeah, bro. We get it. You people
self-reflect every day. No, no one cares. [gasps]
You don't have a girlfriend yourself.
Stop trying to bring people down to your level.
They've got nothing new, nothing good to
say about anyone. Am I lying, Grezy?
On this community, right, whenever you
go on someone's channel, even though
it's not involving me, have you noticed
they've got nothing new or good to say about anyone?
I'm sure I'm not the only one that's
noticed that. Tell me what you think. Um,
all they are is just people that are
being negative on the internet every day
trying to bring people down to their
level, you know, even when they're
talking about other people. I've noticed
that with these little Mongs, these
little fat weirdos that sit on the
internet hating people they don't know
every day. Am I lying? If you're telling
me I'm lying, bro, that's fine. You can
tell me I'm lying. You won't get banned.
But I don't think I am because every
time I have been on someone's live
stream, they're always slagging off
people that they don't know.
That's not someone with money. That's
not someone with a life. I'm sorry, bro.
I hate to break it to you, but they're
not people with money and they're not
people with a life. And I can tell you
that with nothing for nothing. Sorry.
People that come on the internet every
day hating people that they don't know
have got zero in their life. Milch.
And I'm and I'm fairly confident about that.
They're [clears throat] always slagging
someone off. I've noticed that
when they're the ones that ain't got
nothing. They're the ones that are sat
on YouTube every day hating people they
don't know. They're the ones that have
got no family. It's [ __ ] wild, lad. Very wild.
Yeah, [clears throat]
pretty much. Yeah, it is the reality.
No, I'm not doing nothing this year. I'm
doing [ __ ] all, bro.
I'm doing nothing. I don't need to do anything.
No, I don't need to do nothing.
Like I don't know what I'm eating today. Um,
no, I'm not doing nothing.
Reddit bans me all the time.
You You need a girlfriend, Triple H.
You need a girlfriend.
I didn't really wake up in a bad mood today. No thanks. Basically, yeah,
pretty much. Yeah.
But I wasn't in a bad mood today. I woke
up. I wasn't actually in a bad mood.
Triple H, you're boring, bro. You've
said this about a million times. You're
very, very boring, bro. You can't troll
a guy like me. So, just stop. Just Just
stop it now. It's embarrassing.
But yeah, I'm definitely going to do
nothing. Be doing nothing this year either.
>> [clears throat]
>> I don't have to do anything. What are
your plans for this year?
Well, I'm not going to be coming on here
every day. I won't be coming on here
every day. What What's your plans this
year, Feb? Let's Let's hear about you
people. What's your plans this year?
What are you doing? Enough about me.
What What What are you doing?
I don't give a [ __ ] if there's nothing
to look forward to, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] [snorts]
[sighs and gasps]
Yeah, I won't be on there wasting my
life on there.
I've done so much already in my life.
I've already done so much.
I don't even go out drinking anymore,
bro. That's bad, is it? [snorts]
Yeah. No, I've just given up, bro. I'm
not doing nothing.
I was out yesterday.
Most days I just wake up bitter and
angry wanting revenge most days.
Yeah, most days that's how I wake up. I
don't know about you people. Yeah.
No, it won't cheer me up. I don't give a
[ __ ] about going on holiday. I've
already been abroad [snorts]
and I don't be on here every day. I've
been off of YouTube for weeks before and
that doesn't really matter anyways.
just revenge on women basically.
That's what I think about every [ __ ]
day and it just winds me up.
Yeah, I don't calm down now as well. I
used to be able to calm down. I don't
calm down now.
So, yeah, I'm not I'm getting no holiday
booked. I don't give a [ __ ] about going
abroad, bro. I've already been abroad. Yeah,
that [ __ ] won't cheer me up, bro.
Only way thing that would cheer me up is
if I got revenge on these women.
Yeah, they do owe me something. Yeah,
just like your boss owes you something.
If you was to work for a whole month,
they owe you something as well.
Yeah, your your boss your boss would owe
you money. So yeah, women do owe you
something. If you've put that amount of
effort in, if you dealt with their [ __ ]
Yeah, they do owe you something. Yeah,
Case closed. Yeah, they do owe you something. [sighs]
Yeah, it's really bad, Greavvesy, bro.
It's really, really bad.
It's really bad, bro. It's every day as
well, Greavvesy. It's very It's
literally like every day.
And literally like, do you know what's
worse about it as well is like no one
can tell you nothing. Like not one
person can tell a grown man anything. You know,
you know what I'm saying?
Getting triggered. I'm not triggered.
These people on here don't trigger me.
People on here don't trigger me at all.
I was in a bad mood. They're just
repeating bastards. I was already pissed
off yesterday. That's why I was shouting
or sorry the other day I was pissed off.
These people don't These people don't
trigger me at all.
These people are laughable, bro. They
don't trigger me.
Not in the slightest. Do these people
trigger me. I was already in a bad mood.
Why would they trigger me? I know what
they are. So why would these people
trigger me? They're fat, ugly, lowife,
skinned people. Why would they trigger a
guy like me, bro? So
they don't trigger me, lad.
Yeah, I was pissed off before that as well.
Yeah, my last 100. I've got a lot more
than 100 pound, mate.
But you keep telling yourself that. If
that's what you want to believe, bro,
you keep believing that.
That's funny to me, bro. If you want to
believe that I've only got £100, you
keep believing that. If it helps you
sleep at night, that I lost my last 100
pound, then you keep telling yourself that.
So, yeah, you keep you keep telling
yourself that, bro.
Know what I'm saying? greasy.
He can keep telling himself that I don't
give a [ __ ] [gasps] you know,
because I don't want to because I don't
give a [ __ ] about money. Money doesn't
make me happy, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] about money.
I've got money and I don't care about money.
Why is it then when someone's always Why
is it that when someone's in a mood, you
think people don't have no money? Why do
you think that? I'd love to know. Do you
think like money is everything? Cuz it
isn't to me.
Doesn't bother me, bro.
Yeah. So, yeah. So yeah,
how [clears throat] many years, Greg?
It's actually gotten worse. It's not got
better, it's actually gotten worse.
You know, I have no idea why people tell
you it's going to get better when it's
literally It's actually gotten worse,
bro. To be honest, it's actually gotten worse. Yeah. Okay.
Well, I'm telling you right now that I
have got money. And if you don't want to
believe that, that's on you. Simple,
you know. Yeah. Grezy, it's actually
gotten worse to be honest with you.
It's actually gotten worse. [clears throat]
Yeah, people tell you it gets better,
but it actually gets worse
the whole thing. Like, think of the lot
the the last couple of times I went out,
Grevy, it could have ended at madness.
That's never happened before. Obviously,
the mood swings and that, they don't go
away now either, you know.
It's no life here. No wonder why so many
people are living in Thailand now. You
know, Ant-Man's not the only one.
You know, he's not the only one. There's
a lot of people doing it now.
So, yeah, it's actually gotten worse.
Yeah. Well, I'm saying it another two
times. It actually gets worse. It
actually gets worse. So, that's 17 times.
So there you go. That's 17 times I've
said it. I made it my uh I made it my
lucky number. Yeah.
But no, it actually does get worse
though. No, it actually does to be
honest with you. Like even last year it
wasn't as bad as this.
Like trust me.
I don't know why people on Reddit keep
telling you like stuff's going to change.
Um, Greavves, I don't know why people
tell you things are going to get or
things are going to change when they
don't change. Nothing ever changes.
Why? I don't know why people say it to
be honest. I've always wondered that, you know,
never, bro. will never ever ever change.
Damned if you do, damned if you don't.
Ain't it grievy? You poor [ __ ]
I still brush my teeth in that. Obviously, [snorts]
I think you see the world more for what
it is when you get older. greasy. You
know, as you get a little bit older, you
get more bitter. I'm not sure.
You know, I think that's what it is.
You know what I'm saying? I think that's
what happens as you get older. I'm not too sure.
I think so, though. Yeah.
Yeah. No Michael Jackson anymore, isn't it, Grezy?
No Michael Jackson anymore.
Telling you there's hope. No, there's no
Michael Jack. Do you remember when
Michael Jackson used to give us a bit of
hope? There's none of that anymore. Yeah.
It's really weird, bro. Really, really weird.
[laughter] Do you know I actually
thought about getting into gambling again, Grezy?
Well, obviously I didn't cuz that's a
cycle. I actually thought about getting
into it again. Like, seriously, you know?
Oh, you're storing about this plane thing.
Oh, you have got no new content, do you?
No new content, bro. Like, um, yeah, I
actually thought of getting into it,
but I think it's that bad that even if I
had won money, I still wouldn't feel
better. That's how bad it is, bro. That
is really, really how bad it is, you know?
That's really how bad it is, bro.
But I have thought about getting into it
again, to be honest.
And that's how you know you're damn bad
when you're thinking of [ __ ] like that,
bro. You know,
but it's worse now cuz I don't even go
out drinking and that. I mean, obviously
I go out, but I don't go out drinking.
It gets worse and worse every year. I
generally feel like that Oreo man now. I
actually feel like that savvy guy. I
feel like that Oreo man, bro.
I watch his videos.
And anyone that watches his videos have
lost all hope. Like you you you've lost
all hope when you're on that channel,
bro. You lost all hope.
So I I watch these videos, man. And I
like people like that that think the
world's against them. I love people like that, bro.
It's like a buzz.
So yeah, I should have to go out trying
again. I'm 28, mate. Not 25, not 26.
You understand what I'm saying, don't you, Greedy? You know,
Peter Bell is a big adult now.
Peter Bell is a big adult,
you [snorts] know, not um Yeah,
you shouldn't have to be uh going out
doing any of that stuff. Stop being
awkward. It isn't being awkward. You
think I'm being awkward, but I'm not.
How many bad experiences have I had,
right? Compared to all of the other
people that moan. Think about it.
Not good, bro. It's not good.
It's really, really not good, bro. Yeah.
See, people like Jo, they're obsessed
with money. Money doesn't bother me, bro.
You know, it really, really does not bother me. you know,
doesn't bother me like it does these
people. It really doesn't. I don't give
a [ __ ] about it. You know,
if I gambled all my money now and the
next week I got £600, that'd be enough
for me. I don't give a [ __ ] I would
starve. It doesn't bother me. I would
starve. There's no way of me starving.
There's no way of me being skinned.
There's no way of me not being able to
eat. Do you understand, Grezy? There's
no way this that could possibly happen
like it did 10 years ago.
You know, 10 years ago, yeah, when I
used to do balls and stuff and couldn't
afford to eat, that would never happen
again. It couldn't happen. It generally
could not happen.
There's no way it could happen. So yeah, [snorts]
I could lose money now and I'd still uh
would bother me, bro.
It's a negative when you're in this
country, bro. It's a big big negative
when you're in this country.
It's a really It's a negative. women,
gambling, people, government, weather,
[ __ ] waiting around for everything.
It's all just a negative.
It's a country designed to [ __ ] with you
and get under your last nerves. It is.
It generally generally is.
It really, really, really, really is.
Just like America, just like Australia,
I'd say they're even worse to be honest
with you, you know. So, yeah. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah. I don't know why people on Reddit
tell you it's going to get better.
Nothing ever gets better in this life.
I'm surprised why they tell you that to
be honest. Nope. No football bets. Most
of the games got postponed. I done a
football bet yesterday. I almost won.
Yeah, I should have just done a double
both SCO draw. I would have won.
If I put 80 pound on it, I think I would
have got like 600 pound back. What the [ __ ]
And if it was just both score, both
teams just score, I would have won in
the first half. [snorts]
Yeah. Don't know, bro. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, but no, not today. Most of the
games been has have been postponed.
A lot of them did as well. Yesterday got postponed.
Yeah, it's horrible, man. Losing hope in
life currently. Very very horrible when
you lose hope permanently. Bro,
they say money is supposed to motivate
people. It doesn't motivate me.
Does not motivate me at all.
I hate people. I hate society. I want to
get revenge on people. It's what all I
think about every day. Literally.
Oh, only 20 pound.
I've got money. It doesn't motivate me.
It doesn't I've got money.
I've got money and I'm getting more
money. It doesn't motivate me in the slightest.
Not in the slightest.
Nope. It doesn't bother me. I get money.
I make money. It doesn't bother me.
Doesn't motivate me in the slightest.
I'm still pissed off and bitter every day. So,
nope. I'm staying in bed. I don't know
what I'm going to eat later.
No. Money doesn't motivate me.
Money does not motivate me.
Think of all of that money, bro, I had
in the past when you've actually seen
it. It never made me feel better once.
I wasn't bitter. I was more depressed
then, but I wasn't bitter.
Money, money does not motivate me. I
don't give a [ __ ] about money.
You know, it's [snorts] like I was
saying yesterday, I was in I was in uh I
was in um just uh what was I in? JD
Sports and I was like, "Oh, I should get
some stuff." But I was like, "Oh, been
there, done it, had it." And it wouldn't
make me happy.
Been there, done it, had it, worn a
t-shirt. I don't give a [ __ ] about
money. I don't give a [ __ ] about
designer clothes. I don't give a [ __ ] Simple.
I'm not even joking, bro. Like you might
think I'm I'm I'm you know
I don't care about money.
It might feel good temporarily to win
money because it's just nice to win. But
I don't know. It's hard to explain it.
But yeah, money don't motivate me,
Matty. It never did.
Think about it, bro. You're getting
three grand a month and you're still
depressed. That tells you everything you
need to know. You're getting three grand
a month and you're still think about it,
bro. I was getting three grand a month
and I was still depressed.
Okay, [snorts] bro. I'm broke. If you
want to keep telling yourself that, bro.
Okay, I'm broke. I'm not going to argue
with you. You want to tell yourself You
want to You want to tell yourself that,
bro? Tell yourself that. I don't care. I
know I'm not. So, I was getting three
grand a month and it [snorts] doesn't matter how. So,
no, it doesn't I'm definitely definitely
definitely definitely not broke. But if
you want to think that, then think that
that's on you, bro. I'm not going to
argue with you. You can have your opinion.
Yeah, bro. Selling my ass. Yeah.
body really doesn't bother me.
Doesn't bother me up at all.
I was still depressed. More depressed
then. So yeah, money doesn't bother me.
I think it's because where I've already
done so much in my life. I think that's
what it is.
You know, I could go out right now, buy
a Stone Island jumper
and it wouldn't make me feel any kind of way.
It wouldn't make me feel better.
No, there's no clean up. I literally
could do it right now, bro, in the shop
I used to go to and I wouldn't care.
I'm deadly serious, bro. I'm deadly,
deadly, deadly serious.
Deadly, deadly serious.
Money doesn't bother me, bro.
Now, drinking doesn't bother me.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yep. He's here. Yep.
Until I'm shown different. I'll
continuously think this way.
I will continuously think this way. I
don't know if money bothers you, Grezy.
It doesn't bother me.
Really, really doesn't bother me.
Don't know about you. Doesn't make me
happy. Nothing makes me happy. No,
I just need to try and find a way to
break the cycle now. Basically,
doesn't bother me.
Really does not bother me. Grieves.
I was going to buy a tracksuit yesterday
from JD, but then I thought, "Oh [ __ ]
there's no point. I've had all of this stuff
[snorts] and I don't really care." Simple.
I don't know how to explain it, bro. Like, yeah.
That's what happens as you get older.
Like I said, you get bitter.
You get bitter, bro. That's what you
get. Very bitter. And show you should do
show you should do. You know, show you
[ __ ] well should, you know.
I'm not obsessed with money. I don't
give a [ __ ] about money.
He hasn't got money. Nons doesn't have
money. But yeah, I get your point.
It doesn't matter how much money I get.
It doesn't It doesn't matter how much
money I have either. I got enough to
tell you that money doesn't mean anything.
None of your business what I get.
And uh yeah, he doesn't have money. Uh
Timmy, but we get your point.
He doesn't have money.
People that have money don't live in bed
sits and went on holiday the first time
when they were 30 that shops in charity shop clothes.
That's not people that's got money.
He showed 13 grand years ago of his
daddy's life savings which he can't show
anymore of Yeah. Yeah. He showed his
daddy's money about 3 years ago. Yeah.
He hasn't got money and I'm not getting
into the same argument anymore. I
literally don't care. So yeah,
I don't really care anyways.
Didn't I show seven grand multiple times?
But you forgot about that, didn't you?
Cuz you're all biased. This is why I
don't want to get into any of these
arguments, bro. Because it's like
they're all just biased on here. That's
why I don't want to get into any of
these silly arguments.
I've shown a better life. I've shown
seven grand. I've shown [ __ ] And you
still come on here and talk [ __ ]
That's why they're not there's no it's
not worth getting into any with any of these people.
I showed more than five grand multiple
times. Multiple multiple multiple times.
And I've also shown a better life
and it was more than five grand.
Anyways, we're not getting into that.
Anyways, what I've shown, we're not
getting into that. Yeah.
But no, he hasn't got money.
Definitely definitely hasn't got money. Yeah.
Yeah, some people get £400 a month.
Yeah, I think a lot of people in this
community get £400 a month. Think so. Yeah.
You don't need to know what I get.
That's none of your business.
What I get, what I have, what I don't
get, what I don't have. That's none of your business.
That's very personal. You wouldn't ask
You wouldn't ask some random person
that, would you? How much they get?
Yeah, I'm skin. Okay, you keep changing stuff that Yeah.
You really think anyone Let me tell you
something. Do you really think?
Okay, bro. I've got nothing. I'm not
going to argue with you. I'm just going
to agree with you. Okay, you keep
telling yourself that. And even if
somebody [snorts] went to the but even
if somebody And even if somebody went to
the bank, well, they wouldn't go right
now cuz it's on there and showed you
money. You'd still be talking [ __ ] So,
okay, you keep telling yourself that. If
that makes you feel better, then I'm
broke. I've got nothing. Okay,
whatever. You keep telling yourself that.
You've already been shown money multiple
multiple times and it was a waste of our
time doing it. You're not show you're
not being shown money again. You've
already been shown money multiple
multiple multiple times.
Um so when you start giving people
credibility then come back to me.
And that's what and that's what it is
Steven Howard. None of these people have
gave credibility for anything
and they're still asking people to show
them more money.
What the [ __ ] bro?
You still call people a virgin even
though they prove they've had sex. Uh,
you still say that people skin even
though they've showed you thousands of
pounds multiple times. Uh, you still say
that people have got no friends when
they've proven that they've got friends.
So, you start giving people uh
credibility for what they've shown, then
come back to me.
I think that's fair, isn't it, Grezy?
I mean, I've still got people I mean,
I've still I mean, I've still
I still have people call me a virgin.
I mean, I still have people on here call
me a virgin.
I've got zero friends. That's
self-projection. People have seen me
with friends multiple multiple times.
You know, everything that you say is
just about yourselves. So that's why it
doesn't anything that you say, bro, it
doesn't it doesn't bother me because we
know what you people are that do this
every day. That's why they can't trigger
me, Steven Howard, because I know what
these people are.
So that's why they don't bother me. They
don't trigger me when they self project.
Yeah. When they self project, they don't bother me.
So because I know what they are [gasps]
and that's why we call it an autistic community.
You've already sh you've already been
shown money before and you and you still
didn't shut up. And that's the last time
I'm saying it. I'm not repeating myself
anymore. You've you've already been
shown money. Why don't you people start
showing us money?
This is the same argument. I'm ter I'm
terminating this. So, you need to you
need to terminate this very quickly. Um
because if you don't terminate it very
quickly, you start going round and round
in circles and then you just give
yourself a saw head. End the
conversation. It's the same argument.
Same argument, same repeating,
right? We're not having any of that on
my channel. So, yeah.
I mean, LJ is live right now, I think.
[snorts] So, I mean, you you're more
than welcome to go on that channel if you want.
I don't know why they're still asking
people to prove themselves,
Steven. I don't know why they're still
asking people to show their money
when they've been beaten at the money
game multiple times. I don't know. It
must be autism, in it. That's why we
called it autistic.
Yeah, you're bullying me. Okay. What? By
talking about yourself behind the
keyboard. Yeah, I'm well and truly
bullied. Yeah, bro. Take it easy on me.
Yeah, your skin. We've heard that one
before. Self projecting
[sighs and gasps]
must be autism in it with these people.
Same self-p projecting repeating people. Oh, boring.
So boring, isn't it? These people,
These people are so boring.
They're sending me to sleep.
These people are very, very boring.
Oh, I think I'm going to have fall
asleep any minute.
These people are really, really boring,
bro. They're supposed to be bullying me,
but all they're doing is boring me.
What the [ __ ] They're supposed to be
bullying me, but all they're doing is boring me. [ __ ] hell. Anyways,
what you having for um dinner today?
What are you having for dinner today?
We're just going to ignore this self
projector now. Anyways, just self
projecting. This is time of the month.
[gasps and sighs]
Um, and that's the way you do it. You
just ignore these self projectors.
Oh, you still on that diet?
You still on that diet?
Bless you. Poor [ __ ] Yeah,
I've already had this conversation.
We're not getting into it again. Come up
with some new stuff.
You see how I'm not being You see how
I'm not getting triggered, Stephen
Howard? You see how none of these people
are bothering me?
Have you noticed that?
Have you Have you noticed that?
None of these people bother me. They're
not getting me high rate. They're not
bothering me. I don't even need to block them.
Think about it, bro. You know,
cuz all they're doing is show themselves
up. I keep commenting this stuff.
They're just showing themselves to be
what they are.
Losers, skin, low life. They just
They're just showing themselves up.
They're just showing themselves to be
the low lives that they are. So that's
why I don't even block them. They just
show themsel up.
So yeah, the more they keep typing and
doing this, the more it shows what they are really.
It just shows it's all about them and not you. Yep.
I might get I might get some digestive biscuits. Maybe Yeah, maybe.
Yeah, I might get some digestive biscuits. Uh, maybe.
What? So, I can't have digestive
biscuits ever again. Come on, man. Come on.
That's not fair, Grey. [gasps]
That's not [ __ ] fair. Come on. It's
the new year. Don't be a copycat the
first day of the new year.
Don't be a copycat. [snorts] Grezy,
if you don't like Rihanna, you're gay. Yeah,
if you don't like Rihanna, you're okay. Greasy.
No, Steven. I don't know how LT says
that Steven Howard is trolling me when
Steven Howard has defended me on other
chats when I've needed to be defended.
Like when people try to call me a
virgin. I think Steven Howard's the only
one. Well, I think Well, Kieran has as
well. Uh Kieran as and Steven Howard.
It's true. How can someone be a virgin
when they've put a porno out there?
How how can that person be a virgin
along with other things you know? [snorts] Yeah. That is
that is strange, isn't it?
I already said um oh yeah well that
woman you paid I said well firstly I
didn't pay her and secondly even if I
did pay her
um I mean I still [ __ ] her so I mean
who does it matter if I paid them or
didn't pay them?
Are you still self projecting, Matty?
You're boring us, man. You're killing
the chat. You're still doing this.
You're really, really boring. You're not
bullying no one. You're not bothering no
one. It just goes to show that the other
day I was pissed off at something
anyway. See, you people can't even
trigger anyone. You're just self projectors.
They're just little self-reflecting
little bully victims. You just don't
trigger no one. You You just don't You
just don't You just don't bully no one,
man. When are you going to get [ __ ]
stop doing this? Yeah.
All right. Remember JF? Steven Howard
when I was going that nonslegs. He's
like, "How can he be a virgin? He's got a girlfriend."
[ __ ] [clears throat] bias [ __ ] Do
you remember that? Yeah.
How can someone that's got a girlfriend
be a virgin?
[ __ ] hell, bro. I bet you if I was in
a relationship, people still wouldn't defend me. >> Yeah.
That's madness, isn't it? Yeah. What
happens when you're younger and better
looking than these people? They don't
like you. Steven Howard, do [snorts] you
know how many middle-aged men I've got
obsessed with me, Steven Howard?
I got a lot of people obsessed with me.
More than Timmy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. More than Timmy, bro.
Yeah. He ain't got no money. He ain't
got no family. He's a lavry mong.
Anyone that comes from that side of
YouTube, they're all the same, bro. He
He's a lavy mong.
Yeah, you bully me. Yeah, I know, man.
You bully me. You coming on YouTube
every day talking about yourselves is
really bullying me. I'm I'm about to
call the Samaritans. Does anyone have
the Samaritans numbers? Bro, listen. You
people bully yourselves.
15 years you've been bullying yourselves
and you still don't even you you still
don't even realize that you're just
bullying yourselves. You're not bullying
no one but yourselves.
15 years you've been doing this. You
know, get a life. You don't bully no
one. You talk about yourselves every day.
You bully yourselves. You people don't
even leave your [ __ ] house due to
fear and anxiety for crying out loud.
You know, you people bully yourselves.
Fat, ugly 40 year olds that ain't got
nothing in life. Don't bully no one but yourselves.
Yeah, I got a lot of Yeah, I got a lot
of middle age made up obsessed with Peter Belly. Strange that is it? Yeah.
Bro, you need to calm down, man. You
need to stop typing.
You know, you're you're bad. Bro, you're
supposed to be bullying me here. What's going on?
Come on. You need to try harder than
that. You're supposed to be bullying me,
but all you're doing is winding yourself up.
Come on, man. You're supposed to be bullying me.
These people are supposed to be bullying
me, Steven Howard.
What the [ __ ]
Come on, man. You should try a bit
harder than that.
Yeah, you try harder than that, mate.
Do you know what's so funny, Stephen?
How? How they're still calling people
skin in 2026.
Still saying the same stuff. 2026.
Yeah. I don't have one, mate. Oh, really, bro? Really? Really?
Yeah. Have you got anything new to say?
Cuz you're doing a pretty bad job at
trying to bully me.
Yeah, you're doing a pretty [ __ ] job at
trying to bully me. [gasps]
Bro, you need to try harder.
Try a bit harder, bro.
You're sat on YouTube hating on someone
you don't know. I think the loser is yourself, lad.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> I think the loser is yourself
to be honest with you. Yeah.
Let me go and lo J. Yep.
Yep. Same people.
Same people on Lies. Steven Howard.
Same people every day. [snorts]
Yep. Same people, same comments, lad.
Nothing new there.
Same repeating people
on that channel. Grezy.
It's always the same repeating bloody people.
Same repeating people.
Yeah, they're bullying me. I'm so
bullied, bro. I'm so bullied. I know. I
know. I'm so bullied. Yeah.
I'm so bullied. I'm so bullied. What do
does anyone have Has anyone got a Samaritan number? Samaritan numbers.
Yeah, [snorts] you're boring now. See you later.
These people are really, really boring, bro.
They're really boring, these people. Yep.
You big fat stinking copycat.
You're nothing but a big fat stinking copycat.
Why have I got so many middle-aged
people obsessed with Peter Belly? Why,
Steven Howard? Why?
Okay, listen to this. Yeah, add that to
my house paid off. And yes, to answer
him, I am a millionaire. He's one side
bastard. Apparently, this isn't mine and
neither are the wins. Everything is
fake. So sad. So you're a millionaire
that plays fies.
So you're a millionaire that plays fies
in the bookies.
Yeah, that makes sense, doesn't it?
Yeah. Yeah. So, a millionaire
that's playing fobies in the bookies. Okay.
Yeah, that makes a lot of sense, doesn't it? Yeah.
My [snorts] belly is rumbling. Z. Yeah.
Yeah. I was thinking of getting a five,
guys. I don't know though.
It's very expensive, isn't it? Five guys.
Maybe I just get some chicken nuggets
from McDonald's. I don't know.
I'm not sure.
No, I don't join disabled repeating
people's live streams. No thanks.
No, I don't join self projection repeaters. No thanks.
No. Tell him to get a life and get off of YouTube.
Yeah, you can decide. Grievously. Yeah.
All right. Look at these self projectors
on L Steven Howard. Look at these little self-reflectors
calling people skint again when they're
sat on YouTube all day every day. [laughter]
All right, bro. Look at these self projectors
for like 5 seconds.
All right, bro. Look at these self projectors quickly.
They literally have nothing in life.
Having to sit on YouTube hating people
they don't know every day. Says a lot
about their life, doesn't it?
It says a lot about their life,
doesn't it, Steven Howard?
Self-protected middle-aged people.
Same comment, same repeating comments. Yeah.
No, you don't want to go on that channel
because the thing is Stephen Howard, if
you go on that channel and you start
arguing with these people, you're
[ __ ] The moment you start getting
into it with autistic biased people, you
just got to give yourself a headache
and you've achieved nothing. You don't
you don't want to argue with disabled people, bro.
and just goes round and round. I can
tell you exactly what's going to happen
if I go in that channel on on that live
stream. Greasy, I can tell you exactly
what's going to happen. I can tell you
all the words. I can tell you exactly
what they're going to say. It's so
predictable. It's boring. And it's 2026.
So, we will definitely not be doing that.
That's how predictable it is. Yeah.
Why do I call Why do I call people autistic?
And I do not get money for being
autistic. I've never had autism in my
life. But I could You want to know why I
called the people on here autistic?
Was he actually asking a question? I can
answer the question if you want. Because
you've been sat on YouTube for 15 years
saying the same stuff every day. That's
what autistic people do.
So yeah. Um firstly
um I don't get money for being autistic.
I've never been diagnosed with autism
because I don't have it. And it's
because of what you people do on it
every single day. You've been doing it
for years. Only disabled people would do
that. Like that is not even that's not
even a me trying to be insulting. That's
not even me trying to make fun. Only
disabled people would sit on it every
day calling people that they don't know skin.
That is that is straight autism. Like
that is straight autism. Seriously. Seriously is.
I have never said I had autism in my
life. [sighs and gasps] So, okay. Ask me
this then. If you're if you're not
disabled, then why do you sit on YouTube
every day for years
repeating hate on people that you don't know?
Answer me that question then. Ask me
that question cuz I could be I could be
fair. I could be very wrong. Why is it
that you sit on YouTube from the time
you wake up to the time you go calling
people skin and hating on people that
you don't know if you ain't got autism?
Just answer me that question. And don't
say you don't do it cuz you do do it. If
it's not autism, what is it? You know, answer it.
I had a nice bagel.
Uh, Grey, there's a there's a nice bagel
shop. I get a chicken and cheese bagel.
You got nothing good or new to say about
anyone, do you?
You've got nothing new or anything good
to say about anyone, do you? You people
in this community?
Am I lying when I'm saying that? Um, Steven Howard,
they've got nothing new and good to say
about anyone on either of these channels.
All cuz their lives are in the pits. All
cuz they're [ __ ] middle-age losers.
They have to come on here every day
hating people. They got nothing new or
good to say about anyone. Not even one
or the other. You notice that, Steve?
I I was thinking that like two days ago
I was at work. I was like, damn, they've
got nothing new or good to say about anyone.
They're just on YouTube trying to put
people down to their level every day.
And that is literally what the crux of
it is. This community trying to make you
feel their way. Like trying to
demotivate people and they want to make
people feel like them. Ugly, friendless,
no hope. That is literally what they do,
bro. They they have nothing new or good
to say about anyone. Whether it's me,
whether it's Monty, whether it's
[ __ ] it doesn't matter who the [ __ ]
it is, they're always trying to bring someone down.
I've noticed that with this with this
community, just cuz their lives are [ __ ]
you know? That is a madness, bro. If you
think about it,
and then it's demotiv, you know what I mean? Yeah.
Yeah. They got nothing new or good to
say about anyone.
You know, Grezy, you couldn't be on this
community if you was trying to better
yourself. You know that. You know, if
you was trying to better yourself, right? Um,
you know, in any way, you know, you
wouldn't really be able to be on here.
you know that well you'd be able to do
your own videos and not go on any other
channel because if you if you was trying
to better yourself right now listen to
what I'm saying now cuz this makes
sense. If you was trying to if you was
trying to uh better yourself,
right? You wouldn't be able to go on
this sector of YouTube. You do realize
that because they're just negative
losers that just try to bring every
people everyone down to their level
every day. Like you do not see people do
not see negativity every day. People
would not be able to see negativity
every day if they're trying to improve themselves.
You know what I'm saying? Like generally
speaking, you wouldn't you wouldn't be
able to do that. Do you understand what
I'm saying, bro?
He was happy. Good for him, bro. I don't
I'm not other people. I don't care about
other people. So don't compare me to
And you know, do you know what I'm
saying though, Grezy?
You're supposed to be people that you're
supposed to be uh surrounding people
that being surrounded by people that up
up your spirits that motivate you. How
can you be motivated
when you're constantly seeing a bunch of downies
putting other people down every day,
trying to put other people down to their
level? Think about it.
It's not happening, bro. It ain't happening.
Oh, all women are the same. Women Women
are definitely definitely definitely the
same. And I'm not getting into that.
Oh, no. Women definitely definitely are
the same. I've met thousands of women
and I'm not getting into this
conversation again. So, you're wasting
your time even trying to get into it
with me. I've had my experiences. I know
what they're like.
No, no. Women definitely definitely are
the same. Big big big big big big big
big big big big big big big big big big
difference. They definitely are the same.
So yeah, how how could you do it then Greasy,
you know? How could you do it?
Women are definitely all the same. [snorts] That's mad.
I mean, you can do Yeah.
You can you can do what you want.
And women are definitely definitely all
the same. [gasps]
I've got enough evidence to prove what
I'm saying is to be the truth. I mean,
you can do what you want. Yeah.
I think Monty's long gone. Uh, Grezy,
what do you think?
What do you think, bro? You reckon he's
long gone? I think so.
Don't blame him to be honest. Who needs
it in the new year?
I like I like the copycats here, Grezy.
No, women are definitely definitely
definitely all the same.
I'm telling you that they're definitely
definitely definitely all the same.
No, they're definitely all the same.
>> End of conversation. Oh, look.
It's the copycat. No. Copycat.
[ __ ] you trying to say to [ __ ] LT.
Yeah. No one cares about your fat, ugly
girlfriend. I can't stand her either.
I can't stand that fat [ __ ] either. Or
you, you [ __ ] homosexual copycat. You know,
brother, we've already been over this a
million times, and I'm not going over it
again. [sighs and gasps]
We're not going over it again. You're
not going to change my mind, so stop it.
She's a fat [ __ ]
Why are you saying to [ __ ] LT that
you did it? You did say that. Oh, if you
don't, you can't deny she's attractive.
I know. And then when you was caught
being a dirty copycat, you started
taking it back. You [ __ ] virgin.
You [ __ ] virgin copycat. Oh, that's a
go. Cuz you was being bullied by them
two Scottish lads in college.
Yeah. You was being bullied by them two
[ __ ] Scottish lads. You wanted to fit
in with a cool crowd. You little copycat
with no mind of your own.
You know, little copycat, little virgin,
little skin virgin. You [ __ ] skink.
You and your girlfriend's [ __ ] skink.
[ __ ] two skint [ __ ] [snorts]
[ __ ] 34 years of age. Is she 34?
She's going to be 35 this year.
She's got to be 35 this year. She's ancient.
She's [ __ ] ancient, you skint [ __ ]
She's [ __ ] ancient.
She's going to be You're telling me
she's going to be 35 this year?
She going to be She got to be 35 this year.
She's going to be 35 this year, Mike.
Well, you said she was 34.
She got to be 35.
She got to be 35. You said that she was 34.
So that means she's 35 this year. You're
already 30. You're still a virgin.
Hopefully this year you can get laid. I
don't want to see no one die a virgin.
I don't want to see anyone die a virgin.
[ __ ] hell. I don't want to see you
die one. You've never had it in your
life, you skin bastard.
You can't deny she's attractive.
You little skin gay copycat.
You little skin gay copycat. Talking
about color to fit in. Oh, you can't
deny she's attractive. That's what
That's what he said. I [ __ ] can. And
I've had more women than you. You
[ __ ] skinned virgin. I said that to
your [ __ ] face as well, didn't I, mate?
You can't have a different opinion than
[ __ ] autistic [ __ ] people, bro.
You can't have a different opinion than autistic people.
You You literally literally can't, mate.
You literally can't.
Don't make me bring up that time we went
for an Indian. Don't make me bring up
the time you went for an Indian and you
[ __ ] had the shits the next day. I
told Triple H about that the other day,
mate. I've got lots of stories about
you, mate, that I'm sure people on
YouTube would love to hear. [snorts]
Also, um, your stepdad messaged me back.
I forgot to tell you. Uh, yes, we did
the first time we met. Yes, we did.
Yes, we [ __ ] did
We've also been to Nando. Uh we went to
a Chinese, but I didn't eat the Chinese.
If you remember,
you know, we went to a Chinese, but I
didn't eat the Chinese. I didn't eat Chinese food.
You want you want to hear you want to
hear the the Indian story? All right.
So, being the skint one, the new skin
one [snorts] was uh in the M&M shop. I
was like, I think it's time we eat now.
So, we went to this Indian uh
restaurant. I can actually show you
where it is next time we're going to
central London. And uh I said, "Well, I
want the vindaloo." And he says, "I I
want the vindaloo as well." I said, "I
don't think it's a good idea that you,
you know, have a vindaloo. It's not for
your kind. It's for big strong Turkish
men." [snorts] Um, in other words, and
then uh he he literally says, "No, no, I
want vindaloo. I want a vindaloo. I want
a vindaloo." I said, "You don't want a vindaloo,
mate." He got a vindaloo. He was biting
it. He's like,
[clears throat] he was [ __ ] down in
the water. [ __ ] I woke up the next
day and he's like, "Mate, I've got the
shits from that coin." I said, "I
[ __ ] told you." This was the first
time I met the skin virgin.
The skin virgin.
That was the That was the That was the
That was the first time we've been to
Pizza Hut. Uh, I went uh Chinese and
Nando. Yeah. Never went to the Westfield
Nando. Went to the Stratford one. And he
used to have this um purple M&S polo
with a pocket. It was like light uh
velvet. I like that color velvet from
M&S. He used to like um shopping in M&S. Yeah.
Yeah. Never made a story up about you in
my life. Never have. Never will. [snorts] Yeah,
we went to American Eagle as well. [clears throat]
Went to American Eagle. It's no longer
there in Westfield.
And he got a uh check red jacket. Yeah.
Don't know if you remember that. Yep.
Yeah, it was like a I think it was like
a check red jacket from the American
Eagle. I didn't buy anything. No, I
didn't buy anything, mate. [snorts]
No, I didn't buy anything.
definitely definitely definitely
definitely didn't. I'm trying to think what else.
[snorts] Trying to think what else. So long ago.
You need to understand, mate. When
someone don't want to know you anymore,
they just don't want to know you. Just
like Britney, she she didn't want to
know you. She weren't interested. She
weren't interested in you.
Well, I say red. It was Yeah. It was
like a dark red. Yeah. So, what [sighs]
then? And he says that he doesn't like
um doesn't like logos. Yeah. Remember
when your mama used to throw the dog on
you? Silly the dalmatian. That's where
your phobia dogs come from. Yeah.
That's where your That's where your
phobia dogs come from.
Isn't that right?
Listen, another thing a to answer your
question. Just because you've had a
girlfriend or two girlfriends, they are
individual women. Uh before we do this,
you haven't met more women than me. You
don't know more women than me. So, at
the end of the day, um you don't know
you don't know more women than me.
Even if even if you've had a girlfriend,
they are individual women that you're
meeting. They're not women up and down
the country like I [ __ ] met. I don't
know why people think because they've
had a girlfriend or two girlfriends,
they seem to know more about women than
you. They are individual women.
Unless you've had what? 100 girlfriends.
Well, have you had 100 girlfriends? Have
you? Have you? Have you had a [ __ ] 100 girlfriends? You know?
Yeah. He told me a story um about when
he went to the dentist as well. Uh
Steven Howard. He had like a really
really bad panic attack when he went to the dentist.
Yeah. [snorts] He scared the dentist.
That's why his teeth's all [ __ ] up. Yeah. [snorts]
I mean, it's it's knowing what they're
like. I mean, they all do act and say
the same thing. So, I mean, they act the
same. They've got the same mannerisms.
They are the [ __ ] same,
you know, mate.
Yeah. Jackary. Yeah. He was he was a god region
uh lad. He used to bully him in college, you know.
Don't nothing I say about you is made up.
No. Yeah. Jackary. Yeah. Some Scottish lad.
Yeah. That's why why you started talking
about Chev. You didn't want to feel left
out. You wanted to fit in which I don't
I don't judge to be fair because you
know if you're new to a college you know
you would some people do do stuff to fit
in. Nothing wrong with um fitting in
with a crowd.
Do you remember if you don't find her
attractive, you're gay. You did say
that. You did say that. You little
copycat. I brought her up because people
was copying each other and I wanted to
know I wanted to know what your thought
on that was.
Uh yes, I did know you when you was in
college. Uh yes, I yes I did. You
literally went to a college in Crystal
Palace. [sighs and gasps]
Crystal Palace. Yeah.
Yeah. Crystal Palace. Yeah. [snorts]
[clears throat] Crystal Palace it was. Yeah.
I know a lot of stories about you, mate.
I know a lot of stories about you, you
know, and your dad.
Mick Jonathan Robinson
and you always used to project your
virginity onto me when you was you was
the only virgin. And I used to say to
you, you are the only virgin. I don't
know why you keep calling me what you
are yourself. I remember we used to
argue after meeting. I'm thinking why
does this skinned virgin keep calling me
a virgin? you wouldn't believe any of
the escort stories I told you cuz you
didn't want to you didn't want um people to basically
you didn't want like to believe that
someone's had what you would never have
cuz you're a virgin
you wouldn't believe any of the escort
stories because you've never had sex
wanted to bring me down to your level
you skin virgin I've never ever met
anyone else that's never believed any of
them stories is. And it was cuz you're
the skin virgin. The skin virgin all
along. You know what I'm saying, bro? Yeah. Hello.
What's the point of joining if you're
not going to say anything?
Didn't believe any of them escort
stories, did you?
which is a bit strange because they were
definitely definitely definitely real. [snorts]
But cuz you're a virgin, you choose not
to believe him.
That's what it is, isn't it, mate? Come on.
Come on now. That's exactly what it is, isn't it?
That's what it is, mate. Is it? Come on.
Yeah. Come on now, mate. That's what it is.
[snorts] He's got a girlfriend. He's got
a disabled girlfriend. Good for him.
I've got a porno where I proved I've had
sex. What's your point?
Yeah, he's got a disabled girlfriend.
Yeah. What's your point, bro?
What's your point?
Do you want to get any more up his ass?
Do you want to Do you want to get any
more up his ass?
Yeah, he's got a disabled girlfriend.
What's your point? I've actually proven
I've had sex. What's your point?
Do you want a silver medal or do you
want a gold medal? A blowy is not sex.
Okay. Have you seen him have sex?
Okay. Have you seen him have sex? And
like I said, I've been in multiple
multiple women's beds, mate. You've not
seen him have sex. So until you see him
have sex, right? And I'm not going to
let him in now for just for you being biased.
I'm literally not going to let him in
now just for you being biased. So there
you go. When you see him have sex, come
back to me. I don't care about a
disabled girl that keeps being brought
up. I want to see sex. I want to see
evidence. And if you can't provide that,
you know, that's that simple, mate.
[snorts] You know, doesn't matter if
he's got a girlfriend. There's no sex.
There's no proof that he's had sex. I
don't care. I proven I've had sex.
[ __ ] me being in women's beds,
women admitted to sleeping with me. No,
no, no, bro. That's you and your
boyfriend have. You and your boyfriend's
got erectile dysfunction, lad. That's
you and your gay boyfriend with the
disabled girlfriend. That ain't me,
mate. No, that's you and your gay
boyfriend you like to stick up for. Not me, mate.
No, not me, mate.
Not me, mate. You remember when I done
posters of you?
You remember when I done the posters?
I had done that. This little face. [clears throat]
I had on the posters. Do you remember that, Grezy?
I taught you a good old lesson, didn't
I? For a couple of weeks. I had you stop
doing the things that you love.
[snorts and gasps]
You know that'll [ __ ] teach you. You
know that that will teach you for trying
to get people's money stopped.
And it did. That would teach you, mate,
for trying to get people's money stopped.
It did. It stopped you leaving the house
for a couple of weeks and you stopped
going on YouTube for a couple of weeks.
You stopped going to events, too.
You stopped going to events. You stopped
leaving the house. You went running to
the old bill.
You got [ __ ] [ __ ] up the ass, mate.
Personal hygiene. I mean, my hair's
washed. My beard's washed. I don't
smell. I brush my teeth three times a
day. I mean, I'm pretty hygienic, lad.
Pretty pretty hygienic. I mean, yeah,
the beard is the beard is long, but
mate, I don't stink. I shower every day.
I just a little January bear.
Yep, that's what I am. I'm a January
bear. Definitely definitely don't stink.
Definitely definitely don't stink. Look
at my beard. It's clean. My hair's
clean. I brush my teeth three times a
day. No, mate. No. Wear clean clothes.
Nope. Nothing dirty about me, mate.
No, you never.
No, you never. You stopped going to the
events cuz everyone thought you was pedophile.
Everyone thought you was a dirty nuns, [snorts] you know.
Yeah. I can't afford my haircut. I can't
afford any. No, I can't, bro. I can't.
No. No. No. No. I can't afford it. No.
Trip H. Why would anyone get their
haircut in January, bro, when literally
like no one goes out? Why would anyone
do that? I saw people doing it, but what
what's the point?
But no, I like I'm I'm a January bear. Greavvesy,
what am I?
You went to the police.
I'm a January bear.
Greasy, call me the January bear.
No one goes out drinking. Not really. No.
Not really. Not Not really. No,
not really. Well, I mean, they
technically go out to do stuff, but they
don't go out drinking, like, you know.
I've got no clue. Um, who doesn't? I've
got no clue, brother. I've gone out
every single January, and it was dead
every time I went out.
Yeah, cuz I'm skin. Okay, bro. You keep
telling yourself that. You keep telling
yourself that, matey. I'm skin. If that
makes you feel better, you keep telling
yourself that. I mean, Gre I mean,
Triple H, I've gone out every year,
January, and literally hardly anyone went out.
You know, literally hardly anyone went out
last year, the year before that.
Literally, mate, I went to Stratford
Westfield last year and there was not
many people even in the shopping mall.
No, bro. I'm not proving you nothing. If
you want to think I'm skin, you keep
telling yourself that.
You keep You keep believing it, bro. You
keep believing it.
You keep believing it, lad. You keep believing it.
Yeah. I'm a little January bear,
Greavesy. We're going to have a shower
later. Put my little dressing gown on.
I'm the Bear family. I'm Skint, mate.
You didn't go abroad until [ __ ] 30.
And you only went abroad cuz I did. You
copied my holiday, you little copycat.
You went Amsterdam just cuz I went Amsterdam.
You [ __ ] skid bastard. You're not the
king of the money game. You showed your
daddy's life savings years ago. Shut up,
mate. Listen, let me let me tell you
something. Let me tell you something.
Yeah. You showed daddy's life savings
years ago. Show it now. Show the 13
grand now in 2026. I'll put a link up
for you. Let me make sure that you're
not banned. One sec. Uh,
right. I'm going to unban everyone. Right. Who's banned?
Okay. I'm going to unban everyone cuz I
don't know what account you're coming
on. Right. Everyone's banned now. Show
me the 13 grand. Come on, Mr. Buddy
Game. Come on. Show me, show me £30,000,
Mr. Money. All this money. Let's see the
30 grand. Come on. 2026.
Everyone's unbanned. Come on. Let me see
this king of the money game. Let's see
the 30 grand. Come on. I want to see
some money. I want to see some money.
Come on. Come on, mate. Let's see this
30 grand that you ain't got cuz you
don't need life savings. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come
on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
You're not banned, kid. Everyone's been
unbanned. So, I mean, everyone's been
So, you can't show 30 grand because you
ain't got it. [ __ ] king of the money
game. You're [ __ ] skinned in the
shitty council medit. Don't you ever try
and tell me you're the king of the money
game. I whipped your ass millions of
times showing more money than you.
You know, no one's banned. Literally,
nobody is banned. I can show you it
right now. Not one person is banned.
You done this last time. You ain't got
those 30 grand. You [ __ ] skid [ __ ]
You shot in a charity shop, mate. You in
a [ __ ] bedit. Make it make sense.
Yeah. I've I You've not got a pot to
piss in. Really?
Really? Okay. You keep telling yourself that, bro.
You keep telling yourself that, mate.
You keep telling yourself that.
What the [ __ ]
You keep telling yourself that, mate.
Do you want to see my electric toothbrushy?
I'm going to be brushing my teeth again
in a minute.
My Bobby B.
I like it, mate. I think it's pretty
cool. I use it a lot.
I don't need to prove anything to you. Anyways, you
what? The toothbrush.
Well, it's a Christmas present. Yeah.
I brush my teeth three times a day, lad.
So I'm not I wouldn't say I'm depressed
grievy. I'm just bitter if that makes
sense. You know
if that makes sense, bro. You know
I mean, yeah, I asked for an electric
toothbrush, so I mean, yeah,
mate, go away, you little sad, obsessed
bastard. I've already let you in and you don't talk,
you sad little [ __ ]
You're in here. You're not talking. You little mong.
You're not talking. You little [ __ ]
[ __ ] Get a life. You're another one
that's been doing this for years as
well. You sad bastard.
Sad [ __ ] You're in. You're not talking. Come on.
What? You're not talking.
Come on, talk.
What's the point of joining if you're
not going to talk?
Oh, this is tickly.
This is tickly. This toothbrush.
It's good for the old gums.
Good for the old gums, lad.
Yeah, I was going to get like a 50 pound
Indian today, Grezy, but I can't be
bothered. You know what I was going to
do? I was going to get I was just going
to go to like a 200 pound restaurant.
Yeah. Just to annoy these people.
Greasy. Like a nice steakhouse.
Just to annoy him, you know. And
obviously he gives you content.
You know what I mean?
You know what I mean, lad?
I'd love to go to a steakhouse, but you know, um,
gums and [ __ ] in it.
Who the [ __ ] is that? Is that a skin virgin?
Is that a skin version?
You're in. Why are you not talking?
Yeah. Okay, bro. You keep telling yourself that.
I want to go to a steakhouse. Squeezy.
You can't beat a nice steakhouse, can you? Yeah, [clears throat]
you need to be broke to be depressed
according to this community. Greasy,
I'm a January bear.
Why are you in Why are you not talking? You [ __ ]
You're in the hangouts. Why are you not talking?
No, I mean I'm banned from the hangouts.
Why are you not talking, you little sad
bastard? You got a lot to say.
When are you people just going to stop
harassing people every day of your lives
trying to bring people down to your
level? When are you people going to stop
this [ __ ] Everyone's unbanned from
joining the hangouts.
Why, man? Why?
Well, I'm going to brush my teeth. I'll
be right back.
Oh, just passed by that.
>> Oh gosh.
>> Same people, same story. See you next year. [laughter]
Do you remember that, Grezy? Grezy, do
you remember that?
Same people, same story. See you next year. Oh gosh.
Same people, same story. [laughter] I
love Ben Furby. I love Filthy Ben.
Do you like Joe F, Steven Howard? What's
your opinion on Joe F? Do you think he's
one of the brothers?
Do you think Jo is one of the brothers,
bro? I actually don't stink. I'm
actually like, look, I just brushed my teeth.
Yeah, I brushed my teeth. My hair is not
greasy. I'm actually clean as [ __ ] bro.
I do not smell one little bit.
My bedroom's clean as well.
Why are you joining if you're not going
to if you're not going to talk?
If you're not going to talk, what's the
point of you joining you? You're another
little nons legs.
You're another little nons legs. Yeah. [clears throat]
You're another little nonslegs. Another
little middle-age harasser, ain't you? Silver Surf.
I don't know how PE these people are
still doing this in 2026. Quezy, I would
have thought they would have got a life by now.
All right. Stephen Howard with Joe F is
one of the one of the brothers, isn't it?
Why do is one of the brs?
Why is he not one of the brothers? Why not? [snorts]
Why don't you like Joe F. Steven Howard?
They're very biased on here, didn't
they? Very biased.
They never bring up where I've been in
bed with women. Steven Howard, I feel
left out. Grezy [clears throat] Yeah.
Why is he a looney? Why?
He defends non legs, but he doesn't
defend me. Steven Howard
say they when I call him a virgin,
everyone defends him. But when people
call me a virgin, no one says anything to me.
Brother, you are boring. See you later.
You're boring. See you later.
Yeah, he's a non legs lover as well,
Steven. He's a non legs lover.
He's a nonslegs lover, bro.
Nonss has called me a virgin multiple
times. I've never seen people ever say
anything about that when he was calling
me a virgin.
That's what you call an agenda to suit your narrative.
Have you noticed that, Dusty? When
people call me a virgin, no one ever
ever says anything.
Strange, isn't it? But then when I call
nonslegs a virgin, they're going about
this disabled girlfriend.
They've all got an agenda to suit their
narrative, lad. You know what I mean?
Yeah, Dusty. Look, I just I just brushed
my teeth with my electric toothbrush.
People saying about my hygiene.
No, no, no. I don't care about them
calling me it, bro. But I'm saying why
does no one ever say anything when
people are calling me a virgin? I don't
care what they say, what they call me.
I'm saying why does no one else backs me
up like they back nonslegs
because they're biased.
Because they're biased, lad.
That's because they're biased.
That's why they don't say anything um
when people call me a virgin. You get my
point in it.
Yeah, man. My hair is clean, by the way.
I wash my hair every day before you say
I stink. I'm just a January bear.
I'm the January bear this month.
My little blinky eyes. Yeah.
No, I don't care who calls me a virgin.
Yeah, you're banned again. See you later.
What the [ __ ]
I don't know who it is, bro.
Oh, it's not letting me ban you. Why not?
Oh, there you go. stalking me.
Yep. He's still stalking me. Red star,
stop stalking me.
Yeah, I like the dentist.
He's still stalking me.
Sat on YouTube stalking all day. What a
loser. Can we all agree on that? Uh
Steven Howard, that Red Star is a loser.
Can we all agree that he's a loser?
Sat on YouTube stalking someone every
day for years.
Can we Can we agree that's a loser?
or what are we going to agree to disagree?
What a loser. Sat on YouTube recording
stuff every day. What a loser. That is
not even me reacting. That's me giving
an opinion. That's not me reacting.
That's an opinion, by the way.
No, that's not me reacting. That's an
actual That's an actual opinion.
Oh, he's a loser. He's a [ __ ] loser.
Sat on YouTube stalking for years. It
backs up my claims
about these people having no life. It
backs up everything I say. The more they
The more they do this, Stephen Howard,
the more it shows how right I am about them.
Yeah, I like the dentist.
answer that question for you, bro. Uh,
it's a thing called jealousy, that boy.
Yeah, it's a thing called jealousy, lad.
I used to do it to USA easy going her
profiles and stuff, but then I got bored
of it. It's just jealousy, is it? Where
where else is it, bro? We You know it. I
Yeah. That's their life, bro. Look,
being jealous of people that they don't
know every day on the internet. But
they're not disabled and they've got a
better life than you, so they say.
[clears throat] Yeah. All right, mate.
S on YouTube stalking every day.
Come on now, bro. What life could they have? Huh?
Yeah, Red Star stalks me every day. Uh,
that boy. There's a couple of people
that do it,
but they say they've got a better life
than me. Huh? Really?
Right, I'm gone. I might be back later.