Oh, lush.
That takeaway was [ __ ] beautiful.
That was [ __ ] beautiful.
Oh, that's beautiful.
Breezy ass. [ __ ] beautiful.
went down like a treat, mate. Oh, that was beautiful. Yeah.
Just had a lovely end there. That was beautiful. Oh, wow.
What? What did this guy just write? Let
me read that.
Yeah, I did see it. And I want to talk
about that as well. And I tell you how I
did see it, right? Um I tell you how I
did see it because I was on Timmy's and
someone mentioned it and I saw a couple
of people commenting, "Bro, I'm happy.
I'm glad to see anyone win." At the end
of the day, that's a good thing to be
honest cuz now you're no longer skinn.
You can buy yourself a decent watch and
you can actually do some content. I'm
happy. I saw I did see the comments by
the way and if only these people really
understood that I don't care about
money. I really really don't. I just
went to Smoky Bee's um comment on
Timmy's now or just ate by the way. I
don't care about buddy anyone winning
money, anyone losing money. I generally
don't care. But I am happy though as in
like you can actually do content now.
Um and yeah, there were all the all the
comments were dedicated to me. They've
been stalking me on Reddit again as well
before that. And the more they do this,
the more of these people do this, the
more it shows I'm right about them. I'm
not reacting to these clowns, bro. I've
already ordered some food. I just ate.
I I don't care about money, bro.
Honestly, I don't care about money.
Um, see, so he won money and I'm happy
he could do some content now. Yeah. It's
like, and that's what I'm trying to say
to you. No one's jealous, bro. No one's
jealous of anyone winning money. I said
about that Joe F because he's bullshitting.
That's what I'm saying. Because he does
not win all the time. See that? Someone
just won, 1600 pound. And that's good.
That's lovely. You can buy yourself a
decent watch now and you can actually do
some content and you're no longer skinned.
That's good, bro. I'm not jealous of
anyone winning money.
I don't get jealous of people and I
certainly do not get jealous of people
that I don't know. That is not me, bro.
That's not my life.
I'm not on YouTube every day being
jealous of people that I don't know.
Bro, that is a madness. And like I said,
they were stalking me on Reddit again.
Um, they were stalking me on Reddit
again, bro. So, you know, the more they
do this, the more it proves
the more it proves um
I'm right about them. The more they do
it, the more it proves I'm right about
them and everything I say. It's one step
closer. Trust me, bro. So that's it. And
yeah, and the comments as well saying
about, "Oh, Lane is going to be in for a
hard time." Really? I mean, I don't care
about money. I don't care about people
winning money. So, I assure you, Laney's
still going to be sleeping.
I generally don't give a [ __ ] about
money, bro. Or people winning money. I don't care. Seriously, bro.
Um, what makes me laugh, what made me
laugh in the comments though is they're
saying, "Oh, that's more than my monthly
income." Firstly, these people don't
even get £1,000 a month. These people
that are commenting on laws, they're
probably on like £400 a month. They do
not. And and let me tell you something,
right? Even if some of these people do
work here, even if these people do work,
they don't have 13 12,300 disposable
money a month. Uh,
how do I see it? Because I went on
Timmy's and someone spoke said that oh
uh LJ won money so I went on his
channel. Yeah I went on his channel
because someone brought up in Timmy's.
I'm not subscribed to him.
I knew about it because someone said it
on Timmy. So I thought oh let me go over
on the channel. But yeah these channels
bro 1600 is not more than I've got. You
don't know how much money I have. I've
stated that about the 13th millionth time now.
Um, you don't know how much money I
have, but you keep telling yourself that
if that makes you feel better.
You know what? It is kind of to be fair.
Yeah, it is kind of um what's the word?
Uh, it's actually quite entertaining.
Uh, it's not more than I get a month. I
tell you what I want you to know. Um,
and LJ doesn't even get £1,000 a month.
So, that's [ __ ] two times what he
gets, you know? But that's 2 months of
ease money. Um, if you want to put it
that way. And secondly, um, secondly, to
be fair, some of the comments are
entertaining cuz if you read it, yeah,
smoke, that win is four months of PJ's
job seekers. Haha. Get up there, Dads.
If only you knew how much money I had.
If only you knew. So, it is kind of
entertaining when you have these people
talking about you and they don't know
you because they're getting it all
wrong. Everything that they're saying is
is wrong. So that is kind of
entertaining to be honest. It actually becomes
it's like um it is funny Triple H. Yeah.
People that um talk as if they know
anything about you when they literally don't.
And you got all of these comments and
you got all of these cop you got all of
these comments trying to make out that
I'm jealous. I don't care about someone winning£1,600.
I literally don't care. I'm happy you
can actually do content now and buy a
decent watch. I'm very happy.
Like I said, I don't get jealous of
people and I certainly don't get a
jealous of people that I don't know.
Okay, bro. You keep telling yourself
that. Okay, I don't have anything
apparently, bro. Okay, I don't have
anything. You keep telling yourself
that. If that makes you feel better,
bro, just keep telling yourself that.
I know what I have. You don't.
I literally don't care, bro,
for multiple different reasons. You can
keep telling yourself that. You know,
you're not being honest. You don't know
me. You don't know how much money I
have. You're not being honest. How can
you be honest when you don't know me?
Think about it, bro. Yeah. Think about
what this guy saying, Steven Howard. He
literally doesn't know me. He doesn't
know how much money I have.
You know, you've done this in the past
where you've done guesswork and you've
been proven wrong millions of times.
Uh yeah, I just had a takeaway by the way, Grezy.
Yeah, it was [ __ ] lust, bro.
I literally don't How does that work?
How How do I say everyone else's skin?
How do I say it? I say
I say that the people that are sat on
YouTube 24/7 hating and calling other
people's skin are skin. Yeah, they are.
The people that come on here all day every day.
All day every day. All other people's
skin are skin themselves. They are. They
must be because to come on the on the
internet every day hating on someone,
you must be skin. You have to be.
There's no other reason why you you were
on here 24/7. If you had money, you'd
have a life. You ain't got no life.
That's why you're sat on YouTube hating.
Yeah. So, the people that are calling
people skin every day, all day, every
day or skin, Yeah. them people are Yeah.
That's not what I'm doing. So, you know
what I'm saying? So, no,
you know, and that's that. So, but whatever.
You actually thought I was going to be
jealous of someone winning money? Oh,
god. You You really don't know me then, do you?
You really don't know me. I could never
be jealous of anybody, bro. Especially
someone I don't know.
That's not me, bro. That could never be me.
[clears throat] No, it's not because
I've already explained to you why I'm on
here every day, Mr. Autistic. I've
already explained to you why I'm like,
do you not listen when people tell you
stuff? Because I have to. It's like I'm
repeating the same thing over and over
and over again when I've said this a
million times. I've already told you why
I'm on here. I've literally told you a
million times why I'm on here.
So why are you still asking the same question? You know,
you know what I'm saying, man? [ __ ] me.
think I'm jealous of people winning money. Jesus Christ.
What the [ __ ] bro?
That Smokey B thinks I'm on £300 a
month. It's entertaining, bro. It kind
of is entertaining for people to do
guess work and get everything wrong.
It actually is. I had a chicken ticker.
Uh, I had chicken ticker and curry greasy.
Yeah, I had a takeaway, bro.
It was lush. Oh,
yeah, bro. Sorry, man. I'm not on the
diet like you.
Oh, I just got a takeaway. It cost me
£33. You just said I was skin. Oh,
you just said I was skin. See? So, you
got it wrong again. See? So,
what is it with you people, bro? Really?
Really? What is it with you people? See,
that's normal to you. That's why you
think that like I I'm jealous of people
because you think I'm one of you people.
I can't sit on the internet every day
being jealous of people that I don't
know. That's not my life. Like, maybe
that's your life, but that's not my life.
I generally don't give a [ __ ]
I'm on anyone. I'm on here more than
anyone. No, I'm not. And guess what,
bro? I've come off of YouTube for weeks before.
I've been off of YouTube for weeks. So, [snorts]
like even if I won money now, bro,
even if I even if I won money now, I I
don't think I'd care.
I actually wouldn't even care if I won
money. You know, that's how bad it is,
bro. You people are on YouTube every day
from the time you wake up to the time
you go to bed. You don't need to go
live. [clears throat]
Okay, then answer me this question then.
So why is it when people go on Timmy's
live or Lord J it's always the same
people every day? Why is it the same
people 247 every single day? Can I can I
answer that? Okay, answer me that question then.
Why is it the same people every day? I'm
I'm asking that question because I was
on Tim. So why are you people sat on
YouTube every day waiting for content?
Answer me that then. Go on.
Yeah, man. I mean, I don't really go out anymore.
I mean, I'm I'm telling you why I'm on
it. I've actually explained to you. I'm
not going out. I'm saving money. I'm
done with women. I'm done. So,
therefore, I don't go out anymore. So,
that must mean I'm kind of having no
life now. So, that must mean you
definitely have got no life.
So that must mean then you've got no
life then unless you're saving for
something like you need to tell me your
situation. If you could tell me your
situation then I'd understand. How would
you know on loveies? You said I've
literally just explained that bro.
Uh I've literally just explained the
I've literally just explained that about
5 minutes ago. So you're asking me stuff
that I've already answered
bro. You're asking me stuff I've already answered.
What? You're asking me something I
literally just already answered.
Why are you asking me stuff that you've
already got the answer to, bro?
I'll answer it one more time. I was on
Timmy's live stream just before I ate
food and someone told me that LJ won.
So, I went on LJ's channel.
Yeah, that's that's how I went on it.
I'm not sub to the loser. Yeah. And you
can go on his thing as well and you'll
see that I'm not sub to that loser.
I ain't sub to that [ __ ] Mong. Oh, I
do watch Timmy. No, I do watch Timmy. I
do watch Timmy. I do watch Timmy and I
don't watch LJ. It's just common sense
that it's the same people every day
because I've been on it in the past and
it's the same people every day. I do
watch Timmy. I never said for one minute
I didn't watch Timmy. I do watch Tibby,
you know. I do watch Timmy and I
occasionally go on legs channel. I don't
watch LJ and I'm not sub to him, you know.
So, I'm not sub to him. I'm sub to
Timmy. Yeah, I'm actually sub to Timmy.
So, yeah, I am. And I got and I do watch
Timmy. Yeah. I know on Lord JS it's the
same people every day cuz they've been
doing it for years. I don't need to be
on there to know that.
And then they're commenting acting like
I'm going to be jealous over win. What? Seriously?
Well, why are you people on YouTube
every day then? Okay, answer me this
question. If you've got a life, why are
you on YouTube every day? If you've got
this perfect life, I want to answer to
this. One second. Triple H, don't
comment. Don't comment. I don't want
anyone to comment. No greasy. If you
have got all of this money, why are you
sat on YouTube every day? Put me out of
my misery. If you've got this life,
you're not depressed, you're not
skinned, why are you on YouTube every
day? I want this answer.
Why are you sat on YouTube 24/7? Put me
out of my misery. Come on, bro.
Because you haven't got a life. So at
[snorts] the end of the day, we could go
round and round and round and round in
circles, you know,
but it's not going to, you know,
sat on YouTube [ __ ] harassing a 28-year-old. [snorts]
What life have you got? Coming on
YouTube every day harassing a 28-year-old.
Come on, bro. Seriously.
Did I blow my nose? Yes.
So that's that in it. But yeah. >> Mhm.
>> You know what's so funny? Um Steven
Howard though, the thing that I find so
funny Yeah. is that these people in this
community don't even get a grand a
month. And the few people that actually
do work are not left with £1,300 a month
after they've paid everything.
Do you understand, bro?
Do you understand?
Like that makes me laugh. Like that L
like I don't give a [ __ ] about like
winning money and stuff, bro. But I
don't know why people need to lie about
their life. And that's an opinion.
That's not reacting. That's an opinion.
You know, you do not get a grand a
month. No way. You know, you do not even
get £1,000 a month. So, yeah.
I don't know why people need to lie.
Like, people are going to come on the
community be live, bro. Um because I'm
I'm just stating how he's full of [ __ ]
I don't care about money. He's just full of [ __ ]
you know? Did you hear him before Steven
saying that he gets three grand a month?
He has never seen three grand a month in
his life, bro. Never in his life. You
don't sit like I don't know why people
need to lie. Like, this is what I don't
understand. I I understand, bro. Like,
yeah, good for him, bro. 1600. I've got
more than 1,600. Good for you. Um
anyways, um so here's the thing, bro. I
don't know why people need to lie.
That's not caring about money. That's
just stating the obvious why people need
to lie thinking they've got money when
they don't. I don't know. Like I would
never ever sit here and say, "Oh, I've
got all of this money. I've got all of
this money." All I sit here and state is
that people don't know what I've got. I
don't act like I'm doing this, doing
that, owning property and stuff. What
I'm saying, bro, like he does not own
property. He does not get three grand a
month. He literally does not. I'm
telling you, bro, he doesn't get nothing
more than £500 a month. That's why he
begs people for money. He does not have
money. This guy, I'm telling you, he
doesn't. So, I'm happy he won that
money. I'm actually happy. So, now he's
not skinned. You can actually go out and
do stuff now, bro.
So, no one So, no one's allowed to have
an opinion on on liars then. I said I
don't care about people's money. So, I'm
not allowed to have an opinion on
somebody that's lying. Okay then, bro.
Okay. Okay. I'm having an opinion
because a li guys is lying, acting like
he's got money.
Yeah. I'm allowed to have an opinion on
someone that's a liar. Yeah. Simple.
Money or no money. And that's that. I
just want to know why people have to act
like they've got money when they don't.
That's just I'm allowed to wonder that
on a community that I'm in. Am I not
allowed to wonder that? You know,
like people are allowed to wonder stuff
just like you're allowed to wonder stuff about me.
When we have an opinion about your money
lies, I've not lied once about my money.
I've not lied once. All I've said is
that you don't know how much money I
have. Am I sat here saying that I've got
six properties? Am I sat here saying
that I get [ __ ] three grand a month
when I [ __ ] don't. And when I did say
I was getting three grand a month, I [ __ ] did.
I don't lie about anything about money.
I don't say that I own six properties.
You don't see me saying I'm a [ __ ]
dentist. I'm owning six properties.
Whatever the [ __ ] you're lying about,
you know, you sit here every day and
call me skin when I'm not skin.
You know, and you've been proven that
I'm not skin multiple multiple times.
How it's the How is it the same thing?
You know, I [ __ ] autism, bro. I swear
to God. Such an autistic community.
Oh, such an autistic community. I didn't
pay my phone bill. I've already
explained it, bro. I've already All of
these things I've I've already explained.
I've explained the same thing over and
over and over and over again. That's why
I'm I'm not answering it because I've
already explained all of this.
I've explained this multiple times, you
know, [ __ ] get a life and stop
harassing a 28-year-old. It's 2026.
When have you old When are you old men
going to stop harassing a 28-year-old on
the internet? When are you going to stop
being jealous of people that you don't
know and then [ __ ] accusing other
people of [ __ ] doing the [ __ ] same
thing? Seriously, you know, when are you
going to get life and stop being jealous
of someone you don't know every day? [ __ ] me. You know,
and the reason I say this is because
I've already answered what you're
asking. I've answered this time and time
and time again.
Okay. Why are you people on YouTube
every day? If you've got all of this
money, my question still never got
answered. Steven Howard Greavvesy, if
you have got all of this money,
why are you sat on YouTube 24/7? I must
have you by the bollocks for you to not
answer it. If you have got this life and
this money, why are you sat on here
24/7? This is the first time that I'm
asking you. I'm asking you a question.
If you have got all of this money,
Exactly. So, there you go. [snorts]
Why are you sat on here 24/7?
If you're not depressed and you've got
all of this money, why are you sat on
here every day trying to put other
people down? I want to know the answer
because no one that anyone idolizes does
this thing. If you have got all of this
money, why are you sat on YouTube um
what's the word? Uh what's the word I'm
looking for? One second. Um
um what's the word? Hold on. Why are you
What's the word? What's the word? uh
promoting hate basically. Let's just put
it that way. Bully me, but you don't
bully me. But you don't bully me,
though. That's the thing. So, you come
on the internet every day bullying
someone, but you've got this life and
you've got this money. Make it make
sense. If you have got all of this money
and all of these things, you would be on
YouTube saying that you bully people.
But in the in reality, you don't bully
people. You bully yourselves.
You're on YouTube. You got no mates, no
girlfriend, no friend, no money, no
family. You don't bully a guy like me.
Trust me, you don't bully. Listen, bro.
If people was going to bully me, it
wouldn't be sad old losers that have got
nothing in life.
Like, you're sad people with nothing.
You don't bully no one. And if you
wasn't autistic, you would know that. If
you was autistic, you wouldn't
understand. You would understand that
you kind of people don't bully no one.
You bully yourselves. Think of it right.
You are all in your 40s. You are all
fat. You are all ugly. You are all skin.
Who do you bully? You don't bully a guy
like me. You are the bully victims. I
think you Bro, do you know what, Steven
Howard? I generally think, yeah, these
people are getting themselves confused
with other people.
These are the same 40 odd year olds sat
on YouTube hated every day. They are the
real bully victims. No one else. They
are the real bully victims. But I think
where they're so disabled, they don't
even realize that it's them. They're so
disabled, they don't realize that
they're the bully victims. So they get
themselves like mixed up with other people.
Generally, like you people are fat, ugly
slobs. You bully yourselves. If you
bully someone, you bully yourselves.
Yeah. Bully victims don't keep I'm I'm
literally on here now. Yeah. laughing at you.
I'm laughing at you, but you're claiming
that you bully me when I'm literally
laughing at you. I'm I'm having a laugh
out of you, bro.
But you're saying that you bully me.
Come on, bro. Like, at the end of the
day, don't people Don't people that
bully, bro. PJ, you look like you have
downs, brother. I'm better looking than
you. Keep self-p projectioning all you
want. Keep self-proing. I am better
looking than you. Say what you want. You
will never come on camera cuz you're too
fat and ugly. Now go talk about me some
more you little bully. Bye-bye now.
These people don't bully no one
honestly. Steven Howard like I think
their disabilities, right?
He has five subjects and losers. These
pe and they can't and they can't answer
me. Steven Howard, I've asked the same
question over and over and over again.
If you've got all of this money and this
life, why are you on YouTube 24/7
harassing a 28-year-old? And they can't
answer it. They can't put me out of my
misery because they know what I'm saying
is the truth. They know what I'm saying
is the truth or truth. The wrestler,
they can't answer it. They are on
YouTube 24/7. Do not let them tell you
otherwise and try to say that you're
live and you're this. No, they are on
YouTube 24/7. I went on Timmy's today,
bro. And it's the same people again,
bro. Put two and two together. Yeah. How
can they possibly have anything in life
if they're on YouTube hating for 15
years? Put two and two together, it's
four. You know,
they're sad people that have got nothing
in life. Like all the evidence, bro,
shows it literally shows what they are.
They are proving my point. You know when
they Bro, when they do this. Yeah. When
they do this, the more they do this, the
more it's backing up my point. You
understand? The more they do it, the
more it proves it.
The more it proves my point. It backs up
what I'm saying. You understand, lad?
You know what I mean?
Uh, yes, I have had a job. It's just
what it is, Steven Howard. Howard. Yeah.
It's a bunch of fat, ugly losers that
want to bring people down to their
level. Have you noticed it's not me,
it's I'm not the only person that
they've done this to. They've done it to
Monty. They've done it to You've seen
it. Yeah. Multiple times when you've
been on Super Chat. All these losers do
is try to bring people down to their
level. That's their life. And that's not
someone that's got a better life than
me. You understand, bro? That is not
people that's got a better life than me.
They literally sit on here every day
hating on people because you're better
than them. Every And and that's what
they do. That is generally generally
what they do. Sat on the internet hating
in their 40s. They ain't got a better
life than no one. They got no life. They
literally have got nothing.
They literally have got nothing, bro. You know,
they have got nothing in their life.
There's every single bit of evidence
that supports what I'm saying. You know, [snorts]
they're so obsessed with other people.
And the thing is, Stephen Howard, they
don't know how much money I have. They
don't really know how much money I get.
I tell them what I want them to know.
You don't need to prove yourself to fat
spastics that ain't got a life. And
that's why I don't. Steven Howard, why
do you think I don't go to the bank and
pull out three grand? Cuz I don't need
to prove myself to fat spastics with
nothing in life. Do you not understand?
Why do you think I don't do that, bro? I
don't need to prove myself to these
people, these self projectors.
I tell them what I want them to know.
They don't know any side hustles I've
got. They don't know how I make money
and they will never know.
Yeah, the bank's empty. You keep telling
yourself that. These people will not
know nothing, bro. These people don't know nothing.
[gasps] These people, they don't know
nothing, bro. Seriously. Seriously.
Seriously. They don't like the the worse
they think. Yeah. The better
the better, bro. The worse they think
the better. To be fair,
you know, they don't know anything. They
literally don't know nothing.
I find it strange to be honest, bro. Why
they're so obsessed with other people's
lives. Yeah, we know. No, what what you
know is that you're skin and on pip. No,
no, no. What what you know is that
you're skint and on pip and you've never
had a bird. Uh, back to you again. No,
that's your life, bro. Not mine. See,
look. You really think, Steven Howard,
if these people had anything, they'd be
doing this? Do you really really think
if they were better than me, they'd be
doing this? Think of Look at it right
now, bro. Look at these comments. Yeah.
You don't even need to go on anyone
else's stuff. Yeah. You really think
these people have got more than me?
Look, they make a million and one
accounts. Yeah. To get banned every day.
That's not people with a better life
than me. that is nowhere near someone
with a better life than me. Bro,
you really think these people, they
literally live to hate to get banned?
Their life's losers. That's why they're
so accurate with what they're calling
you because it's themselves. Why do you
think, bro? Yeah. They're so accurate
because it's their life they're talking about.
No money, no girlfriend. Everything is
them. Like these losers have been doing
this now for 15 years. These life's
losers, these bitter old men have been
doing this now for how many years.
They have truly got nothing and then and
they want to take out on the world. See
these people, Steven Howard, they've
always been bullied. They've been
bullied their whole life and they hate
the fact they've been bullied and that's
why they come on here. That's why they
come on here cuz these people have been
flat out bullied their whole life. No
money, no girlfriend. Okay, let's Okay,
ask ask yourself this, Steven Howard.
Have they been seen with women? Nope, I
have. Have they been seen with money?
Nope, I have. Have they been seen with
friends? Nope, I have. So, go figure
what I'm saying, bro. And that's all I'm saying. Simple.
Who's the one that's been seen with all
of these things and all of the ones that
have not been seen with these things?
Think about it, bro. Come on. These losers.
Pips. I'm I'm on £348 a month.
I'm on £348 a month. That's That's news
to me. That's You learn something new
every day, bro. £348
a month. That's how much money I get. Really?
Really? Oh, repeating M again. Like I
said, do you know why I don't block
these people? Because they're proving my
point more and more. Steven Howard. The
more they do this, the more it shows how
disabled they are and low life they are.
That's why I don't ban them.
[ __ ] [laughter] That's why I don't ban
them because it proves everything they
are. They make a fool of themselves.
That's why I don't ban them. See, what
they're doing is they're thinking that
they bully people, right? But they're
just talking about themselves and
showing themselves up. But in their
heads, they in their heads they think
that they're bullying people, but all
they're doing is embarrassing themselves
on YouTube. That's that's that's what
that's what's really happening. That's
what's really really really happening.
That's what's really happening,
you know? They're just embarrassing
themselves. That's what's really happening, you know. So, yeah. Uh,
I can't believe LT called you a troll,
Steven Howard. Nah, you're not a troll,
man. I see you back me on Timmy's.
I saw you back me on Timmy's.
£348 a month. Where the [ __ ] bro? Are
you people sure you're not actually disabled
with like the the the lunatic [ __ ] that
you come out with?
the mad. You come out with the most
weirdest random things. You know that?
Are you sure you're not disabled?
Are you actually sure you're not
disabled, bro? With the [ __ ] that you
come out with
the r You come out with the most
randomest things. I Steven Allen, I
generally don't know yet if they're
disabled or they're just talking about themselves.
I'm on £348 a month. What the [ __ ] bro?
I know he's on I know he's on less money
than me. Lush. That's why he has to come
on YouTube portraying a lie like he owns
properties and bro the guy is skinned.
Like I'm actually happy that he won that
money, bro. So he can actually go out
and do something now and actually get a decent watch
cuz unlike these people, I don't become
jealous of people that I don't know
if you're not.
Prove us wrong. Prove us wrong. Prove us
wrong, brother. You have been proven
wrong multiple times. Why don't you
prove me wrong and show you're not a fat ugly bastard?
Why don't you prove me wrong that you're
not a fat ugly bastard? I'll put a link up.
Right. Why don't you prove me wrong that
you're not a fat ugly bastard?
Why don't you prove me wrong and prove
you're not a fat ugly mun? Exactly.
And this is what these people have been
doing now for 15 years. Steven Howard,
they have been doing this for 15 years.
These disabled people, they were truly
bullied in life. These people were truly
bullied. They they have been doing this
all day. You know, these people on their
last I' I've literally banned accounts.
They've made more accounts. They truly
have been bullied their whole life. Like
it's so obvious now, bro. These people
are the actual bully victims. And I feel
sorry for them. Even though they claim
that they bully me. Oh Jesus Christ,
bro. Like they bully themselves and
embarrass themselves on YouTube. That's
what they do. You know,
they really are the bully victims, but
they're so disabled they don't even
realize they're talking about themselves.
Anyways, I'm banning these boring people
now. Anyways, so yeah. Anyways, uh back
to you. Uh I know he's on less I lo I
know he's on less money than me. You
know the people that watch him that bro,
they're probably on like £348 a month.
They're They're probably on like £348 a
month. They don't even have £1,200 a
month, £1,300 a month, whatever. They
don't have that, lad. They don't have
that money. Ask yourself, I asked these
people this year. They couldn't answer
me. Yeah. If you've got all of this
money and you've got this life, why are
you sat on YouTube hating 24/7? They
couldn't answer me. They literally could
not answer any of my questions.
I asked like five times and they still
couldn't answer it. If they've got all
of this money, yeah, and this life and
everyone else's this and everyone else,
why are they sat on YouTube hating every
day for 15 years?
Couldn't answer it. Cuz what you'll find
is everything that they say is about themselves.
The stuff that they come out with, bro,
is insane, bro. It really, really is.
And and and it is entertaining as well
because they don't know anyone. They
only know their own position in life. So
what they do is they go off their own
life and project it onto other people.
You know, they think that people are
jealous of someone winning money because
they're jealous. They're [ __ ]
jealous. you know, are people that they
don't know online every day. So, they
think that you're the same as them.
Really? I don't know if they're just I
don't know what they are, bro. You know,
same people repeating themselves every
[ __ ] day, bro. Madness.
Yeah, I do feel so for these people,
bro. Living to hate madness.
See, look. Here we go again with L J
Steven Howard. I wouldn't waste my time
walking to the bookies to do a eight
pound bet. That what what was he trying
to score? See, the guy talks like he's
got money, but bro, he doesn't even get
£1,000 a month. This is what I mean with
these people. I don't know why they feel
the need to to lie about their life. If
you're going to come on here, just don't
lie about I don't know why they lie
about their life.
>> It's actually pathetic.
>> PJ, how you doing, lad? >> Hello.
>> Hello. Can you hear me?
>> I can't hear him. Is he talking?
>> I can't even hear him, bro.
>> Hello. We're going to have to come back.