Yo yo yo, I just wanted to say this
quickly. Yeah, I'm not on here engaging
with these retards, but what was the
point of that? Seriously, like what the
[ __ ] Like, I have got I've got a couple
of different YouTube channels and I'm
just going to upload them all on that
channel. Like, what the [ __ ] is the
point of that? Seriously.
But I like it in a way cuz like I said,
it proves what I'm saying about these
people to be true. the more like when
you're off here, right? And the more
these people do this, the more it's
proven what you're saying about them is
to be correct. No life, no friends, no
money. Um, so I love it to be honest
with you because it just proved my point
even more that they've got that they've
got nothing to be fair when they're
stalking people on different platforms.
It's all right to be honest with you cuz
it just shows that you really dedicate
your life to someone that you're jealous
of. So it doesn't it doesn't bother me.
It's actually quite entertaining to be
fair. Um, you know,
it just shows that you've got a bunch of
middle-aged draggers that are jealous of
you and they dedicate their life, they
dedicate their whole existence to
stalking you cuz that's the right word
is stalking. That's all I basically
wanted to say to be fair.
You know, madness. What? Bro, you do
realize I've got like different
channels. I'm just going to put it on
just a different channel.
You and you and you really want to tell
people on here that you've got something in life.
Really, bro? You really really want to
say that you've got something in life
when you're sat on a platform stalking
people all day? Seriously? Seriously,
man. Come on now. Make it make sense.
Make it make sense. And that's basically
um what I've uh come on here to say,
bro. And that's it. I'm not on here
anymore. I've only just come on here to say that.
You know, it's sad, isn't it? Like
actually stalking people on Reddit.
Oh god, it's so bad. It is actually to
think Yeah. that [laughter]
Oh, Jesus Christ. That these people are
older than me and there and they're
stalking me every day on Reddit. [ __ ]
hell. They got nothing. This is what I'm
saying to Stephen Howard. How much more
evidence do you need that these people
have got nothing and nobody despite what
they're trying to say? You know,
you know, it's not even like I
understand it. Yeah. Like YouTube. Yeah.
You provide content. You provide content
and and people have an opinion. And I
get I get that, but it's not YouTube,
mate. These people literally stalk you
off of here. Like, oh, they're stalking
me on Reddit again, bro. pretending to
be women. I showed somebody my
approaching videos and then they all
know about the channel. And I said, "But
it's just pointless because I've got
different channels and I'm just going to
put all them videos back on another
channel. What What is the point?" And to
be honest with you, SL bro, it doesn't
bother me, bro. It just proves my point
more and more what they are. The more
they do this, bear in mind this is off
of YouTube, the more it shows what I'm
saying is right about them.
virgins, no life, no friends, no money.
It just shows it's them and not me, you
know. It's it's a bit it's it's
different, you know. Um you know, when
you're not on it, when you're on
YouTube, it's different because
obviously you're on here and whatever. I
won't I weren't planning to come back on
here, bro. To be fair, I've only just
come on here to say that. I I'm done
with this [ __ ] now. This shitty YouTube,
bro, you know, for different reasons.
Yeah, it was my other channel, man. I've
just deleted all the videos. I'm just
going to put on my other other channel
is pointless. I'm just going to put all
the videos on my other channel now.
So, it just shows anyways that like for
you to sit there and do that every day,
it just shows you got nothing stalking
people on the internet every day. It
just shows you got nobody and no one.
That's all it shows. It doesn't bother
me. You know, anyone can come in here
and have an opinion. It just shows that
you got nothing in your life but autism.
And the reason I wasn't going to come
back on this community, brother, is
because uh they've got nothing new or
good to say about anyone, you know,
think about it, bro. Yeah. If you're if
you're thinking negative as it is, how
are you going to ever be motivated by a
bunch of dregs? Yeah. Trying to bring
other people down to their level. It's
never going to happen, bro. It's
literally never ever ever going to happen.
I've just come on here to basically say
that they're they're stalking me again,
but they're actually they are actually
dedicating their life to you. They're
not people with money in their life and
friends. Sorry, not sorry. They're not,
bro. Because this is more than YouTube
now. They are actually stalking you, you
know? They they are dedicating their
existence because they ain't got a life
into stalking someone that they don't
know. Yeah, bro. I've come on here to
laugh at that cuz it's kind of funny.
It's sad, but it's funny as well.
Um, so yeah, I've got another channel
and I'm just going to I'm just going to
put my videos on the other channel.
Pointless, bro. I've got them all saved.
What was the point of that? There
literally just no point of that.
Pointless. It's literally pointless.
Silly, bro. All it is is just silly. You know,
obviously there was a risk that I
thought oh that was going to happen, but
I did like they actually like they what
they do on here [ __ ] maker, right? They
will actually pretend to be women on
Reddit. So I message them like they take
stalking to a whole new level. They
actually pretend to be women. Um and
they they they they track you and they
stalk you and everything. Bro, these
people that's not people with a better
life than me. Sorry to say, bro. That
that is not people with a better life
than me. That is not people with more
money than me. Um, they literally will
pretend to be women. Uh, they will make
accounts from like months ago and write
stuff. They haven't got a life, bro.
Like, I'm I'm telling you, brother, they
don't. They have got nothing in their
life. And it's not wrong of anyone to
assume that they're jealous. Um, and and
that's why we think that they're
jealous. Uh, because we've got the
evidence to, you know, back up. Yeah.
They pretend that they're whi they
pretend that they're women. Um, they
will make posts pretending to be a woman
in hopes that I message them. These
people ain't got a better life than me,
bro. I'm sorry. They don't. People that
do that don't,
you know? It's not even like you're on
here and then you're saying stuff and
then people coming on here. They'll
actually they're actually stalking you
off of YouTube. Now,
just silly really though. Very very very
very silly because I've just deleted all
the videos and I'm just going to put
them all up on my other channel. What
was the point, you know?
There was literally no point in that
other than showing what he was.
Oh yeah, I was about to send a picture
of my dick as well. [ __ ] losers. They
are proper proper losers, lad.
They dedicate their whole entire life
into stalking people that they don't
know, brother. If that's if that's not
enough evidence to show that they've got
nothing, I don't know what possibly will.
You know, you go on L J's, they're
talking about me non-stop. What the
[ __ ] bro? Every one of Joe Joe's um
comments is about me.
Have you got anything new or good to say about anyone?
Like, they've got nothing new or good to
say about anyone, these people, [ __ ] is
it? That's another thing you've got to
think about this community. They have
got nothing new or nothing good to say
about anyone. I telling Ley about this
as well. It's it's these people that sit
on here every day slagging people off
when they're worse than anyone that
they're slagging off. So that's YouTube,
but then they stalk people off YouTube
as well. What the [ __ ] lad. So yeah.
Yeah, they they prop up they they
properly don't have a life, bro.
Properly don't have a life.
all of that just to find someone's new
channel when I'm just I've just got
another channel. What the what are these
people doing with their lives, bro?
Seriously, what are they doing with their lives?
But they're not jealous. Don't forget
[ __ ] maker. They're not jealous. They
just waste all their life on you. But
they're not jealous. Nah, they got a
better life than you.
Yeah. They pretend to be women and
everything, bro. On this Reddit, proper
proper stalkers. They are actual
stalkers, bro. Actual stalkers. Not when
like a woman is saying that someone
stalking them when they give it. No. No.
They are actual stalkers. That's what they are. Sad bastards.
Sad, sad, sad, sad, sad, sad bastards.
That's all I've come to say really. I'll
stay alive for a little bit, lad. Yeah,
they're pretending to be a woman.
They're pretending to be women.
Um, yeah, they'll make accounts of women
pretending to be them.
I don't think these people have got a
better life than me, bro. Somehow, I
somehow don't think that they've got a
better life than me.
I really, really, really, really,
really, really, really don't.
>> And I said I was done with this
community, bro, because it's just the
same thing with them. It's just a bunch
of old men talking about themselves
every day. That's why do you think Monty
man don't come on here anymore, bro? Why
do you think that Monty man and other
people don't come on here anymore? It's
because people are tired of it. People
are tired of the repeating. People are
tired of the hating by middleage slobs.
We're tired of it, you know. We're tired
of these little lowife [ __ ] skin
[ __ ] dregs, whatever you call them,
bro. People get tired of it. Why do you
think that people don't come on here anymore?
They've got nothing new to say. They've
got nothing good to say. Yeah,
it really is madness.
Really is madness, bro.
Yeah, it's bad, ain't it, lad? Bad.
Yeah. Yeah, it's Red Star again. Jesus Christ.
You didn't get my money stopped either.
Uh, replying to you on Reddit.
Red Star wins. What did you win, bro?
What? Stalking someone on Reddit.
You You won. And you didn't get my money
stopped either. So, keep telling
yourself that. Yeah. And that's why we
call these people jealous. Uh, and this
is exactly what I was trying to explain
to um Bingy. This is how you know that
they're next level jealous, you know.
But when you try to explain this stuff
to uh Joker or LT, they won't have any
of it. They are next. They are
definitely definitely definitely
definitely definitely jealous for people
to dedicate their life to someone that
they don't know every day for years.
They're jealous of something you got, bro.
I'm telling you, that's not what normal people do.
If a normal person would under uh would
understand it, you've spoke to me for
the past 3 hours
pretending to be a woman to get my
channel. What is your life, bro? And
you're and you're more than likely older than me.
What the [ __ ] bro?
This is this is ridiculous. And I only
come on here to say that, bro. I don't
really want to be on here anymore. And I
don't think particularly Laney wants me
on YouTube. So, you know, I I would I
I'll use it to my advantage, you know,
that, you know, Laney doesn't even like
me on YouTube, to be honest.
So, I just I just use that as a perfect
excuse now not to entertain these
weirdos, you know. though that that's
like the perfect excuse,
you know, even though if I live by
myself, I still wouldn't come on
YouTube, but you know what I'm saying.
Yeah. No, they are definitely they are
definitely definitely they are
definitely definitely definitely jealous
100%. There's a there's a few there's a
few there's a few um there's a few good
people on here, bro. Like Charlie um
uh How Hard Can It Be? There's actually
some all right people on here, bro.
That's actually got lives and and stuff.
But yeah, I mean, whatever LT was saying
before about you're providing them
content and whatever. Well, what's he
going to say to these people pretending
to be a woman for 4 hours?
They were pretending to be a woman for 4
hours. What have you got to say about
that? I'd love to see what his opinion
on that is cuz Okay, yeah, you come on
YouTube, you give them content, so they
stalk you, right? So, you give them
ammo. Okay. So, what's the answer going
to be when these people are sat on
YouTube pretending to be women? You know,
bro, how hard can it be? He's an all
right guy, bro. And he doesn't even like
me. But, you know, I actually know that
guy is just not jealous of anyone. I
know that Charlie's all right. Ben's all
right. There's some actually all right
people on here. Very, very few people.
But the rest of them, they're just the
rest of them, bro. What they are is
they're just people that have failed at
everything to life and they're just
trying to bring people down to their
level every day. And the thing is, if
you're if you engage with these people
long enough and you keep interacting
with these people, you're going to
you're going to become one of them.
You're literally going to become one of
these people or like not not or you
might not be any better than them, you
know, at the end of the day.
Even if they're not talking about you,
bro. Even if they're not talking about
you, they're just little weirdos that
just write negative [ __ ] on the internet
all day because they got no one. They
got nothing. That's their life, bro.
That is literally literally their life.
How do you think Ant-Man's living in
Thailand? How do you think Ant-Man's
like living his best life? Because he's
not on it interacting with these people.
And Monty's probably living his best
life now as well cuz he's not
interacting with these slobs that are
jealous of people that they don't know.
And and like I said, bro, you're sat on
you are pretending to be a woman. You
you was pretending to be a woman for 4 hours.
That is obsession. That is jealousy on a different platform.
Weird. Very, very, very, very weird.
You could just tell that these people
have just been bullied their whole life
as well. Like you can sense like the um
you can sense the um
bitterness and the anger as well.
They hate the fact that they've been bullied.
Yeah, they would. Yeah.
Yeah. They're trying What they are is
they're trying to bring other people
down to their level. That's what it is,
bro. I've already sucked this community
out. They're fat, ugly skin slobs that
want to bring other people down to their
level every day. I mean, I asked a
couple of questions um yesterday. Not
one of them could answer me. I said, "If
you've got all of this life, if you've
got all of this money, why are you sat
on YouTube 24/7?" They couldn't answer
me. And they tried to revert it back to
me. Um, and why are you on YouTube
hating every day of your life if you've
got this life? They can't answer it
because it's the truth. They know I'm
correct. So, when they know that you're
correct, they can't answer what you're saying, bro.
Yeah. They would still carry on. I know
this like I I've been saying this to LT.
Yeah. For ages. I've said it to LT. I've
said it's a [ __ ] bias Joe that they
don't do it for a reaction because even
I'm sick of repeating this bro it's
giving me a headache already even if you
never reacted to them again they would
never leave you alone even if and by
leave you alone I mean stalk you and
that's what I mean I mean stalking you
so they would never ever stop stalking
you ever even if you come off the
YouTube for 20 years and I've explained
this to quite a few people and it still
doesn't sink in and that is that is
Why upload them to another channel if
they're going to They're not going to
find them again. They only found them
because I linked it to them. I thought
it was a woman. They never found it,
bro. It was I thought I was talking to a
woman on Reddit. I thought part of me
thought it might be them. But then they
had posted stuff, so I was like, you
know, if it is one of them, then I'll
just go on my other account. They never
found it, bro. I linked it to them
because I thought it was someone else.
They they didn't find me. They can't
find me. That's what I'm saying. They
will never find it unless I link it.
Yeah, bro. I thought it was uh I thought
it was um I thought it was like cuz they
posted stuff cuz I went on their thing
and it's like, "Oh, I'm 27. I'm in
London." And it was posted 2 months ago.
So, I thought, "Okay, there's a good
chance it's 50/50. They're either real
or they're not." Um
and it was. So, yeah, they never found
me, bro. They're stalkers. They're
absolute stalkers, bro. They haven't got
anything in their life, you know? I
would I would love LT's opinion on that,
bro. I would really love LT's opinion on
that cuz now they're actually stalking
you off YouTube pretending to be women. So
yeah, that's not people that's not
people that's got a better life than
you, bro. Sorry.
You want a little football better? Yeah, man. why not?
little football bet, bro. Yeah. [snorts]
Yeah. So, that's that, man. It's just
weird why they do it.
And if you're trying to improve
yourself, you can never be on this
community all the time because if you're
constantly seeing people slack people
off, people are supposed to be
motivating you, not demotivating you.
And how could you get the mo how could
you get motivated if people are hating
every day on YouTube? Think about it
like that. Um, [ __ ] maker, if they're
hating people every day, not even you
like, and they're writing, "Oh, this
person's down." You're you need encouragement,
not people trying to put you down to
their disabled, spasticated skin level.
Why do you think Ben's not on here much?
[snorts] Why do you think How hard Hard
Can It Be is not on here much? Why do
you think you never see Charlie much?
How many times have people come in and
said, "Oh, my brain hurts." And then
[ __ ] off for like 3 months. Do you not
understand why? Because of that exact reason.
You're supposed to be having people um
you know, motivate you
or say positive stuff. And if if there's
no positives on this community, how can
people, you know, and about anyone? It
could be about anyone, bro. You know, it's uh
it's a community full of a bunch of
middle-aged bums slanging off people
every day that they don't know. What the [ __ ]
Like, what the [ __ ] bro? You understand? Like
see even with Oreo man. Yeah. Even
they're not slagging each other off.
This is a very very very disabled
community, bro. They are actually
slagging off people that they don't know
every day because their lives are in the
pits in the gutter.
See on this channel they they they talk
[ __ ] about themselves. They are negative
about themselves. They're not flagging
off other people. Do you understand?
that they don't know.
That is mad.
That really really really really is next level. Um yeah,
that is that is really bad.
And you didn't stop anyone's money. And
that's the last time I'm going to say
that. You keep telling yourself that,
bro. If that makes you sleep better that
you keep telling yourself how you
stopped people's money. You keep telling
yourself that it's very boring now. You know,
it is bad. It is. It is really, really Really bad. You know,
got a lot of [ __ ] people obsessed
with me. I've got more people obsessed
with me, Timmy, than they're obsessed
with you, lad.
And you've been on here longer than me.
I literally have people. I mean, yeah,
you might have one or two people, but I
have got people that are literally their
lives are dedicated to me. You've only
got Mr. B and [ __ ] Müller.
You don't have as many people obsessed
with you as they are with me.
What do you think, [ __ ] maker? I think
I've got it worse.
And it's obviously cuz you're younger
than them. It's obviously cuz you're
better looking than them. It's obviously
because you've got a better life than
them. And if you're not going out,
that's by choice. Uh that's a good
that's another thing. Like say I go I
stay in there for another two months. I
don't go out drinking or whatever.
That's by that's by choice. You
understand? So when something's by choice,
um then it's a it's a different story.
Whereas these people, they have no
choice. They got no money. They got no
life. They're ugly as [ __ ]
Um so that's why they do this every day
on YouTube. Yeah, Grezy, man. They're
stalking me again on Reddit, pretending
to be a woman again. They found my Well,
they never found my other channel. I
linked them my other channel cuz uh
Yeah. And I just said, "What's what's
the point of that?" Because I'm just
going to go on my other channel now and
upload all the videos I deleted.
So, they're actually pretending to be
women on Reddit now.
I don't think these people have got a
better life than me, mate. I really,
really, really don't think they've got a
better life than me.
I really really don't. They're backing
up my claims even more now, bro. They're
really really backing up everything that
I say now. Even more. Cuz now they're
taking it off YouTube.
They are uh
they are really they're actually taking
it off YouTube now. Uh Grezy, they're
really like it's not even it's not you
being on YouTube giving them content.
They're actually stalking you on forums now,
pretending to be women. You think that's
normal, bro? Like, you you really think that's normal?
Come on out. Like, all jokes aside,
you really really think that's normal,
lad? What's the day today? Oh, Monday.
[ __ ] Chinese open.
You really think that's normal, bro?
Come on. Like all jokes aside,
they literally are [ __ ] weirdos.
I was waiting for that uh video of the toothbrush. Greasy.
You said you was going to do a video of my toothbrush.
I weren't going to come on today if it
wasn't for that, bro. I'm done with this
[ __ ] now, man. I'm past it.
I'm past these losers now, mate. I'm
pass them cuz I realize that you're
never going to get anywhere engaging
with these people that just write
negative [ __ ] every day.
You understand what I'm saying? Grezy.
Monty's not on it for a reason.
Ant-Man's not on it for a reason.
There's a reason why people are not on
it. And if they are on it, the genuine
people aren't on it constantly. Do you
not do you not know there's a reason for that?
There's a there's a reason. And it makes
sense. It makes a lot of sense. But yeah,
that's just weird [ __ ] bro. They're weird.
It's like they're trying to like Oh,
it's like they're trying to make you
fail at everything like they do because
they're losers. Because they're like
losers. They're trying to like bring you
down with them. Does that make sense, Greasy?
>> I hope I'm making sense with what I'm saying,
>> but yeah, they're stalking me on Reddit
pretending to be women. So,
>> hello. Get Salt on the chat. Get AI fraud on
>> I can't hear him. [laughter]
>> Oh, no.
>> Get fraud on here. I want to own that [ __ ]
>> We're coming to Liverpool tomorrow.
Salt. Don't do what you did to Jade
Willow where you hid behind the bed.
Show up and you've got the opportunity.
>> I tried saying the same [ __ ] thing.
>> You can get salt dead.
>> One second. One second. One second. Think Fox.
Why do you keep stalking me, man? Do you
want my ass on topic? I can give you my ass.
>> Let me ask you a question.
>> You weird. >> Listen,
PJ, be quiet a second. >> Yeah.
>> Can you Can you hear yourself talk?
>> When you're talking,
>> are you listening?
>> I just PJ, I just heard you listen. I
was just listening to you and you said,
"Yeah, people come on here, they should
be trying to motivate you. They're just
trying to demotivate you." Oh, no.
>> Yeah. On your channel. Yeah. On your
channel. On your channel. Have you seen
your channel? Have you seen what they
say on your channel?
>> PJ, can you do you not remember all the
mad [ __ ] that you've said and done on here?
>> I'm not talking about me. I'm talking
about any You slag off anyone you can.
I'm not just talking about me. I'm not
>> You were just talking about me. Oh, why?
Why can't anyone try?
>> Okay, Timmy. Timmy, belly, you're always
doing it to someone. And I'm thinking,
bro, you are the ones on YouTube 24/7.
Skin. Nobody's on 24/7.
>> No one's on 24/7. Guess you
>> I'm not on 24/7.
>> Listen, your viewers, you and your
viewers are on YouTube 24/7.
>> Okay, go live yesterday.
>> Go live right now.
>> How long were you live for yesterday? 10 hours.
>> Go live right now and see who comes.
>> 10 hours. PJ, you were late for a total yesterday.
>> You know, go go like that.
>> Have an amazing life.
>> Anyway, why would anyone PJ Why would
>> How much did the How much did the bet pay?
>> I don't know. I haven't collected it yet.
>> So, you you lost 200 pound in the machine.
>> Unlike you, I don't have to set up all
night over a couple of quid.
>> I mean, I sat up overnight so none of
you got it. I mean, I explain that story
because I didn't want anyone anyone.
>> Okay, put it this Okay, put it this way.
Put it this way. If Let me Let me
explain something here. If the bet
Listen, listen listen to me. If the bet
was £40 to collect and it cost £80 in
the Uber, I'd pay £80 in the Uber to get
the 40 bet just so you don't get it.
>> Do you understand? That's what makes you a spicy.
>> No, because I don't want I didn't want
you getting the last laugh.
>> So, you'd rather lose money. this one up.
Never heard the last of it.
>> PJ Norm was going to get your bet.
>> Yes, they was.
They were not cuz they needed it. They
would have done it because they listen.
They would have got the money just to
have you on their own. Listen listen,
they would listen to me. They wouldn't
have got the money because they needed
it. They would have got the money to
laugh at me. Not cuz they needed it.
>> Well, PJ, we were laughing at you
anyway. You stayed up all night on YouTube.
>> You know what I'm saying? So like
>> you were standing outside the bookies at
a quarter to 7 in the morning.
>> So why are you always slagging people
off on your channel anyway?
>> Because I like ask why you always
slagging people off on your channel.
>> Because people like you and valley and
Mac and Lims you need to be constantly ridiculed. That's
>> Yeah, but you know Yeah. But okay, Lims.
Let's talk about Okay. Lims. Yeah. But
the people on your channel was no better
than Lims. Lem just owns it.
>> Lambs has a better just owned it.
>> Huh? Lambs. Lambs has a better life than you.
>> But bro, Lem have got a better life than
all of your the people that follow you.
>> But the thing is with Lim,
>> but you see the difference.
>> Lambs has
>> Lamb's had a girlfriend. You haven't?
>> We've never seen you with a woman. We
have seen me with a woman.
>> Ma's had a girlfriend.
>> We've seen me
had a girlfriend and you
>> boring repeating. Hey Mike. Um, they're
stalking me on Reddit again, pretending
to be a woman.
So, I'll have to tell LT about that when
he's on here. When he's on here again.
They actually stalked me for 4 hours on
Reddit pretending to be a woman.
[snorts] Now, that's the reason why from
live to basically say that I've got
another channel. I'm just going to put
them approaching videos on my other
channel. Like, they're not [ __ ] on YouTube, bro,
watching your content anymore, bro.
They're actually coming. They're
actually going on a different platform
pretending to be women.
Yeah, that's not people with a better
life than me, bro. Someone coming on
Reddit pretending to be women for five,
bro. They were stalking me all morning,
bro. I was at my I was at my sisters.
Yeah. And then I sent the account
because I thought it could have been a
woman and it was Red Star, bro. Oh, do
you know what? Yeah, it's it is funny to
be honest. It is It is funny because
every time they do this, the more they
prove my point. the more they prove my
point, the more they keep doing this and
they're doing it off YouTube now as
well. It proves my point in what I say
about the jealousy and the obsession.
So, if anything, they're just proving
they're proving me right, lad. No, it's
not nons. It's not nons. I know exactly
who it is. So, they're just proving what
I'm saying to be true. You know,
they it's proven that it's the truth.
You know, they're actually stalking you
on different platforms pretending to be
women. So, we can safely say that their
life is actually dedicated to me. Yeah.
That's not someone with a better life
than me, bro.
Yeah. Definitely. Definitely. That's not
people with a better life than me. I
don't care who they are.
>> So, yeah. Madness.
And this is what I was trying to explain
to bloody LT. Why? Why not ignore it?
Because it's weird. And I just wanted to
say how weird it is.
Yeah, it's very very weird. You people
clearly are jealous or something. And
this is what I was trying to explain to
LT. Would you pay £40 for
Yeah. If it meant these people not
getting the money? Yeah. Yeah. The point
was if it if it meant these people not
getting that money, I would do it. Yeah.
Just so they didn't get the last laugh.
Yeah. Bro, why do you think I stayed up
all night and my sleeping pattern was
was normal? Why do you think I stayed
out? Why do you think I stayed out all
night? Why do you think I stayed out all
night? I stayed up all night, bro. Cuz I
needed £110. No, not [clears throat] at
all. Didn't need that £110. It's cuz I
didn't want these people catching it in
and getting the last lot. The jealous
bit makes no sense at all. Okay. Okay.
I'll tell you I'll tell you what makes
no sense. How Okay, let me let me let me
explain this. Yeah, Mike. Right. Anyone
who's watching this, so do you want to
know what makes no sense at all is how
you claim that you're not generous. How
you claim you've got a better life than
everyone yet you're stalking someone
247. That's what makes no sense. You sit
on here and you swear to your blue in
the face that you're not jealous. You've
got nothing to be jealous of. Meanwhile,
you're sat on the internet for hours
stalking, hating every day, not leaving
your house, not living your life all
because you're obsessed with me. That's
what makes no sense. Everything that I
say makes complete and utter sense, you
know, and we're not talking about
YouTube now. We're talking about Reddit.
You're actually on Reddit pretending to
be women, you know, pretending to be
women for 5 hours, brother. You're
jealous of something. You clearly,
clearly are. You just don't know it. You
might not even know it yourself
because you're stalking people all day
on the internet for years, for years and
years and years and years and years.
Stop lying to yourself when you're
saying that you're not jealous of
something. It's making you look extra
extra extra extra silly.
You know, it really, really is. You must
be jealous of something to sit on the
internet doing that. Controlling my
mood. No, they're not controlling my
mood. I'm just talking about how you
people are low lives. I'm not pissed
off. I'm completely calm. I'm just
talking about how much you are sados.
Don't try and reverse the psychology
now, mate, because I've said something
that makes absolute sense. You're not
controlling my mood. None of you's
controlling my mood. I just came on to
talk about how sad you were and are. You
how sad you are. You're not controlling
my mood. None of you are controlling my
mood. You don't bother me at all. Yeah.
I'm just coming on here to talk about
how sad you are. Cuz what you're doing is sad.
You know what you're doing is what
you're doing is uh is very very sad. Do
you see me pissed off? Do you see me
smashing things? No. Cuz you're sad bastards.
That's what you are. You're sad
bastards. That's probably where you got
the uh the uh the word from to be honest.
So, you're not jealous of someone, but
yet you sit on YouTube all day. You you
you literally dedicate your life to
stalking someone and hating someone all
day, but you're not jealous. Yeah. Make
it make sense.
Make it make sense.
There's no there's no logic in that whatsoever.
Bless you. You don't even know that
you're jealous or something.
Oh, you could be gay. Oh, you could be
gay. Why you upset? Be happy or young,
attractive. Oh, here we go. Like I said,
bro, when you The more you do this,
you're just proving my point.
You're just proving my point, brother.
You just you you enjoy disproving my
[ __ ] What? My crap.
You haven't disproved any of my crap. I
told you to go live in the bookies
gambling and you couldn't do it. So
until you can do that, you haven't
disproved anything. You've never
disproved anything. You haven't showed
me that you're not scared to talk. You
haven't gone live in the bookies
gambling to show that you're not only
putting up wins. You come out with some
[ __ ] excuse that you was going to
get banned. So you haven't disproved
anything. Try again. [snorts] Try again.
No obsessed old man. You didn't disprove
anything. You go live in the bookies
gambling and show me that you're winning
as much as you claim and then that's the
day you prove me wrong
and you can't do it because you're going
to get banned. Jesus Christ. Come on,
bro. You're fraud. Doesn't take Einstein
to see Einstein.
No, no, no. You You said that you get
banned in the bookies. You don't get
You don't get banned in the bookies for
for um for live streaming. You don't get
banned in the bookies for live streaming.
That's [ __ ] I've live stream live
stream and at the end of the day, mate,
you don't get that. Stop talking [ __ ]
How many times have me and Lone live in
the bookings? Come on now, man. It's
pathetic. Really, really, really
prophetic. I know he's full of [ __ ]
bro. You don't need to tell me. No, we
know the guy's full of [ __ ]
I know it's [ __ ] He's just another
red star. He's just another nonsense. It
doesn't bother me, but I know what he's all about.
Stalking people on Reddit all day again,
pretending to be a woman for 4 hours.
You've got a very, very unhealthy
obsession with Peter Benny.
You've got a very, very, very, very bad
obsession with Peter Belly.
You don't. It's uh it doesn't matter if
you've got choice or not. You don't get
banned for live streaming in the
bookies. You do not get banned for live
streaming in the bookies. Stop talking
[ __ ] And don't you travel all the time
to leagues and stuff in Newcastle? You
said listen mate, you're a fraud.
Everyone knows it.
Everybody knows it.
No, you don't. No. I've been to more
bookies than you've had dinners. I've
gambled more than you've had hot
dinners. No, you don't. No, you don't.
Yeah. No, you [ __ ] don't. You
remember that time, Grezy, when I was
live playing Fishing Frenzy? Uh, when
was it? Uh, last year. Do you remember?
I've gone live. I've gone live. I've
gone live in bookies, haven't I, Grezy?
I'm pretty sure, Grezy, you've seen me
live in Bett shops playing fishing frenzy.
Haven't you, Greavves? Haven't you? I've
been live in multiple bookies and I've
never been told off a band once.
Someone's telling Pies.
Someone's telling lies.
Somebody is telling Porcupies.
Well, okay. Put it like this then. When
you're next in Leads or whatever city
that you go to, go live and and and and
we'll see them. We We'll see if you get banned.
You're talking [ __ ] mate. You're a
fraud. That's what you are. You're a
fraud. You're really bad at trolling as
well. You need to step your game up.
You know, you're talking [ __ ] man. Oh, [ __ ]
You need to get a life, bro. Seriously,
how long are you going to keep doing
this for? I'm not going to be lifeboard
at an hour today.
sat on YouTube stalking people every
day, pretending to be women, but you're
not jealous of anything.
I would definitely not be doing that to
someone that I'm not jealous of, but
hey, that's just me. [snorts]
[ __ ] hell. You take stalking to the
next level, man. Jeez.
Yeah, that's fine, bro. I don't mind
because you don't have the balls to
approach women. You never have and you
never will. So, um, you're sat there
probably never spoke to a woman in your
life. So, yeah, I don't care. Good for
you, bro. No one cares what any of you people think.
We know what you people are all about.
Why do you think Monty don't come on
here anymore? We know what you people on
here are all about. That's why you don't
bother us. I was pissed off the other
day cuz I was already in a bad mood.
You can laugh all you want, bro, but I'm
not scared to speak to women. You You
can't approach women. You can't talk to
women in real life.
Again, it's what I said earlier, trying
to bring people down to your level.
You know, you trying to bring people
down to your level
regarding anything. Yeah. It's not going
to work with me, bro. So, you're better
off just going on another channel and doing it.
And yeah, to answer Laura J. Oh, yeah.
You said stuff about kids, brother. Firstly,
yeah, your girlfriend. Well, that would
be a bit hard cuz you don't have a
girlfriend. So, yeah, you got a
girlfriend, but you're on YouTube 24/7.
Strange. Uh, so anyways, uh, what I
wanted to say was, um,
what was I saying about you? Yeah. So,
that's how we know. Oh, yeah. LJ um
talking about kids, bro. You slag off
people that don't talk about kids.
You're always writing negative repeating
[ __ ] in your in your chat.
And you're still going on about what
people have said about kids ages ago.
That's another sign of autism. That's
another sign of autism. I don't
understand how your brains work. Is that
really literally like how your brain
works? Like elaborate a little bit. So
someone says mad stuff on the internet
and then you become obsessed with it for 30 years.
Really, bro? Really?
You sure you're not autistic?
Like, and that's not even me, that's not
even me like trying to um yo, insult cuz
think of all the stuff that Monty said
about um kids and that. Yeah, bro. It's
You forget about that half the time.
That is I think that's just their
excuse, Mike. It's their excuse for the
the jealousy that they do. Oh, you said
stuff about kids. Oh, you said stuff
about whatever, you know? I think that
is just literally their get out of jail
free card for being jealous [ __ ]
stalkers. That's what it generally seems
like to be honest with you. Yeah. And
Pat's put my sister's kids up. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. And Pat put my sister's kids
up and he spoke about my dead brother.
So everything that I said was in retaliation.
For [ __ ] sake. You was Wasn't you
talking about my dead dad the other day?
Wasn't that skint virgin in the bedsit
and my [ __ ] off [ __ ] brother who
I've seen once. Yeah, [ __ ] off about
kids. Don't try to play the mole high
ground. Do not try to play the mole high
ground. It's not even going to wash in a
washing machine, mate. The Samsung model
washing machine. At the end of the day,
you've spoke about people's dead [ __ ] relatives.
Nons has done it as well and Pat
Mustard. [ __ ] off, bro. Don't even try
and play the more high ground. Yeah.
Don't even try to play the [ __ ] moral
high ground, mate. Don't even try to
play the moral high ground.
[sighs and gasps]
Yeah. Bet you didn't know what that word
means. So, you spoke about people's dead
relatives. Um, you know, multiple
multiple times. You spoke about people's
dead relatives. No, they don't bring me
down to their level. They try to bring
me down to their level. skin, fat, ugly,
but they're never going to bring me down
to their level. And they try to bring
other people down to their level as
well. I know what these people do. I
know what they're like. It's never going
to work, you know?
>> Hold on. You're right.
>> What's going on?
>> [ __ ] all, bro. Just chilling, man. These
weirdos are stalking me on Reddit.
>> It's always the same people, bro. You
know, you know they're st You know
they're stalking me on Reddit and that?
>> How? Doing what?
>> Like pretending to be women and that and messaging me.
>> They're [ __ ]
They're sados. They're sados, man. Sados
really are, man. Really are.
>> You still got You still got beef with Timmy.
He's a fat symbol. You can't be ass.
You never He don't leave, does he?
>> What do you mean? It's the same people
like when you go Lord Jesus [laughter]
to get a job and works themselves.
>> Harry, how are you doing, Salt?
>> Who's this?
>> Hello, Salt. You know who I am, Salt.
Don't go. Who's this?
>> Oh, Harry, Sluggy, bro.
>> So, anyway, Harry, instead of crying
like a lefty coward, come
tomorrow and you can kill Salt.
You can kill me and you can celebrate at
my funeral, can't you? Cuz you're
rattled over a fiberactic cable.
>> This geese is 41 years old.
>> Yeah, I'm 41 years old. Stop talking
[ __ ] I'm a child to death tomorrow. Or
are you going to cry for another year on
crack that you want to death?
>> You need to grow up, bro.
>> Yeah, I'm tragic. Blah blah blah blah.
No one. Are we going tomorrow or are you
going to spend another 12 months on
crack cocaine crying that you want slug dead
>> by the time you go to war?
>> No, no, no. No one gives a [ __ ] about
you crying. You want me dead. I want to
fight and I want to end you slug. I mean
end you. I want to end you salt. I want
to beat that.
>> What do you mean what you want about?
You said you want me dead. So I am
giving you an opportunity for you and me
to fight for the death. Dan,
>> what you about? Stop [ __ ] self
projecting. You're owing no one back. I
will put the comments up where you said
you me dead. So, you've got an
opportunity to fight for the death tomorrow.
>> You ain't got the money to come here.
>> I've got the money. All right, sunshine.
I got more money than you. You live in
your mom's [ __ ] bedroom.
>> God, you're boring me.
>> You're like PJ, aren't you? giant ears
all day rattled over me and it's [ __ ]
lush and I love it.
>> I'm the same [ __ ] every day.
>> I [ __ ] love it. >> M.
>> Yeah, I'm a tragic mess. Oh, look at him
leave the [ __ ] handouts. Enjoy your
day with your big giant earphones on on
crack cry with your bacon boyfriend on
WhatsApp. Ponty [ __ ] tragic.
>> To me, it's the same show tomorrow. The
slug has another year living life,
living the dream as salt.
>> Timmy, it's the same. Timmy, it's the same argument.
>> Oh, we know it's the same argument. I
want to meet him and beat the [ __ ] out
of Salt because I'm telling you one
thing, me and Mikey will be going back
up Liverpool mates and you will not show
and you'll be owned again like Jay
Willow owned you, Salt. All you are is a
druggy mess, pathetic loser to society,
salt, and you will never move out your
parents like PJ.
>> This is just saying [ __ ] [laughter] to
>> They think because someone has an
opinion, they think it's bullying. I am
going to meet you, Salt, one day. I know
what you look like and I am going to
beat the [ __ ] living daylights out
this lefty. Timmy, where did where does he live?
>> Where did he live?
Where does he live?
>> Where does he live? >> Liverpool.
>> Go Liverpool now and go live.
>> I can't go to Liverpool right now. I'm
in my box of shorts. But I'm in my box
of shorts. Why don't you go later? Why
don't you go? Why don't you go later?
>> He will be going live tomorrow outside
the Weather Spoons at Argus in the city
center of Liverpool.
>> He won't show. He'll never show. He's
just a little lefty cry baby like you
who wants attention.
>> Okay. Well, well, Timmy, if you're if
you're hard, go there now then.
What? Go there now.
>> How can I go there now, PJ? I'm in my
box of shorts. I can't
>> get changed. Get changed and get the train.
>> So, how can I go there right now? I
haven't got a magic carpet. I haven't
got a TARDIS. So, how can I get there?
>> Oh, you walk to the train station and
get a dipstick, aren't you, monster?
>> Yeah, cuz you're not about it. That's
why you're not You're all Listen, Timmy.
>> PJ, you're going to meet
the way back. Timmy, I've met you and
you're not about it.
>> You have done nothing PJ.
video. If you're about it, go to Liverpool now.
>> Go to See, look, look, look. These This
is what I'm trying to say. They just
want to talk. I'm kicking him for a
second. Yeah. He just wants to talk. All
he wants to do is talk [ __ ] But they're
not They're not trying to meet anyone.
You know what I'm saying? These people
are not trying to meet anyone.
You know, I said, "If you're about
something, just go tell Liverpool now."
And he won't do it because they just
want to argue and just go around in
circles. So boring and pathetic. I'm
gone now anyway. See you later. I've
only gone live to say that. Stop
stalking me on Reddit pretending to be a
woman, you [ __ ] sad [ __ ] low
lives. And that's all I wanted to say.
So see you in a bit. Yeah. Peace out.