You're not still alive. [clears throat]
Just wanted to see if it's the same
faces. Surely not.
not on a [ __ ] Tuesday evening.
Surely not, mate.
Surely not. Can't be save people. Surely 26 [laughter]
people every day. They call the elephant
people. You never know. Hopefully different people
listen to people.
Not [clears throat] the same little mix up
the same faces. [laughter]
Oh, by the way, um I shouldn't even be
doing this to be fair, but um
I'll be going to Reading soon, by the way.
So, if that Prime wants round two, I'm
not going for him, but I'll be going
soon cuz I need to go meet a friend. I
don't mind knocking the prick out,
you know, cuz I know he lives down that right way.
So, I'll actually be going there uh kind
of soon. Well, whenever I do, I'll let
you know beforehand
because I need to go and meet a friend.
So, I don't mind smashing this [ __ ] one
on round two. I have no problem.
>> I'm the January bear.
>> No, I'm not staying in a hotel, bro. I'm
just going to meet a friend,
you know. I'm just going to meet a mate.
It's been overdue. We've been meaning to
meet up, but it just hasn't happened.
So, I want to see if this if this guy is
really about it, bro. I'll let obviously
I'll let you know when I'm going. It's
not this week or whenever, but it will
be happening. 100% it's going to be happening, bro.
Well, just say that I'm going to read him soon.
Triple H to go and meet a friend in it.
So if that Prime wants round two, I
don't mind smacking him one if he wants round two cuz obviously one sec.
Um, yeah. I'll be when I go to Redin,
I'll be I'll be calling this [ __ ] out,
bro. I'll be calling this [ __ ] out cuz
we know he lives there. Newbury Red and
it's the same thing. So, yeah. My friend
messaged me back. He said, "Yeah, I'd
love to show you around and we can go on
a little piss up."
A little piss up, he said. Grievesy, I
was tempted to uh share the voice. A
good little piss up. [laughter]
A good little piss up, but it it will
only just be me um trying to meet this
[ __ ] It won't be it won't be him. I'll
do it either before or after, obviously,
cuz it's not going to be a twoon one.
Yeah, I'm still waiting for the answer
about the biasness, Grezy. I had some
chicken and chips earlier. I don't think
we'll ever know the answer
as what I was saying. Um, so I'm going
to have to stop asking it because I
don't think we're ever going to get the answer [gasps]
and I'm sick of bloody waiting like that
guy in the shop. So I don't think we'll
ever know really. [snorts] So yeah, I'm
going to give up asking that.
I was thinking about it on the way to
the shop and thinking about on the way back. M H
I don't think we'll ever know, do we?
Will we Grey?
I don't think we'll ever know.
Is this woman mad?
No. Are you?
She is taking a piss. One second.
This escort bro is really taking a piss.
She messages me. She messaged me. I was
someone I saw before. She's like, "Oh
yeah, you should book a hotel in North
London." So, I've looked up the hotel
prices talking like £65
and then she's trying to say, "Oh, yeah,
on top of that £150 per hour, you can
[ __ ] right off. That does not cost that,
bro. Are you mad? You can [ __ ] right off
top of £65. So, over 200." Yeah, get
[ __ ] That's [snorts] not happening.
That's not happening, matey. So,
don't try and take a piss out of me.
I've seen this person three times as
well. Three or four times.
And they messaged me. No, I wasn't. They
were messaging me.
And so you want me to So you want me to
book a hotel and 150 on top of that? No.
That's taking a piss. Get [ __ ]
If they had said, "Yeah, you know, 2
hours for 100 on top of the 165." Nah,
maybe I would do it. But 150 per hour
plus that. So what you're talking almost
£400. Yeah, that ain't happening. [gasps]
That's not happening, mate.
It's not £150 per hour, matey. [snorts] Yeah.
Anyways, he was messaging me, so I
thought, [ __ ] it. We'll see what the
[ __ ] got to say. 150.
Are you taking a piss? Well, an hour
probably about 90 100
90 or 100 maybe an hour. £150 plus the
hotel prices. No, cuz you're staying in
my hotel. So, I think at the end of the
day, obviously I've met them a couple of
times. I don't think that's fair to be
honest. No, I know them. I know them
from before cuz you're staying in my
hotel and I've known you from before.
So, I'm not I'm not paying that
cuz I I have to pay the hotel. Do you
understand? So, I don't think that's
fair. So, I won't be doing that.
[snorts] So, you can [ __ ] off.
She's a [ __ ] as well, bro. She's been
acting like a [ __ ] recently.
It was never ever ever ever ever 150.
You could literally get an escort to
come to your house for that price.
Yes, she's Brazilian. You could
literally get an escort come to your
house for that price.
Like your house. So why am I going to
pay 150 on top of her? That doesn't make sense.
Yeah, you need to stop saying that.
scenes thing, bro. That's proper boring.
It's 2026, lad. You need to stop saying
that word. That's very, very boring.
And it's not trying to get discounts.
The price is not 150 to begin with.
I mean, the price is not 150 to begin
with. So, I mean, that's not even the
price to begin with. And you need to
stop saying that scenes as well, bro.
That's boring as [ __ ] That's been going
for like 15 years now. You need to
switch it up a little bit. It's not 150.
I'm not getting ripped off. It's not
discounts. So I'm not getting ripped
off. Simple. So,
and that doesn't count as an out call
and as an out call when I'm in their I'm
literally in I'm in their area. I'm
actually in their area.
So, that's not really I mean technically
it is an out call, but you're literally
in their area cuz the hotel's in their area.
So, I mean it's in their area when Okay.
When Okay. No, no, no. Normally normally
when they come to a house you pay for
like their their their what the reason
out call costs more is because you're
you're paying for their taxi. You're
paying for like you know the taxi they
get a taxi here so you're paying for the
taxi. This is in their area.
So it's not like they're coming all the
way here from where they are. That's in
their area. So they're that doesn't make
any sense. So when they charge more for
alcohol that's to pay for their taxi as
well. So they're paying so like the taxi
and time getting here. But that that's
literally in their area. So it doesn't
make that doesn't make sense.
Uh like 80. But I went to them. They
they used to be in Stratford.
It was 80 with a [ __ ] without a
condom. So So it's normally 80 90 an hour.
You're boring. Bye-bye. So,
no, no, no, no, no. It used to be an in
call and then they've moved.
So, yeah. Yeah. So, it's like normally,
but obviously I got the condom move out.
So, it's like 90 100. It's not 150
and alcohol that's in their area. Like
that's literally in their area. So, it
shouldn't be more. You understand what
I'm saying? In back in the day, they're
coming from other areas. That's why
they're charging you more cuz they
obviously get a taxi or whatever it is.
They're coming from different areas.
They that is in their area. So why would
you why are you paying more? It doesn't
make sense. [snorts]
So yeah, they're trying to scam me, lad.
150 an hour. Get [ __ ] [snorts] It was
never ever 150. Never ever ever ever. [snorts]
Yes, she's trying to take the piss, but
it ain't happening, mate.
Yeah, I'll just say let me know when
you're back in Stratford.
Yeah, let me know. She said I don't I
don't work with agencies anymore. You
want me to come to out call and give you
the same price? And another thing, it
was 50% agency fee there. I don't work.
No, no, no, no, no, no. But you're in
the same area. You're not paying for any
Ubers. You're not. No, no, no, no, no.
And I'm pay and I have to pay for the
hotel. That's another thing. I'm not
doing that, bro. I ain't doing that. [snorts]
You want me to come to out call?
Yeah. It's not happening, bro. I wasn't
born yesterday. Don't try and take the piss.
Cuz if they were coming all the way here
from there, then it would be different
because obviously they're getting a taxi
and obviously that makes sense. that
what they're saying doesn't make any
sense cuz you're going to their area
paying for the hotel which is £65 and
they're basically not traveling any distance.
So that is and they've actually hired
and they put the price higher as well.
So yeah, sort of taking a piss, you know,
I'm not doing that. So
that's a madness, bro. They're not
traveling out the area. Do you understand?
I'm going to tell Ant-Man about this as well.
No, I never I never used to get I used
to just get a [ __ ] and that was 80
without a condom. So with the sex. Yeah.
No more than 100.
Yeah. It's not 150. And I've got to pay
and I've got to pay for the hotel as
well. So I'm not doing that. Pretty much. Yeah,
she actually used to be right. She did,
Dusty. Now she's just turned into a
[ __ ] She was a [ __ ] last time I spoke
to her as well. She was a proper proper
she was being a proper [ __ ] [ __ ]
Like she's changed over time as well.
And now she's trying to scam me.
And now she's trying to [ __ ] scam me.
What the [ __ ] Then she's being a
[ __ ] and now she trying to [ __ ] scam me.
What the [ __ ]
[ __ ] that, bro.
Yeah, but she's trying to take the piss.
Yeah, she's providing a service, bro.
But she's trying to take the piss.
She's trying to actually scam me. So So
no, she's taking the piss.
And she's not a model. She's like
average. She's nothing special. She's
Why would I do that, bro? Why would I do
that when I could literally just pay
£200 right now and get someone over
here? That doesn't make sense, bro. I
could pay £150,200 now and and literally
pick anyone I want to come here. So, why
would I why am I going to travel out the
area? Why am I going to travel out the
Why am I going to travel out the area
and then pay for a hotel? That doesn't
make no sense. That doesn't make no
sense at all. So, you want me to travel
out the area to your area, pay for a
hotel, so you walk down the road and and
charge me more? That's not happening.
That doesn't make sense,
mate. I'm not the one that skin. You're
the one that's showing daddy's life
savings four years ago. I've got more
money than you'll ever have. And no,
you're the one that needs a little
part-time job. Get yourself out that
shitty council bedsit. progress in life.
You're the one that need a little
part-time job. You little copycat
talking about Cheryl Cole. A little
copycat trying to call me gay because I
don't find Cole attractive. You [ __ ]
skin virgin. [ __ ] copycat virgin
trying to show off and then trying to
[ __ ] backtrack when [ __ ] people
call you out for it. I've got more money
than you'll ever have. I don't need a
part-time job, matey. That's for me to
know. You'd never find out. [snorts]
Don't show your daddy's life savings
again from four years ago. [ __ ]
virgin. [snorts] [ __ ] virgin.
That's not my dad's life savings. When I
showed mine mixed with my dad years ago,
that was actually [laughter]
Oh, so you've got £1,000 then?
So, so you've got £1,000. You [ __ ]
skin. Get yourself a little job. Do you
the world of good, mate. [snorts]
So, yeah, she's trying to scam me, bro.
She's trying to [ __ ] scam the [ __ ]
out of me. That ain't happening, bro.
You [ __ ] skink.
Faky skink you are. You've never had 13
grand in your life. You wouldn't be in
that shitty bedsit wearing them shitty
clothes if you had 13 grand. Make the
story make sense. That's what I used to
say to LJ. Well, I still say to LJ. You
need to make the story make sense. If
you're gonna lie about having money, mate,
you know, if you're gonna lie about having money,
you need to get yourself a little
part-time job. It'll do you the world of
good to get out of the house. It will do
you the world of good getting yourself a
little job. Just a part-time job cuz
you've never worked. You've never
worked, mate. I'd love to see you
deliver food, you know, with Uber Eats.
It would [ __ ] kill you, mate. You
wouldn't have it in your
working. You don't have working in you.
You're not interested in working, are
you? You're just interested in [ __ ]
lying around in that shitty council
virgin bedsit. [snorts] You know,
you dress like an absolute virgin, but
that's cuz you are an absolute virgin.
You're an absolute skin virgin. [laughter]
You said shovel was attractive. You copy
him. I want to give you a little nuggy.
I want to give you a little nugget in your head.
Look, I'll give you a little Oh [ __ ]
give you a little nuggie
on your head for being a little copycat.
Imagine being a keyboard warrior on
YouTube in your 40s.
I win, you lose. See you later.
Anyways, we're not having stupid people
on my channel. Anyways,
so yeah, back to this escort anyways
trying to scam me.
Yeah. So, you're saying about agents?
Well, one second. You want me to come to
you out call? Actually, you're the one
that suggested out call, not me, and
give you the same price. And another
thing, it was 50% agency fee that I
don't work work with agencies. So, if
you don't work for the agencies, then
the money should be less then, shouldn't
it be? Then it then it should be less.
If you're not working for an agency
anymore, then theoretically, shouldn't
the money be less instead of higher?
Doesn't [snorts] make sense, bro. I want
to tell Ant-Man about this
cuz he likes stories like this. is [ __ ] mad.
You want to out call? I don't want a
[ __ ] out call. And that's not even an
out call when you you're not even
leaving your [ __ ] area for [ __ ]
sake about out call.
You're not even traveling [ __ ] more
than 0.3 [ __ ] miles.
[ __ ] absolute clown she is. She used
to be right as well. Um Greavvesy,
now she's just a [ __ ] trying to scam me, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, I will ban you. See you
later. We don't have idiots on my channel.
150. So, yeah, that's almost £400
they're asking and they're not even
leaving their area.
And you'd have to wear a condom. Yeah, get [ __ ]
And you'd have to wear a condom. That's almost £400. No.
No, I'll probably go to Reden soon to be fair.
Late January or February.
I don't know yet.
I don't really want to go back out, but
I've been meaning to meet this guy. He's
a cool guy, man, for a long time.
But yeah, they are they are trying to
scam me, aren't they, Slutmaker? Well,
cuz that's where he lives. And I want to
go somewhere different.
It's just somewhere different, isn't it?
I've not been drinking there before. So,
but yeah, she's definitely trying to scare me.
Yeah, I met him months ago. A couple of
months ago, the second time I last went
out. Yeah, he's a cool guy, bro.
You're another [ __ ] talker, mate. You're
another one that [ __ ] shits talk behind
my back. Wrista. Sad bastard.
Sad bastard, mate.
But yeah, she's trying to She's
definitely trying to scam.
If you want £150 per hour, mate, you're coming here.
You're coming here, matey. You're I'm
not going there to pay a hotel. It
doesn't make sense. How does that make
any sense? That defeats the whole object. They literally
They literally That defeats the whole
object. Oh, yeah. About Thailand. Yeah.
Um Antman's girlfriend was like, "Oh,
yeah. He's she thinks I'm good-looking."
His girlfriend says, "Oh, I'm
good-looking." And she can't believe I
can't get women in England. She doesn't
believe it. She's like, "Oh, come
Thailand. Come Thailand." Because
Ant-Man told her again today. He sent me
another voice note and she can't believe
it. And she's like, "Oh, I'm the same."
And Ant-Man's like, "No, it's not the
same because he can't get dates. He
can't get sex.
You can." And then she shut up. [laughter]
He said, "You get a woman within a day
there." That's what he said.
You should [ __ ] be getting women
here. You shouldn't have to leave your
country to get [ __ ] women in sex.
You shouldn't have to.
Why have I hid from Jo? I haven't hid
from Jo. But yeah, that what she's
saying defeats the whole object. That
defeats the whole object. Do you get
what I mean? Um, Greavvesy.
That defeats the whole object.
If you want 150
then you would be coming here.
That's why I used to give that only fans 150.
I used but she used to travel far so I
didn't mind giving it cuz she used to
travel far away and I didn't have to use
a condom. That was a bargain to be fair.
She didn't live she didn't live anywhere
near her. So she used to drive so the
petrol and that so I didn't mind you
know I didn't mind giving her that. So
it was different but obviously if you want 150.
Yeah. But she No, cuz what she's trying
to say Dusty is it's out call but it's
not out call because you're wanting me
to go all the way there to book a hotel
just for you to probably walk to the hotel.
Do you understand what I'm saying? So,
she's trying to trying to say that, oh,
it's alcohol, but it's not really
because proper out call with someone,
it's like traveling out of their area.
If you're not even leaving your area and
you're trying to charge alcohol prices
and I'm having to buy a hotel, it's not happening. So
yeah, that doesn't make it doesn't make
sense, bro. It just does not make sense. Uh,
see you later
again. You're blocked. All right.
[snorts] Yeah, I'll get a different one.
I can just go to I can I know where the
brothel is. If I want one, I can I can
just go to Stratford to the brothel.
It's an apartment if I want. I don't
know why she's trying to scam me. I've
seen her like three times and she's
trying to scam me.
She's trying to scam me, bro.
And she messaged me back. I didn't
message her. And she's trying to scam
me, bro. I I know where to go if I want them, bro.
[snorts] Just doesn't make no sense.
That does not make no sense. You want
somebody to travel all the way to North
London to pay for a hotel to then charge
them 150 an hour.
What the [ __ ] bro? That doesn't make any sense.
There used to be this escort I saw a
couple of times. Yeah, but I lost her
number and that.
The only bad thing with the escort is
you've got to use a condom. That's the
only [ __ ] thing about it.
That is a bad thing about that.
People [snorts] on Reddit still telling
me I'm going to meet someone asylum, lad.
Yeah, really, bro. Really?
Yeah. Really? Really? You're going to find someone?
Yeah, I know.
You reckon I will one day? So, why
hasn't it already happened in six years?
No one typed for a second. Yeah, I just
want to hear this guy's um this guy's
answer. So, why hasn't it happened in
six years with all of these approaches?
But you probably dismissed that, didn't
it? Didn't you? Cuz it don't suit you.
No. If you was going to find someone,
you would have found someone by now.
Think about it, Grezy. Look how many
times, right, I've like come into money
and then won money and then other things
have happened throughout the years. And
this is already this is already stayed
this has stayed the same. There's no way
if you was going to meet someone, you
you would have met someone by now. And
there's there's nothing anyone can say
to that. You would you would find someone.
You're you're going to die alone as
well. You don't have no one. Same are
you then cuz you're you don't have
anyone and you'll never find someone
same as you. But anyways, um you you'll
see in years that this has stayed the
same and it would always be the same.
And if you didn't dismiss people's
struggles, you would know that.
That's why I don't go out anymore
because I know there's no hope.
I know there generally generally is no
hope and I don't contradict myself so no. Yeah.
Oh, it's just a pub.
It's just a pub in central London. It
gets busy. It's good for Guinness. I've
done loads of approaches there.
Well, you're delusional if you've got
hope, lad. You're delusional.
very very delusional. If you if you
think I'm going to meet someone,
you're very very delusional.
That's all I can say, Dad. Cuz it would
have already happened.
Cuz it's funny how you can win money,
right? You can you don't know what's
going to happen in the future. You don't
know what's going to happen tomorrow.
But with this, it's always the same. You
know, that's what I find a bit weird.
You know, it would have happened by now.
You would have been happy. You would
have been having more success even if
you didn't meet anyone,
you know. So, that's just the way I I
just put logic to it to be honest. And
then you got [ __ ] escort trying to
[ __ ] scam you.
No, I wouldn't.
Yeah, things happen when you least
expect it. I mean, I've given up now for
over a month and nothing's happened.
Nothing's happened at all.
Nothing's happened at all. And I'm not trying again. So, you know,
I mean, I'm still on Instagram. I'm on Reddit.
So, I won't be going out trying.
I don't even know if I I've said I'm
going to go red, but I don't even know
if I actually will to be honest.
The more you think about your
experiences, the more it makes no sense
of you going out trying.
So, probably not to be honest with you. >> [snorts]
>> I can't justify going out again. Bro, I
I did talk to my friend and that, but I
can't justify it to me. It does, in my
head, it doesn't make any sense
when something's always going to be the
same. That's not depression. That's
facts. That's not even depression. That is facts.
Where is this?
I mean, gambling is banned in Thailand. You know,
damn's banned in Thailand.
Yeah. Gambling's ban Thailand, bro. I uh
And I sent them dick p I sent dick
pictures to people that I met in Waxies Triple H.
Yeah, I sent dick pictures. Yeah.
No, he'll never get laid. He'll die a virgin. [snorts]
No, he will die a virgin, mate. I don't
even think [ __ ] Thailand will save him.
No, I don't even think Thailand would
save that virgin, mate. Seriously, don't.
You still there? You still there? Uh, Grezy
boy, the people in this community are
biased, [ __ ] maker. What do you think?
Even LT is biased. I didn't expect it
from LT, you know, but even he's biased.
Yeah, they are biased, bro. They are
they are definitely definitely biased
with the Virgin thing. I'm sick of
repeating it. Sorry if it sounds boring,
but they they definitely are biased.
Sorry, but they are.
No, they are definitely definitely they
definitely are biased.
What they're saying doesn't make any sense. [snorts]
What do you think, UK asylum? That what
they're saying don't make no sense.
No, no, no. But LT is still biased. LT
is still biased because when he was
talking to me the other day, bro, I said
to him, "Oh yeah, oh yeah, Nonlegs is a
virgin. Nonlex is a virgin." And he was
saying the same thing. Oh, how can he be
a virgin if he's got a girlfriend? But
doesn't this guy call me a virgin when
I've literally proved I've had sex? Like
I've No, no, no. I have proved I've had
sex multiple times. So I mean, okay,
cool. He's got a girlfriend. I've proved
I've had sex. So, by logic, it would be
more ridiculous calling me a virgin than
me calling him a virgin. I would have thought.
I mean, what do you think? Do I think it
would be more ridiculous him calling me
a virgin than me
actually proves I've been butt naked in
bed with women, but apparently that
doesn't count. But he can't be a virgin
because he's got a girlfriend. But
someone that's actually been butt naked
in women's beds in hotel rooms and
actually produced a porno, there's a
there's a chance they're a virgin.
Really, mate? Really? Really? I don't
think so. And that's how they're biased.
You see, that's [snorts] how they're
that's how they're biased.
Even LT is biased with it. Um,
so, and Kieran will tell you as well
when Kieran's on here that it is
biasness. It is biasness, bro. >> [snorts]
>> Sorry to say, hate to say it, bro, but
it is it is it is definitely definitely biasness.
Um, and um, I mean, Steven Howard, when
people call me a virgin, Steven Howard defends me,
which uh, well, doesn't I wouldn't even
say defending, it's stating the obvious.
It's not even defending me. It's stating the obvious.
Um, and then LT's calling him a troll.
How can he be a troll when he's stating
facts when people are slagging me off?
So him Kieran.
Yeah. Strange that isn't it?
And [snorts] then he was like, "Oh yeah,
you paid for it." Bro, even if you paid
for it, it still counts. To me, it does.
Okay. How How do I put it this way?
Right. Okay. So, this is hard to
explain. Like, if someone pays for sex
share, it doesn't count as a
It doesn't count as a body count, but it
proves that they've definitely had sex.
They've definitely definitely definitely
had sex and they're definitely
definitely not a virgin. Even though it
doesn't count as somebody that you'd add
it to, but you've definitely still
[ __ ] them. So even if you played,
you've still [ __ ] someone and you're
still not a virgin. I mean, it counts,
but it it doesn't count as a body count,
if that makes sense. I mean, I don't
count as a body count. Some people do,
some people don't.
So I still say mine is six, even though
I bang loads of escorts. So to LT, it
doesn't matter if I paid or I didn't
pay. There was several women that I
didn't pay. So it's more ridiculous you
calling someone like me a virgin. That's
where the bias comes from. You know, we
expected from Joseph Ferrar because he's
a Lav Mong.
So yeah, I said to LT, "Okay, well I put
a porno out there." And he was like,
"Oh, you paid for it." I said, "Mate, it
doesn't matter if I paid for it or not.
I've still proved that I've done sexual
stuff. I've still been seen with women
in hotel rooms naked that have admitted
to sleeping with me. So, it's more
ridiculous you calling me them calling
me a virgin than me calling someone
showing a disabled girl in pictures.
But they it doesn't go through their
minds. So, they've all got their own
agenda even if they act like they don't. Yeah.
Yeah. And it doesn't annoy me. It's just
weird. It's just strange to be honest.
Doesn't annoy me at all.
And I know it sounds ridiculous. Yeah.
But it and I know it sounds immature,
but it's the way to prove that they're
biased. As as immature and ridiculous as
it sounds, you know, it's it's the way
to, you know, and then they'll sit there
and say, "Oh, well, you showed a
blowjob." Okay, but there's no proof
that he's had sex with his girlfriend.
If you want to put it that way, if you
want to put it if you really want to put
it that way, bro, there's no proof that
he's [ __ ] his girlfriend. If you if
you want to put it that way, saying
that, oh wait, what do you think? She
just stopped at a [ __ ] So what do
you think? This woman that was sucking
my dick just stopped at a [ __ ] See,
they're all biased. So I can I can say
the same thing then, can't I? [ __ ]
biased pricks. They are biased, bro.
They are biased.
They are biased, lad.
Don't know why, but they are. Yeah. [sighs] [snorts]
I got only I got [ __ ] of escorts.
Well, bro, well that it's proven. It's
proven more than him then, isn't it?
Well, if I've proved I've got a blow
Okay, listen. Listen. Okay. So if I
proved I've got a [ __ ] off of
escorts, then that's showing more than
nonslegs then, isn't it? You know that
that literally proves
that I've had more than nonslegs then theoretically.
So [snorts] but that's what I'm saying.
They're biased. And what about Sig? What
about Manchester? Um what about the 19year-old?
Um and it was a one night stand I had on
my birthday as well uh two years ago. I
mean what about all of them times? They
weren't just sucking my dick.
>> No, I don't need to prove. I just don't
understand the biasness, especially from
LT. Um, you know, I don't obviously
Joseph is a Lavy bong, so we expected
from a L J buttlicker, a little
buttlicker, but we we wouldn't expect it
from people like LT. You know,
how can you say it's ridiculous me
calling someone a virgin that's got a
girlfriend when you're trying to call me
a virgin when I've proven I've actually
had sex multiple times? That doesn't make sense.
That That does not make any sense. It
doesn't make no sense. That's even sillier.
So, stop going on about this disabled
girlfriend that he's proved that he's
done nothing with. [ __ ] me. That's
annoying, bro. You know,
stop going on about this girlfriend.
[ __ ] me, [snorts] bro. But I've proved
more than just some [ __ ] shitty
girlfriend in a in a couple of pictures.
It's stupid, bro. It's really, really,
really, really stupid.
And then Joseph Ferrar was like, "Oh, we
know you're not a virgin."
Then I say to him, "Okay, then why are
you sticking up for non legs, but you're
not saying anything? I don't need you to
defend me. I'm asking you why you're
doing it." If that's the case, then you
don't need to defend people. Why are you
defending Nonlegs? And he can't answer
it cuz he knows I'm right.
If you know Nonlex is not a virgin, why
are you straight to his rescue?
If you know that we're both not virgins,
why are you to one rescue? Why are you
to one's rescue and not the other? Does
it make sense? Especially when you think
someone's a nons, you know, [ __ ]
It's just little stuff like that, bro.
It just doesn't make sense. I was making
my tea earlier when I woke up and I'm
thinking, "Oh, bro, it just doesn't make
sense." I was actually going to message
LT about that as well.
I was going to message LT about that,
you know, think asking like what's
what's going on, bro?
It just randomly popped into my head,
you know, like what the [ __ ] bro? That
doesn't make no sense.
And it doesn't matter if you paid for it
or not, you still it still counts. But
it doesn't count as a body count to me.
It doesn't count as a body count.
But it still prove that you've [ __ ] someone.
If you won if you won300 on roulette
right now, right? Say you won £300 on
roulette right now and you paid £300 and
you paid an escort £300 out of money
that you won, right? So you've won. So
that doesn't count as having sex.
So So people that are in the porn
industry that get paid for it, the man
get gets paid and the women get paid.
So, does that mean that they've not had
sex then because it was theoretically
paid for? Doesn't make any sense, you know?
Does it? It doesn't make no sense. It
doesn't make any sense.
Doesn't make no sense at all, bro.
But a lot of people in here don't make any sense.
And I don't I generally think he is a
virgin. I generally generally generally
think he is.
And and and LT was like, "Oh, what? So
you don't think people do business?"
Brother, I've shown you the business on
four or five different occasions. I've
shown business with women. I've shown
the actual business,
you know. I've been I've been shown I've
shown the actual business.
Oh, nothing, man. We're just going on
about LT being a bit biased like you. We
expect it from you because you're a Lav
Mong, but we didn't expect it from him.
But no, we're not going to get into it
anyways. Uh, but just just just one of
these things we don't understand on this
community. No biggie.
Being wanted by a woman is priceless. Well, [snorts]
yeah, not really.
I mean, most pe most of them want people
for their money anyways. So
yeah, they are biased. They are biased.
They don't even LT is biased. Even if he talks sense.
No, but he's still biased with the
nonslegs thing and the virgin thing.
He's He's still biased. The only people
that are not biased on that is Steven Howard, Kieran,
Ben. A lot of these people on here are
very very biased. And it sounds
ridiculous, but it's true. who they are.
Um, you know, someone that stands, I've
never known a name. Only difference is,
well, it doesn't matter if you paid for
it, you didn't pay for it. You still
[ __ ] You still had sex. It doesn't
matter. If this Oreo man paid for an
escort right now, I'd say that he lost his virginity.
I would say he lost his virginity.
You know, imagine he played roulette and
won £300 and paid £300.
you've still had sex. I don't count it
as a body count, but you've still had
sex. You are no longer pure.
So, yeah, I just find it very very
strange how when you call this uh skin
nonslegs virgin, a virgin, everyone's
talking about this girlfriend
and how it's ridiculous. I think it's
more ridiculous to call someone a virgin
that's actually proven they've had sex
like I have. I think that's even more
ridiculous. But each to their own. Oh,
and this escort tried to scam me as well, Joe.
We're talking about an escort that tried
to scam me. I mean, that's more
ridiculous, to be honest. It's It's more
It's utterly ridiculous to try to call
someone a virgin that's actually made
porn videos like I have. But we'll never
know the answer to that. Yeah,
but you've all got your own little
agenda. It's no biggie. We know what you're like.
So, and another thing, Joe, if you know
that I'm not a virgin and you know that
I'm not a virgin, why did you stick up for nonslegs?
I I want to know because I don't think
LT because So, if you know that both of
us not a virgin and you don't need to
stick up for me because I know I'm not a
virgin, why do you keep sticking up for
your boyfriend? Cuz it's more ridiculous
him calling me a virgin. Is it cuz you
got your own secret agenda? Um,
okay. So, just this just escort me,
right? And normally she charges £80 an
hour for a [ __ ] So, let's just say
for sex it's £100. So, let's just say
it's £100 an hour now. Yeah. So, she's
telling me to go to her She's telling me
to go to her area, book a hotel, which
cost £65, and now she's trying to charge
£150 an hour. That's defeating the whole
object. That's literally defeating the
whole object. An out call is when you're
trying to get somebody to come to you,
not you to go closer to them to book a
hotel for them to rip you off. So
yeah, she's trying to scam me basically.
And then she's saying about oh before it
was because it was an agency fee. So if
it was an agency fee and now you're no
longer working for an agency, shouldn't
you be charging less?
So she's just trying to scam left,
right, and center basically. So you want
me to come all the way to your area,
book a hotel, and class as an ink and
then alcohol and then charge me extra? No. [snorts]
No. If you was coming all the way here
trying to charge that, it'd be a
different story cuz taxis, you pay for
their taxes. Why am I going to pay for a
room? Have you walked to the room and
then tried to charge people [ __ ] out
call prices? Get [ __ ] man. Trying to
scam me. And they're messing me out the
blue as well. Trying to [ __ ] scam me.
Really? That is not happening, bro. I
used to pay the Only Fans one 150, but
she used to travel miles away. She used
to travel and she had to pay petrol and
that. So, I didn't mind that
cuz she come all the way here and I
didn't have to use a condom either. I
thought that was a bargain to be honest.
Yeah, she's a proper She's trying to
scam me, Dad.
Well, obviously I'm not an easy target
because I'm not going, am I? Yeah.
But you people are definitely you've
definitely got your own agenda on here.
Would you agree, Joseph, that you're
definitely biased and got your own
agenda? I think that's one we can agree on.
So, it's ridiculous calling someone with
a girlfriend a virgin, but someone
that's actually proved they [ __ ] women
and being in women's uh bed butt naked,
there's a chance of them being a virgin.
[ __ ] [snorts] logic. [ __ ] logic in the ass.
Yeah, she thought I was, but I'm not
trying to scam me. I've met her four
times as well, and she's trying to scam
me. That's why Joey, we called you the nonsle lover.
That's why we called you the nonslegs lover.
Cuz it's more ridiculous calling someone
like me a virgin, but I don't see your
little comments when your boyfriend's
going at me, but as soon as I go for
your boyfriend, you're straight to the
rescue. Do you remember that? You're
straight to the rescue.
Do you remember?
Do you remember, lad? You were straight
to the rescue like Superman. You
couldn't defend him any quicker. Oh,
he's got a girlfriend. He's got a
girlfriend. Yeah. You didn't bring up
the pornos and the women I slept with.
You admitted to sleeping with me. You
based gun. You [ __ ] dodge lover. You
dirty nodded slubbing bastard. Yeah.
All right, devil.
Yeah, that's weird. That is That That is
That is very weird. It is very weird.
It's very It's very [ __ ] weird. And
then if I had a girlfriend, they'd
probably say that
um she's your friend and she's cheating
on you or something.
That's funny, bro. That is really,
really funny. How can [ __ ] LT call
Steven Howard a troll?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. But you haven't said it on his
channel when he's going at me. No, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. You've not
said it on his channel when he's going
at me. So,
and he is definitely definitely a
virgin. 100% a virgin.
He literally he has never had more sex
than me. He has not had more sex than
me. No, no, no, no, no. He has not had
more sex than me, mate. Definitely
definitely definitely definitely not had
more sex than me, mate.
Everyone I've shown that's had a
[ __ ] I have [ __ ] more than [ __ ]
I I have actually [ __ ] them. All the
women that you've seen, I've [ __ ] them.
He hasn't had more sex than me, mate.
And he hasn't had more women than me either,
which is uh another thing, though. A lot
of these people haven't a lot of these
people that defend women haven't had as
many women as me, but they still defend them.
But they still defend them. I know. It's
weird, isn't it? They actually haven't.
A lot of these people, most of them that
defend women. It's weird, isn't it? You
would have thought it'd be the other way around. Okay.
You haven't had more women than me, matey.
You haven't. You know, you
I've only bear backed an escort once years ago.
Yeah. She trying to She definitely took
I said to her, "All right, Joe." I said,
"Let me know when you're back in
Stratford." She said, "No."
And I'm going to reply back, "Scammer.
Once you get you have No, no, no, no,
no. Cuz if I had a girlfriend No, no,
no, no. Cuz if I had a girlfriend, you'd
still be talking [ __ ] No, no, no, no,
no. You'd still be talking [ __ ] You'd
basically say that it's not my friend
and I don't [ __ ] her, brother. You're
biased on here. Even if someone had a
girlfriend, you would still talk [ __ ] I
mean, I've had more women than him. It's
been proven. And you still talk [ __ ]
Women that I've met more than once,
mate. Even if I was in a relationship,
you would still come out with [ __ ]
I mean, you've done it with all the
things in the past, being shown more
money, more women, better life, better
looks, better food, and you've still
somehow spoke [ __ ] So, at the end of
the day, that's not going to be no
different. You would still talk [ __ ]
You would you would still find a way to
talk [ __ ] even if I was in a relationship. So,
and I can call him because he's he's
with a disabled girl and all of the
women that I've been with has never been
disabled. So, yes, I can call him a big
fat stinking virgin with a disabled
girlfriend. I can call him I I can call
him and I will call him and I just did.
So, yeah, I can call him with a disabled girl.
You know, it would then move to the
likes of Timmy who's not
not having a 28. Why do you care if I've
had a girlfriend or not? Worry about
your own life. It's not like you can get
a girlfriend in this country anyways,
brother. I've had more women than you
have. And that's not even me just saying
that. I've had more women than you and
non-slegs combined. Worry about
yourselves. Why are you obsessed with a
28-year-old whether they've been in a
relationship or not? It's none of your
business whether I've been in a
relationship or not.
You know, at the end of the day, lad,
I've had more women than you and nods
legs. I've had more women than you.
That's pathetic. And you're both older than me.
So, why is a someone in their 40s
worried about a 28-year-old? Obsessed.
Obsessed with a 28-year-old. Have you
looked at your lives, bro? Listen, Joe.
I bet you right now that your MS is
bigger and fatter and uglier than
anything I've ever been with.
And that that's facts. And you think
that's an achievement. See, you see the
thing is with you and nonslegs, right?
You think being with fat ugly women is
having one over on someone, but it
isn't. But it isn't. You having fat,
ugly women that no one wants. You think
that's having one over on someone, but it isn't.
That's mental to me that someone would
be with someone fat and ugly. I can't
fathom that. But you don't see me
talking about it. You don't see me
talking about it every day.
I would never get with a big fat ugly
woman. But I don't you don't see me
saying that to you every day,
you know. Well, I find it hard to
believe that someone would get with
anything as stinking as you and Nles
legs. But, you know, that's that's one thing. [snorts]
I think it's mad how you would pick
someone fat and ugly.
Big, fat, stinking, and ugly. And I have
had a girlfriend as well. That's another
thing. I actually have had a girlfriend.
Um, to prove you wrong, I actually have
had a girlfriend and I've also had more
and I've had chances to be in relationships,
you know, and I and I've had more
chances to be in relationships and I
have had a girlfriend.
So, try again. Obsessed.
[gasps and sighs] Obsessed.
I mean, the women that you that you have
Well, not well, not nonslegs. I mean, I
wouldn't even I was going to say you
would use them for a one nighter, but
with nonslegs as misses, you wouldn't
even [ __ ] the [ __ ] one night. She's
that ugly and disabled. You would You
wouldn't even [ __ ] her.
You literally wouldn't even [ __ ] her.
What? You literally wouldn't even [ __ ] her.
I don't, bro. I'd rather have no woman
than have a big fat ugly woman. I'd
rather have no woman.
I would rather have no woman than have
anyone with someone be with someone
that's big, fat, and ugly. I'd rather
have no woman. I'm owning it. I'm not in denial.
Uh I've had a girlfriend, Joe, and I've
had multiple chances to be in
relationships. Try again.
Try again, Joe. Try again. I've been
with more women and I have had a
girlfriend. Stop your obsession with a
28-year-old, you weirdo. You're in your
40s and you're obsessed with a
28-year-old. [ __ ] off. Do you know what?
My sister went on the phone was on the
phone to me yesterday and she said, "Do
you know why these people go at you?"
She says, "Cuz you're better looking
than them." Even my sister said it as
well. My sister does not talk no [ __ ]
And that's three people now that says
they go for you cuz you're better
looking. Have you seen these people on
here? Yeah. Fat, ugly, glasses. Not one
of them are handsome. I swear to God,
bro. My My sister said it's cuz you're
better looking than them. They don't.
And I've said the same thing and she's
never ever heard me ever say that. But I
was on the phone to her for like 40
minutes. She said, "You need to stop
this YouTube shit." And she's like,
"Have you seen these people on here?
They're fat, ugly." Like, she's not the
only one that said it. I swear to God
because she's not the only one that said it, bro. You know,
why do I rant about women? Because
they're [ __ ] What do you mean if
I've had You've seen me with women, bro.
What do you mean if I've had all of
these women? We've seen it. There's
There's no ifs about it.
No, no, no. She's not agreeing with me.
She's literally saying that you are
jealous. And And And And I'm not the
only one that said it. And I'm not the
only one that said it as well. You know,
it's the truth. That's [snorts] Yeah, it
is the truth. I know that as well, lad.
I know that. Anyways, I already knew
these people were jealous. I I know
that. You don't need to tell me anything.
Yeah. Sounds incest to me. No, we're not
all you, Joe. We're not all you.
No, we're not all you, mate.
And why are you saying if you've had You
know I have.
You literally know I have.
What do you mean if I have? You know I
have. Weird. You literally know I have.
What the [ __ ] >> [snorts]
>> I do hope you get the help that you
need, man. Honestly, I do hope you hope
you get the help that you need.
Generally, generally do.
I hope you get the help that you need, man.
That's all I'm saying.
Yeah, they did. They're sick bastards.
That's what they're like on here.
They're sick, bro. Yeah, they've made a
lot of sick stories up. That's their
life though, isn't it, bro?
That's their life.
Yeah, that's their life, bro.
[snorts] They're sick. I need to tell
Ant-Man about this [ __ ]
person that was trying to Oh my god. He
loves them kind of stories to be fair.
So now you're not going to let me know.
So I just said that they're a scammer
basically. They have a reply back.
Yeah, they didn't reply back, bro. Scammer
as adult. Weird. [snorts]
O, Triple H thinks that you're showing
fake wins as well.
He wanted to talk to you earlier, but
you didn't come on.
Yeah, he thinks you're also showing fake wins.
Yeah, he thinks that you're also showing
fake wins, but you didn't come on. He
had a bone to pick with you earlier. Yeah.
Well, not fake wins that you're only
basically showing uh wins. Yeah,
that he wanted to uh he wanted to call
you out on that, by the way. Yeah,
he wanted to call you out on that, matey.
Strange that, isn't it? I lose on it,
Triple H loses on it, LJ loses on it,
but you always seem to win. Oh, Smoky B
loses on it as well, but you seem to win on it.
Very, very odd.
But you seem to win on it
all the time. Do you know what? It's not
even all the time. You seem to win like
every two days.
Bro, you should just give up work.
You're winning so much on these
machines. I think you should just give
up work now, lad. You said that you
could afford to lose thousands.
Why are you at work, bro? You need to
stop. You need to If you're winning all
that money, I don't know why you're working.
To be honest with you, you said that you
can afford to lose thousands.
Well, you seem to be winning a lot of
money, so yeah, I guess so. Yeah.
I don't seem like that recently. But you
have to understand I may visit three
different bookies in that day. But on
post the one win I also been on a decent run.
And the reason why you'd post losses is
because it's a gambling channel.
I mean, it's a gambling channel. So
that's why you'd post losses because
it's a gambling channel. Your channel
was basically a gambling channel.
[snorts] That's why you would post
losses just like Secular Slots. Just
like what I used to do, just like what
Seven Neighbors used So yeah,
your story [snorts] doesn't add up,
mate. To be honest with you,
your story doesn't add up.
Your story really doesn't add up.
I can't lie to you. It just doesn't add up.
I went I found a site earlier. I was
going to play some roulette online. I
found like another site, but I don't
like the deposit fees. You shouldn't
have to They shouldn't be charging that
much to deposit your own money
and they charge a lot as well. It's not
even like a couple of pound.
So, that's out the window. Basically,
it's actually charging people to
deposit. That's madness. I'm not pay I'm
not paying to deposit my own bloody money. Yeah,
[snorts] they charge a ridiculous
amounts of money, bro. Just charge you a [ __ ] thing.
[snorts] She tried to scam me, bro.
She tried to scam me.
Not much, bro. Just chilling. I
shouldn't even be on YouTube to be
honest. Laney doesn't even want me on
YouTube. It's a good thing to be honest
with you. You know,
you look back in two years and be like,
"Oh, you save two years arguing with
just these hating biased losers." It's a
good thing to be honest. You should use
that to your advantage.
Yeah, I was I was suggesting that,
Dusty. I was suggesting that.
>> Yeah, I'm going to do that, you know,
actually. [ __ ] it.
Yeah, I was thinking that to be honest.
for just for trying to scam me in it.
Yeah, she's a scammer, bro.
She's a scammer.
She is a scammer, mate.
I was going to go to Red and Dusty
because they're real Cockney. You know,
people from Redden. Yeah, people from
Reading or Cockneys, isn't it?
No, I was going to go read and see my
friend, but I just can't justify going
out anymore. I can't justify it. I can't
justify trying again.
And it's not because I'm skinned because
I got more than enough money before you
keep trying to use that. So,
I don't know what I'm doing, bro. [snorts] >> [snorts]
>> Oh, speaking to a married woman, Joe,
she says that she will come to London
and um do the deed cuz her husband don't
give her sex. We was talking all night
um yesterday and we was talking a little bit today.
She's from Scotland.
Yeah, it is boarded up. No,
Joseph Ferrar is very upset with me. You
know, he doesn't talk about anyone else
but me. If you go on if you go on large
Yeah. He doesn't talk about anyone else but me.
I [snorts] think you're another secret
red star me, mate. You all you talk
about is me. I've seen it myself. PJ PJ
PJ [ __ ] yeah. I met them on Instagram. [snorts]
Yeah, you're another one that's Yeah,
I do think a lot of people on here are
jealous to be fair. I can't lie. I
actually do think a lot of you use
actually are you haters.
You pro you you're proving me wrong.
You're not proving me wrong. If you want
to prove me wrong, go live gambling.
You've never proved me wrong ever. go
live in the bookies and gamble and don't
try and say that you're going to get
banned because you're not.
So, you've never proven me wrong. I've
asked you to talk multiple times, you
haven't. I've asked you to show your
face multiple times, you haven't. Um,
I've asked you to go live in the bookies
multiple times. You haven't. You have
never proved me wrong. Ever. You have
never ever proved me wrong. The three
things I've asked you to do, you won't do it.
Starting with come in the panel right
now and talk. You can't do it.
Mate, you've never proven me wrong.
You have never ever proven me wrong ever.
[snorts] You haven't. You haven't proven me wrong.
And another thing, right, is you're
saying about how like you're not
jealous. You're not jealous. But we can
safely say that most of the people on
here are uglier than me. They're fatter
than me and they've got a worse life than me.
And like I've said multiple times, I'm
not going to keep repeating myself. If
you join the hangouts and you turn your
camera on, I will prove it. But you
won't do it. None of these people on
here that's hating on me is younger and
better looking than me, bro. Do you not
think that's a bit strange how they all
seem to be fatter and uglier than you?
Yet they swear by Almighty that they're
not jealous really. Okay, bro. [snorts]
You will have to keep guessing and
wondering. I don't need to guess. I know
you're fat. I know you're fat. I know
for 100% you're fat and I know you're
scared. I'm not guessing at all. I know
you're a fat bastard by your hands.
I can tell by your hands that you're
fat. You're fat as [ __ ] You can tell by
someone's hands if they're fat, by the
way. So, I'm not guessing anything, mate.
I'm not guessing. Everything I say about
people is right. Look what I said about
the bomb. Fat, ugly, bold. I was right.
Everything I've said, I've been right. You know,
you are all you are older than me. You
are uglier than me. You are more low
life than me. The people that are hating.
I believe it. Yeah. Yeah. You would
never slap me up, bro. Never in your
life could you slap me up. I'll be
calling out that prior anyways. If I do
go to Readen, I will be calling him out.
I'll let him know beforehand as well
since she lives in that area.
I'm always happy. Are you happy or you
still self- projecting your skintess
every day onto people? [snorts]
You're big. You're big enough to slap me
up, bro. Really? Really? You wish, mate. You wish. [clears throat]
Yeah, man. [cough]
You are all fatter and uglier than me.
The people that hate. The people that
sit on here and hate. Definitely definitely are.
Definitely definitely definitely
definitely definitely are. And you can't
prove me wrong. That's why I don't get
mad at you cuz I knows what you all are.
I knows what you're all about.
I knows what you all are. I knows what
you're all about. So that's why it's
hard to like
get triggered by you clowns because we
know that you're you not even worth
reacting to. You know
what's your plan for this week? S on
YouTube stalking me as usual calling me
skint when you skint yourselves. Oh,
aren't you the one that says that I use
colada? [laughter] Never used colada in
my life. That's you self projecting,
bro. Takes one to no one. I've never
used colog in my whole life.
Just cuz you can't afford 200 lb jeans
and 200 lb trainers, lad.
I know what you are. Yeah, I know what
Yeah, I know what you people are, bro.
That's why it doesn't bother me.
[snorts] The only reason I was mad the
other day is cuz I was already in a bad
mood. You don't bother me, bro. You
haters. Not Not one little bit.
I shouldn't really be on here to be
honest with you lads. I really shouldn't
be on here because like
[snorts] you're wasting your life. Yeah.
On just these wasters, which is why
Monty man don't go in there
on these wasters, you know.
I like Charlie, you know. I like How
hard can it be? I think they're decent fellas.
I like Ben Furby.
They're great guys, you know. They're
they are great guys.
I mean, you write paragraphs about me every day.
Every day. I've seen your paragraphs on
me, so that's a lot of energy.
I don't know, bro. I can put some of
your paragraphs up if you want. You seem
to you seem to put a lot of energy into
me. I think you do.
[snorts] It's good, you know. It's good
Monty's not on here, you know. He
doesn't need to be on here. He should
have got off ages ago to be fair. I
shouldn't even be on here, you know.
Like I shouldn't.
I hope he doesn't come back to be
honest. He shouldn't come back, you
know. [snorts and laughter] Should go
and get his I think it's something to do
with the kids, you know. That's why he's
not on here because it's going to
jeopardize the court case. I think
that's why he's not on here.
And hopefully he stays off here. To be
honest, he needs to stay off here, bro.
For multiple different reasons.
He needs to stay off here, bro.
You know, I mean, I've got another
channel where I put my content on. I put
all my content on my new channel, my
approaches and [ __ ]
cuz these people on here, they're just haters, man. Straight haters.
Can't believe that [ __ ] trying to scam me. Jeez.
That is cheeky, bro. Very, very cheeky.
Yeah, this escort tried scamming me. Steven Howard.
[sighs and snorts] Uh
oh, some escort that I've met three
times. He's trying to scam me, bro. Not
the Not the Chinese one. The other one. Yeah. scammer.
Why do you try to scam someone you've
met three times?
They tried it in a [ __ ] brothel once
in it. I said, "If you don't give my
money back, I'm going to [ __ ] do your
windows in." They soon gave my money
back. Yeah, that's even that's not a
walk in the park. Even if you want to use escorts. Um,
even that's no walk in the park. That
can be quite
toxic to be honest.
They thought they were going to scam me,
bro. I want I want [ __ ] about. I
said, "Give my money back. I'm going to
do the windows in.
There was a big There was a big window
like but I said half my money back cuz
you still [ __ ] out." I said, "No, give
give the full what it give half the
money back. Not the whole money back cuz
obviously but they were trying to scam
me in it. We we agreed on a deal." Yeah.
And then [snorts]
you're trying to scam me. Really?
[ __ ] off, man.
No, not that one, bro. Some No, no, no.
I don't talk to her anymore. She deleted
me on Snapchat.
I don't talk to her anymore.
She never tried to scam me. She was all right, bro.
I used to just give her 150. She used to
travel from far. So,
she traveled from far. So, >> [snorts]
>> I didn't mind. [sighs]
No, not that one.
I'd never be seeing Chinese Izzy anymore
because I'm not going to Blackpool and
I'll probably never go to Manchester
again either. So,
that's where she stays.
Joseph Ferrar, stop it. It's boring now,
kid. It's not going to work. Stop this. Stop it.
Any football bets tonight? No, there's
not many teams playing to be fair.
No, there's not many teams playing.
Stop it, Joe. You're obsessed. Just just
stop it. Just just stop it.
Just just just stop it. [snorts] So, yeah.
I've got one more number, you know, from
when I went out with my sister and they
said that they couldn't meet because
they were looking after their daughter.
And this was obviously in December. So,
I might message them like I do, you
know, and and see if they want to come
out and that. But obviously, if they
don't come out, I will not be trying again.
I will be doing I'll be doing no
approaches. I'll be doing none of that
stuff. So, unless somebody actually
wants to meet someone I find on the
internet or someone I've already
approached, I'm not doing it. No. No, no, lad.
Yeah, he's definitely definitely 22 stone.
I've [snorts] got a question though. How
come when all
you haters on here get exposed, you
always seem to be fat and ugly?
Can I ask that? Um,
why is it you always seem to be fatter
and uglier than me? when your looks get out there.
I just find that very very strange for
people that claim they're not jealous.
Just just just throwing that out there. You know,
you sit here and you constantly critique
people and you can do it for up to a
year or two years and then when one of
you get exposed, you always seem to be
fat and ugly.
Does that not tell you something about yourselves?
Bomb Pat Gray Cat
seems very strange, doesn't it? Do you not think?
You always seem [snorts] to be older,
fatter, and uglier.
You sure you're not jealous a little bit? You sure?
I mean, at the end of the day, you can
still look good at 45. You can still
look good at 50. I mean, there's people
that are 45 that still look good, but
none of you do. So, I mean, if you
looked after yourselves, you would have
still looked good at your age, actually.
So, actually, no, you can't even use
that because there's people that are in
their 40s that actually look good.
So, if you actually look after yourself,
you will still look good for a very,
very, very long time.
So that's actually bollocks. What you're saying there, you know,
[snorts] chanc you people was always
ugly to be fair.
You know, there's people that are
[ __ ] 50 that still look good.
It's an old photo, bro. It's an old old
old old photo. [snorts]
So, if [snorts] this person meets,
they're a single mom. But that's that's
not that bad. How old is she? 26.
Yeah. But if not, then Yeah. I can't
justify trying again. Sorry, Joseph Ferrar.
Sorry, Joseph. I can't justify it again.
I I literally can't bring myself to try
again. I got no desire to try again, sadly.
[snorts] Yeah. And I'm holding on to the
resentment as well. It's very hard to
let go of,
which it was going to happen anyways,
you know. It was it was always going to happen.
I'm so stubborn now. I can't even let it
go like I used to before, which is which
should be uh which um
which is normal. Which is normal.
The sh experience I've had is normal.
Definitely definitely definitely definitely normal.
So [ __ ] knows.
I think I've got like bipolar, bro. It
seems as if I've got bipolar or
something. You know,
one minute you're right and then you
think of your bad experiences again and
then you get [ __ ] you go mad again.
It's weird, bro. Like, it's kind of like bipolar.
I don't have anxiety, but I think it's
[ __ ] bipolar or some [ __ ] I don't know.
And you got Escorts trying to bloody
scam you. What the [ __ ]
Yeah, pretty much. Yeah.
I just can't bring myself to try. I
can't let go of the resentment to even
want to try again, Dusty.
I literally can't let it go, you know?
I'm not depressed. I still go and do
stuff. I still [ __ ] eat. I still
brush my teeth, bro. Like I [ __ ]
still do [ __ ] but I can't let it go,
bro. Until I'm proven different. If
until I'm proven wrong, I can't.
Yeah, like PDF. Yeah, something like
that. Something like that. Oh, I got
guess how many thumbs up I got. Uh, Joseph.
Yeah, pretty much. Yeah.
Hey, I got so many thumbs up on this. Yeah,
cuz [snorts] they know what I'm saying
is right. Can you hear me? So, this
woman, this guy was like, "Oh, so you
have a baby and then you try to look for
a good father figure. Aren't you spent
to Aren't you supposed to look for the
good father figure before having a
baby?" Then this woman was like naive.
Things happen that's out of out of your
control. Some women get played, lied to,
etc. That's not always straightforward,
I'm afraid. She got eight thumbs up. I
wrote, "Nah, women always choose
[ __ ] They they ain't interested in
nice guys." And I got 57 thumbs up
because there's no coincidence that
these women are just ending
[clears throat] up with these bad
narcissistic men. There's no there's no
there's no coincidence.
There's no coincidence, bro. Cuz you
could you could go out right now and try
and meet someone and you wouldn't get
anywhere. You could be nice and you
wouldn't. So what they're saying, oh
they act nice at first. Oh, these men
act. No, it's [ __ ] because then
there would be no one struggling then.
If if that there would be no one
struggling. There's no way that they
just end up with
with these [ __ ] men all the time.
There's no way. I'm sorry. There's no
And one and I got 57 thumbs up. And this
is on Instagram.
I follow a lot of reals. Then and this
guy what this guy said made sense as
well. Where was it? Um,
one sec. One sec. One sec. Wait, what
did he write? Hold on.
No, no, no. One sec. One sec.
Basically, he was saying that um they
know the men's behavior before getting
with them. basically.
So, yeah, but they're not going for nice
men. They're not going for nice guys.
Cuz you'll get women that say, "Oh,
you're nice." No, no, no, no, no. And
then make up excuses not to get with you
cuz they don't want normal nice people.
They want [ __ ] [snorts]
They want drug dealers. They want
scumbags. That's the kind of women that
people That's the kind of people women
want. And then they moan about it and
then complain about it.
They go for them kinds of men and they
complain about it. Doesn't make sense.
Because if they're really going for nice
people or what they think is nice,
you would be getting dates. You would be
getting dates. If they re Listen, how
many women have said to me, "Oh, you're
nice, but I'm not looking for anyone at
the moment." So, by their logic, then
you would be getting dates then.
You would be getting dates if they're
really going for these nice people at
first. It's [ __ ] It's bollocks. And
if you are going to go for them people,
continue going for them people. But
don't moan about it.
Nope. It's not the kind of men my
sister's gone for. It's it's it's loads
and loads of different people, you know.
They always seem to end up with these [ __ ] people
regardless of their skin color. They
always end up with these [ __ ] And
then the nice guys that are decent
looking don't get nothing dusty. And
then have you ever heard about that nice
guy thing, Dusty? Have you ever heard
the term nice guy? Do you know Do you
know where that come from?
Do you know what that means when people
say, "Oh, you're not a nice guy, are
you?" Have you I'm sure you've heard of
that um term before.
Basically, what it is is that when you
How do I explain it? uh when you talk
the truth, right, they will think of
something to take their accountability
away from women. So like for example,
when a woman does something shitty, oh,
they don't owe you anything. Or when you
point um out that you know, women go for
[ __ ] and they don't want normal
nice guys. Oh, oh, well, what are you a
nice guy? Are you um trying to make it
seem like you're the problem? They they
will do anything to take away accountability.
Um, no. And and that's why they they say
all of these things about people don't
owe you [ __ ] I said, "Well, what about
what about them when people lead you
on?" It's easy for them to say that cuz
it sounds good. But they're not in your
position. They wouldn't be saying that
if they were in your position,
you know, you've tried and [ __ ] and and
and and you've tried more than anyone in
the world. They wouldn't be saying that [ __ ]
They would not be saying that [ __ ] So,
it's easy for them to sit there and say
that people that don't try or women that
get people or women that get sex, it's
easy for them to say that cuz it sounds
good. You know what I mean, Dusty? It sounds good. You know,
and yeah, cuz it sounds good them saying that.
But how would women be like if they
couldn't get sex and dates? How would
they be like? They'd be moaning. They'd
be complaining. We know they would be.
So, and if they never if they don't get
sex and they don't want anyone, that's
their choice. That's not because they
can't get it. Do you understand? So,
they don't I don't think there's enough
um I don't think there's enough sympathy
for men struggling nowadays. I don't
think it's talked about enough, you
know? I think it's well out of order. I
think it I think it's out of order, me,
bro. A lot of it is. I think a lot of it
is out of order.
Um, it's bad. It's a bad generation to
live in to be fair.
The fact that they can get dates and sex
and then complain and then be depressed.
Well, then how do you think a man would feel then?
Like, I don't know, bro. I hope it makes
sense what I'm saying, but it's it just
you would understand what I mean.
I've had to go out. I've had to deal
with so I'm surprised I've not ended up
in prison. The amount of [ __ ] I've had
to deal with, no one gives a [ __ ] They
just tell you, "Oh, go [snorts] out
again and try again." And that's going
to solve the problem. Is it? No. Is that
going to solve the problem?
No, it isn't, bro. It isn't.
I wouldn't mind if you were getting
dates or you was meeting people that
were normal. I wouldn't mind. I
generally wouldn't mind. And I'd be
like, "Oh, well, okay. You haven't found
someone yet, but that is not I haven't
had a date since April. It's not normal,
bro. I've tried to put the conversations
out there and my friend, this guy I
speak to in Belgium. He said, "Oh, you
should come back to Belgium."
He said, "It should be easier there."
But obviously I haven't. Yeah.
I was talking to Yeah, I speak to some
black guy in Belgium. He's cool, man. Mad, [snorts]
I don't know what you can say or do, but they
they do go for
they do go for these scumbag guys. I
don't know why they go for them, but they do.
I'm I'm surprised when I was speaking to
this woman yesterday, Joe. I was I was expecting excuses.
You're too young for me. We live too far
away. Cuz you know, you're always
expecting [ __ ] with these people.
But there was none of that.
And they also didn't change the next
day, which is what normally happens. They switch. Well,
they switch. It's more like they're fake
and they can't keep it up for um
you know too long. I guess
it's bad. You know that
she's more mature brother. I had a 45
year old three weeks ago and she was 45
and she was doing the same immature
[ __ ] So they don't get mature with age.
She just seems to be a different breed.
What? She's mature. Not cuz she's 45.
She might be mature, but that's not cuz she's 45.
Cuz there's 45 women that do the same
thing. Trust me. I spoke to one 3 weeks
ago before Christmas
and she was doing exactly the same thing.
So, she might be mature, but it's not
because of her age. Yeah, but I just
assume that you would have thought um
like Yeah, they're just Yeah, I don't know, bro.
[sighs and gasps]
I reckon I'd have more like in Belgium,
to be honest. There's more people that
look like me there. Maybe I'll go back
to Belgium. I don't know.
I never tried to date. I done one cold
approach when I was in Belgium, but I
never tried to date when I went overseas
cuz I wasn't there for that.
I never tried. I didn't even use the
dating apps. I should have used the
dating apps to be honest just to to
compare if I got any more m like if I
got any matches. But
yeah, it would have been a good like
little um experiment, you know, just to
jump on a date night. But I didn't want
to go [ __ ] approaching when I'm, you know,
when I'm on holiday.
So I never tried. I like I said on one
approach. The result was good. good. I
done one approach in Belgium and it was
actually good, you know. I got a
Snapchat and that and yeah, and she paid
for my and she paid for my taxi
and that was only one approach I did. So
I thought h what's the chances that
would ever happen in London where you
approach someone, they pay for your taxi
and you get their Snapchat and you've approached someone.
That would never [ __ ] happen, mate.
you. They wouldn't even ask. They
wouldn't even give you directions. If
you ask someone for directions, they
wouldn't even give you directions.
They're [ __ ] [ __ ] And I know
that from when I used to work. So,
don't know, man. Might have to go back and try. Yeah. [snorts]
This guy in Belgium said, "If it was
anyone else thinking of going to
Thailand, I'd think they were a loser
and they're taking a coward's way out.
But you, I could understand it after me
showing him all the stuff I tried and
the experiences and that." He said, "No,
if you do it, that's that's that's understandable."
But he says like anyone else that hasn't
tried as much, he would just look down
on them. But he said, "Oh, well, this is
pissing me off, man.
This is pissing me off." He said just
reading this [ __ ] [gasps]
Why don't you go somewhere you've never
been before, Joe?
What? Why don't you go on holiday
somewhere you've never been before
the world of good [snorts]
you grievy? Why don't you travel
somewhere you've not been before? Well,
to be fair, you ain't been many places,
have you, poor [ __ ]
Have you, Grezy, you poor [ __ ]
always had it in your mind but never
quite did it. Poor [ __ ]
No, Grezy. You should really do
something though, while while you're,
you know, whilst you're still young, you
know, like just go to Scotland or
something. It'll do you the world of
good, poor [ __ ]
You should try, Greasy. Like, it'll do
the world of good, honestly.
I've done so much in my life. I don't
even feel like I'm missing out.
That's why I feel like my problem is
where I've done so much in my life. I
don't feel like I'm missing out. Dusty,
I'll go to JD. I'll see these new
garments and I'm like, it wouldn't even
make me happy buying it. It wouldn't
even make me happy buying it, bro.
Obviously, the jeans and trainers, I
needed jeans and the trainers, and I
like, yeah, I could buy it, bro. But
it's not going to I don't know, bro.
I've had it done it. I had it done it
worn on a t-shirt, bro. You just don't understand.
You know what I mean?
Do you know what I'm saying? Like, I
don't know how to explain it. I've done
so much in so many different ways, you
know, in the past four years. I don't
even feel like I'm missing out on anything. you know,
and clothes. I don't really care about
clothes anymore, bro.
I don't know, man.
I got my roof at the bear trousers and I
got my shoes and I got my blazer um
dusty. I'd rather go out spending £200
having a good time. You understand?
Like rather than buy [ __ ] clothes. I
don't know, man. It's weird. I think
your priorities change as you get older. [ __ ] knows.
You know what I'm saying though?
But if I need trainers and I need jeans,
I wouldn't wear cheap stuff.
Does that make sense? I don't wear cheap
stuff like Joseph Ferrar
and his little 30 jeans.
These little 30se little 30 pound jeans, eh? [snorts]
Yeah, I've got the dentist tomorrow, Grezy.
I'll video it if you want, Captain.
I'll video it for you if you want, Captain.
I just wanted to talk to Greley.
That's what, [ __ ]
Well, you must be the same then because
you're on here with us.
You're on here with us, lad.
You're on here with us. So, you must be similar.
Give me a little nugget.
You [snorts] also want to Ah, [sighs]
wear 200 lb jeans whilst you're with a
brass out when she me and tell her
this. I can't believe she tried to scam your belly. [sighs]
So what? You're just going to stay in
your whole life, Grezy?
You're just going to stay in your whole
life and not do anything. Really, bro? [snorts]
So, how are you going to [ __ ]
How are you going to meet anyone?
We're talking about you now. We're not
talking about me. I'm not going to I'm
not going to talk about my experiences
because I don't want to demotivate you.
So, how you going to meet someone, lad?
I can prove that you're not better than
me, bro. [snorts] Join the hangouts and
show your face. Until you do that,
you'll never prove you're better than
me. But yeah, Grezy, how are you going to um
how are you going to meet someone if
you're if you're staying in all the time?
Yeah, I woke up today with a [ __ ] ear ache.
This woman blocked me, then she
unblocked me, and then she started following me. It's weird. Which one?
The one with the bounces. I've seen
every one of these videos, man.
But yeah, I know why Timmy defends me
now. And he should defend me cuz I used
to defend him. You know that whole L J
thing about me talking about his kids?
That was all because of Timmy. You know
that? I used to back Timmy up with uh
Pat Mustard and stuff. So that's why I
think he backs me up.
Yeah, I saw that, bro. That's old.
That's why I think he backed me up to be fair. [snorts] Yeah, Timmy.
That's why he backs me up with those legs.
I used to I put myself through a lot,
you know, backing up that Timmy cuz I
thought that we were bullying him. I
used to back him up, you know, with Pat
Mustard and LJ.
That's why I said stuff about LJ's kids.
It was actually because of Timmy cuz I
wanted to see if he was fast enough to
come for me. And he wasn't. He still
come, but he wasn't fast enough to come
for me. But yeah, I I actually got into
a lot of [ __ ] you know, because of
Timmy, you know
We're Oh, virgins. Oh, really?
I'm a virgin. That's nice to know, Dad. Yeah. Um,
yeah. Did you see his win? Did you see
LJ's win? What did he get?£1,200. Yeah, man.
[ __ ] it hard to win them bloody football bets. Nothing. No,
just was talking to my friend earlier
and an escort tried scamming me. Yeah.
But yeah, I'll [ __ ] that 45year-old.
If she comes to London, I'll do it cuz
her husband doesn't give her sex. Joe,
isn't it? It would be rude not to.
See, this is where this is where we're
not uh men are not selfish like women.
We can see someone struggling, Greavesy.
We can see that their uh their husband
is not giving them sex when they're
supposed to. Um
and um yeah, and we're obviously willing
to help out whereas they wouldn't help anyone out,
you know. They wouldn't help anyone out out.
There was loads of goals you would have
won if you put a bet on. Well, I don't
know. I did a bet. I don't know. I don't
know. Uh three both score, no draw, and
I got two out of three. One was 3-2, one
was 2-1, and the other one was 1 nil. So
I almost got it kind of almost.
The thing is with both teams has got you
got a lump on it.
You've got a lump.
You got a lump on them. [ __ ]
£250 off 20 pound.
So if I put £80 on just two teams, it
would have been like 600. But I would
have just done it both teams to score.
But you on the both teams to score,
you've got to lump money on it. And
obviously you're risking a load of
money. That's the thing. But it would
have been 250 off 20.
It was almost almost
I mean the fact that I got [ __ ] two.
The fact that I got two
was quite good. You know, even two is
quite hard. Like, but I've been studying
them and that, but that game just
weren't having it at all, man.
The thing I don't like about both scores
is it can easily [ __ ] you up.
It can easily [ __ ] you up in the last
minute, Joe. It can easily [ __ ] you up
and it has done before. Like say it's
3-2, they get a penalty right before the
game ends and then it [ __ ] it. And then
what happens is you think, "Oh, I wish I
just done the both teams to score instead."
But I noticed that whenever you try to
do three teams, it never works. Whether
it's to win or whatever it is, you can
never get three.
More than two, you just never seem to be
able to get it. That's why I normally
stick to two.
Yeah, you get them up a lot. You get
them up a lot if you do the Southern If
you do the South National League, you
get them up a lot of the time even in
the first half.
But obviously you can lose a lot of
money. But if if it doesn't win, that's
the thing. But if you do a both score no draw,
it's gutting when it when it when
there's a penalty in the last [ __ ]
You know, if they both score, they both
scored. There's no it can't [ __ ] you up.
It's the end.
Um, so they both scored, but obviously
if it's a both score, no draw, you can
get [ __ ] the last minute or last second even
and then you just wish that you done.
But yeah, even if you put 80 on a double
both score, no draw. I'm sure it's like 600 pound.
I'm sure it is.
I've done a lot of both both teams
score. I won a lot.
[sighs and snorts] >> [sighs]
>> Yeah, I found a new online casino, Joseph Ferrar,
but I don't want to get into that [ __ ] again.
No, I don't want to be getting into that
[ __ ] again, matey. No, [ __ ] that.
Just give it a little while. Oh, I don't
actually know if it's fees, but I'm
assuming it is cuz to get your winnings,
you need to enter an eyeband. So, I'm
guessing it is fees.
It's okay. Well, it's not okay if you
want to deposit like if they take a
small like with Golden Bet they used to
take a small fee, but that wasn't as bad
because it was only winnings, but they
they shouldn't charge it when you deposit.
They shouldn't charge it to deposit, you know.
That's bad because obviously if you win
and they take a very small amount then
it's like me.
But I I deposited £200 and I lost £217.
£17 is a big that's a lot of money just
to for ape it's not even like it was two pound
but golden bet used to take a little fee
a tiny fee so obviously I didn't mind it
but that was withdrawals that wasn't
deposits it was withdrawals
yeah that was withdrawals
Do you remember Joe? Do you remember
Joe? I like shovel cole. [laughter] Do
you remember when you randomly wrote
that? I was thinking about that today.
Oh, not [ __ ] you. Not you. You little copycat. [snorts]
Yeah, but that was a withdraw. It's not
as bad when it's a withdraw.
Yeah, but that's withdraw. Oh, but Oh,
ATM. Oh, okay. Okay. That's bad to be
fair. Oh. Oh, yeah. Yeah. I'm thinking
of a nine. Yeah, that's bad to be honest.
That is pretty bad.
What? 30? Why?
That's disgusting. What the [ __ ]
But online they shouldn't be charging Yeah.
Oh, bless you then.
Bless you in life,
[snorts] Joseph. Bless you. Yeah,
I know about motor casinos, bro. I
already knew about them.
I already knew about them from um back
in the day. You know them um you know
them sites like Royal Panda and that
they're all uh they're all casinos in
Malta. I already knew about the casinos
in Ma, bro, from online.
They have them in Lapia as well. A lot
of the dealers were British, but they
were in Malta.
I already knew about the M the casinos
in Malta, bro. that's been going for years.
I knew about it from online back in the
day. And my sister's been to Malta as well.
My sister's been to a lot of countries,
[sighs and gasps]
one of them. And she's been to Malta.
It's not a bad destination in the
summer. I suppose I I suppose
in the summer I suppose.
[sighs and gasps] Yeah, probably. Yeah.
I like sh dusty
Joe's birthdays in November everyone. I know that
your birthday's in November. Yeah,
you poor [ __ ] I missed that account.
You know, Greavvesy, you can't deprive
You can't deprive Greavvesy.
You poor [ __ ] Yeah, I'm a Scorpio, too.
Yeah, I'm a Scorpio.
You poor [ __ ]
I don't want to deprive Grezy of
content. So, it puts me in a bit of a
hard position to leave YouTube.
I don't want to leave Greasy without
content, poor [ __ ]
You know, he's been he's been [snorts]
good to me, you know, [ __ ]
Greasy, do you remember that comment?
Do you remember?
No, it wasn't Dusty. It wasn't Dusty. It
was one It's one of them accounts that
comes and mocks me and says, "Oh, you
can't let these [ __ ] women win." Nah,
it's the same person every time. It's not Dusty.
It's not Dusty, bro. It's someone
they've made so many different accounts.
It's like there when I and it comes when
I do approaches. I done some approach I
done an approaching video. Yeah.
And uh Greavesy it was like oh but
people on Reddit say you can get sex
whenever you want. There's nothing Peter
Belly can do to change these [ __ ]
situ. I don't know who it is bro. I
don't know who it is but it's the same
person under them accounts. [snorts]
There's nothing Peter Benny can do to
change. He's [ __ ] in Sid show. And [laughter]
Greasy, do you remember? Do you remember
when an account used to come in and
said, "Uh, them [ __ ] were laughing at us. [laughter]
Them [ __ ] were laughing at us." Do you
[clears throat] remember? They were
ladies are miserable old sod. [laughter]
They said that ladies said that we're
going to meet someone.
Laney said we was gonna meet someone.
Yeah. And they said, "Lany's a miserable outside." [laughter]
I said to Laney, "You're a miserable old fucker." [snorts] Yeah.
Yeah. You lead content.
I don't know. I just call her Laney.
I like calling her Laney.
[sighs and snorts]
I like Sher Co.
You're gay if you don't like Sher Co.
So, why do you like LJ? Anyways, Joe, [sighs]
I'll do a football on Saturday.
I only bet on the National League.
The normal leagues are hard to even get
both teams to score on. They're hard.
Yeah, they're hard, you know.
I only like the National League South. [snorts]
>> Yeah. [ __ ] hell, bro.
He ain't got a personality. He's a [ __ ] repeater.
He's a repeater
and he's a pretend.
He's a repeater and he's a pretend. Ant-Man
doesn't come on this community anymore.
No, I don't I don't go on um I don't go on Lavies.
I don't go on Lav Steven Howard because
it's the same faces.
Yeah. Own me by what? Repeating the same
[ __ ] every day for seven years. You
don't owe Peter Benny, mate. That's why
I don't go on it, bro. Cuz it's just
repeating, is it? Like the same
repeating people. They say the same comments.
That's why I don't go on it. Because
it's the same faces,
same repeating people. Yeah.
No, his channel's dead, bro. It's dead
because it's just the same [ __ ] on there. No.
They don't own me, bro. They talk about themselves.
If any of them people typing actually
put their cameras on, it would show you
what they all are.
It would show you what they all are. If
they actually put their cameras on Yeah.
and spoke, it would show what they all
are. That's why they don't bother me,
cuz I just know they're just life's
losers. Middle fat slobs. That's why
they don't get to me.
We know what they are, bro. So nothing
they say bothers me
at all cuz deep down they're just
talking about themselves and they know
it. So yeah. [snorts]
Why don't you go to Australia, Joe?
Why don't you go to Australia?
should go to Australia this year.
Do a world of good.
So, who here likes LT now? Anyways,
LTS are right in small doses. I still
don't agree with everything, but it
would be boring if everyone agreed on everything.
Taylor. And I'm not trying to get people
to start on him either because he's not
going to start on random accounts. I
just want to know everyone's opinion.
No, he's not going to start on random
accounts. Duh. But yeah, no, bro.
It's essentially British.
Yeah, that's where um Nonsex's dad went
to when he was caught being a nons.
Yeah, when he was caught being a nons.
He's got a very very dark past.
Yeah, he's got a very very very dark past.
every dark ass father does.
Then you went to [ __ ] Australia. The
coward. That is so cowardly, you know.
So cowardly. Honestly, it is. Yeah.
No, I don't think he's a s over the USA
thing. I don't think he was singing, but
it's weird how he we don't hear him for
months and then when I go out a woman, he's there.
Maybe it was a coincidence,
maybe it was a coincidence.
Doubt it though.
I don't know, bro. What's the ch? I don't know.
Do you remember when he said, "I'll
light up your battleship." [laughter]
That was joke. He said, "I'll light up your battleship." >> [laughter]
>> Oh man, that was funny as [ __ ] I've
never heard that before. Yeah, curry
goat. It's a Jamaican dish.
It's normal. I've never had it, but
I don't talk to him. I don't like him. I
I don't [ __ ] I don't like him. I
don't talk to him.
I don't talk to mate here. Uh
LJ was scared of LT though. Joe, you
know that. You know that for a fact.
That's one thing we could all agree on
that LJ was definitely definitely scared
of LT. I'm not even trying to start
[ __ ] I don't really want anyone
starting, but I'm saying he was
definitely scared of LT. See, with LJ J,
he's an opportunist. He might act like
the big hard man, but he's not the big
hard man. He is definitely definitely
definitely an opportunist.
He's definitely definitely an
opportunist. He knew that he could never
meet LT. And I don't I don't talk to the
guy. I'm not even lick I'm not even like
licking ass. That's actually been
proven, bro. I'm not even trying to start anything.
But yeah, he is definitely he's
definitely scared of LT. He is.
Yeah, he definitely is, man. When that
[ __ ] was going on. Yeah.
Even he was even kind of wary of me to
be honest with you. I mean, yeah, he
come on the door, but bro, do you know
the amount of [ __ ] I had to say to get
him on that door? All Timmy had to do
was laugh at something.
So, he is Yeah, he's an opportunist with
who he meets. Uh, that large.
Definitely. He would never meet someone
that will give him a challenge.
Trust me, you will never meet anyone
He knows you'd get his ass whooped. Why
do you think he didn't go live in
London? Why do you think he went Sunday
8:00 in the morning? He knew, bro. He knew.
He actually He actually knew, bro. And
he had beef with LT around that time as well.
I've never had go. Yeah.
Yeah, man. So, Timmy's actually the root
cause of a lot of this [ __ ] you know,
on this community.
Yeah, Timmy's actually the root cause
for a lot of it.
I am. And also Timmy,
if you think about it. Yeah. >> [snorts]
>> I don't need to get one alone, lad, cuz
I'm not skin. So, and them skin comments
don't bother me, bro. They're just
That's just self-projecting comments.
Yeah, I got into this community cuz of Timmy.
I got introduced to Gamblin and I
watched Timmyy's video. That's how I got
into this [ __ ] This shitty community, bro.
You need to stop that skin thing, bro.
It's really boring, man. No.
But no, I've never had goat. Curry goat. No,
never had that. I've had lobster. Have
you ever had lobster, Joe?
That might be a life experience I have
that you don't. Have you ever had Have
you ever had lobster?
Okay. I don't have a coat. Oh, okay. So,
um, you ever had lobster, Joseph?
I've had lobster. Yeah, I've had
lobster. Laney hasn't, but I have.
Nope. He was before my time.
Yeah, I [snorts] have had lobster.
It just tastes like fish kind of. It
tastes like sort of like fish.
I don't like that you have to break the
[ __ ] shell open to be able to eat it.
But you know,
it was okay. But
yeah, he doesn't have five houses.
That's his little lie.
Someone that has five houses wouldn't be
begging for money on YouTube.
But and this actually has six houses he
says he has, not five. Doesn't add up.
He stories doesn't add up.
But he's just a shame to admit that he's
on benefits. That's all it is.
cuz to him to to him that's like oh uh
I'm looking weak. I'm looking weak. I'm
looking weak. So I'm I'm looking not
like I'm better than everyone. So that's
why he says that he owns six properties
when in reality he's just on benefits
just like most of the people on here. [snorts] So
but he would never admit that. He will
come on here saying, "No, I own property.
You know, I get money." And it's all
lies. And I don't care. It's just all
Um because it's obvious, you know, that's that.
Yeah. I watched Timmy's video. Why is he
asking me to show him [ __ ] Why is he
asking me to show £1,000, bro? What the [ __ ]
What would I get Steven Howard from
showing Timmy £1,000?
I played this game with him last [ __ ]
February and I showed him [ __ ] £1,400
in cash multiple times and he just kept
[ __ ] he just ran away.
He says he says show him £1,000. What
the [ __ ] bro?
You want to see £1,000?
Oh my god, bro.
And I pulled out £1,000 and then what?
You still talk [ __ ]
I've got more than £1,000, matey.
But yeah, I don't know who started all
of that [ __ ] Show money, show money,
show money. I don't know who started all of that.
I don't know why they do it.
I don't need to film the balance. I
don't need to prove myself to anyone on here.
I don't need to prove myself to anyone
on here, matey.
Not [clears throat] at all. So, yeah.
Nope. I'm not showing no money. Never again.
Never ever ever ever again.
Not £5, not£10, not 20 pound, not
nothing. Never again.
And what makes me laugh is that you can
say that I'm skint, but that's
impossible because even if I done my
balls in, I still get money every week.
So I could never ever be skint.
I could never ever ever be
[clears throat] skinned because if I
done my balls in right now, yeah, I'd
still get money every week.
So, it would never happen. It could
never ever ever happen.
Never. Literally never.
So, that's that.
Yeah. Okay. I didn't have the train fair.
Yeah, man. That's that's uh really
Nope. I'm not doing no cold approaches, lad.
I'm done with all that [ __ ]
Unless I find someone online that proves
they're different. Joseph, that's me done. No.
I start I want to be uh
Oh, you remember that? That's B's account. [sighs]
Bum's account, man.
I just went to get some food earlier. Yeah.
But yeah, someone's willing to prove they're different.
If someone's willing to prove that
they're different. I'm not depressed.
I'm not depressed at all, bro. I'm fine.
I'm just tired. Yeah, I ate earlier. If
someone proves that they're different,
uh, Joseph Ferrar,
did it heal by itself? No,
I just started brushing my my teeth
three times a day and just reducing
sugar and it went away. But I'm still
I'm still going dentist tomorrow anyways
cuz I can't miss any appointments.
No, I brush my teeth three times a day
with electric toothbrush and just cut
down on Coke, which I seem to be and
sugar and that seem to have worked. It
seems to be getting I still I'm still
drinking a lot of Coke lately. So, I
need to stop.
But yeah, that that electric toothbrush
comes in a hand.
It was bad, bro. That cavity over
Christmas. It was really bad.
I tell you what's also bad is a is a ear ache.
Yeah, I do get free dental um care and I
don't want to I don't want to miss an
appointment because it's so hard to get
an appointment and if you keep missing
your appointments, they won't give you
any. And trust me, it's hard to get a
dentist appointment, you know? So, I'm
not I'm not wasting it, bro. [ __ ] that.
That's what I I don't understand with
people like Belly and [ __ ] certain
people that you know like nonsicks. They
actually get free dental care. Yeah. And
they don't even go to the dentist. What the [ __ ]
And they got [ __ ] up. Like I don't
understand that, bro. That's madness.
Nah, bro. But your mom will.
I know what caused my cavity anyway.
Sugar and that, but you know how hard it
is to quit sugar.
It's very, very hard to quit sugar.
Very, very, very, very hard. And that's
the thing that [ __ ] your teeth up.
Yeah. It's not nice to have a teammate.
Yeah, some people don't get him if they
just drink water and that. But I can't
just drink water, bro. [ __ ] that. I
can't just drink water.
There's no way I could just drink water.
No way. Don't know about you. Nah.
And also my diet is [ __ ] as well, so I
know what caused mine.
But I might just get a fill in tomorrow
anyways just in case. Who knows?
Are you sure they've got dentists in
Belgium? Triple H. Do you remember that
conversation earlier? He was like,
obviously in it.
I said to you, do you do they have do
they have do they have do they have
dentists in Belgium?
What do you think, Joe?
No, they might not in it.
Nah, maybe not.
Nah, no. Waxies is a cockfest, Dusty.
You need to go at the right time. It can
be a cockfest. So, like Sundays are
good. That's why I met Finnish Izzy in
um in Waxies and I sent her a picture of my dick.
Yeah, you need to go to Waxies at the
right time though, like a Thursday or a
Sunday. Otherwise, it's just a cockfest.
New Year's Eve, it was just going to be
a cockfest. I was going to go New Year's
Eve, but it's just a cockfest, bro. March, April, Thursdays.
You're laughing, mate.
Yeah, it's a cockfest. I don't want it
to be, you know. That's why Yeah.
What's in waxies then, Dusty?
Yeah. I go to Waxies for the roast dinner.
Yeah, I go to waxies. I said to I said
to LT, "Me, you, Terry, and Mark should
all meet up and go on the piss.
Me, Terry, Arsenal, Mark,
you know, LJ." [laughter]
He said, "You need to grow up." I said, "Nah,
we should all go and meet up in it. Get
on the piss,
you know, like a reunion." Yeah.
What do you think? H [laughter]
what what do you think? Huh?
Oh, I saw that Arsenal Mark's back by
the way. I saw him. Um
I don't know who who was he on. I I
don't think he was Jay. He was on
someone's the other day.
Take Jimmy Eldridge. [laughter]
Now, me and Monty had a good night out in Birmingham.
Yeah. Do you remember when I met Monty
went to [laughter] It was a good night
out, isn't it? Yeah. [snorts]
Waxies. Yeah. [laughter]
When I've done approaches in Maxis, they
said they've got boyfriends. Dusty, when
I approached in Maxis,
what did she say? This escort said,
"Tomorrow, if you want, let me know. We
can stay for just an hour. Pick up at seven sisters."
Yeah, I'm just going to make her go and [ __ ] like shovel. [laughter]
I like shovel. I can't stop saying that.
That's [ __ ] hilarious. Yeah. [snorts] [laughter] >> [snorts]
>> [ __ ] [ __ ]
I'm going to knock him out.
Do you remember Timmy? He's a [ __ ]
spaz. Do you remember that when Timmy
was like, I'm going to knock him out? He
was talking about a bond in it.
I'm going to knock him out. [laughter] [ __ ]
>> I want to bring the skin virgin, but the
[ __ ] manager doesn't want to let me
in. No virgins allowed.
Literally no virgins allowed.
No virgins allowed. That's what the
manager says. No skin virgins allowed.
Sorry mate. Can't bring the virgin.
Can't bring the virgin, mate.
Yeah, he was getting rough.
Yeah, he was getting quite rough.
Yeah, that sounds dodge. But yeah, he
was. I don't think Monty could beat me
in a fight though.
Maybe a hamster, but I don't think he
could beat me in a fight. >> [laughter]
>> Who do you reckon is going to win round
two? Steven Howard, Leo Prime.
When I go to Reddit, [snorts]
>> he said he's going to put me in
hospital. Absolutely no chance.
Absolutely no chance, mate.
No charge in Ala.
No, she doesn't work for an agency. She did before,
but she doesn't now.
Who Who do you reckon's going to win? Be prime
two and a half years later. I reckon I'll win.
I reckon this time I I'll win.
Yeah, Peter Bennett is quite strong.
He caught me off guard and I was scared.
That's what happened. He caught me off
guard and I was scared, bro. I wasn't
even prepared for that to be honest. I
weren't even prepared. Think of all the
times I've been prepared before, but I I
think I actually would win
this time, bro.
I reckon I would actually win this time.
What do you think, boss?
I reckon I would actually win two and a
half years later. Bennett is a lot bigger now, you know. Yeah.
I don't think he would win, bro.
I don't think he would win.
What do you think, Stephen?
Do you remember that prime?
[laughter] He's like, you're meeting me,
but then he's going to try and pretend
that he [ __ ] lives now. He's going to
pretend he lives in Birmingham [ __ ] [ __ ] house. >> [sighs]
>> I don't know, but I ain't weighed myself.
What do you think, Steven Howard?
Do you think he's going to beat me? [snorts]
The January bear?
What? You think he's going to beat me?
If you think he's going to beat me, you
can say, but I'm not going to block you or anything. >> [snorts]
>> I don't think he would.
Definitely don't think he would. [snorts] [sighs]
No, definitely not. [snorts] Prime.
I don't need a boxing gym, bro. [snorts]
To to be that guy. I don't I don't need
a boxing gym.
That was like [ __ ] USA is his ex. He
was getting cheeky, wasn't he?
Yeah, he was getting cheeky that USA is his ex.
Do you remember?
What is that? >> [snorts]
>> No, I just made myself a tea, Bro, with two sugars.
What the [ __ ]
Oh, he's so obsessed, bro. This LJ is so
obsessed. You tell them one thing. Yeah.
This is what they're like on here. Like,
an escort tried to scam you. They're so
They're pathetic, bro.
So, so pathetic. What the [ __ ] [laughter] So pathetic.
They're so pathetic on here, bro. Yeah,
I've just seen it.
They're so pathetic, it shows that
they've got no life, bro. They obsess
over every little detail and twist [ __ ]
It just shows that they got no life.
Why do you think he will never show
again, bro? Oh, just one guy went live.
Why do you think they'll never show again?
That's pathetic. I said that an escort
tried to scam me and they're twisting it
and making stuff up.
Proper life losers, bro. It just shows
that they got no life. They have to
bounce on everyone else's. It just goes
to show it.
It just goes to show me
Lav is obsessed. Triple H.
Lavy is obsessed. [snorts] Obsessed.
No, I think I'll go back to China. I
think I'll go back to Chinese. I think Yeah,
Chinese as he licks my ass.
There was this escort break. She licks
my ass, man.
Yeah. You're obsessed, bro. You're [ __ ] obsessed.
Peter Belly needs to quit sugar in it.
I'm going to have to learn to live
without it or cut down on it a lot.
He needs to get himself a little job.
Yeah, he needs to get himself a little
job. This this LJ, do you know what this
LJ needs to do in this [ __ ] nonslegs?
They need to get themsel a little part-time job.
Just a little part-time job. Part time
job will never hurt anyone. Never has
hurt anyone. Never will hurt anyone.
It's just a little part-time job.
Just a little part-time job. We've all
worked before. I know I have. What's
wrong with a little part-time job? You know
what's wrong with a little part-time job?
Part-time job? What's wrong with a part-time job?
Yeah, she licked my ass. I didn't ask
her to. She just did.
Yeah, she was Chinese
and then she gave me a [ __ ]
We're going for a good little piss up, Triple H.
That's what That's what this guy in
said. We're going for a good little piss
up. [sighs and gasps]
Yeah, I did like it. It felt good. She's
so lucky I had a bath, you know, before
going. Otherwise, she'd be licking a
load of [ __ ]
She would be licking a load of [ __ ]
mate, if I didn't if I didn't have a
bath and that cuz of my diet in it.
So, she's so lucky I had a bath before going
because she would have actually been licking [ __ ] You know
why does why does Nonss not talk about
Sher Co anymore? Dusty,
did he get caught out copying?
Did he get caught red-handed being a little copycat?
that why he doesn't mention it anymore.
Is it because he's a little cubby cat?
Is it cuz he's a little cubby cat, dusty?
He's gone very quiet, hasn't he? About
that that that subject. [sighs]
Oh, that LJ is a s. I'm just I'm
watching him. He's a simp.
Why did he f Why did he fancy Sho Dusty?
Oh, you know, do you know Bart Quest is
behind an account called Fiona Macdonald? Fiona Macdonald.
What an account, eh? Fiona Macdonald.
Some of these accounts, yeah, they make me laugh. Fiona McDonald's.
Yeah. Fiona Macdonald.
Fiona Macdonald. [laughter]
Uh, [snorts] well, I did bring it up to
him. Yeah. I said, "Oh, do you know what
do you think of this shovel coh?" Like,
people keep copying each other. So, I I
bought I brought up I brought [laughter]
it up to him and he was like, "Oh, yeah,
she's attractive." I said, "Oh, I don't
find her attracting me." He said, "Well,
you're gay." I said, "How can I be gay?
I just don't like her. she's not my
type. And he's like, "Bro, that's gay.
That's homo vibes. If you don't find her
attractive, you're gay." I said, "Well,
I don't find her attractive."
That's what it is with someone with
autism, bro. You can't [ __ ] meet
people like that, bro. You can't have a
different opinion than them. Yeah,
that's such a silly thing to say looking
back on it. But it was silly. It is
silly, but people just used to say it to fit in.
You know, if you if you go online,
Dusty, they all copy each other. They
all call each other gay.
They all copy each other.
So, what you're saying, Dusty, is it was
a trend back in the day then?
Are you saying it was like a trend or Triple H?
That trend's been going donkeys, mate. Yeah.
all copy each other.
That is silly though to call someone gay
for not liking someone. Jesus Christ. Yeah. Yeah. [laughter]
You can't deny she's attractive.
No, I'm not a little copycat.
Why do I wear Stone Island? Um,
cuz I can afford it
and I haven't worn Stone Island for ages.
I mean, if you can afford it, why not?
Yeah, you don't need to be a football lad.
If you've got the money, bro, spend it in it. Yeah.
Nah, Peter Belly don't copy, lad.
Peter belly don't copy. I like
that's copying though. That's That is copying.
No, she messaged me.
Oh my god, I'm sick of this boyfriend
[ __ ] man. Every time I watch these
approaches, Dusty. Yeah. It's always the
same thing. They're saying they've got a
boyfriend. I'm sick of seeing it, bro. It's annoying.
Don't they do or say anything different
ever. God, it's annoying just watching
it, bro. I'm going to I'm going to unsub
from this guy, bro. I'm going to unsub
from this guy on Instagram, bro. I'm
sick of these videos keep popping up,
these approaching videos.
Jesus Christ, lad.
Well, they're not saying it to me, lad.
So, your logic's [ __ ] They're saying
it to someone else.
They're [ __ ] [ __ ] man. I hate
seeing it. They're not saying it to me, are they?
They're saying it to this guy.
Like, it's so bad. Yeah. Triple H that
it pisses me off even seeing it happen
to other people. That's how bad it is.
Like, ch change the record. Like,
actually different. You know, you know,
the past month and a half, almost two
months, I've given up. Yeah. I've been
watching this um I've been watching this
guy approach and this other guy
approach. And I've not seen one of these
women act different at all. I've not
seen one of these women act any
different than the other. And bear in
mind, I've given up. I'm not out there
approaching. I'm just going by what I
see. And I haven't seen any of these
women say or do anything different.
That's all the proof you need to know
that they're the same. That's all I'm
saying about it.
There's so many people that do this and
it comes up on Instagram and they do and
act exactly the same way as the other one does [snorts]
cuz you know that was another thing with
nonlegs back in the day.
Oh, you don't know all women. You don't
know all women. That's what he used to
say, bro. He used to be very very defensive. Um,
Dusty, you don't know Wibby. You don't
know Wibby. I used to say that they're
[ __ ] and that in it back when I was like
17, 18. And he used to say, "You don't
know what women." And I used to say, "I
know [ __ ] more women than you, you
cunt." And that's how all of these
[ __ ] arguments um started, bro.
This is how all of these arguments started
from like different opinions and [ __ ]
Yeah. I said, "I know more women than
you, lad." And I do know more women than him.
Yeah, I know more women than you.
As immature as that sounds. Yeah.
Yeah. You know why nonslegs is obsessed,
isn't it, uh, Triple H? because I was
his only friend and he doesn't have any
friends now. Do you know that?
That's what happens. People become obsessed.
Well, I never approached, but when I did, yeah,
when I used to approach, yeah, but I
don't approach anymore.
Hoping I can meet somebody from
Instagram. If I can meet a woman on
Instagram that actually proves that they're different,
then yeah, but if not, then I won't be
approaching. I won't be doing anything, lad.
If I can meet someone on online and they
prove that they're different, then
that's a different story. But I won't be approaching. Bro,
if the weather was better,
maybe I would, bro. If the if it was but
if the weather was nice, I would
actually maybe I'd go out and drink. I'd
go out and drink. So, I probably would
approach. But I'm not going out in the cold, bro.
Maybe if it was really, really, really hot.
But I think it's just the weather that's
keeping me in to be honest, bro. I think
it's just too cold
to go out. Yeah,
but I still went I still never went out
drinking every week. Anyways, I done a
lot of Uber in the summer, bro. I was
working for Uber in the summer, Bob. It
was lovely, bro.
I saw nice areas. I went I cycled all
over London, bro. It's good, you know.
It was actually It's actually a good
thing to do. You know, you take the piss
out of the wage and that. Yeah, you take
the piss out of it. But it's actually wasn't bad.
It was tiring,
but like it was good, man. I got to see
some nice places.
It was something to [ __ ] do. People
take the piss out of it. Yeah. Oh, you
know, you you made 90 or 100 pound, you
know, in 10 hours. But, you know, it was
something to [ __ ] do.
And I got a nice tan as well. I went all
over central London. I all the areas in
London, you know. It was something to
actually do and actually come home and
then just chill, bro. Like, it was good.
It was tiring though. Like, you couldn't
do it for 10 hour. I don't know how
people do it for 10 hours, then the next
day do it for another 10 hours. [ __ ]
up, bro. And it's not it's not your legs
because it's an e it's your actual
vision that starts going after 10 hours.
Yeah. You start your vision starts
going. Does that make sense? Like your
eyes start like you cuz how tired you
are. It's not even um your whole body
feels [ __ ] Does that make sense? So
the next day you can't do it if you do 10 hours.
I remember I done like 10 hours before.
I tried to do it the next day, bro. And
nah, it weren't happening. Over time you
probably could if you got used to it, but bro,
and it's not your legs because you're on
a e pedal bike. So
no, it's good. It's a good thing to do
to be honest, bro.
And I didn't spend any of my money as well.
So I bought a TV and I earned the money
back from like the the the job.
It was good, bro. Some nice places in
London, you know, in the summer.
It was actually something to do. I was
living by myself, bro. Well, with the tenants. So yeah,
it was fun, bro. It was good.
I used to just get I had a nice time,
bro. A nice time.
Yeah, I made £88 in 9 hours.
That's better than nothing, bro. It's
better than nothing if you think about
it. What else would you be doing?
Sitting home doing nothing if you
weren't drinking. So, it's better than nothing.
I had like 160 going.
I had like money going in, bro. Yeah,
cuz he's a loser. Yeah, Dusty. But it
was better than nothing in the summer,
isn't it? Cycling around, seeing them
nice areas. It was something to do.
It was better. It's better than doing
nothing is it
like and it's not even just for the
money. It was just something to do.
What I done, Dusty, I rented bikes. I
rented a bike here in Leicester Square.
So, you rent the bike. It's an e- pedal
bike. It's not an electric bike, but
it's an e- pedal. So, it's it's
electric, but it's pedal as well. So you
pedal, but it it doesn't hurt your legs.
Like you don't wear you don't wear your
legs out, if that makes sense. So you
rent it in Nester Square and it takes you everywhere.
Everywhere, bro. Everywhere. The jobs
take you everywhere. All over London. I
went [ __ ] Shepherd's Bush. I went
[ __ ] Victoria, [ __ ] um Camden, Angel.
[ __ ] everywhere, bro. It's good. It's
good in the summer. It's something to do,
you know. Um, it was £12 a day, so
obviously in free deliveries, you make
the money back. Or you can rent it for £54. Um,
and then um
you can rent it for 54 uh and that's a week.
So, but obviously I used to do it three
times, three days a week. So you'd get
that money back. So
you laugh at it, bro. But it's still
better than nothing. It's still better
than nothing, lad. It was tiring though.
It was went Liverpool Street. The only
downside is is when the battery runs out
when you're on your way back cuz
obviously you can change the bikes. When
the battery runs out, you can just put
in the dock and then get another bike. I
remember, bro, I was coming back from
Angel. Yeah. I was halfway back to
central London from Angel and the
[ __ ] battery run out. Oh my god, bro.
You can't pedal it. You can't do nothing
when when a battery runs out, bro. It's so heavy.
It's so heavy, bro. And like it's hard.
It's hard to even pedal it. So, you want
to make sure that [ __ ] don't run out
if you're not near the near the dock.
So, um but yeah. Yeah, I made £88.
But think about it, Dusty. Say you done
that for five days, you'd make money. No,
you would make money, wouldn't you?
Think of it.
Say you done that for four days. Say you
done some cracking hours, you'd be making money.
You would still be making money. Better
than nothing, in it.
The only bad thing is is that um on
Saturdays, most Saturdays, they blocked
the the the road. Um
they blocked the road that goes, you
know, the road where you keep going down
and you you're at Westminster.
When you're at Westminster.
No, I worked three days a week and I No,
no, no. I paid £12 a day and I worked
for 3 days.
But listen bro, you know the road, you
know when you you know Trafalga Square,
you know that long road that goes to
West Minister, like the long road and
you see West Minister, you see um the
London Eye. Now on Saturdays, most of
the time they block that road. So when
they block that road, you can't work
because that's like 80% of deliveries.
like there's no point in working because
it takes you to [ __ ] uh
By it takes you to like all sorts of mad
areas. So once they take once they block
that road, you're basically [ __ ] The
only place you can work is like North
London and there's no way around it. So
I had to go home a few Saturdays because
they would block it. You understand?
It's blocking 80 90% deliveries. So
there's no point working. [snorts]
So [clears throat] sometimes I'd have to
come back and then go. You'd be very
lucky on a Saturday. I remember dusty.
Yeah. There was I was I was working on a
Saturday. Yeah. The weather was perfect.
Not too cold, not too co cold. I was
making like over10 an hour. Yeah. And
they blocked the [ __ ] [ __ ] road,
bro. And I had to come back. It was
perfect. I used to start at 10:00 and
come back at like 12:00 at night, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. I started at 10:00, worked
until 5:00, charged the phone off, and
then Yeah. charged the phone, and then
I'd come back at midnight, bro. Yeah. Simple. Done.
So, yeah. It's better than nothing, bro.
Better than nothing.
I'm actually brave to do that job, bro.
I was very brave to do that job.
The only thing I hated about that job,
Dusty. Yeah. Is when you had to deliver
it to the apartments and some of the
apartments, they all look the [ __ ]
same. You know the ones that say court
at the end of it, like blaze court,
blood court, bro. They were like, I
swear to God, bro. I went to one place
last time, bro. It took me about 15
minutes to find a [ __ ] If you got a
house in one of them jobs, you were
lucky, bro. If you if you actually went
to a house, like when I went to Angel, I
went Angel two times. Yeah. And like I
remember, yeah, there was on one
Saturday I done Angel twice. £7 back. £7
back. If you got a house, you were lucky
cuz them apartments, mate. [snorts]
Oh, and sometimes they wouldn't come
down. Sometimes the customers wouldn't
come down as well. So, cuz most of, you
know, most of the people that that
ordered the food were just Chinese students.
They were all Chinese students.
Most of them were Chinese students and
they were always apartments cuz they
were at uni. It was a [ __ ] bro. It was
a [ __ ] sometimes trying to find them.
Um, there was one I went to Kilbin and I
couldn't find it. I couldn't find it,
bro. I was looking. I couldn't find the [ __ ] Um,
so yeah, I went everywhere, bro. Everywhere.
It's good, you know, bro. It's good, you know.
But there's other apps where you'd
probably earn 150 a day, Dusty.
There's an app where you could probably
earn about 150 a day.
It's something to do, bro. I was making
money from the house and it was extra
money, is it? Like to me it was just independency.
I went to a gym, you earn your own
money. It doesn't matter what the money
was, it was still money. You understand?
It was still money where I had to I
could live off that and not I was living
off money that I was making myself. So I
didn't mind doing it, bro.
You wouldn't be doing anything else.
Think about it. And it ain't even that
bad. You just cycle around seeing new areas.
It's not supposed to be a main job,
Dusty. You know, you know, it's not
supposed to be a main job. That's
another thing. It's not supposed to be a
main job. That's why it's minimum wage.
Even though there's people that do it
for a main job. It's like, say, for
example, you wanted like you wanted
weed. Yeah. If you smoke weed or you
wanted cigarettes, that would pay for
the cigarettes, that would pay for the
weed. Do you understand what I'm saying?
Like say you wanted like or you wanted to like um
you know you know you wanted to um
you know pay for a night out you know
that's what it's it's extra money for
something. It's not supposed to be a a
main job bro but there are people that
do it as a main job but obviously you
have to put a lot of hours in but it's
not like it's not for that
and it's still money. It still added up.
I done I done three days and they
weren't proper and I made 170. Where
else are you going to get 170 from being
your own boss?
You're not, bro. So, it just depends how
you look at it.
It depends how you look at it. But the
thing is, I tell you what it does do. It
makes you really hungry, bro. It makes
you really [ __ ] hungry.
I still think it's a good side hustle
though. I think it's good in the summer
cycling around, seeing new areas. I
don't think it's too bad to be fair,
bro. You can make a good couple of
hundred pound. I don't think it's bad me
in this day and age. There's not many numbers.
I mean, I've got a number going at the
minute, but I'm not going to say what it
is, Dusty, because obviously snitches on
here. But yeah,
I'll never say what it is. But I'm
saying in in terms of something being
legit, that's a good that's a good um
and it used to pay for the escorts as
well. So I used to just go to work and
then there's one time, bro, I just got a
[ __ ] from an escort and obviously
that paid for it. So yeah,
what else would you be doing in the summer, lad?
Because think about it, you'll be
cycling. A lot of people cycle around in
the summer, don't they? They just like
to cycle wherever they go. So you're
you're basically doing that, but you're
making money as well. Think about it.
Yeah. But there was one day, Dusty, bro,
I worked on Sunday. Yeah. I swear to
God, it took me eight hours to make £50.
8 hours to make 50 [ __ ] pound.
eight [ __ ] hours.
What the [ __ ] So, you also need to do
it at the right time as well.
That's why I'm saying it's not a stable
income and you never know how much
you're going to make. Whereas you say
you do security work here. Say you do a
job like another job. You get a set
amount an hour.
Obviously with that, that's not a set
amount. You can earn 150 a day and one
day you could earn £50. So, you know,
you don't know how much you're ever
really going to make on the day. You can
estimate it, but you know, you don't
know fully. Whereas, if you're, like I
said, if you're like, if you work for
security or I don't know, you're a
bartender, you get the same amount of
money. You know how much you're making
if you work 10 hours. £15 an hour.
Uh, £50 an hour. Say you get £15 an
hour, you do 10 hours, you know, you're
going to come home with 150. with this
job. It's not that because you don't
know how much you're going to make.
Yeah, that's a good thing. You can stop
when you want because it's a side hustle.
You don't have someone telling you, you
know, um you have to do this, you have
to do that.
It is good. It is. I I think it's not
bad to be fair. If you're one benefits,
that was literally the only other way
you can make extra money.
But you can make 150 a day. That's all
right. Is it dusty? If you made 150 a
day, you can because there was this guy
15 a day. That's decent. That is decent.
150 is Yeah. £88. Not, but it's still
money, bro. It's still money.
You don't You just don't declare it.
You just don't declare it. And you need
to be earning a certain amount as well,
but you just don't declare it. I mean, I
don't do it anymore. Obviously, if I did
do it, I would never tell anyone on here
because they're grasses.
I wouldn't tell my business. I only told
after I had lost the account. You
couldn't tell any of these grasses
anything, bro. But yeah, but you just
don't declare it.
And you have to earn over a certain
amount as well. I think it's over 127.
So, if you're still in a threshold, they
can't and you lose you lose one benefit
and you actually no, you lose one benefit.
Um, but you have to be over the
threshold. If you're not over the
threshold, then you don't.
And I think it's like it's something a month.
So, you need to be really you need to be earning
like with the subleting. I had it in
another account. So, that's why they
never caught me because I had it in
another account because I already knew
about these glasses.
Yeah. Long term you probably would.
I mean you you can earn a thousand
before declaring it. They say yeah. Yeah.
That's the thing. Yeah.
But I still think it's good as a little
side hustle, bro. I don't think it's
that bad. I think it's a good little number
cuz you know you can stop when you want and Yeah.
But you lose so much energy and at the
end of it you have to eat. I used to go
to Jub um Jubilee at the end, Dusty. I
used to have a lot of orders at uh
Jubilee and at the end I used to just go
to Jubilee cuz I was so hungry,
you know. So by the end of it, it is.
But the only bad thing in the summer is
it's too hot. That's the thing. But you
obviously I used to just I just used to
get like a bowl of water and put in my
bag. I used to just make a backpack of
like water and that. So it was fine. Yeah,
you can make money from it though. Is it
Dusty? If you put enough hours in. What
do you think?
You could make money in it. Yeah.
Yeah, you could. There's this guy that
does it, bro, on YouTube. His name's
London um his name's London Hustle, but
he never shares how much he makes.
He never shares how much he makes like
the other one does. There's London
Hustle and then there's London Eats, but
London Eats shares how much he makes.
The other one doesn't.
Yeah, the other one doesn't.
I'm sure you've seen them channels in it.
I don't like that London Eats, though. I
can't stand his voice, bro.
His voice grinds on me. Yeah, I'm sure
you've seen him. Yeah.
It's all gone to [ __ ] ain't it, Dusty?
It's hard to win money nowadays.
What do you think?
It's all gone to shite. >> [snorts]
>> But yeah,
160 in three days.
Peter belly makes money though, Dusty.
It's a shame you can't tell anyone
anything on here though, is it? Because
they just grass.
That's the thing, Dusty. They just
grass, isn't it, lad? So you can't tell
them like anything on here. >> [snorts]
>> You know what I mean? Ain't it?
Their bloody glasses on here, lad.
Yeah, I've still got my Uber account,
but it's they banned me, so I can't do it anymore.
I peeled it, but
they're not interested.
Your pill was denied.
They didn't even give me a second chance.
I ate the customer's food.
There was a reason for that, though.
There was a reason for that.
The map kept [ __ ] up. Yeah.
Do you remember USA? Izzy Dusty.
She was a scumbag in it.
She was a scumbag, lad. I'm back. >> [snorts]
>> Have you ever used an escort, Dusty?
I can't use them now because I don't
like using a condom. [snorts]
So, I can't use them. Me, lad.
Good thing I like [ __ ] isn't it?
A mouth is a mouth, is it?
I don't like wearing [ __ ] condoms, bro.
Oh, [snorts] I saw your thing with the
woman on the train. Yeah, Dusty.
I saw your comment on about that woman
on the train.
I was waiting for an incident like that,
you know, yesterday, the day before, you
know, I'm wait, you know, when I'm in a
bad mood. Yeah, which is most of the
time I wait again on one of them in incidents.
Not that I didn't do anything last time.
I told her about herself last time.
She's an ugly crackhead. But like, you
know, when you just want to take her to
the extreme this time,
like I done what I had to do anyways. I
wasn't scared. But I mean, I want to
take her to the extreme, lad.
like to the extreme. But I just couldn't
be bothered. I said what I had to say. I
wasn't scared. But I mean, take it to
the extreme because they know it's it's
it's a thing of like this, Dusty, right? Like
as in like you've got a problem because
you got issues in your life and I'm
going to show you that like you're not
going to take your issues out on other people
because I've got problems as well. Do
you understand, bro? So, I'm just
waiting for someone now like to start
something so I could just take it to the extreme. [snorts]
Just take it to the extreme next time.
That's what I'm going to do, bro. And
see what they're really on. See what
they're really on, you know. Anyways,
and about the American. Yeah, cuz she's
a [ __ ] Anyways, [ __ ] with that.
Yeah, cuz she's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, she's a [ __ ] [ __ ] That's why.
We were just talking about working
before you joined.
It was snowing here earlier, but it's
calmed down now.
I [snorts] didn't piss myself. I went to
piss. Every time I try to Every time I
go to piss, it comes up piss on my thing.
I never I didn't piss myself, lad.
I never pissed myself.
A job's a job, lad.
A job is a job, matey.
[snorts] A job is a job.
Simple as that. A job is a job.
Never pissed myself, lads. Never pissed myself. [snorts] Whoa.
Oh, that video was grossing again. I
just seen it. Dusty
Wow, bro. Wow. [sighs]
V was grassing again on people.
Oh, you know, there's a comment that
sticks out, Dusty, you know, and it and
it doesn't leave my mind, you know. I
think about it like every now and then.
There's a comment that never seems to
up. It always pops up, you know, bro.
some comments never never, you know,
never. Um, there's just some comments you remember,
some things you remember, you know. >> [sighs]
>> That's why people use other accounts, I guess. Yeah.
Where is Ronald Pump nowadays?
Where's Ronald Pump nowadays?
I don't know, bro.
Where is um
where's Ronald Pump, lad?
Got an old pump.
I don't know. They're old videos, bro.
the old videos of Timmy.
One second. I want to go on someone's channel here
and see if they're still stalking me. >> [snorts] [sighs]
>> Do you know this red star? I don't know
how he doesn't get bored of this after
all these years. To be fair, lad,
you know, you would have thought these
people would have got bored in it, lad.
You would have thought.
You would have thought they would have
got bored in it. Um Steven Howard,
that takes a lot of energy, you know,
every day, bro, to do this.
That takes a lot of bloody energy. [snorts]
I'm just on uh this thing.
This is what I mean. Yeah. Look. Oh,
he's still there. Steven Howard.
I'm just on this red star thing now.
You didn't [snorts] get anyone's money
stopped. Think of it, Steven Howard.
Yeah. Listen, bro. If they got my money
stopped, yeah, and they sent evidence of
me subleting, I would have been I would
have been in court for subletting or my
mom would have cuz she was on the teny.
If they really got my money stopped,
somebody would have been done for it.
Like, my mom would have got fined or I
mean, I I wouldn't have got fined. Like
if they actually got your money stopped,
there would be a court case. They would
literally do you for it, bro. They would
literally do you for it. The guy never
got anyone's money stopped, bro. He
emailed them. Yeah, anyone can email
anything, bro. I can report the police.
I can report stuff to the police.
You really didn't get anyone's money
stopped. Cuz if that was the case, it
wouldn't have took four years. Like that
never happened. That definitely
definitely definitely definitely never happened.
You emailed, you ear dropped something,
and then you made a story that you got
people's money stopped. And yeah, you
never got anyone's money stopped.
It's not up to you to do that. So yeah,
you didn't get anyone's money stopped,
bro. That's not even P me being
triggered. You didn't get anyone's money stopped.
They they knew from the time that LT
broke into the house. Steven Howard.
So, how did it take you 4 years to get
people's money stopped? Cuz you didn't
get anyone's money stopped.
And that's how people knew, bro, from
the LT uh breaking uh breaking uh
breaking in. They didn't get anyone's
money stopped. They didn't get no one's
money stopped, bro. Not one person at all. [snorts]
But they keep telling themselves that
they got people's money stopped. They're
only lying to themselves.
They really are because you would have
been done for it if they got your if
they provided evidence. Yeah. Of you
subleting they would you would have been
done for it.
You would have actually been done for
it. Like a fine or you can go to prison
for that. You know you would put in
prison but you can go to prison for it.
So what they've just let you get away with subletting
really for all of them years bro it's
[ __ ] They they did not get anyone's money stopped.
They would take you to court. If these
people sent evidence and they took into
account the evidence they shown, you
would be in court paying that money
back. But are they just going to like Do
you understand what I'm saying, bro? [snorts]
Do you understand what I'm trying to
say? They would have all the evidence
that they need, but they don't because
they never got anyone's money stopped.
they would want that money back. Do you understand?
I might do a video, bro, explaining this
just in case people um like generally
believe in this guy.
Like I don't care. I know the truth, but
just in case like people are easily led
into thinking that this guy actually
stopped my money, but he didn't stop my
money. He didn't stop any of my money,
bro. Believe you me. Like it doesn't
even matter what I've got now or whatever, bro.
Um, he didn't stop anyone's money, lad.
And yeah, it takes a lot to be on
someone's case 24/7 as well.
If they shown evidence, right, and they
got your money stopped, why haven't they
took you to court? They would take you
to court, bro, they wouldn't just stop
it. They would take you to court.
They would take you to court, bro. And
you would probably get a fine. You
wouldn't go to prison, but you'd get a
fine cuz it's a civil matter. So what?
They've just let you because they didn't
stop anyone's money. They never stopped
anyone's money. You would be in court.
Everyone knew about the subleting when
uh when LT broke in the house.
So you didn't you ears dropped and you
made up a story that you got people's
money stopped and then you've done
things where you've sent evidence. Bro,
anyone can report anything. You might
have reported stuff, but you didn't get
anyone's money stopped. That's not up
for you to do that.
That was always going to happen. That
was literally always going to happen
where the landlord wanted the property
back. They were trying for years and
years and years and years and years and
years and years before anyone knew about it.
So, I might do a video addressing this
just in case anyone believes this guy's
[ __ ] lies. Um, I can literally
report someone to the police. Does it
mean that they're going to get arrested?
No, it doesn't. You didn't stop any of
my money, bro. That's why I'm so calm
about it. [laughter]
You didn't stop anyone's money. I just
don't want the right people to start thinking that.
Do you know what I'm saying?
You know what I mean? [ __ ]
Yeah, this guy, this red star is on
YouTube 24/7 stalking cuz he's got no
line. So, do you think in four years,
bro, they would have found stuff to be
able to report you for?
And I'll tell the whole story about like
the benefits and them trying to them
trying to stop the benefits.
I'm not eating again, bro. I'm fasting.
I ate earlier. Like the benefits and stuff.
Do you know what I'm saying? And look
how I acted.
You didn't stop anyone's money. Stop
telling yourself that. You need to stop
lying to yourself, kid. You might have
reported something, but you didn't stop anyone's money.
You got a lot of uh you got a lot of
time on your hands, bro. Like do you
remember this Stephen H when I used to
[ __ ] with USA Izzy? Yeah. Do you
remember when I used to [ __ ] with USA
Izzy, bro? And I stopped after like a
year and this was someone that I slept
with, someone that I met. Yeah. And
obviously after I didn't do it every
day, but I used to [ __ ] with them. This
guy has been doing it for years. Like
I'm not reacting to these people. I'm
wondering, bro. like you're allowed to
have your opinion on it. You would think
that if they actually had something
going on in their lives, how they would
find the time to do this 24/7
and the fact that they stalked people on
Reddit pretending to be women. You would
think to yourself, really, bro, if these
people had anything going on in their
lives, how they find all the time in the
world to do all of this stuff, how they
stay bitter for so long
to someone that they don't even know.
You would ask you would actually ask you
would actually ask yourself this how
they could be bitter to someone that
they don't know for so long.
It's very concerning, isn't it, bro?
Very, very concerning.
And then when you take that into
account, and this is not me reacting,
bro. This is me being real realistic. Yeah. >> [snorts]
>> And when you take all of this stuff into
account, that's where we can say that
safely say that they're jealous.
Because how can someone sit on the
internet and be bitter every day for
years to someone that they don't know?
Like maybe people are too disabled to
understand that, but bro, you got to understand.
And I can compare it to the USA thing. I
[ __ ] with her for ages, bro, because
of what she done, but then I just gave
up. You think anyone that's got a life
can sit on here doing this every day?
There's no chance in hell.
There's no no no no no no chance in hell.
And that's it, lad.
Yeah, I know they're jealous, bro.
Everyone knows they're jealous.
They're definitely definitely definitely definitely jealous.
But I might [snorts] do a video anyways
addressing this red star anyways. Just
in case the just in case the wrong
people believe it.
Yeah, just in case the wrong people
believe it, lad. We don't want the wrong
people believe in lies now, do we? We
don't care about the other people, but
we care about the uh [snorts]
um we care about the right people. We
don't want the right people believing
this stuff. You didn't get anyone's
money stopped. You tried to get people's
benefits stopped two times cuz you're a
low life. But then I had your boyfriend
stopped going to events for two two
three weeks because of it.
You really think I would be so calm
about someone getting two grand and my
money stopped? You really think someone
would be that calm about it?
Why am Why Why am I so calm? Because
it's [ __ ] You didn't get anyone's
money stopped. It's [ __ ]
And I bring up the posters as well cuz
that poster thing was because of the uh benefits.
That was because of the benefits.
And when they were asking me to send
them that and I'm thinking, okay, you
want to cause an inconvenience in my
life, I'll cause an inconvenience in your life.
You know, I I will I will cause an
inconvenience in your life. And that's
what I done with the posters. You want
to take something off YouTube, I'll take
something off YouTube and I'll stop you
leaving your house. And that was over
benefits, bro. That was over like shitty
benefits. But it's not the point,
you know? That's not the point. You try
to get people's money stopped, I will
[ __ ] your life up. Simple.
You understand what I'm saying, lad?
So, you really think if I knew that you
got any of my income stopped, I would
just sit there and allow it? [snorts]
Not saying I could get you. I might not
be able to get you personally, but
obviously I would get someone as
naturally anyone would.
You need to stop lying to yourself
because it's not it's not a good look.
You're stalking people on Reddit. You're
pretending to be a woman. That's just an
that's a that's just an opinion on how
sad you are. By the way, that's not
reacting. That's just an opinion to how
sad you are.
You know, that's not reacting. That's
that's telling you you're sad.
There's a big difference. Steven Howard, you know,
like you're saying that it's an opinion.
Everyone's allowed to have an opinion.
And your my opinion is that you're sad
with no life.
Yeah, you didn't stop any of my money,
lad. You didn't stop any of my money. Do
you know what? I'll do a video to you
later. Anyways, lad, I'll do a video to
you later so the wrong people don't so
the so the wrong people don't believe
you, bro. You didn't get anyone's money
stopped. You did not get anyone's money
stopped at all. But I'll be talking
about you anyways later on the video,
you little loser. Just an opinion
because you put yourself out there on
YouTube. You didn't get anyone's money
stopped. And I'll explain to you exactly
how you didn't get anyone's money stopped, right?
And and that's it.
I'll explain to everybody
how you did absolutely not get anyone's
money stopped and you're lying to yourself
and you've absolutely got no life as
well. And sorry, I'm going to have to
bring USA Izzy into this as well. Um, so
I can actually tell you that this guy
generally has got no life. They've been
sat there doing this for years. LT is
wrong about this.
LT is wrong about this loser, bro. Cuz
this guy actually stalks people off of
YouTube as well, pretending to be women.
He's got an obsession because he's some
fat skin ugly low life. An opinion, not
reacting, just like anyone can have an opinion.
He's a sad sad sad stalker with no life.
Um, you know, I don't know how someone
can sit on the internet for years doing
this and not get bored. Unless they were
jealous or gay, to be honest.
Unless they were jealous um, and gay or
gay. I don't know how they could do it.
And every day as well, bro. Like every
single day. And they also take it off of
YouTube as well.
Because then by rights I should be
[ __ ] with people every day then
I should be [ __ ] with women every day
by rights then in it Stephen Howard I
should be [ __ ] with USA is he every day
but I don't have the time for it. I
don't have the energy for it. I don't
have the time for it.
As you wouldn't think these people would,
but they do.
Proper sado. You are, man. You're proper propos.
You are. I feel bad for you.
[sighs and gasps]
You didn't stop anyone's money. You need
to stop telling yourself that. If you
really gathered evidence, why has people
not been to court and got a fine?
Never happened, lad. Absolutely never happened.
Never ever ever ever happened. And what
you were showing is not actually proof
of someone's subleting either. You never
even showed any proof to get anyone's money stopped. Sad bastard.
Sad. Sad bastard.
>> So, you want to take stuff off YouTube?
I'll take stuff off YouTube. Yeah.
Yeah. He's a He's an idiot, bro. He
didn't get anyone's money stopped.
Didn't get anyone's money stopped at
this guy's definitely been bullied his whole life.
Everyone knows you, Spanner.
Brother, you didn't get anyone's money
stopped. That's why I'm very, very calm
about it, lad. Because I know you didn't
get anyone's money stopped. Why do you
think I'm so calm?
Why do you think I'm so calm? You
bitter, bitter old man. Sad bastard. Sat
on YouTube stalking every day. [snorts]
If you're going to sit here, you control
my life. You don't control my life at
all. You're just a sado.
A bitter jealous sado. And also, if
you're going to sit on here every day
doing this, I can have an opinion.
Posters to the neighbors. You can put
You can do posters to the neighbors all
you want. No one cares. The neighbors
know about you.
You sad sad bastard. The neighbors all
So you can do posters all you want. They
all know about you.
You sad sad bitter old man. I'm [snorts]
going to do a video on to you. I'm going
to do a video on you um later. But I'm
going to do a video on this sad bastard.
I'm going to do a video on this sad sad
bastard. Bro, I really am.
This sad bastard.
So, does that mean right if if if Timmy
got arrested right now? Yeah. And I
showed me reporting Timmy. Does that
mean my report to Timmy got him
arrested? No, it never.
You sad, sad, sad, sad bastard.
How you can sit here doing this for
years? I truly feel sorry for you. And
[snorts] only somebody that doesn't have this abilities.
But then the thing is Steven Howard then
this Joe this Joe then wonders why we
think people are jealous. He he he
always he always wonders why we think
people are jealous. But we we've got the
answer. We've got the evidence. Sat
stalking every day. Stalking people on
the internet. You tell me someone that's
got a better life than me that would do
that. You tell me, bro.
Cuz it really really really really
did not happen. It really, really,
really did not happen.
Oh, yeah. When nons we lost. Okay.
Right. I'm going to be doing a video on
this red star. Yeah. Greavvesy
cuz I need to clear a couple of things
up about his stalking tactics.
Um, and his lies as well. [sighs] Yeah.
Cuz I'm I I need to I need to clear this
up, bro, on this video. And I don't want
I don't want the right people believing
this guy's lies, claiming that he's got
people's money stopped when it it, you
know, when it hasn't been stopped
because of this guy. You know, I don't
want people thinking that.
And I'm going to bring up USA Izzy in
this as well, Greavvesy, because um
[snorts] back when I was [ __ ] with
USA, you know
what I what I don't why what I don't
understand, Grezy, is how someone can
sit on the internet
uh [ __ ] with people for years from
the time they wake up to the time they
go to bed. I just can't I just can't uh comprehend it.
What kind of lunatic would do that?
You know, and it's an opinion. It's not
reacting. It's an opinion. You put
yourself on the internet. I I just can't
I just don't know where the desire comes
from to want to sit on the internet and
stalk people every day from the time you
wake up to the time you go to bed.
I would love to know where that desire
comes from. Maybe we can actually get an
answer. You know,
you're stalking people on Reddit. You're
pretending to be a woman.
You sure you're not gay, bro?
You sure you're not an absolute, you know?
All them years talking and you're saying
that you're not bitter and you're not jealous. Seriously. Really? Bro,
how long has he been doing this now? Let
me let me I can actually tell you how
long he's been doing this.
He's been doing this for years.
He has actually been doing this now for years, bro.
One second. Let me have a look.
He's been doing this for years. I don't
know where that desire comes from, lad.
You got a lot of time on your hands to
sit here and st That's like me still
doing this to USA uh Grezy.
This is like me, right? Yeah. Still
doing this to USA all day, every day.
Could you imagine that? Like just just
think about it for a second,
right? For one second. Say say I was
still doing this every day, right?
because I feel like I've got I'd have
the um I'd have the right to do it, but
you wouldn't do it. Do you understand?
This guy is definitely disabled, bro.
And [snorts] I feel like, you know, when
you've got something to talk about, it
makes a good video. It's not reacting.
It makes a good video. I love it, to be honest.
And it shows what LT doesn't know what
he's talking about as well, cuz this guy
also stalks people on Reddit. He sits
all day stalking men on the internet.
What a loser bastard that he's never met
as well. That he's literally never met.
He's a loser, bro. He's an absolute loser. [sighs] You know,
I thought I was bad doing it for like a
couple of months to somebody that I met
once. Squeezy. This cunt's been doing it
for years to someone that he's never met.
knowing damn well I could get nonslegs
as well. I could actually get non-slegs
as well if I wanted to. So if you
actually stop someone's money, I could
easily get nons within a month. So
you did not stop anyone's bloody income.
You did not stop anybody's bloody income. >> [sighs]
>> And that's another thing before crying
about posters. You you want you don't
you don't take stuff off of YouTube and
then moan when someone puts posters up
of you. You know, you don't try to get
people's money stopped, right? And then
cry when someone puts up posters about
you. Isn't that right, Gre Isn't that right, Grezy? Right.
You don't try to get people's It doesn't
matter how much the money was petty
amount. You can't try to get people's
money stopped and then moan when they're
when they're [ __ ] um putting up
posters of you. You understand?
You understand that?
It doesn't work. You don't you don't say
what people can and can't do when you're
trying to trying to get people's money
stopped. And at the end of the day, bro,
it's not it doesn't really matter, you
know, if you put your business out there
or whatever. Like people, there's a
certain line that you don't cross cross.
And I think, you know, trying to stop
people's money that they're entitled to
is is the lowest of the low. You
understand, Grezy? I think that's pretty
low to be honest. And I think anyone
that that does that to anyone on here
deserves Yeah. posters, everything.
You don't keep harassing people and then
think you're going to tell people what
they can and can't do.
I would have never done that posters if
it wasn't for the uh benefit what they
were trying to do with the benefits.
Do you understand, lad? I was ne I would
have never done it. I would have just
went back. I said I was going to do it,
but I would never have done it. I was
never ever going to do it. It was only
because they tried stopping my money.
It was only £180.
So you're claiming that you've made
someone lose what? £1,800 a month
and they're just and they've just let
you get away with it. When we've seen
the evidence, what your boyfriend, he
was scared to leave his house for 2
weeks because of me. People lie and
pretend it never happened, but that's
that's what they're saying now. That's
not what happened then.
Do you understand what I'm saying? So,
so yeah, I definitely would have been
able to get nons legs. Obviously, I
don't know who that red store is. Oh, I
would have just got someone.
It would have just been someone. I would
have I would have got someone, you know. So, yeah.
Yeah. Maybe maybe he can answer me on a
video where the desire comes from to
want to stalk someone every day.
Maybe he could tell me, make me
understand it. But you've got a better
life than people and you're not jealous.
So Joseph Fra says
that's a lot of hate and your energy
every day for somebody that you don't
know just because they've said stuff
online to people. That's a lot of energy, bro.
Do you understand what I'm saying, Greavvesy?
You understand what I'm saying?
I think what I'm saying makes sense. No,
correct me if I'm wrong here, you know.
It's just madness, lad. It's just really mad.
Oh [ __ ] he's got my [ __ ] dick there,
bro. As well.
Yeah, I just thought I'm bored, so I'll
just do a video, you know,
[sighs and snorts]
21st of February.
You showed a video. You showed a
screenshot of you reporting something.
Anybody who can report something. [snorts]
Is it okay if I do a last video about this, Grezy?
Is it all right if I do a last video
about this, lad? [sighs]
Yeah, I need to address this weirdo, bro.
[snorts] You know, and again, it's an
opinion on what you're doing, not reacting. big difference.
We're allowed to say that you're a sad
bastard stalking people on the internet
because that's what you're doing without
using the reaction excuse, you know, and
that's that. Bro,
I feel like just putting this [ __ ] in
his place, you know? I don't I don't
make videos very often, but when I do [snorts]
And I don't know why you keep calling
people skin when the only one that's
showing that their skin is you being sat
on YouTube every day stalking people on different platforms.
Yeah, you got your own business. Really,
do you, bro? Okay. Anyways, bro, I'm
going to do a video on you anyways
[snorts] cuz your actions have been appalling.
Yeah, you got your own business. Really?
Oh, okay. Of course you do, man. I'm
going to do a video on you anyways, lad.
You got a lot of time on your hands to
be stalking people and pretending you're
a woman and [ __ ]
That's the thing. Like they're actually,
this is what I was trying to explain to
this LT before as well and he doesn't understand it
is that even if you left the internet,
right, they would literally like stalk
you every day, bro. Like even even if
you left the internet forever, they
would literally like
sit on Reddit all day waiting for you to
post. They're just sad people with
nothing in life.
And I'm going to get onto that notch
legs as well. That that's another thing
I want to talk about it. Bro,
just to clear one thing up.
You didn't get anyone's bloody money stopped.
You did not get anyone's money stopped,
lad. You need to stop lying to yourself. [snorts]
Seriously, you need to stop lying to yourself.
And you know even if you did and let me
tell you something you know even if you
did got even if you did get someone's
money stopped it would have got stopped
eventually anyways maybe 6 months or a
year later you do you do realize that
that even if you got it stopped it would
have stopped anyways which you never got
it stopped either way you never got the money stopped. So yeah,
6 months a year. I mean, it was The
point is it would have always stopped.
You didn't get anyone's money stopped.
You're just a stalking little bastard
that's got no life.
That's what you are. That's what you
are. I mean, I can understand like
someone, but every day, lad,
he never got my money stopped. I'm doing
a video to this guy anyways, bro. just
to clear it up. And I'm going to explain
the whole story as well, you know, of
what happened and how it come about and
the rooms and stuff because this guy
keeps telling lies and no one likes a
liar and I don't want the wrong people
believing it. Um, and that's that, bro.
So, um, yeah. Simple.
Yeah. I want to tell the whole story
and I'm also going to explain what you
what I done when you actually did try to
get my money stopped, which was my
benefits and what I done to your
boyfriend when I went to his area,
bro. He did it. No, no, no. There's no
emails, bro. There's emails of him
reporting it. Yeah. There's emails of
him reporting me. There's no emails of
them stopping anything because of him.
There's no proof that they stopped
anything because of him.
Right. Like I said, if they stopped my
money, I would be in court. My mom would
be in court. Yeah. Because my mom Well,
it wouldn't be me cuz I was on the
tendency. My mom was on the tendency.
So, if he's proved that someone's
frauded, then my mom would be in court.
My mom would literally be get done for it.
So, no. There's evidence of him
reporting me via email, I can report you
right now. That doesn't mean you've been
arrested. [snorts] Right. So, at the end
of the day, if he's shown enough
evidence, then my mom would be in court.
Yeah. For frauding. Not me. It wouldn't
be me because I wasn't on the teny. So,
what? They've just let you get away with
subleting a house for all of them years.
So, no, bro. Not at all. Yeah. He sent
the emails. Yeah, he reported me. But he
didn't get my money stopped.
He didn't get my money stopped.
Yeah, he sent emails. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah,
he sent emails. Yeah, I know he did.
Yeah, he sent emails. But he's not the
one that got anything stopped.
He is not the one that got anything stopped.
No, that is not what happened. That is
literally [snorts] not what happened.
Because if that's what happened, if
that's what happened, right? If that's
what happened, then my mom would be in
court with a fine. If they had enough
evidence, then they would have done my
mom for it. But they never. So that's
not what their exact words was. Go put
that up with us. If that's their exact
words, put it up. Put that up right now. Yeah. Simple.
Uh, nope. I had that house for four
years. Making Nope. I had that house for
four years. So yeah, you're talking
absolute [ __ ] But I'm going to do a
video anyways on you. You literally did
not get anyone's money stopped. And even
if you did get someone's money stopped,
which you never, they would have got it back anyways
because my mom moved house. So yeah, he
pays so much and Mark Red sourced, which
is why he's Nope. I'm not skin. I've got
plenty plenty plenty of money. you and I
make money as well. That's for me to
know and you to never find out.
So, I mean, bro, they would have always
got the house back and you did not stop
the money either. Stop saying that you
got people's money stopped, but you
never You've only got emails of you
reporting. That's all you've got. I can
report you. I can report you on YouTube
right now. That doesn't mean anything.
That doesn't mean anything at all.
So, I mean, why didn't my mom get done
for it? Why didn't my mom get done for
If you literally shown them evidence and
they had evidence, my mom would get
[ __ ] for it. So, you're talking
absolute [ __ ] You ear dropped the
story and then you made it to what suited yourself
and you were showing your reports,
acting like you're the one that got it
stopped when you absolutely did not get
it stopped. And I will do a video as
well explaining the whole story about the house.
So yeah, I'll explain the whole story of
the house and everything and how I was
left that house because it's we kind of
got like the wrong it's like the wrong
people believe in it. You pay monthly to
stop him from going to school.
Nope. That's not what happened. Triple.
I'm not fuming at all. Bro, I'm not
fuming. I'm completely calm. You're,
bro. You're the one that's triggered
every day. You're the one making videos.
You're the one that's making community
posts. You're the one that's triggered.
Not me. I'm extremely calm.
I'm extremely extremely extremely calm.
Actually, you're the one that's stalking
men on the internet 24/7. Cuz you ain't
got a life.
Because you ain't got a life, lad.
You're the one that's fuming. You're the
one that's bitter every day. You've
ruined my life, bro. You could never
ruin my life. You could never ever ever
ever ever ruin my life. So, I've got a
better life than you. I'm younger than
you. I'm better looking than you. I
don't stalk men on the internet every
day like you. Cuz you're a loser. You're
a skip loser. Every day on YouTube
stalking. Straight onto YouTube stalking
from the time you wake up to the time
you go to bed. You're a loser, bro.
You're an absolute absolute absolute loser.
You've never ruined my life. I'm still
sat here better looking than you. I'm
still sat here with more money than you, lad.
You more money in a day. You keep
telling yourself that, mate. You keep
telling yourself that. You keep telling
yourself that. See you later anyways, kid. [sighs] Uh,
nope. My mom doesn't pay any money. My
mom does not pay any money. Nope. Not at
all. The only money that they wanted
back Triple H was they're not paying the
rent. It was only from not paying rent.
And obviously my mom don't pay it. So if
you proved somebody was doing fraud, why
has there been no court case?
Why have they not took someone to court?
Think about it, bro. Actually think
about it. Why have they not took you to court?
Why have they not took your mom? Well,
it wouldn't be me. It'd be my mom
because I'm not in the tendency. it it
would they would literally, you know,
well, they never they're not getting it
back and there was no call because he
never stopped it. He didn't stop anyone's money,
you know. He might have emailed them.
Anyone can email anyone, you know, but
that's not the landlord, bro. He
literally made he ear dropped a story
and made it to what suited himself to
make it seem like he stopped but he
didn't stop anyone's money. That's why I
haven't gone for anyone. That's why I'm
extremely extremely calm.
Nope. There's Triple H. There's no fine.
My mom didn't go to court. I didn't go
And if you provided enough evidence,
somebody would have been getting [ __ ]
for that. Somebody would be getting
[ __ ] for that. [snorts] So, you didn't
stop anyone's money, mate. You really,
really, really, really didn't stop
anyone's money. Not in the slightest.
But you keep telling yourself that.
Yeah, you're on my way to my mom's,
brother. You can't even leave your
house. Stop it now. You're very, very,
very boring. But yeah, you didn't stop
anyone's money, bro. I'm going to do a
video on this red star. Anyways,
like I tried to explain this to this LT.
Yeah. But sometimes I actually feel like
the guy's got disabilities, bro. Like
you can't get through to him about these
people. And it's like, not even to be
nasty, but you do come across like
you're disabled sometimes, LT, bro.
Like, someone has to explain something
to you like a million times.
Yeah. Stay alive, brother. You've said
this a million times before.
Oh, I know what you're trying to do. Oh,
it's not going to work. Yeah.
Stay live and you'll see. Oh, no. No. L
No, LT. No, no, no. But you do you do
act disabled sometimes, bro. Like
someone has to explain something to you
like a million times. But I was actually
going to email I was going to email you
today, bro, and actually say like, "Bro,
I swear down someone has to say
something to you like a million times sometimes."
Like, man, it's like explaining
something to a baby sometimes with you,
bro. I swear down.
Seriously, bro. No, you're not, bro.
Okay. Let Okay. Let me let me Okay. All
right. Okay. Let me let me let me clear
up some things. Yeah. Let me clear up
let me clear up a few things. Yeah. You
know the other day when you was on my
live stream. Yeah. And I was calling
that nons legs that nons legs, right? A
virgin. You're sat there saying about
how can he be a virgin. [ __ ]
How can I be a virgin when I've
literally proved that I [ __ ] women?
I've not just shown a disabled girl.
I've [ __ ] women on camera. Bro, I
[ __ ] women. I've been butt naked in
women's beds and you're finding it
ridiculous that I think he's a virgin.
And then you wonder why people think
that you're disabled when you're coming
out with [ __ ] like that. Secondly, yeah,
the stalking on YouTube. Do you know
what these people have done the past
couple of days, bro? They've literally
been stalking me on Reddit pretending to
be a woman, bro. Yeah, they were
actually cuz I was like, do you know
what? Yeah, maybe you're right, bro.
Bro, how can he be a virgin? How can I
be a virgin when I've literally proved
I've had sex? Listen. Okay. Okay. How
can I be a virgin when I've literally
proven I've had sex? He has not proven
he's had sex. It's more ridiculous him
calling me a virgin than me calling him
a virgin. But trying to explain it to a
[ __ ] you you you can't, brother.
He's got more chance of being a virgin
than me. He's got way more chance.
Brother, I've shown me get my dick
sucked. I've shown me in bed naked with
women. How can I be a virgin? How can I
be a virgin? But again, trying to
explain this to someone, it's like you
can't explain, bro. Trying to explain
stuff to you sometimes, it's mad. He's
in a relationship with a disabled
girlfriend. He has not shagged her.
Yeah. I have proven that I have had sex.
Brother, brother, brother, listen.
Listen. I have proven that I have
[ __ ] Listen, bro. I have proven that
I have [ __ ] So, do you not think that
it's more ridiculous
someone trying to call me a virgin than
me calling him a virgin? Do you not
think? Yeah. Do you not think for one
second that in your brain that it's a
bit more silly trying to call someone
like me a virgin?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Bro, I know. I Bro, listen.
Listen. Do you not think it's more mad
him trying to call me a virgin than him
calling than And then you're saying to
me and then you're saying to me, "Oh,
you got a [ __ ] brother. Yeah, I've
got a [ __ ] on video. That's more than
what he's shown. Yeah, that's more than
what he's ever shown sexually, bro.
Yeah. Yeah, a [ __ ] Do you think it
stopped that [ __ ] bro? Does Does
anything stop at a [ __ ] brother? A
blowjob's more than what that [ __ ]
showed with his disabled girlfriend.
You're biased. Yeah. Even Kieran will
say the same thing. Kieran says it.
[ __ ] Ben Furvy says it. You're
biased. That's the definition of biased.
Yeah. This is what I'm trying to
explain. You're talking about me only
getting a [ __ ] Yeah, a [ __ ] that
led to sex. What have you seen him do to
his girlfriend? Have you seen them [ __ ]
Have you seen them [ __ ] No, you
haven't, bro. No, you haven't. We have
seen me I'll go over everything here
that we've seen me do. We've seen me get
a [ __ ] We've seen me [ __ ] be in
hotel rooms with women naked, bro. Like,
come, bro. It doesn't matter if I paid.
It doesn't matter if I paid. It don't
matter if I paid or I didn't pay. I
still got it. I still got it. And there
were several women I didn't pay. Okay.
So, did I pay for the woman in
Manchester? No. Did I pay for Sig? No.
Did I pay for who was the other [ __ ]
The 19year-old in a hotel, Sig. Did I
pay for the woman in Manchester? No. So,
so I mean, I've just listed you three
people that never got paid. So, what, bro?
And you're talking about this guy having
a disabled girlfriend and that proves
that he's had sex. Please, bro. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. That is even
more ridiculous to call someone like me
a virgin. But again, you're just a
you're just biased,
bro. You don't know if he, brother, you
don't know if he slept with his
girlfriend. Same thing to you then. You
girlfriend. For all we know, okay, one
second. One second. Steven Howard, for
all we know, this guy can't get his dick
up. For all we know, this guy can't get
his dick up because because listen,
listen, listen. One second. One second,
bro. Just chill chill chill. If If you
can't prove that me being in naked in
bed with a woman isn't proved sex, then
we don't have his word that he don't
have erectile dysfunction. Same thing
goes to you then. So then we we can say
exactly the same thing that this guy
might have erectile dysfunction and he
can't pull it in Sarah. We can say the
same thing then because if if you want
to go by that logic if you want to go by
that logic. Yeah. Oh, you don't know
that you slept with that woman that you
was naked in bed with in hotel room then
bro we don't know that he's [ __ ] his
girlfriend. For all we know this guy
could have erectile dysfunction. For all
we know, bro, that guy could have no
dick like that man on TV. But you
wouldn't say that, would you? Cuz you're
biased. I'm trying to explain the word
to you. Biased. You're trying to sit
there and say to me that there's no
proof that I [ __ ] that girl in
Manchester, bro. There's no proof he's
[ __ ] his disabled girlfriend. You
don't know him. You don't know her. You
know, it sounds pathetic. I know it's
pathetic. It's a pathetic argument, but
it's proven my point. You're biased.
Yeah, it is. It is immature. It is very
immature. I agree. But it's proven. If
that's what it takes to prove that
you're biased, it proves it. It's pro
It's proved it, lad. He could be
[ __ ] He could have erect He could
have erectile dysfunction.
Okay, I'll give you an example, LT, if
you want. And this is actually a true
story. I'm speaking to this married
woman and she don't get sex. She I've
been speaking to this woman yesterday on
Instagram and her husband don't shag
her. She's wanted to come to London for
me to [ __ ] her from Scotland. You know,
one second, one second. I'm telling you
right now that her husband does not [ __ ]
her. This [ __ ] was talking the maddest
filth to me. She [snorts] and and she's
serious, bro. And we we were sending
voice notes. So, how do we know that
this guy don't have erectile
dysfunction? How do we know that this
guy ain't getting sex? Because if if if
a if a married woman is not getting
[ __ ] by her husband, how do we know
she's not giving him sex, bro? And I'm
not and this isn't this is a true story.
I've been speaking to her today,
yesterday. She's legit, bro. So, how do
we know that his girl ain't giving her
ain't giving her no sex? Cuz if this
married if this married woman is not
getting the dick, if this married woman
is and she's serious as well. She's deadly serious.
How do you know that he's not getting sex?
Do you understand the point I'm trying
to make? Do you understand the point I'm
trying to make, bro?
You don't have no reason to be biased.
So you, Bro, you are biased. You are
biased, lad. You are biased. You You
call your bi What do you mean you're not
biased, bro? Even Kieran says you're
biased. You are biased with the virgin
thing. You're biased with the virgin
thing. You're biased. You might not be
completely biased, right? But you are
biased because brother, listen to what
you're saying. You're saying that I
there's no proof of me sleeping with
someone even though I've been in bed
naked, but naked with women. I've
literally put a porno out there, but
there's not that's not enough proof to
prove that I've had sex.
Brother, are you listening to yourself?
Are you actually So, I've been in bed
butt naked several times with three women.
in a hotel room, but that's not proof
that I've had sex with them. Bro, are
you are you listening to yourself? And
then you're saying that you're not
biased. How are you not biased? How the
[ __ ] What do you Okay, so what the [ __ ]
am I doing lying in bed next to a woman
naked in bed? You You What? Oh my
[ __ ] god. Bro, what do what the [ __ ]
do you think I was doing?
Anyways, it doesn't matter. Anyways, and
and on your point yesterday, Yeah. about
uh this YouTube thing, bro. Yeah. About
oh that you put content on YouTube.
Listen to me, LT. Yeah. You know, when
you were saying about how they how they
how they uh how they how like they stalk
you cuz you're on YouTube, bro. These
people stalk me on Reddit. They stalk me
on Reddit every day refreshing that page.
You You're mad, bro. You You really
think Yeah. If you left this community,
they'd leave you alone? You You actually
think they would stop? You act You
actually think these people would stop
if you left YouTube, bro? They would
never stop. They would never stop, bro.
They would never ever ever stop. Even if
you left YouTube for 10 years. Yeah.
They would be on Reddit every day
refreshing that [ __ ] page. They'd
never leave you alone, bro. Come on,
bro. They would never leave you alone.
You're You're You know what? Yeah, with
the YouTube thing. Yeah. I thought, you
know what? This LT is right. Yeah.
You're putting content out there.
They're stalking you. But bro, I had
these guys pretending to be women
yesterday for five hours. They they post
Listen, bro. You don't understand what
they do. Yeah. They
post stuff on Reddit pretending to be
women in in in hopes to trap me, bro.
You You don't get it, bro. I don't think
you understand that the the the in depth
what these guys on here actually do. I
think you think it's just YouTube in it,
bro. Like, actually, I think, bro, you
think it's just YouTube.
Bro, you you don't understand what they
do on here, bro. I I don't think you
understand what they do on here, lad.
And And like, you know, they don't just
do this on YouTube. You do realize that
they pretend to be women, you know? I I
pretended to be I pretended to be women,
brother. I made a profile, a dating
profile for as a woman. Yeah. For an
experiment. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Not to
stalk someone and try to get another man's attention.
I mean, bro, no, no, no. I done a No. I
done a I done a dating experiment. A
dating app experiment, brother. Yeah.
That's a big difference. I done a dating
app experiment as a woman. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. For about 1
hour. Yeah. Yeah. Not to try to get in
touch with another man. Bro,
these people's lives are dedicated to
me. I don't think you understand the
severity of it.
They stalk you on Reddit. They stalk you
on [ __ ] like this red star. I'm I
need to do a video on this red star,
bro. This is And you know what? When you
were saying about I stalk people, LT,
let me let me tell you something. You
know this I'm going to talk about this.
This USA Izzy I gave up after a year,
bro. This was somebody I actually met.
This is somebody that I actually got
with. You don't see me stalking people,
harassing people every day. You do not
see me stalking people and harassing
people every day for 4 years. Do you see
me do that for 4 years? Do you see me do
that every day for four years? No, you
don't. When was when was the last time I
went on Izzy's profile? When was the
last time I went on USA Izzy's profile?
Tell me, bro. Tell me. When was the last
time I started [ __ ] with I I was
[ __ ] with these people.
Nah, bro. This Red Star is another
level, bro. He is He is obsessed. Nah,
this guy is is prolific, bro. [snorts]
You know, this guy is [ __ ] absolutely prolific.
It's mad, you know. [ __ ] [snorts] me.
Yeah, but I don't still do it. You don't
understand. I met USA. I met Izzy. This
guy's never met me, bro. This guy's on
my ass 24/7. Like, I think you need to
come out the closet.
I actually think Yeah, you need to come
out. I think he needs to come out the
closet, my man.
Yeah, he needs to come out of the closet
cuz this is um
this is serious serious serious serious
[ __ ] Do you know that? This is actually
serious serious [ __ ] bro.
You need you need to come out the
closet, lad. I'm telling you. Cuz this
is this is very unhealthy, man. You
dedicate your life to [ __ ] with
someone 24/7 for years.
Do you not understand? Does anyone have
a brain cell on here and realize how
[ __ ] up that actually is?
That is that is actually madness, bro.
that is really crazy. I can't imagine
these people to be young and out there
living life if they're doing this.
They can't be young and out there living
life, can they, bro? They can't be in
it. They can't be living their best life.
They literally So you and this kill guy
have been having convos while No, not at
all. No, no, no. He never said about
you. He just says that they're biased
about the virginity thing. This was ages
ago, bro. This was ages ago.
And he never mentioned you. He just said
that they're biased about like the
nonslegs thing. They said that they
defend him when I call him a virgin, but
they don't say anything about me even
though I proved I've had sex with women.
Oh, it wasn't dedicated at you. It was
just generally they're biased
which they are biased. Yeah. No, they
are biased. Yeah. He wasn't saying you.
He was saying and I'm saying Kieran is
saying that it is biased cuz it is biased.
It is biased, lad.
It is 100% biased. 100% is. Yeah.
But no, this this Redshot know they
actually do stalk me on Reddit. They actually do.
So that must mean that they're in love
with me then. Ain't it, bro? That mean
that's that must mean that they're in
love with me.
They can waste all this energy every day
like dedicated to [ __ ] with someone,
bro. What the [ __ ] They can't be young
living their best life.
They can't be young living their best
life. They really can't, bro. They they
honestly can't. I haven't been on USA
[ __ ] or Izzy [ __ ] for ages.
And furthermore, when I went on it, I
just clicked on it for like 10 seconds.
Do you not know there's a difference
between peeking on someone's profile and
literally sat there recording something
every day like what Pat Mustard used to
do? It wouldn't surprise me if this is
Pat Mustard, to be honest.
So, they're either gay or they're
jealous. And if they're not jealous,
they're gay, bro. If they're not
jealous, they're actually gay, lad.
No, they're gay, bro. Like, if they're
if they're not jealous, then they're
just gay in it. If they're not jealous,
then they're gay in it. Like, it's got
to be. They've got to be gay in it.
Like, there's nothing else they can be, bro.
Yeah. And that Yeah. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, but that's a reason, bro. Yeah,
but the thing is, Red Star, you will
never meet anyone. That's the difference
with you. You will never ever meet
anyone. You're an actual coward.
Do you know what I'm saying?
So, you're a coward.
Well, someone asked you to set me up,
LT. What was it? His boyfriend. Was it his boyfriend?
Oh, but the thing is though, I met USA.
Do you not understand, LT? I actually
met USA. This guy has never met me.
Okay, ask yourself this question then.
Yeah, LT, listen. Listen. Do you want me
to name you a couple of people on here?
Yeah. That I know have actually got a
life. And even some of them I can name
you that don't like that that that don't
actually like me. Yeah. And I don't
care. I can name you three people right
now, bro. Yeah. Unworthy clock. How hard
can it be? Ben Furby, ask yourself this
question. Yeah. How hard can it be? All
of these people, why are these people
not doing the same thing? You need to
ask yourself the question on this
community. Yeah. The question needs to
be asked. Yeah.
Why do you think these people are not
doing this and you get someone like this
that's doing this?
You know, you not you not understand
like you've it's it's selective people.
Do you not understand?
You don't see. And you know how hard can
it be? I know that guy, bro, and he
doesn't like me. I can tell you, bro.
But I I tell you 100% that guy's got a
life. 100% that guy's got a life off
YouTube cuz he's come on my door. He
doesn't hate. He doesn't hate at all.
Yeah. And he gets on with his life, you
know, and he goes on J. You, you know,
brother, there's there's a difference
between watching someone and stalking someone 24/7.
There's there's there's a big
difference. There's a big big difference
between watching someone and actually
stalking someone 24/7.
This red star has definitely been
bullied all his life. The fact that you
can sit here stalking men 24/7 for
years, brother, you you haven't got a
life. You honestly have not got a life.
For you to be doing this, you have not
got no life. You really ain't got no
life. You don't stalk 247. Yes, you do.
Every single time you get unblocked,
you're on here within seconds. You ain't
got no life outside of YouTube, bro.
Everyone's seen it when you've been
unblocked. You're on here within
seconds. You ain't got a life. Just like
your boyfriend. Nonss. Yeah. Just like
And you know what? If I if I ever do
find out your chase, I'm I'll be calling
you back out when when I'm in [ __ ]
Cardiff again. Yeah. when you when I'm
in Cardiff again, I'll be calling you
out. I'll be [ __ ] calling you out cuz
you're another little [ __ ] Or
furthermore, even if you're in London
again, let me know, you know. Not a
problem at all. Oh, by the way, LT, I'll
be going to Reen soon. Anyways, I meet
my friend in Reden soon, so that'll be
the chance for me to call that prime out again.
You did not get my house taken at all,
lad. You did not get my house taken at
all. Listen, I'm going to do a video
explaining this later. Yeah. And I'm
going to explain the posters and
everything. You didn't get anyone's
house taken. Yeah. You didn't get
nothing taken. I'm going to explain in a
video later. Don't worry, bro. Cuz we
don't want the wrong people believing
your lies and your [ __ ] You're on
YouTube every day hating, bro. You're
you're more bitter than I could ever be.
And that's an opinion. That's not even
reacting. That's an opinion. You haven't
got anything. People that's got a life
don't do what you do every day.
Okay, bro. If you want to say that it's
not going to happen, then that's on you,
bro. Is it? That's on you, is it?
Well, I will be calling him out. So,
that is what is going to be happening.
But he probably won't even meet anyways.
So, he'll probably just say, "Oh, I
don't live there anymore." But I will be
going to Reen soon
to meet my friends. So, yeah.
I will be going soon. [cough] [clears throat]
Yeah. So, I will be
I'll be going to Reden soon cuz I need
to meet my friend.
Brother, you ain't got nothing. Anyways,
you're getting banned now. I'll do a
video on you later. And here we go.
Terryy's another one.
Still giving it a big. Yeah,
even though he didn't turn up when I was
in his area last time.
Oh my god. Come on, bro. It's 2026. Just
allow it now.
Please just allow it.
Please, just allow it, man.
But yeah, you um
I mean, yeah, even if you even if you
owned your own business, listen, you
know, even if you owned your own
business, think about it. You could do
so much in your life. You could go to
the gym, you could go traveling, you know,
you know. Yeah, that's that's fine, bro.
But he told me to go to his area and I
did and he didn't show up. So, I mean,
he didn't even show up when I went to
his area last time to even run away. So,
that's even worse to be honest
because he he didn't even turn up when I
went to his area last time, let alone
run away. So, that's even worse. [snorts]
And, bro, it doesn't matter because when
I ran across the road, he got beat. He
didn't beat me.
So, I mean, he didn't even beat me in
the first place. And then when he called
me out again, he didn't even show up.
So yeah, anyways, I don't care about any
of that [snorts] cuz you're just going
to go round and round and round in
circles and this guy is just never going
to meet anyone.
Brother, you called me to go to your area.
I went to your area and you didn't come out.
You did not come out.
You literally did not come out.
He didn't beat me. I ran across the
road. I ran across the road and we was
pushing each other. Yeah, we was pushing
each other. He didn't win. How did he
win, bro? He didn't even knock me to the
floor. He didn't knock me to the floor,
right? He didn't knock me to the floor
or do anything. He didn't beat me at
all. And then when I told him to come
around the corner away from the public
eye, he didn't want to do it. So, he did
not beat me. He did not beat me. It
wasn't a Prime incident where Prime beat
me. This guy didn't beat me. That's not
even me being awkward.
Yeah, that's not even me being awkward.
You didn't You didn't even get me on the
floor, bro. You didn't even get me on
the floor or made me do anything. How
did you beat me? In what universe did
you beat me, bro? In what universe did
you beat me?
What universe did you beat me, bro? Come
on. What universe did you beat me?
Come on. Listen, I'll do you a deal
right now, Toby. You come here right now
and I will pay for your Uber. I'll smash
your face in and I'll let you stay the night.
If you're really on that If you're
really about that life, you will do it.
Yeah. This years ago, you beat me. I
turned up. Oh, bro. Whatever you Why
don't you get an Uber right now?
Why don't you get an Uber right now?
I'll smash your face in and I'll let you
stay the night.
That's a perfect I mean that's a perfect
offer, you know.
And if you're not going to do that, shut
up. I mean, I've I've offered to pay for your Uber.
So, if you really want to do it, come
and do it. Stop all the past talk with
going back and forth, bro. No one cares.
If you're going to come, just come now.
You know, I'll even I'll even order you
an Uber down the road so it's away from
the house down a nice little alleyway if
you want. And if you're not going to do
it, then shut up. Just shut up. Simple.
I'll pay for your Uber here and back.
I'll pay for it there and back. How
about that one? That's not even a bull.
I'm being deadly serious. And if you're
not going to do it, just shut up, man.
Brother, I'm not bad. No one's banning
you. I'm asking you to come now. I'm
asking you to come now. And do you know
the reason why you didn't come? And
you'll even say this as well, LT, is
because he didn't think I was going to
show up. It's the same thing with Oh,
listen, bro. The reason you didn't show
up last time is because you knew you was
going to get [ __ ] up. You knew that
you was going to get really [ __ ] up.
And you know, even even if I didn't beat
you the first time, you knew the second
time you was going to get [ __ ] up.
You knew for a fact you were going to
get [ __ ] up cuz think about it. You
didn't beat me or do me any damage the
first time. So you knew the second time
you wasn't going to
cuz you're an opportunist, Terry. You're an opportunist.
You are an opportunist. You're a bit
like that Lord J. You're opportunists.
Even if you meet someone and they don't
beat you, because they throw up a fuss
and because they've done something that
you didn't think they were going to do,
even if they didn't beat you, you're not
going to want round two. That's why you
didn't come out. That's exactly why you
didn't come out last time. Tell the
truth. Tell the truth. That's why you
didn't come out last time.
Cuz what you probably thought is Yeah.
Listen, listen, listen. I'll tell you
what it is. What you thought last time
when you when you showed up. Yeah. You
didn't think I was going to show up. And
even though I ran across the road, I
eventually stopped. And you didn't do
any damage. You didn't knock me out. You
didn't knock me to the floor. And you
knew you wouldn't you weren't going to
win the second time.
And that's it. Tell me I'm lying, bro.
Tell me right now I'm lying. I'm not
How many? I'm not lying, bro. It's like
L as well. You know L J. Okay. You know
you know when you come on the door that
time L. Yeah. This is why Timmy backs me
now. How what did I have to say for him
to come in the door? What did Timmy have
to do for him to go to Timmy? Do you
understand? They're opportunists. People
like you. You weigh up things like that.
That's what you do.
That's what you do, bro. You weigh up
things. And even if you don't beat them,
even if you don't beat them, like it's
hard to explain what I mean. Like you
don't have to beat them.
Oh yeah, Prime beat me. Yeah, Prime beat me. Yeah.
I'm not saying he didn't beat me, but
Terry Terry did not [ __ ] beat me, bro.
But I'll be calling him out anyways
before I go read him just to see if he
wants to meet. I'll give a notice as well.
I don't know, bro. He is here. Yeah,
but you you did get scared, Terry, cuz I
asked you to come around the corner. You
wouldn't come around the corner
when it got broke up. So, you knew you
weren't going to win. You knew the
second time you was going to get your
ass whooped. You knew you was going to
get your ass whooped.
It doesn't matter if Prime beat me. You
knew you was going to get your ass whooped.
You didn't think I was going to turn up.
That's what it is. You didn't think I
was going to turn up. You just thought
I'm going to and you're not and he's not
going to turn up and that's what you
thought. You thought I weren't going to turn up.
You know, that's what that's what it
was. You didn't think I was going to
turn up. And then when someone actually turns up
and even though they might have ran
across the road, eventually I stopped, I
put the car into into reverse. So, and
you couldn't beat me. You couldn't
handle me. You didn't put me on the floor.
Think about it, bro. I'm not lying. You
can't even tell me I'm lying. You
haven't tried to meet me, Terry. I went
to your area and you didn't come out.
How have you tried to meet me? How have
you tried to meet me when I came to your
area, you didn't come out? What the
[ __ ] How How have you tried to meet me?
Okay, listen. Why don't you meet me
tomorrow in Stratford?
You know, why don't you meet me tomorrow
in Stratford if you want? We'll meet
halfway. Come on. You know,
brother, listen. Terry, Terry, Terry,
Terry, Terry. I came to your area and
you didn't come out.
Do you not understand? One second. One
second. One second.
You told me to come to your area and you
did not come out. Let me try and explain
it to you again. Why did you not come out?
Tell everybody why you did not come out.
in Turnpike Lane. Tell everyone.
Uh you follow through with Stratford,
I'll pay you. I will follow through with
it. Yeah. Listen, listen. You meet Okay.
Okay. Okay. Yeah. Go to Stratford
tomorrow and I'll meet you. Yeah.
So, listen. One second. One second. One
second. Why is it that when I come to
your area, you didn't show up? Can you
ask him um LT why he didn't show up when
I went to his area last time?
He's not answering me. He continuously
keeps ignoring me. So, you're not
biased, are you? I came to turnpike lane
and you didn't show up.
Why did you not show up?
Because you're not about that life. So
anything that you say now, you just look silly.
You know, you look you look very very
very very silly. It is. It's so it's
it's ridiculous. I went to your area and
you did not show up
and you're still trying to act the big man.
It doesn't make sense. You know,
nonslegs. At least he knows that he will
never meet anyone and he's a [ __ ] But
you're actually still trying to act like
you're trying to fight people, bro. But
you're not trying to fight people
because we've all seen when I was in
your area live and you didn't come out.
A bit like Mark Samson. Oh, Mark Samson
was on the other day. I don't know whose
channel we I forget whose channel he was
on, but he was on someone's channel. So,
you're trying to act the big man when
you didn't turn up. That doesn't even make sense.
And you just keep reversing and and
changing the subject. You called me out
to come to your area and you didn't come out.
Doesn't matter if you won or you lost,
you didn't come out. Yeah. You know,
you know what I'm saying? No, it's is
it's his it's his turn to come to me
now. Or Stratford. We said Stratford.
No, no, no. I'm not going there. He can
meet me halfway.
He can meet me halfway.
It's just the same argument, bro. It's
just the same argument. Well, listen.
I'll meet you in Stratford tomorrow. Yeah.
You know, and if you're not going to
meet me tomorrow in Stratford, then
you're a [ __ ] house. That's the way it's
going to end. That's it. So, that's
halfway for both of us.
>> I should have to go to North London
again. You didn't turn up the last time.
So, because you can't be trusted. Okay.
Okay. Let me put it this way. So,
because you can't be trusted to come
out, because you can't be trusted, no
one's going to come to your area now
because you can't be trusted. Because
when someone went to your area last
time, you didn't come out. So, if you
don't meet me in Stat If you don't meet
me, if you don't meet me in Statford,
I'm done with you. Simple. Yeah. If you
don't meet me in Stratford, I'm done with you. You know that's that.
So I'll meet you in Stratford tomorrow.
Yeah, kid. I'm going to the dentist
tomorrow anyways. So
yeah. Why are you still trying to act
like the big man, bro? You're not a big
man. You're a little wimp. You're a mont
ugly little wimp. And if you come out
that day, you would have knew what you
would have known what time it was.
You would have known what time it was.
and you know it as well. That's why you
didn't show up. You didn't even show up.
You're a little [ __ ] You can sit there
and say, "Oh, you
you did not show up. Shut up. You didn't
I came to your area and you didn't show
up. You're a [ __ ] Shut up, man." Yeah.
You didn't show up.
If you really thought that you beat me,
you wouldn't have called me out again.
You wouldn't have called me out again.
If you really believe that you won, you
wouldn't have called me out again. You
called me out again and you didn't show up.
You did not show up when I was in your
area. How does that make sense? You
know, you're not about that life, man. [ __ ] off. [snorts]
Yeah, you need to get some new trainers,
you [ __ ] bun.
I was going to [ __ ] you up, bro, and
show everyone your ugly face.
I was going to show everyone that you're
the you're the [ __ ] mutter with terrible traders.
Yeah, that's not what happened. Yeah.
You need to stop it. You're not about
that life, lad. You're just like
nonslegs. You're not about that life.
You're really, really not about that life, mate.
You had several chances to put me on the
floor and you never You didn't even get
one hit on me.
You know, you you you did you didn't
even get one hit on me. What the [ __ ] No, no.
So, you coming to Stratford tomorrow?
But yeah, I can I can I can I can talk
smack because the reason I can talk
smack is because when I went to his
area, he didn't even turn up.
So that's exactly how I can talk smack.
That's exactly how I can talk smack
because you called me to your area and
you didn't come out. So that's exactly
how I can keep talking smack cuz you
didn't even show up. >> [snorts] >> So,
I don't know why you're still doing this
in 2026, Terry. I could knock you out
with one hand,
you know? I could literally knock you
out with one [ __ ] hand.
You're not about that life. I don't know
why you're still I would even say Tiger
stronger than you. And that's saying
something. Tiger's [ __ ] stronger than you, you know. Jesus Christ.
Listen, come to Stratford tomorrow.
Come to Stratford tomorrow.
Come to Stratford tomorrow, mate. Yeah. Simple. No, no,
bro. This is boring now, bro. This is
just the same [ __ ]
Yeah. Listen LT
listen LT. So what do you think about
Terry saying for for me to come to his
area and him not showing up? What do you
think about that? So
I mean there is no pattern because if he
doesn't come to Strapford I'm not meeting him.
So there is no pattern. There is no
nothing until he leaves his area. I'm
not meeting him. So I'm not going around
in circles. There's no going around in
circles. You come to Stratford or I'm
not meeting you.
Easy way to break the cycle. I went to
your area. You didn't come out. End of.
Until you come to Statford, I'm not meeting you.
Nothing else. So that's it.
That's it. You come to Stratford,
right? Not interested in the past. Come
to Stratford. Oh, I'm not meeting you, you know.
Okay, you send me you send me 100 Okay,
you send me £100 and I'll go there tomorrow.
Is that a deal?
You send me £100 and I'll go there tomorrow.
Okay, I'll go there tomorrow. But I'm
not wasting my money on an Uber. I'll
just get the train there. [gasps]
No, I'm just going to go there and go live. Yeah.
Yeah. So, that I'm going to do that
tomorrow and I'm going to stop talking
about it then. Yeah. Simple.
No, I need to go to the dentist
tomorrow. I'm busy. I'm busy tomorrow.
So, I'm going to go after.
Nah, I don't need £100, bro. I don't
need to rip someone off £100. I've got
money, man. I've got money, mate. I
don't need to rip someone off £100.
Why would I want to rip someone off 100
[ __ ] pounds, mate? Come on. You know,
I need to go to the dentist tomorrow so
I can't [snorts] be up too late.
I hate that. You know, I can never sleep
properly when I've got to go somewhere
tomorrow cuz you know, you can't just lie in.
All right, LT, you know that I know I
know a white guy with a black brother.
They're half brothers. You know that.
I'll be meeting you tomorrow anyway.
Send me the£100. I'm not changing the
subject, but send me the £100 and I'm
going to go there tomorrow after the dentist.
I'm not changing the subject, but I'm
just saying I know a guy that's got um
he's white and he's got a black half brother.
Yeah. Well, know of Yeah. [snorts]
What's your opinion on that?
Do you believe in that kind of stuff? [snorts]
Okay. But I won't,
brother. I've got to go live there tomorrow.
If you're so smart, if you're so smart,
out, let me ask you, let me ask you
this. If you're so smart Yeah. One sec.
One second, bro.
No, I don't believe that. So, I'm
speaking to this guy in Belgium. Yeah.
And he's saying he's saying he's saying,
"Yeah, bro. I'm going to go live tomorrow."
Yeah. And he's saying about my profile.
He said, "Oh, you need better pictures
and stuff." I don't think it's pictures, bro.
What do you think? Um, Steven Howard,
no selfies, whatever. They're just
pictures, in it. I don't I don't think
so, bro. I don't think it matters cuz at
the end of the day, you meet people in
real life in it. So,
nah, I don't think so, bro. Cuz you've
got like three good pictures, even if
the other threes are [ __ ] Even if three
other pictures are [ __ ]
like the other three is good, isn't it?
So, no, I don't believe that, bro. I
don't believe it's it's that
I don't want to get into the whole
dating app thing anyways. I don't use
them. I don't want to I don't want to use them
because I'm going to the dentist tomorrow, [ __ ]
Because I I need to go to bed soon. What
do you think, Steven Howard using better
pictures? Do you reckon it will change
anything on N? [gasps]
Nah, bro. It won't. [snorts]
No, it won't change anything.
I don't think so, bro.
If you don't stop it, Al, I'm going to
get my Belgian friend on you. He's from
Carolina. I forget the I forget where he
told me. It's Kam. I'll get my Belgian
friend on you, bro, if you don't shop.
He's black as well.
He's black, bro. And he would he would
actually do you.
Yeah, he's got dreadlocks.
Yeah, he was on here the other day on
someone else's channel.
What's that place he said? Oh, Cam
Cameroon he's from.
Yeah, he'll do you him, bro. He's a hard
[ __ ] He speaks French. If you're so
intelligent, LT, why didn't you go to Oxford Uni?
Just the same old [ __ ] in it. Trying to
act hard, but everyone just laughs at
Mark now. Everyone laughs at Mark.
Nah, it don't make a difference, bro. Um, listen.
Listen to me. Yeah. Um, if you're so
smart, why didn't you go to act? Why
didn't you go to Oxford Uni?
Can you answer me that?
>> No, they're not good. You know, bro,
people that go to Oxford Uni aren't good.
You people that go to I met this guy.
Yeah. And he was he was mixed race guy.
Yeah. And his brother his
[clears throat] brother's white. They're
half brothers in Liverpool Street. And
the guy and the guy went to Oxford Uni.
Bro, you can't talk to people like them,
bro. They're so stuck up and think
they're better than everyone. They're
just unbearable, bro. Like there's posh.
Yeah. And then there's just like there's
just too stuck up. You can't I can't
bear people like that, bro. And his
friend like come. Then his other friend
come, not the brother. The brother was
all right. And he's he's it was his
brother, the friend, and him. And the
brother and other one was all right. But
him, bro, they're unbearable, bro.
People that go there, they just think
they're better than everyone cuz their
parents are rich. I don't like them kind
of people, you know. Bro, I I really I
don't like them kind of people.
>> He was just bare like snobby, bro.
Like, have you not noticed it? Like proper snobby.
You know what I mean? They just you just
I just can't bear them, bro. >> Like,
yeah. I just don't like people like
that, bro. That just that are just
snobby and that just cuz they're posh.
I don't like people like that, bro.
It was just unbearable.
It was just like proper like
and I was like it's like you can't
reason with them as well. Like I was
like oh yeah oh yeah like it come up in
conversation. I was like oh yeah I like
blow it sounds weird but I was like oh
[ __ ] I was like oh it's kind of a
fetish. And he's like oh no it's not a
fetish. You just kind of like them. And
I said [ __ ] it's a fetish when
rather when someone would rather a
[ __ ] than [ __ ] having sex. And
just like little stuff like that. He was
he was just unbearable bro.
But not his brother and the other guy,
they were all right.
And but his friend come and he was even
worse. You can't like you can't um
what's the word? You can't thing you
with them. What's the word? You can't um
negotiate with them.
Like you can't negotiate with them, bro.
And you can tell obviously they think
they're better than you as well because
obviously they go to Oxford.
No, I don't think he was doing that. He
was just talking [ __ ]
Oh yeah. Was it Timmy's? Yeah, I knew it
wasn't LJ's. It was one. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. But everyone just laughs at Mark
now. But they only started laughing at
Mark when they had a problem with him.
Have you noticed that? You do realize
they all started calling Mark when LJ
had a problem with him. So [snorts] 30
other times when he come on here doing
this, people went along with it. It's
only until LJ started having a problem
with him, then they all started having a
problem with him. Cuz that's what they
do. They follow the crowd. Do you not
understand? They they follow the crowd.
Yeah. They follow the crowd, you see.
So, [snorts] um
yeah, they only started calling him when
when that's the way it works, this
place. Do you not understand?
[laughter] Is it a copycat community? Grezy,
you big fat stinking copycat. [laughter]
It's a copycat community. Yeah.
So, Grievy, this guy from Belgium says I
should have better profiles on dating
apps, but I don't think that's going to
I don't think that's going to make a
difference. What do you think, Greavvesy?
One second. Let me read what you just
wrote, Lie. Not being funny, but when
you get uni jobs, they look at the uni
that you attended. So if your uni is low
down the rankings, chances are you won't
be accepted over someone who is Yeah, I
know. Obviously, but there's no need to
be like snobby and that ain't it.
They're just unbearable. People like
that are just unbearable, bro. His
brother was all right, though.
His brother's friend was all right and
his brother was all right, but him, he
was just he was unbearable, bro. them
kind of people.
It's um just snobs in it. There's no
need for it, bro. Like, I'm from London.
I can pretend I'm better than everyone
just from being from London, but who's
really going to go around doing that? [sighs]
It's weird, isn't it? Yeah. He goes Oxford.
[snorts] That's a very hard uni to get into.
What do you think, Grezy? If I put like
different um dating dating pictures up,
dating profile pictures, do you think
I'll get success
on this on this copycat community?
This copycat community
copycat community. Yeah. [laughter]
What do you think? You reckon I'll get
some success if I update the pictures?
I think my pictures were all right. They
could be better, but I didn't think
there were anything wrong with them.
No, just use me. But just just better quality pictures. [snorts]
So what? And then you think the apps are
going to work?
[snorts] Nah, I don't think I could ever
get into dating apps, bro. They're not for me.
Dating apps are not for me, bro.
Oh, he's gone live. Has he the virgin?
Let me have a little peek.
One second. Why is this not working? [snorts]
Why are you [ __ ] stirring out, bro? Why
do why do you want him to join when you
know that he's a stinking grass as well
as a stinking copycat? You don't like it
when people talk [ __ ] that's never going
to meet you. So why you encourage him to
why are you encouraging him to come on
mine knowing that he's never going to meet me
knowing that I could go [ __ ] mad and
crazy and this little copycat's not
going to meet you. And not only that
he's not going to meet you, he's
actually a big fat stinking grass as
well. You wouldn't like it if someone
done that to you, would you?
This ain't working, bro. This app,
my YouTube app is not working.
Yeah, you wouldn't like it if someone
done it to you.
We both do the same thing as each other.
I went to his area three times, brother,
and went live. He didn't come out.
So, how do we do the exact same thing
when I've gone to his area and I've
actually like tried meeting the [ __ ]
How do you work that one out? How does 2
plus two not add to four?
No, I can say his name whenever I want,
but I call him the virgin. I've always
called him the virgin. the non-legs
Yeah, others went to my area. Okay, but
he but he would never meet me and he's
the one going at me.
This [ __ ] my YouTube app ain't working, bro.
Beat the app and reinstall it. Will my
account still be on there?
Why isn't it not [ __ ] working?
[ __ ] He needs to get laid, mate.
That's what he does.
And delete the app. The app's not working.
G me earlier. Uh um
[sighs and snorts]
yeah, this this guy
I don't have a freedom pass. I wish I
[ __ ] did. My mom does, but I don't.
No, I [ __ ] don't. I wish I [ __ ]
did. Hey, um, Dusty, this guy from
Belgium says that if I've got better
dating app pictures, I'm going to kill it.
Nah, I don't trust I don't.
Uh, the rail card wasn't for disabled
people, but okay. [snorts]
But yeah, this guy from Belgium says I'm
going to kill it if I have better
pictures. I don't believe him.
I don't believe him, bro.
For some reason, I don't believe him.
I'll never get sucked into that thing
again, bro. Them dating apps and that.
I'll never get sucked into it.
I would never ever do it.
I don't think I'd ever get sucked into that again.
That is like it's they're so bad for so
many different reasons. Dating apps are
bad for so many different reasons, I reckon.
Um, the fact that like you don't know
what they look like before meeting them.
There's too much competition.
It's just I just would never get into them, bro.
I can't even go on my YouTube.
[clears throat] Oh, it's working now.
Yeah, I can see that. Is the skin is the
skin virgin live? Oh.
It need to get light.
Yeah. Look, Red Star straight on.
I love it when they do this, bro,
because it proves I'm right about them.
The more they do this, the more it
proves what I'm saying about them is to
be correct. Do you understand, Stephen? Dusty.
The more they do this, the more it shows
that what you're saying is the truth
about them. The more they do this on
YouTube, it it proves it, bro. It does.
It proves my point more than anyone
else. It It proves my point.
No, I was just talking to someone on Instagram. Bro,
if I was trying to date, if I was trying
to if I was going to date on social
media, I would just make my Instagram
profile better and try on Instagram, but
I wouldn't use dating apps.
Yeah, that red star is constantly on YouTube, man.
No, my sister was speaking facts. My
sister basically said that she's been on
um the My sister said, "Yeah, LT, that
she's been on um that she's been on um
people's uh uh YouTube on here." And she
basically says, "Have you noticed that
none of them are [snorts] handsome?
They're all fat and ugly." And she
thinks that's where the jealousy comes
from. which is basically what I've said
as well. There's a lot of jealousy on
this community. And if you think about
it, it is true. Like these people really
are I hate saying it, bro, but they are
fat and ugly and you are better looking
than them. And that's why they go for
you, which is what I've been saying all
along, you know, and I' I've said that
all along with these people.
They're asked to come on camera several
times. They will not show their faces.
every time they show their faces.
Oh, L J's, Timmy's,
um, she's seen other people in it. So,
and and stuff and she thinks, "Oh, yeah,
they're" And I knew that anyways.
And she never heard me ever say that. I
knew that. Everyone knows it. For people
to sit there on YouTube every day doing
this, it shows that they're either
jealous or they're gay. It's either It's
one or two. They're either jealous of
you or they want to [ __ ] you.
Um, so there's there's, you know, that's
the end of that, bro. Unless I mean the
day that someone does this every day and
they're as young as me and they're
better looking than me, then I'll be
like, "Okay, fair enough." But that will
never happen. That day, that day will
That day will never ever happen where
these people are young and they're
better looking than me. That will never
happen. These people that do this every
day on here, that would never happen.
How did she find their channels? Because
she knows about L J. So she probably
went on L J's Timmy's. Obviously Nlex
wears glasses. It's obvious, bro.
They're [ __ ] stinking ugly.
Why do you think they're on here every
day, bro? Doing this like Red Star and
that. Why do you think they're on here?
Think about it, bro. It's not even You
just put two and two together.
Yeah. So, and that's and that she Yeah.
She was probably talking about them three.
It's obvious, bro. We all know why they do this.
A lot of these people do this, lad.
All of these people are uglier than you.
They're older than you. Everyone knows that.
That harass and stalk and all this
madness. We know that, bro. We
absolutely know that.
I never said everyone on here is
jealous. I don't think everyone on here is jealous.
I don't think everyone is, but I think a
lot of people are.
I don't think Charlie's jealous. I don't
think How hard can it be? He's jealous.
I don't think Ben Fury is jealous. I
don't think these people are jealous of
anyone judging by their um thing. And I,
you know, you can, like I said, you can
tell. You can you can tell, you know,
and how and how like dedicated they are
at doing this
all they've got is hate and bitterness
for somebody that they don't know. Bro,
it doesn't it doesn't add up that
they've got a better life than you.
Why would Why would I I never said you
were jealous of me. I'm saying that
these people are jealous. I never said
you're jealous. I'm saying that these
people are jealous.
like Red Star, Nonss,
um all the people that are writing
paragraphs every day. It's not adding up, lad.
Those were just three that came to mind.
But no, there are definitely jealous
people in this community.
They are definitely there's definitely a
lot of jealous people in this community,
bro. Because of what they I think I've
got more people obsessed with me than Timmy.
Definitely. Definitely. Definitely.
And then and then they always say and
then they always say, "Oh, what have you
got to be jealous of?" Well, come on
camera and show your face. And they
won't do it. So,
you know, you're you're,
you know, your life doesn't have to be
perfect, bro. These people are [ __ ]
fat, stinking ugly. Because the way that
I've got it in my head, yeah, is if
someone's better, if someone's worse
than me, I don't waste my time on them.
And that's how someone should do if
someone's if someone if you're better
than someone, right? Yeah.
You wouldn't dedicate your life to
[ __ ] with them unless you was in love
with them or you you know, so that you
wouldn't dedicate your life to someone
that especially somebody that you've
never met. You know, that's just that's
just common sense.
Rob people up the wrong way, brother.
These people have never met me. I mean,
they've never met me.
No, I think Ronald Pump was right.
You're you're better looking than them.
You got more money than them and it
kills them. I think my man was right.
You know, bro, I think my man was right.
You're younger. You're better looking.
You got more money than them. It's the
truth. That is facts, bro. I never see
that account anymore, but it's facts
because the way these people go on, they
It's the truth, bro. it. I think that
guy was right to be honest with you. But
I don't think it's necessarily just just
money. I don't think it's necessarily
like money. I don't think it's just
money as well, bro. Because think about
it right here. These people like someone
on here I don't think it's just that
because these someone could have more
money than me on here, but I'm still
younger. I'm still better looking than
them. I can still go out and do stuff.
They're sat indoors. I don't think it's
all about money, bro.
But obviously you've got more money than
them and you're better looking than
them. So, and you've got more of a life
than them as well. So, obviously that's
it. But it wouldn't [snorts] it would
take more than just money. Do you know
what I mean?
You know, it would take more than just money,
my lad. The police have got my passport.
You should feel lucky I'm doing this.
Passport's right here, lad. Brand
spanking new one.
Possible right here. Brand smack one.
You really do talk [ __ ] don't you,
mate? Yeah, but you're young compared to
these people. Yeah, but you're young
compared to these people. You are still
technically in your 20s. These people
are old men, bro.
These people are old men.
And if you see this community LT,
they've got nothing new or nice to say
about anyone. Have you noticed that
they've got nothing new or nice to say about anyone?
So, if anyone's really trying to better
themselves, I suggest they want they
shouldn't come on this community. Even
if they're not talking about you,
they've got nothing new or nice to say about anyone.
If people are trying to better
themselves, they they need to be
surrounded by like positive people. Um
they need to be they need to be
surrounded by positive uh people and not
haters every day. And that's how you
know these people are the worst version
of themselves to sit online every day
promoting hate to people that they don't
know. They're not living their what
they're not living their living their
their best lives.
Sorry to say it, but it's the truth.
Sorry to bore you, but it's it's the
truth. And yet, you haven't even done
anything that bad. Think about it, man.
Pat Mustard put kids all over YouTube.
No one had a problem with that. Look at
Look at what Pat Mustard done. All of
the stuff that I've done was in retaliation. You know,
and that's it.
You know, a lot a lot of what I've said
and done is out of retaliation.
So, you know, it's like if Pat Mustard
started talking about raping [ __ ]
kids, no one would have a problem with it.
So, at the end of the day, mate, like
it's not about what you said because
look at all of the stuff Pat Mustard did
to Monty's kids. So, at the end of the
day, everyone licked his ass. Everyone
liked Pat Mustard. So it isn't anything
to do with what you've said, you know.
It isn't anything to do with what you
said because Pat Mustard's done worse.
So that's that.
Everyone liked Fat Mustard
even though he puts people's kids up.
You put people's kids all over the
internet. So, it's not about what you've said.
Yeah, I know I did. And I got [ __ ] for
it and he never. That's what I'm saying.
I got [ __ ] for it and he never
um Yeah, I know I did.
Monty's. Yeah, but I got [ __ ] for it.
Pat never. That's what I'm saying. So,
you know, you've You know, the maddest
thing is, you know, back on the
PlayStation community, kids were never
mentioned. Did you know that
kids were never ever mentioned? No
racism, no kids. As [ __ ] up as it was.
Yeah. The the the community I was on
with Monty. Yeah. There was no one's
kids ever mentioned. You do realize
that? Nothing. None of that [ __ ] was
ever mentioned until I come on this community.
No, not one person's kids was ever
mentioned. You do realize that? It's
only until we come Well, I come on this community.
So that's that's saying a lot, bro. You
know, and it must have started somewhere.
It must have started from somewhere. No
one ever spoke about anyone's kids back on PlayStation. Yeah, man.
I found it through Timmy Eldridge.
And even if you go on like a nonsg's
channel, they're all obsessed. Like this
poo account, look, these are middle-aged
ugly old men obsessed with me every day.
Their life's losers, bro. Think about
what they're doing. And I found I found
it on um I found it cuz of Timmy.
Do you know what? I wish I never got
introduced to gambling, you know? Then I
would have never been on this community,
you bit of gambling. It's not even that
bad cuz I've won and I've still had a
life. So, it never really ruined my
life. Could have done without it. But,
you know, it's not too bad. But, bro, I
wish I never gamble cuz then I never
found this community. The gambling is
not even that bad cuz I won and I still
lived a life and I still had the house
and you know, it's bad. It is bad, but
you know, I wish I never found this community, bro.
Um, I found these videos in 2018. I
think I found these videos in 2018, but
I come on here in 2020.
So, I found him a couple of years before
coming on and I found Charlie and that
and then I come on and Yeah.
Yeah. That's how I found him. But I wish
I never got introduced to gambling
because of because of cuz of because of
this community, bro. It's not even gambling itself.
I'll meet him when I go live. Lad,
you sit on here and hate every day. I
don't get it.
No, I've been on here since No, I think
it was 2019 I've been on here. My
mistake. I think it was 2019.
Why do you think these people do this
every day, Gary? Do you think they're gay?
Well, you will see it because I'll just go live.
You don't need to have a perfect life,
bro. Like you don't need to have a
perfect life for people to be jealous.
You know what I mean? You don't have to
have a perfect life. It's hard to
explain it. Like the thing is like these
people, these haters can come on here
and try and critique your life. Yeah.
And say that you're this and you're that
and you're this and you're that and
you're this and you're that. But the thing is,
what are they? Like, oh no, no, no. One
second. One second. What are they? They
can sit there and say that you're this
or you live with your mom, but bro, what
are they? Fat, stinking old men. Like,
think about it.
So, your life doesn't have to be your
life does not have to be perfect in
order like it's hard to explain it. Like,
I can't explain it, bro. But, you know,
your life don't have to be perfect for
people to be jealous of someone. You
know what I mean?
Like I'd be very surprised if some of
these people even leave their house to
be honest with you. A lot of these
people I'd be very surprised, you know,
sat on YouTube hating every day. It's
madness. I couldn't do it, bro. I
honestly couldn't do it. I seriously
seriously could not do it. Like it's me,
it's mental, you know.
And they're saying, and even when you
come on here all day, Yeah. Even when
you come on here all day. Yeah. Say you
come on here all day. Like say you come
on here all day. Say you come on here
all day. Yeah. And the thing is is that
if you come on here Yeah. for 5 hours a
day for a week, it also proves that
they've got no life because they're on
here with you. So theoretically, if they
had a life, you should just be talking to yourself.
You know, if they're on here constantly
with you, then that just also shows that
they've got no life. Man,
just like Christmas that was on YouTube Christmas. So,
I just don't understand it, bro. This is
supposed to be a gambling community, not
a [ __ ] hateful community. [ __ ] mad.
But yeah, I do think people like Red Star that
I do think they're jealous, bro. I would
put money on it, bro. Sorry, but I I do
think they are because, like I said,
they're worse than you. No matter what
they want to say about you, they're
worse than you. Looks, [ __ ] money,
[ __ ] no family. Like, they're they're
worse than you in every way, bro. Like,
it's not even one thing.
That's my opinion anyways. Who knows?
They put Maybe they put their camera on
one day and they're younger and maybe
they're like, well, they don't have to
be younger. Maybe they're younger and
good-looking. Who knows? Doubtful, though.
It's just weird. Like
very very weird. Can you hear me? Yeah. Who knows? Yo. Yo.
Phone's [ __ ] I think.
Yeah, you need to do stuff this year, Grezy. Man,
you're actually like wasting your life,
bro. Like, you actually need to do
something, brother. I've I've already
done a lot. Not as much as I can do, but
I've still [ __ ] can look back and
[ __ ] I've done and that, bro. But come on, man. You know,
I think you should spend like 3 months
doing something or 6 months,
you know? You don't want to look back.
Like, obviously me, I've done a lot of
stuff and obviously I'm still going to
be doing stuff eventually, but don't
want to look back, man, and think [ __ ]
you know, you wasted your life, bro. You
know what I mean?
just even if just go like you wanted to
go to Scotland just go to Scotland you
know and you don't have to go abroad I'm
not talking about abroad just do what
you want to things that you wanted to do
you know [sighs]
I think once I go to a couple of places
I've done um I've done most of what I
wanted to do bro
that's why I don't feel hard done by
because I've done so much stuff
that's why when I was when I was in JD
the other day I didn't think oh I need
to buy this oh cuz I've had it all broke
I've got money and I have and I've had
it all. So, I've had the restaurants,
I've done the drinking, I've had the
I've got the designer clothes. You know
what I mean, lad?
Like I said, if I was to spend £200,
£250, I'd go out spending it and
enjoying myself [snorts] rather than
buying garments. I would just enjoy myself.
Um, what happened?
Hey, he doesn't come on anymore.
I didn't know about that Jack the Ripper
putting things up his bum to be fair.
But you know [snorts] that Jo um
LT, he wears 30 next jeans.
I wear 200 pound money jeans.
Yeah, I wear 200 pound of money jeans. Bro,
what do you think about 30 jeans? So,
what I mean is if I need clothes, I'll
buy like good jeans and good trainers.
But but um how do I explain it, bro?
It's hard to explain. I wouldn't I
wouldn't wear cheap stuff when I need to buy stuff.
You know what I mean,
bro? Bro, quality things don't don't
ever run out of don't run out of
fashion, bro. Quality jeans don't run
out of fashion.
They never They never run out of fashion, bro.
They never I'm wearing vapors. I got vapor.
They cost me 210. I got vapors.
Bro, it's like Lacost and Ralph Lauren.
How long have they been going? You know,
I can't wear I can't wear cheap jeans.
I can't wear cheap jeans, bro. And the
thing is, LT, it's a good price. You
know, you know, £200, that's lasting you
three years, mate.
Yeah, I know. I know. I know what you're saying. Yeah.
But like you know 200 pound you buy you
pay 200 pound for jeans they're lasting
you years mate. My ones [snorts] lasted
me like two and a half years and the
button the button went out on him. The
button [ __ ] broke so I bought some new ones. Yeah. [snorts] Yeah, bro.
No, I'd rather spend money now and just
like going out, eating good food and
that if I was to spend money, bro,
but I got them I've got them Stone
Island jumpers, bro. If I I could buy
another one. I could buy four or five of
them, but I'd rather just go out and
just spend money going out and [ __ ]
To be fair,
if I would like to spend money that Oh. [groaning]
I don't know, bro.
So, what jeans do you wear then? [sighs]
What jeans do you wear, LT?
We pretty much wear similar stuff
like the Vapor, the jeans. We pretty
much wear [ __ ] similar [ __ ] don't we?
But you know what though? That I tell
you what though. Yeah. That Timmy is a
[ __ ] bro. You know the thing is, yeah,
you don't need to wear designer stuff.
You can wear you can look good. Yeah.
And at a reasonable [ __ ] good price.
He is just a straight champ tra champ,
bro. Like there's a difference, you know, between,
you know, it's like you can you can go,
for example, okay, I you can buy a nice
pair of trainers, you can buy a nice
white t-shirt. Yeah. And [ __ ] what?
You know, um, not Primark. Not Primark, but
what's the thing? Uh,
not Primark. [ __ ] like
even S jeans. So you don't you don't
need to spend big big money as long as
you got a nice pair of trainers. But he
the way he dresses, bro. And and the
maddest thing with him is he's had
money. That's the thing. He's had money.
And you can't sit there and say, "Oh,
well some people because no, like you
don't have to buy designer stuff. We're
not saying that you have to buy designer stuff.
You don't have to. You can wear good
clothes for a cheap price if you wanted to."
But some people they're just like
they're just tramps
really. Like it's really really are.
Yeah. I don't either to be fair. I went
in and JD. I could have easily bought a
tracksuit the other day, but I never I
don't really care, bro.
All I got is my nice little Rit the Bear
trousers and my little shoes. Put my
dancing shoes on. That's all I need. Is
[snorts] that right, Grezy?
I'd rather spend I'd rather spend money
on an escort probably now than buy
expensive clothes. That's how bad it is.
Getting my leg over. Yeah.
Rather spend money getting my [ __ ]
leg over, bro.
If I won like £300. Yeah. I was just
going to spend one 150. I would just
spend it on an escort, bro.
rather than that
getting my leg over
because the thing is LT as they say
you can never regret having too much
punang on your deathbed you know
punang on your deathbed you can never
you can never you you can't bro you literally on. [sighs] All right.
And I'm not owning Greavves at all. I'm
trying to help little Greavvesy.
Grieves is a bit older than me, but I've
done You're older than me, Greavvesy,
but I've done more than you in life.
Well, at least you don't copy people's holidays.
At least you're not a little copycat. [gasps]
At least you don't copy people.
You dirty stinking copycat. Yeah.
All right, let me have a look, bro.
Yeah, that's the past. Yeah.
Is that right, LT?
Because I only get [ __ ] That's why.
Yeah, I'm scared of him. Really?
Yeah, I'm not scared of anyone, matey.
I'm not scared of anyone. [snorts]
Yeah, but it's better than nothing. I do
it because I don't want to go through
the [ __ ] of approaching and having
to deal with their [ __ ] and that. Well,
I don't use escorts anymore, but when I
did, I used to.
I don't have the only fans because I
just didn't want to deal with their [ __ ]
You have to be really mad to want to put
yourself through that, bro. That is mad.
I don't know how I did it for so long. Yeah,
there's different reasons why people do it. But yeah,
that's what I have done.
That's what I have done.
What I done with the Only Fans when I
used to use it like once a month.
That's all you need. I can have that one
sex once a month. I could have one. I
could have sex once a month and that's it.
If I could find someone I could [ __ ]
without a condom, I would just use them
once a month and then just get move on
with my life. That's what I would do.
Yeah, it's not going to happen. That
boy, lad. It's not going to happen. Do
Do you want to Do you want to know what
my opinion on this that boy? You know, I
was I I sent Ant-Man this yesterday.
Yeah. And I sent a couple of other people this.
But the thing is the thing is do do you
know why I I don't I I don't believe
that. Well, there's two reasons why I
don't believe that.
Well, three reasons why I don't believe
that. There's actually three reasons why
I don't believe it.
I don't believe that, bro. Not in this
day and age.
Oh, [ __ ] [snorts] Ant-Man's
girlfriend was like, "Oh, he should come
to Thailand. He's good-looking." Antman
Ant-Man's girlfriend can't believe I
can't meet anyone. She She doesn't
believe me. She's like, "Oh yeah, you
should come to Thailand. We'll get you
someone within a day."
Oh, that's funny as [ __ ] But no,
listen. I do want Do you want to know
why I don't believe that? That boy.
Do you want to know why I don't believe
that you'll find someone?
And by you, I mean me.
Oh, that looks like an updated terminal.
And it's very and it's quite logical. I
think what I'm going to say is actually quite logical. [snorts]
It's very very very very very very
unlikely you're going to meet someone.
Very very very very very unlikely.
People will be giving you the same
advice when you're 50
and you're [ __ ]
and you're [ __ ] you can't even get
your dick up. They're still going to be
telling you the same thing.
Are you still there? That boy.
Do [snorts] you want to know Steven
Howard why I I think you're not going to
meet? Is anyone any Is anyone interested
in in hearing?
And I want you to give me your thoughts on it. [snorts]
I don't think that you're going to meet
anyone. So, the first reason being is is
that you haven't had a date since April
or March. I still can't remember which
one it was. April, March, despite going
out a million times. So, you haven't got
a date. You haven't got any. I don't
even think I've kissed anyone since
then. So, there's been no little
successes, no dates. God knows how many
people that I've approached. Also, um
the other thing is is that um I've given
up now for about a month and a half
since I last went out with my sister.
Now, I've been browsing these
approaching videos who I follow on
Instagram. this black guy, this white
guy, whatever. And every single
approaching video that I've seen is
the same. It's the same [ __ ] They all
act the same way. So even when I've
given up, so I've given up dating now.
I'm watching other guys approach and
they're getting the same [ __ ] and not
one of them has been different. So
that's the second one. And the third one
is that um is is that it would have just
changed by now.
you know, how how often has it been
where where you've where where you've
come into money or things that's good
has happened all over these years and
this has stayed exactly the same. So, I
think that is logical. That's a logical
enough reason to to think that
that's not it's not going to happen
because if you look over the years on
things that changed for the good, this
is the same. This is never going to change.
I think that's that's that's logical, bro. So,
I don't I I think that's logical what
I'm saying, Greaves. Yeah. I I think that's logical
because at the end of the day, bro, like
you um and the amount of [ __ ] as well,
like you know, you have to deal with the
[ __ ] Oh, you're too old, you're too
young for me. Oh, even that Muslim that
was trying to lie to me as well, I told
her I'm not an idiot. And all of that
toxic [ __ ] as well, bro. Like, [ __ ]
that. Hell no.
So, I think that is logical.
You can wake up one day and win the lottery.
You'll wake up one day and you'll still be single
or sexless or whatever. That's That is
true. That is true.
So, I think like there's no uh there's
literally no hope and that's why I don't
try because if I generally believe there
was hope, I would try.
But there literally is no hope. So, I'm
not going to try.
And it isn't about money either. I've
got money and I get more money than what
I used to get as well, bro. Even when I
was on 700 a month, I was going out every week.
You know, when you first told me about
this whole uh going out [ __ ] LT, I was
on like 700 pound a month and I was
still going out every week.
Don't ask me how I could afford it, but
I did it. So, you know, you'd always find ways.
If you have hope, there's a will and
there's a way. I get more than that now.
So, at the end of the day, like, you
know, you would you would if you had if
you had hope, if you had hope, you you
you would do something.
You know, you'd find ways to make more
money. You'd you'd find ways to lower
the cost of things. You'd find a way. If
a man has got hope, they'd find a way.
There was no hope.
Unless I meet someone on social media.
So, I mean, unless someone on social
media is going to prove they're different. So, yeah.
What do you think, Steven Howard?
I think what I'm saying is is true.
And also, it's been going on for years
as well. It hasn't been going on for
months. This has been going on for years.
This has actually been going on for
years now. And it's like what Ant-Man
says, it's been going on for years.
So, that's that, lad. Like, it's not
going to be any different.
It's not going to be any different. And
then when you try it, it's going to make
you worse. So it's like you're pretty much [ __ ]
I have no desire to try again.
No desire, bro.
It's never going to happen, lad.
Oh, you made Yeah, you made up Yeah, you
said about football to fit in. Yeah,
just when you was talking about Cheryl
Cole, you said that to fit in as well,
you little copycat.
Yeah, just like when you was talking
about Yeah. You You pretended you like
football, you also was talking about
Sher Cole, you little cubby.
You little cubby.
Yes, you [ __ ] did say that she was
hot. You said if if you said if you
don't find her attractive, you're gay. I
swear to God you said that. I swear to
God in my mom's life, he said if you do
not find her attractive, you are gay.
No, you didn't say that to annoy me, you
little [ __ ] [ __ ] It was when I was
I'm listening to this live stream back.
Sorry, one second. Yeah, I was No, no,
no, no. This is back when I was meeting
you and you did start talking about Chev
to fit in. Yes, you did.
No, no, no, no. You said that if you do
not find her attractive, you're gay. And
when he got caught to be a stinking
copycat, Griezy, he was trying to
retract his statement.
You can't she's attractive. That's what
he used to say.
Oh, no. It is something that I'm trying
to say. It definitely is something that
I'm trying to say. You said that if you
don't find her attractive, you're gay.
No, no, no, no, no. That that literally
is something I'm that you said. Yeah.
How can I whack him when you know the
guy's never going to meet me? That's
another thing. You know that he's a
police informant. You know he's never
going to meet anyone. So yeah, I don't
know why you're telling people. Yeah, good point.
Yeah. People copy each other to fit in.
You copy. You copy each other. You copy people.
You look he says that he said that he
liked football to fit in.
Oh, dusty [clears throat] on his live
stream. He's saying yeah that he used to
pretend to like football to fit in.
He's a stinking copycat, Grezy. He's a
big fat stinking copycat.
He's a big fat stinky moldy copycat.
That's [ __ ] hilarious.
You didn't lose me, Albert Square, but
you keep telling yourself that, matey.
If if if you lost me at Albert Square,
why am I still sat here with more money than you?
You didn't lose me no Albert Square. Oh,
that reminds me. I need to do a video
about that just in case the wrong people
believe you, mate. Listen, I tell you
what you did do. Yeah. Right. You You
tried stopping my benefit money. Yeah.
And literally what happened when you
tried stopping my benefit money? It was
only £180, [clears throat] by the way.
Right. What did I do? What did I do,
mate, when you tried stopping £180 when
I was getting three grand a month? I
literally went to your area and had you
stopped leaving your house for two weeks
over over £180. I somehow don't think
that you've took £1,800 out of me, mate,
a month. I really don't. Not me. You
didn't, mate. No, you never.
You tried stuffing my benefits and
because I had to send them [ __ ] I had
to send them like bank statements, bro.
And it cost me like 40 quid. And I
thought, "No, no, no, no, no. This
country is going to pay for that." You
know, even thinking that you're going to
try and stop my money. Yeah, mate. I'm
going to your area. I'm doing posters.
See, if they kept this See, the thing
is, LT, if they kept this uh off of
YouTube, I won't I was never going to do
posters. You know that I was never ever
going to do these posters. If if they
never ever done this, I was never going
to do the posters. I threatened it, but
I don't think I was going to do it, bro.
He went running to the police. He didn't
come on YouTube for 2 weeks. He ran off
of YouTube for 2 3 weeks. He did not go
to that event and he was crying to the
police. Let's not all forget what
happened. And that was over £180. And
it's not the point. You're not going to
try and stop any of my money. That's the
difference between being YouTube and not being YouTube.
I put posters all around the gaff, mate.
all around the gaff. And that was
because he tried to get my money
stopped. The benefits
like the small like it doesn't matter
though. It was £180, bro. Like he he
they wanted to harass me and tried to
stop my money and I done that. So you
really think that you've stopped me
getting two grand a month, bro? Come on
now. That never happened. Stop telling yourself that.
Yeah. Yeah. Do you remember that when
they were trying to get people's money
stopped? And that's what makes me laugh,
LT. Yeah. When they say that it's just
YouTube. It's not just YouTube. You
know, when they say that, oh, it's just
YouTube. But how can it be just YouTube,
bro? When these, you know what I'm
saying? Like, it's like Yeah.
Yeah. But, bro, I left I left before that anyways.
I left before the posters,
you know. I left before all of them
posters. You do realize that?
I left the house like a week before
that. So it never happened whilst I was
living here. But yeah, it did like my
mom and [ __ ] Yeah, but not mate. I
weren't living there, bro. When that happened.
Yeah. Yeah. When when they send the
letters, I weren't living there, bro.
I weren't living there cuz I won't I
wouldn't I wouldn't have left because of
the posters. I wouldn't have left.
I I left the week before that because of
um Why did I leave?
No. No. People, I tell you how I left,
bro. Because my [ __ ] mom locked the
door because [ __ ] people's messaging
on YouTube, things that I was saying and
I was being loud over gambling and then
she just chucked me out, bro. And then
the post just happened like a week later.
Yeah. It happened like a week later,
bro. It never happened whilst I was living here
and then I went back to Elbert Square.
I was I would have never left. If they
put up posters, bro, where I'm living
like say I would never leave. I would
never ever ever leave. [sighs] So So
yeah. Yeah. The posters then they done
the posters again, but then the
neighbors know about them in it. So
yeah, the neighbors know about them,
bro. So yeah, [snorts]
but I done post this because he tried to
get my money stop, bro. And I had to
spend I had to spend £40 sending them bank statements
cuz you had to do it like you couldn't
do it digitally. So I had to spend my money.
So I was like, okay, some cunt's going
to pay for that.
Someone is going to pay for that, you
know. So that's that. They done it twice
as well. Um, and then obviously after
the third time they just stopped
investigating. So they've actually tried
getting people's money stopped.
Yeah, they tried they tried getting
people's money stopped.
Um, and they were saying the maddest
things. And I'm just saying, bro, like
every time Yeah. This they they were
doing this, I was like, these are people
that ain't they ain't got a better life
than me, bro.
You know. Nah, bro. Don't even try. You
wonder why people don't show their face.
[ __ ] out of here, bro. Yeah, Bomb's face
got out there and he was clapped and no
one found out who he was.
No, no, no, no, no, bro. Don't even use
that excuse. There's been a lot of
people that's been that's been out
there. No one's found out who they were.
And they always clapped as well. Even
Even if that's even if that's true.
Yeah. They're still butters whenever
they're whenever they're shown, they're
always ugly. So,
but yeah, they tried to get people's money stopped.
They've tried to get people's Yeah,
that's why I done the posters.
Yeah, that's why I done the posters. I
told him as well, like, if you keep doing it.
Yeah, that was over the money thing. Yeah.
Definitely definitely was
cuz I was living at my mom's at the
time. I said, "Oh yeah, you want to go
down that route, do you? Okay, [snorts]
I'll get your money stopped."
Sorry, [snorts] I would do posters of you.
Yeah, you like the posters, didn't you?
Everyone was just lying in bed. Yeah.
Everyone's just lying in bed waiting for
them uploads in it. And then bam. Yeah.
He went to the police. The little grass.
He went to the police, man.
Yeah, I've pled I've pled not guilty to
it, mate, cuz I've got evidence of you
harassing me. And I told the courts that
as well, lad.
So, [snorts] yeah. And it does matter
because when the judge sees all of
what's with what what PJ's little
evidence packs uh has got, it will
matter. It will 100% matter. And they
even said that as well.
[ __ ] that, bro.
[ __ ] that. I'd rather I'd rather risk
going prison. Think about that, bro. It
would make no sense to plead guilty when
Think about it, bro. Yeah. If the
court's in 3 years, it's probably going
to get dropped. A if it don't get
dropped, you know, like it nothing's
going to happen. And bro, I'd rather
risk going to prison than [ __ ] than
than than pleading not guilty when
someone's been harassing you every day.
There was no way in hell I'd rather go
to prison, bro. That's the kind of
person I am. You're mad if you Bro, that
weren't even a question. [ __ ] that. That is mad.
I feel guilty to something that I've
done if I smash something. But no way.
You think you're going to sit there and
harass me every day and I'm going to pay
some stupid fine or do some community
service? No way, bro.
No way. And I'm and I'm sure people
would would feel exactly the same way.
You're a loser, mate. The amount of
times that you went to the police,
you're a loser. You're an actual actual actual loser.
And you know, the thing is, LT, you
know, when he went to the police, he
went to the police over just name
calling. He didn't only go to the police
because people went to his um uh area
and stuff, you know. He went to the
police over like stuff that wasn't even
that as well. He's an absolute He's an actual loser.
Like he he actually went to the police
over voice notes. Yeah.
Yeah. He actually went to the police over
over voice notes.
Not even just people go like even like
people going to his area that and knew
where no one knew where he lived. He's a
he's an absolute loser, lad. You think
I'm I was gonna [ __ ] No way, mate.
[ __ ] absolutely no way.
Absolutely no way, bro.
That was never going to happen. Yeah. [ __ ] mad. [snorts]
Yeah. Yeah, he went to the police over
voice notes. He's a proper proper proper loser.
Proper proper proper proper loser.
It's not even like LT. Yeah, he he
called the police over the posters and
then he stopped. He actually called the
police over voice notes. He's an actual
loser, bro. That's like you sending me
voice notes right now and me calling the
police on you. That doesn't make sense,
bro. He's a loser.
He's a [ __ ] loser.
Yeah, but I've got a little evidence
pack. Isn't that right, Greasy? PJ's evidence pack.
You can see my evidence pack if you
want, Triple H, but it's going to cost you money.
It's literally called PJ's evidence pack. No,
I don't know why he keeps calling me a m
when I'm better looking than him. Must
be autism, bro. [snorts] How can someone
that's uglier than you call you a m?
I I don't think we'll ever know the
answer to that one.
How can a rat looking [ __ ] with missing
teeth call me a M? I mean, it's [snorts]
not even like we don't know what they
look like. I just think it's one of them
things we'll never really know.
And also, you talk about me balding. Uh,
you're the one that's actually balding.
That's another thing. I've seen your
hairline, you [ __ ] skimp virgin.
I've seen your [ __ ] hairline and it's
worse than [ __ ] Morgans's, you
[ __ ] skimp [ __ ]
You you you skint [ __ ]
You skintit virgin [ __ ] You know
this is all repeating.
This is all repeating on here, bro. Ain't it?
How have I been live for 5 hours?
PJ, you're skin. You got nothing.
Brother, can you can you go one day
without calling yourself skin?
You are the ones that are on here 24/7.
No life. Don't even leave your house. I
think you'll find you're the ones that
are skin. I think you'll really find
that you are the ones that are skint lad
on YouTube 24/7. And I've got evidence
that they were on YouTube 24/7 as well,
de lads. Just like now you will need to
do this once in a while, bro, to see
who's on YouTube.
How would you know that I've been on on
you? I I've been on YouTube for 5 hours.
So, you must be on YouTube yourself, then Actually,
the woman that I um I approached
uh the woman that I approached never
called me anything. It was actually her
friend. And anybody can call anyone
anything. All you got to do is come you
anybody can run into an insecure [ __ ]
that tries to call you ugly. Anybody can do that.
Anybody can run into an insecure [ __ ]
that would just call someone ugly cuz
they're ugly. I mean, look at it, bro.
You call me ugly every day and I'm
better looking than you. I mean, so I
mean, anybody can run into a rude ass
entitled [ __ ] because they used the
simps and then then and then start
calling you ugly.
That doesn't mean anything, mate. That
literally does not mean anything at all.
That really really does not mean
anything. I mean, I had somebody be rude
to me on the train, you know, [ __ ]
and then I was rude to her back. I mean,
it's it happens in this society, mate. It happens, you know,
and that's it. See you later.
Like, anybody can be called ugly by an ugly [ __ ]
an ugly insecure [ __ ]
you know. Hey, bro, have you seen this
self-reflector on uh on the virgins? I'm
serious. If you leave YouTube forever,
your life will improve. Get a part-time
job, get a girlfriend.
Coming from the guy on YouTube 24/7. [laughter]
Bro, these people are so pathetic, bro.
You just got to laugh at them.
They're so so pathetic. Aren't these
people in their 40s?
Aren't these people supposed to be older than me?
Jesus Christ, they're such sados, bro.
These people are supposed to be older
than me, you know? They should know better.
Why do I feel like I'm the I'm the most
maturest on this community, you know?
Sad sad bastard. Listen to that account.
Poo brother, you don't have a girlfriend.
You've never been with a woman. You're
still a virgin.
You have never had a girlfriend. What
would you know about problems and not
problems? Listen, most of you people
that are trying to call other people are
sad, sad bastards that have got no life,
no girlfriend, no life, no money. Why do
you keep talking about me? Why do you
keep talking about someone better than you?
Why? Someone younger, better looking,
more money than you. Why are you trying
to talk about me?
Why are you trying to talk about me when
my life's better than yours, brother?
I'll put the link up one more time for
you. I'll be I'll be absolutely I'll be
very, very nice. I'll put the link up
and prove all the things I'm saying
about you is to be wrong. Look, I'm so
nice. I'm actually wasting my time.
But you can't do it.
You can't do it, bro. You literally
can't do it. Seriously,
you're sat there with no girlfriend, no
money, no life,
and you're talking about me.
Seriously, bro. Seriously,
I need to get help, bro. What do What do
I need to get help for? Saying that
women are [ __ ]
I mean, I don't know what I need to get help for.
What? Stating the truth and not being a s.
I don't really think somebody needs help for that.
I mean, they are they are [ __ ] And
I and I've had more women than you and
your boyfriend. So, I'm not biased when
I'm saying this. And I'm not trying to
even sound immature, but I don't need
help, mate. I generally generally don't need help. You know,
my life's already good. You don't, mate.
I promise you that won't happen because
my life's already good.
Listen, bro. It's women that are the
problem. So, I could be the best version of myself
and women are still going to be stuck up
[ __ ] women. I see people that are
better than me all the time. They get
the same [ __ ] with women. It's You're
not going to change women when someone's the problem,
mate. I could be a millionaire. I could
go to the gym [ __ ] five times a week.
I could [ __ ]
you know, whatever. And and women are
always going to be the same old [ __ ]
[ __ ] Nothing to do with you improving
yourself. You need to tell people to
improve themselves for themselves.
Women are always going to be the same [ __ ] [ __ ]
Okay, women are stuck up. Why is it They
don't go for you, bro. They go for other
men. They don't go for you. Why are you
talking about other men? They don't go for you.
And I don't compare myself to other
people. But to answer your question,
well, they don't go for you. So, what's
that saying about you?
Why don't they go for you? You said
other men. So, why have you never had a girlfriend?
Same thing to you. Why have you never
had a girlfriend in your 40s? Same
question to you. Why have you got no one? Exactly.
Yeah. No, they don't go for other men.
They don't go for 90% of men. That's why
most people go to Thailand. And they
don't go for you. I've had more women
than you and your boyfriend. Before
saying about they don't go for for me,
I've had more women than you and your
boyfriend. Stop deflecting. Simple.
They are stuck up [ __ ] Stop trying
to bring up a small percentage of people
that are in relationships, lad. [gasps]
Most men do not have girlfriends. No,
they do not have girlfriends. And you
don't have a girlfriend. Most men do not
have girlfriends. And you don't have a
girlfriend. You don't have a girlfriend.
Stick to the subject, bro.
You do not have a girlfriend. Most men
do not have a girlfriend. Most men do
not have girlfriends, you [ __ ] I've
got many, many, many friends. I know
many, many, many, many people. Most
people are [ __ ] single. Most people
that I know are single, mate. It's like
50/50. Most men don't have girlfriends.
You don't have a girlfriend. Most men do
not have girlfriends. And I will get I
will get the statistic up right now, you
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Why do you think
so many Do you know how many people that
I know that live in Thailand now? Do you
know how many people I know that are
moving out of Thailand?
No. Most men don't have girlfriends. No,
they absolutely do not have girlfriends.
It's like 50/50
or No, no, no, no, no. Most men do not
have girlfriends, so that's wrong. See
you later. Bye-bye.
So, yeah, man. Bro, most men do not have
girlfriends. I'm I'm I'm sure it's like 50/50,
bro. Most people are not in relationships.
I'm telling you right now, Stephen
Howard, most people are not in relationships.
Most people are definitely definitely
definitely definitely not in
relationships. I know so many people,
bro, and so many people I know are single,
you know, and other things, bro. That is
utter utter [ __ ] what that guy is
saying. That is bollocks, bro.
I know so many people, lad, and they're
not in relationships.
It's [ __ ] That is utter utter utter utter bollocks.
Listen, I when you explain why you don't
have a girlfriend,
right, then come back to me. You don't
have a girlfriend. I've already explain
what women are like. They're stuck up
[ __ ] [ __ ] You don't have a girlfriend.
No, they have not. No, they absolutely
have not. And we're not talking about
them. We're talking about now. There are
so many single people out there. Women,
men, women, men. Trust me, bro. There's
loads of single people out there. So
what he's saying does not make sense.
Why do you think so many people are
going to Thailand?
I know loads of people that are going to
Thailand now. I know loads of people
that are single. That is [ __ ] bro.
About most men are in relationships. No
the [ __ ] they're not. You know how many
people that I know? No the [ __ ] they're not.
Yeah, he's calling me a virgin. He's a
virgin himself, lad. But no, seriously.
Um, no. Most people are not in relationships.
That is that is utter utter [ __ ]
And there's so many single people out
there. So many so many single people.
So many people are are single.
So yeah. And I could I could explain the
whole thing about how people in
relationships, but I've already
explained it before, Dusty. I could
explain to you how like other people are
in relationships. I could but I've
already explained it before so there's no point.
I mean if you if you want to hear how
other people are in relationships,
Stephen Howard, I can I can answer you.
If someone wants to know, I can tell you
how they're in relationships, but most
people are not in relationships. But if
you want to know how people are in
relationships, I can tell you.
I could tell you exactly how that I
could tell you examples of how people
have been in relationships.
I know how some of my sisters have been
in relationships. Um, how other people
have been in relationships. I can tell
you how. And they've got nothing to do with me.
None of these people have got nothing to
do with you. Just like your luck has got
nothing to do with them. You understand?
You understand what I'm saying, lad?
Some people are just not meant to have
anyone. Some people are just not meant
to meet anyone.
Some people like, so how people have got
in relationships is that like they might
have got lucky on a dating app. They
might have met through work. They might
have met through school. Um they might
have got lucky from an approach. All of
these things does not mean you're going
to meet someone. Do you understand?
That's what it is meeting someone. It's
not because other people have done it.
That doesn't mean you're going to do it.
That's why there's so many people that
believe, you know, that it's it's not.
And Dustin, I'm not being awkward. Yeah.
I know you're unbiased. And I know that,
you know, you might think I'm being
difficult and I think I know everything,
but bro, do you do you not generally
think that if I thought there was hope,
I'd be trying? Considering I'm not skin,
considering that I've got money, like
enough money to do what I want to do, I
can go and do what I want. Do you not
think that I would be out there trying
every day if I thought there was hope?
No. I would be trying, would I? So, the
fact that you're not, it says I believe
what I'm saying.
I believe exactly what I'm saying, you know?
So, it's like I mean, I've given up. So,
I mean, I've given up for over a month
now. Almost two months now I've given up
for. So, at the end of the day, lad like
I was done with it even back then.
I done with that if I knew if I thought
there was hope in something, bro.
Knowing the kind of person that I am in.
I would be trying every day. I'd be
trying every day. But I know they're
stuck up. I know they're [ __ ] I
know they're evil. That's why I don't go
near them. I don't contradict myself. I
don't go anywhere near them. Sure, if I
come across someone on Instagram or if I
come across someone on social media and
they prove me wrong, then they prove me
wrong. But until that day, I will not be trying.
Simple. I'm I'm stubb I'm a stubborn ass [ __ ] lad.
Like nowadays, bro. Like you you don't understand. One second.
Also, I hate the double standards, LT,
but you've had all these women and turn
women. It does. Yeah, I know. And that's
what makes me unbiased. Yes. And when
you're saying that, but you've had all
these women and turned because what when
I'm saying this stuff, bro, I'm saying
it because I'm believing it. I'm not
saying it because I'm a virgin or
because I'm saying it because I've been
I've been met enough women. So that's
how I know this stuff. I've had more
women than non-slegs and he defends
them. You know, you get what I'm saying?
Like because I'm unbiased when I'm saying this.
I'm on bias, bro.
So that's what I mean. Um, I can say this stuff,
brother. It's because I'm weird. Listen,
bro. I've put up enough messages and
enough normal approaches. If you dismiss
that, that's your problem.
If you want to dismiss that, that's your
problem, bro. I mean, I've put enough
evidence backing up what I'm saying to
be true. If you don't believe it, that's
on you, bro. You're entitled to your own opinion.
And another thing I tell you another
thing that that that made me give up LT
is is actually the double standards.
It's like you know when someone Okay say
okay put this way now. Yeah. Say that
I'm I'm complaining about a woman. Yeah.
Or I'm complaining about women and
someone calls me an insult. Now I tell
you what, bro. It used to annoy me. It
doesn't annoy me anymore. Someone if
someone says to you, "Oh, you're an
insult. You're an insult." What it means
is that you're a man complaining about a
woman and not a woman complaining about
men. So, it doesn't mean anything other
than you've got a dick in between your
legs and not a [ __ ] in between your
legs. It's all it's because of your
gender. Because when women complain
about men, everyone feels sorry for
them. So, when you start learning the
game and you know about the double
standards, it don't bother you. If
someone calls you that, it's like
someone calling you a [ __ ]
No, no, no, no, no. But LT, it's not
though. No, no, no. It's not LT. No, no.
And let me tell you why. Yeah. Let me
tell you why, LT. Right. And I tell you
how this is unfair. Right. There was
this woman, you haven't heard this, that
was moaning that she was with a guy for
2 weeks and he broke up with her. He
broke up with her. Yeah. And she was
feeling depressed about the dating game.
Even though she was getting sex, she was
getting dates. What about me? What? What
the [ __ ] about me? not get getting a
date for almost a year. That doesn't
even get acknowledged. So, it's not even
like you're dealing with the same [ __ ]
as women and you're bitching. It's not
even like you're you're bitching.
Like, you have a right to say what
you're saying, bro. That's that's that's
not normal, bro. That's not normal.
There's a difference between bitching,
bro. Like, if you was going through the
same thing as them and you're bitching,
okay, it's different. Then, you know
what I'm trying to say. So, no, that's
that's wrong, bro. That's that's double
standards. And then what makes me laugh
LT is that okay, one second. So if
they're if they're getting daycare and
they're getting sex and they're
depressed and that's and that's making
them depressed, then what about men that
can't get anything but bad experiences?
Does that mean that they
potentially what they're saying is that
they can kill themselves then really if
you think about it. So it's all wrong. I
hate the double standards. I hate
everything about it, bro. And when you
know you're playing a rigged game, bro,
it's pointless. If you if you're Why
would you play a game that's rigged?
You know, as I got older, bro, I saw
this [ __ ] for what it was,
you know? I saw it for what it was.
That's why I gave up
cuz you actually see it for what it is.
Rigged, sexist, biased. It is. It is. I
mean, bro, I don't your your
experiences, bro, they don't even get
acknowledged. That's how bad it is. They
It doesn't They don't even acknowledge
it. Not I don't want sympathy. I don't
want sympathy from no [ __ ] But bro,
they don't even acknowledge it. Do you
not think that's like kind of [ __ ] up? So
yeah, it's it's uh Yeah.
And also it started out as even if you
choose to give up, you're called weak.
They don't call women weak for for giving up.
If women give up, lad. Yeah, I'm meeting
him tomorrow. Yeah, if women give up,
uh, they they're not called weak.
So, no, I'm done, bro. I'm done.
They can [ __ ] right off until someone
proves me different, lad. That's the way
I am, lad. That's it. And that that
actually is like that's actually being normal, bro.
That's like, do you know what? I'm not
going to lie. I watch the Oreo, man. I
actually watch that Oreo man. Like, I
like his content now. You know, back
like a year ago, two years. I never used
to I used to watch him occasionally and
think, nah. But now, I actually watch
all of them videos, bro. I marinade
myself in them videos.
I actually like I I I watch his stuff,
you know. I'm interested in that stuff.
I actually like watch stuff, you know, that
Oreo man. Yeah.
No, no, no. But the difference is The
difference is I've tried and he hasn't.
The difference is I've actually tried
and he hasn't. And you can't knock
someone for trying. See, the thing is
with these people that you watch on the
internet, right? Let me let me tell you
something. With these people that you
watch on the internet, right, like I
don't know who it is, Elliot Rogers or
Oreo Man, you got to understand that
what diff what differs me from them is
I've actually tried. So I've actually
got a right to complain. I've got a
right to never want to try again. They
don't. The difference with them is they
really don't because they haven't really tried anything,
bro. Oh, bro. I made a I made a I made a
comment on on someone's thing on
Instagram earlier and I got 57 thumbs up.
I got 57 thumbs up. I won't get into it,
but I got 57 thumbs up.
Yeah. And it wasn't anything to do with incels either.
I got 57 thumbs up, bro. I don't watch
that incel [ __ ] on on on uh Instagram,
but bro, I got cuz I got 57 thumbs up. Yeah, man. So, yeah.
No, I like Oreo Man, bro. I like Oreo Man. [snorts]
Do you still watch his stuff? Oreo man.
No, I like Oreo Man, bro.
Do you see my comment on his thing? Yeah.
Like [snorts] I said, out, I was
thinking of joining the porn industry.
No, I haven't. Bro, you people don't
bully Peter Belly.
You You people don't bully Peter Belly.
The lads, you can never bully Peter Belly.
[sighs and gasps]
I don't know.
The dating game is rigged against men.
It is. I wish it wasn't this way, but it
I feel like I might as well just go back to gambling, you know.
And what's that going to do, bro? And
what's that gonna do?
You know, I've lived by myself before. Yeah.
No, I'm like Oreo man.
I wasted that six grand. No, I never,
mate. I live life. Something that you
should you people should be doing.
I wasted it, bro. Do you think all I had
was six grand? I had more than six
grand, bro. And I didn't waste it. I was
enjoying life with it.
Yes, I would have made money at Stratford.
What do you mean if it wasn't for you?
What are you on about if it wasn't for you?
What are you talking about, bro? You
never gave me that idea.
You never gave me that idea at all, bro.
And also, I had more than six grand, bro.
I had more than six grand and I didn't
waste it. I was enjoying life, which is
what people should be doing at 40
[ __ ] 24,25, lad.
Brother, I was still living there when I
was renting it.
I was still living there when I was
renting it, lad.
The most I think I've ever had is about nine grand.
But that was my money. That wasn't loans.
Oh, bro. I used to do a lot of [ __ ] man.
I think I've had nine grand. Yeah,
that's the most I've ever had. [snorts]
On top of three grand a month. So that's
loads really in it. [sighs] Yeah. Well,
I had to pay gas. I had to pay electric.
So I still had to pay for stuff in the house. [snorts]
So what's your opinion on this dating
thing then, Stephen?
I think you're pretty much screwed.
Oh, I got to be up for the dentist, man. That sucks.
Hate having to wake up to do stuff.
Well, I'm not the one that said it, was I?
I'm just going to the dentist, that's all.
Oh, that's funny, bro.
Because I've got evidence of him
harassing me. Sorry, it's hard to keep
up because I've got evidence of him harassing me.
Wait, LT, why did you bring Monty? Yeah.
Why? Why did you Why did you bring Monty
on here? LT,
you made him lose everything. Cuz you
brought him on here.
You brought him on here.
Yeah. Copycat. He's a copycat.
So, you sure he's a copycat, Dusty? [laughter]
Are you sure he's a copycat?
Oh, bless you then if you got verbal ticks.
Bless. Well, have you got Tourette's, Grezy?
Oh, bless you then. Have you got Oh,
have you got Tourette's?
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> What if they go on his door? What if
they go on Nons's door and they say,
"Grezy, you're under arrest
for suspicion of being a big fat stinking copycat." Huh? [laughter]
For being a big fat stinking copycat.
You're under arrest for being a copycat.
Would that make you laugh? For following the crowd?
You're under arrest, mate, for playing a [ __ ] guitar. [sighs]
For playing a [ __ ] guitar, mate. Yeah. >> [snorts]
>> No, you are broke out here. You are kind of broke.
[snorts] You are kind of [sighs]
You need to become millionaire status.
That's what you need to do. You need to
become millionaire status.
Do you think you could do it in millionaire status?
I'm going to go watch some Oreo man in a
bit and go sleep. >> [snorts] [sighs]
>> You know,
I'm going to watch some Mario, man.
Is that okay with you, Greasy Boss,
if I watch some Incel stuff before I go to bed?
Groovsy, is that okay with you, boss?
Okay with you, [ __ ] [snorts]
[sighs and gasps]
All right, [ __ ]
I live in poverty. You don't know how
much money I have. [gasps]
Stop talking about people that you don't know.
Yeah, I was at my sisters the other day
and I was on Reddit and I was getting
mood swings, bro. Really bad mood
swings. I had to go home.
Yep. I I I was getting these really
nasty, dirty mood swings.
These dirty ass mood swings. They were really dirty.
And I had to go home, bro. And I just
went to bed. Yeah,
maybe I'll start daily vlogging. Grievy,
what do you think? Daily vlogging. Oh, I
forgot to tell you, Greavvesy. I saw a
Stitch toy in Smith's the toy shop. It was £80.
It was a big Stitch.
Yeah, it's quite pricey.
I never think positive, mate.
I never ever ever think positive ever.
Not anymore, bro. I used to, but not anymore.
I don't anymore, lad.
That's what happens, bro.
[snorts] When you've had enough bad
experiences, you become bitter. You
know, as old people, they get bitter.
You get bitter as you get older.
Like me, I'm bitter now
cuz all the bad experiences I've had, bro.
I'd say I'm a danger to the public.
Yeah, I'm a danger to the public, me,
I don't like to go too far nowadays.
I'm an agrophobic [ __ ] >> [snorts] >> Yeah.
And if I get into a toxic situation
again, someone's getting hurt.
Someone's getting seriously hurt.
Yeah. Someone's getting seriously
seriously injured, bro.
[snorts and sighs]
Seriously, seriously injured.
I don't want to I don't want toxicity in
my life, bro. [ __ ] that. [snorts] Greavves. Salamkum. [snorts] Salamkum.
I can't believe USA Izzy's friend thinks
that she's going to get her cousins
[ __ ] to shoot me. I would bad them
up, bro. I would bad them all up. Cory,
I would actually bad them all up, bro.
your cousins. Really, bro? [ __ ] off.
They never touch Peter Belly, bro.
Peter Bell is too powerful.
Isn't that right? Peter Bell is too powerful. >> [sighs]
>> I could go there and just create
carnage, bro. Should I go America and create carnage?
I can afford to go. I can actually
afford to go. Do you want me to go and create carnage?
Yeah, it's like two grand, bro. I can do
it, bro. I can afford it. Yeah,
it's like what Oreo man said.
You know what I mean, Cory? I like to I
like to hang around with people that
think the world is against them. I like
them kind of people.
I like them kind of people that think
the whole world is against them.
It sounds funny, but it's it's true,
don't it? I like to be around them kind
of people. I swear now, bro. No, I'm not
even joking. I'm being serious. It sounds funny,
but it's true. Yeah. [snorts]
That think the world's against MLC.
Like, you know, like you know, Ar man,
I wouldn't get ragged out by none of
them, bro. Not any of them.
Well, some people in America don't play
about, but they play about. The people
that I was [ __ ] with play about. Some
people don't [ __ ] about, but they they
they play about, bro.
I've been hopeless for a I've been
hopeless for a very long time. Greavvesy
Yeah, bro. Doesn't change either. My
mood used to get better after a while,
but they don't get better anymore.
They don't get better anymore.
It's really bad, Greasy.
It doesn't get better anymore, you know.
It doesn't get better.
>> [clears throat] [sighs]
>> I don't know why these people on Reddit
keep thinking that there's hope for me,
Grievy. There isn't. [snorts]
I'm sick of people telling me that
there's hope when there's bloody well not. You know,
there's no hope.
And even if I win money, it's not going
to make me happy. So that's why I don't
gamble. You see [snorts] [sighs]
people on Reddit Greavesy keep telling
me that I'm going to meet someone.
You don't know what's around the corner. Yeah, right.
And the only time I do feel good is when
I'm thinking about getting revenge on
all these [ __ ]
that's led me on and stuff. grieavves
led me on and and been [ __ ] I said
to that Muslim girl, I said, "I'm not an
idiot. I know you're bullshitting." She
didn't reply back. Don't treat me like a [ __ ]
Cuz I know if I hear I have a boyfriend
one more time, I will break someone's
[ __ ] jaw, bro.
Trust me, there's no point me going out
and doing anything, bro.
I am not going out, lad. [gasps]
Nope. I don't use escorts. I only I was
only on about an escort cuz she messaged
me. She was trying to scam me.
So, no. I I got I got uh
[snorts] She messaged me, mate. I don't
use escorts. I don't use escorts, lad.
She just messaged me. So I thought I
won't use escorts, bro.
I've not used escorts for months,
months and months and months. Months, bro.
[snorts] I don't use escorts, lad. Not for months.
I only really use escorts when I used to
go and drink. When I used to approach
and I used to drink, lad.
That's the only time I really used to
use escorts until I broke the cycle. I
don't I don't just go and use escorts, bro.
Cuz I don't like condoms and I shouldn't
have to use condoms.
Yeah, she fought wrong. So, yeah.
there is no hope.
There is no hope sadly.
There's none whatsoever.
And all I think about is revenge Greavves constantly.
this revenge, you know, like all jokes aside,
maybe I can get revenge on this escort,
make her like go her she actually scammed me.
Yeah, we need revenge, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Triple H. I was thinking of going
back to gambling, but cuz I don't care
about money, so even if I done my balls,
I wouldn't care. But nah.
Yeah. My life. Yeah. [sighs and snorts] Yeah, bro.
I've gotten worseer as I've got older.
Yeah, I can't stop thinking about how
women's [ __ ] me over and [ __ ] Like, I
have actually thought about starting
that American [ __ ] up again, bro. And
this time actually being serious about
it. Like, I have actually been thinking
about it, bro.
And I'm I'm being serious, Grezy. Like,
all jokes aside, lad.
Do you want to really know why I don't
go out as well, bro? Greavesy, do you
really want to know another reason why um
I don't go out and drinking and stuff?
Obviously, I can afford it and stuff,
but I'm trying to like save as well so
that like if I ever need to [ __ ] just
[ __ ] off and fly somewhere, I can just do it,
you know, just to build up that little
um thing. You know what I'm saying, bro?
It's all It's all like I have actually
been thinking of doing it, bro.
But not being a keyboard warrior. I
don't want to be a keyboard warrior,
bro. I don't want to just start [ __ ] and
never have like what Red Star does.
Like, I actually want to do something,
bro. Do you understand?
When I'm out drinking again. Never, bro. Never.
No, cuz I was thinking of messaging a a
friend that I was talking to saying,
"Oh, yeah. You really want to go there?
You know what I'm like, Grezy?
Oh, you don't need that negativity. Oh,
I do. I do. I want that negativity in my
life. Let's do it. Let's do it." You
know what I'm saying, Grezy? I'm that
kind of [ __ ] You know, I want that
negativity in my life. I love it.
And your cousins aren't going to do a
damn thing to me, you know?
I will go there and I'll and I'll I'll
I'll make the country mine, you know?
I'll be the new Donald Trump. Like, you
don't know what I'm like, bro.
Seriously, you don't. I'll be the new
I'll be the new Obama, bro. Barack
Obama, and own the country, and it will
be all mine, and there's nothing that
you're going to [ __ ] do about it.
I'll come here.
I will do Yeah. I will do it dirty. I'll
come here. I'll call out a female and
you will do nothing.
Yeah, I'll do it dirty, bro. Proper
you know, just like I done nons dirty. [gasps]
Yeah, cuz I love it. I'll be the new
I'll be the new Donald Trump. I'll dye
my hair blonde, bro. You know what I mean? Yeah.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah, bro. Just like as a f to just to
get revenge on someone. [snorts]
All the [ __ ] that they've put me through
over the years. Yeah.
No, triple. I've got to be up tomorrow.
[ __ ] go dentist. I hate having to be
up for things.
I hate having to be up for things, Greasy.
It could be anything, you know, when
you've got to be up for something. I I never sleep.
You know what I mean? I can never sleep,
bro, when I have to be up for stuff. So weird.
So, what you you still buying your little DVDs?
No, I don't have anxiety, bro. I'm not
scared of the dentist. It's anything.
No, it's not giving me anxiety, bro. I'm
not scared of the dentist.
No, I just don't like having to be up
for stuff cuz I lie in
because I lie in. I'm not scared of the
dentist, bro. It's anything. If I have
to be up for anything, I don't like it.
I'm not scared of the dentist, bro. It's
anything. Depends how early you have to
be up and that cuz my sleeping pattern's
[ __ ] And obviously, I know I've got
to be up, so I can't I I can't if I know
I've got to be up for something. I can't
explain what I mean, bro. I'm not scared
of the dentist, bro. I go to the dentist by myself.
Why would I be scared of the dentist
when I've been to the dentist millions
of times by myself, bro?
Every time I've been, I've been by myself.
No, I got a feeling a couple of months ago
cuz I've got an early appointment and I
hate having to be up.
Oh, it's annoying, isn't it?
Cuz I don't want to do anything
tomorrow. I want to stay in bed and
that, but obviously I've got to go. >> [snorts]
>> I be scared to the dentist, bro.
I just wanted to stay in bed tomorrow.
I'm not scared of the dentist.
Laney is scared of the dentist. Not me.
[snorts] Not me. M.
No. [snorts] No.
Yeah, Laney is I'm not
I've been live for [ __ ] 6 and a half hours.
It's horrible, man. Waking up bitter and
angry every day. Greasy.
I just wanted to stay in bed tomorrow. I
don't really want to go out.
I have to, bro.
I don't think these mood swings are
going to change.
going to change this time. Greasy.
In order for you to change, the
experiences have to change.
The experiences have to change.
That's true, isn't it, Grezy? In order
for the mindset to change, the
experiences have got to change.
Do you see where I'm coming from?
Do you want me to record a dentist
tomorrow for you, Grezy?
You think I'm scared of the dentist,
Greavves? I'm not scared of the dentist.
I just wanted to stay in bed tomorrow. I
hate having to be up for things.
I ain't scared, bro.
Well, I I might be getting a filling, bro.
I might Well, I should be getting a filling
if I still need it, which I think I do.
What do I need?
a little part-time job.
No, I'm not scared of the dentist, bro.
I just wanted to chill, you know? Yeah.
The only thing I don't like about the
dentist here is the Well, I don't mind,
you know, the X-ray. That's the only
thing I don't like, but they don't
bother me, bro.
Yeah, I'm too depressed to sleep, bro.
Just sat here thinking about my bad experiences.
It's Valentine's Day soon. I wonder if
it will be another lonely Valentine's.
Wow, what a day. E, Valentine's Day.
What a way, what a way to poke fun out
of the people that ain't wanted by nobody.
Let's poke fun out of the people that
ain't chosen by no one.
I think the person that made Valentine's
Day is a narcissist.
This holiday was invented to to to poke
fun out of the people that ain't chosen by nobody.
People say on Reddit that you're going
to meet someone though.
Yeah, bro. It's annoy Yeah, [snorts]
that's the only thing.
The X-ray thing is a bit weird.
Yeah, the X-ray thing is weird. Yeah.
Yeah. It's only down from now, is it, lad?
It's not going to get better. Nothing's
going to change.
No, they won't pull a tooth. you nasty virgin.
You nasty skint virgin.
Is it going to improve this life greasy or not?
Is this life going to improve?
But Dusty, people on Reddit say that you
don't know. You don't know about the future.
[snorts] I've just given up on life like Greavvesy.
I'm just another Greavvesy now. Yeah. [snorts]
Yeah, I'm just another greasy, I think.
What do you think I should do? Grievy?
I just like lying in bed feeling sorry for myself.
I think it's the best way in it.
Yeah, I love block I loved Blockbusters.
I loved Blockbusters, bro. Oh, man. I
used to go there every Friday. Popcorn,
rent free DVDs.
There's one left in America, you know.
There's one blockbuster that exists in
in in a cinema in uh in America.
Reddit told me I was going to meet
someone grievy. I'm sad.
Have you been to America, Dusty?
Have you been [snorts] to America? Yeah,
maybe I'll stay live until my dentist
appointment tomorrow, Grezy, and just
carry on. Is it?
Do you know that USA Easy thing,
Greavvesy? That was bad. You know,
that had like two years of my life.
I'm just thinking back when I used to go
O'Neals and that.
Do you know how bad that actually was, bro?
Like you laugh at it. That was actually really bad.
That's really, really, really, really bad. Oh gosh.
I'm just changing positions in my nesticles, Greasy.
[gasps and sighs]
It was actually really bad, Greasy. You know that?
[gasps] And then you you laugh at it. It
was actually really, really bad.
Grezy, you think you think it's funny,
but it's not funny. Yeah.
Good luck trying to find a woman in this
day and age, Grievy. Poor [ __ ]
You won't find anyone that won't be
normal. You're never going to find
someone normal that won't lead you on
and play games.
I'd be very surprised if you do, lad.
Very surprised if you do. Yeah.
I'll be very surprised if you do, that [snorts] Yeah.
It's Trip Rates his birthday soon on the 23rd. Greavves.
That's cute, isn't it?
Imagine being born in January. That must
feel so weird, isn't it? Just a dead
month just snowing it.
What about you? Well, I kind of like
January cuz of the snow and that.
What about you, Dusty? Do you like January?
[snorts and sighs] [gasps] January.
It's kind of nice to wrap up warm and
that. It's like a gym month, isn't it?
It's Yeah, it's all right. It's just
dead, isn't it?
Yeah. July is nice and warm, isn't it?
It's your birthday in two months, isn't it, Greavves?
Yeah. July is good. July is good.
It's your birthday. Uh, Grezy,
it's your birthday in two months, isn't it?
Oh, USA is born in April.
You're you're both born in the same
month, you poor [ __ ]
I've always found you. I like April. I
always find, you know, March and April,
good thing good things happen and then
after that the rest of your year, [ __ ]
I know it's that, Dusty. My barber was
telling me this. I was like, do you know
what? Yeah, come to think of it, you're
right. After April, it's just downfall.
After April, you're like, it's just over
until next year. I've noticed that as
well with my life as well with dating and stuff.
After April, it's finished over
the rest of it. [ __ ] Especially
November as well. I've noticed that.
Bless you. Then if you're born April,
you're in life. Just cute.
You're a couple months older than me.
Yeah, July is a good month. My dad was
born in July,
[snorts] but my dad's dead.
Yeah, July. That's Yeah.
>> [snorts and gasps] [sighs]
>> I don't know why people on Reddit are
still telling me I'm going to meet someone.
This guy in Belgium said, "Use better
dating app pictures." Yeah, like that's
going to work. Can I show you my dating profile, Grezy?
I just put it up on the screen.
This guy in Belgium said, "Put better pictures up."
Oh, where is it now? One second.
Hinge profile when I was on Hinge. I
deleted it now. This was ages ago.
I think at least three or four of them
pictures was all right. Right. Let me see.
There we go. There are some of my pictures.
Those are some of my pictures. >> [snorts]
>> Oh gosh. Yeah.
And I got a couple of matches and then
they didn't reply,
but people still going me to tell me to
go on the dating apps.
They still tell me to go on the dating
apps though. Grezy,
do you think the pictures are all right?
Do you like the pictures? I can't even
remember what the bio said.
Yeah, that's all they want to do in the
society. Just pick on a man that's tried everything.
Blame the poor [ __ ] that's gone up and
down the country trying, you know.
[sighs and snorts]
Do you like the pictures, Grezy?
And I don't know why people talk about
description and bios because people
don't even read it.
People don't even read the bios. You do realize that.
So what if I if I put up better
pictures, Greasy? Would I still have
would I still struggle on the dating apps?
I reckon I would to be fair. [snorts] I
reckon even then I would would struggle
cuz I struggle to meet people in real
life and I'm decent looking in real
life. So, I mean probably [snorts]
reckon you would still have problems. person. Yeah, it's bad. Really bad.
I don't know the answer. That's why I'm asking you.
The guy in Belgium said that if you have
better pictures, you're going to kill it
on the dating apps.
So, I don't I don't know the answers.
I actually don't know the answer.
What do you think, Dusty?
No, I don't know the answer.
Now, do you believe me? I'll never try
again. Steven, how would you believe me
now? Is it
I still haven't told Antman the story of the escort.
Let me type it to him just in case I forget. >> [sighs]
>> Oh, you know this guy from Redden. How
comes he's got an accent, Dusty?
How comes he sounds different to me?
This guy from Redden.
He sounds a bit He sounds a bit farmerish.
He sounds a bit like a farmer.
[sighs] I was expecting a London accent.
What do you think?
No, they're definitely definitely
farmers, bro. People from Reading are definitely farmers.
Yeah, they all former lad.
Yeah, because you you said that people
from Reading are Cockney. How can they
be cocky, bro? They're not. They're
farmers, bro. It's farmerland.
It's not like full-on Bristol, but it's still farmerland.
It's the same as slow as well. The
accent starts changing.
Yeah, the accent starts changing once
you hit slow.
I went I remember before I went to uh Chichester.
They sounded like farmers there as well.
You know Chichester?
I thought they were going to be cockn Dusty Chester.
No, they're definitely farmers, bro.
They're definitely farmers.
Yeah, but I thought they could have been
Cockney and Reen as well. [laughter] Crazy.
Yeah, I I'm from East London, but I
don't I don't class myself as a cockney.
I don't class myself as a cockney, though, bro.
Yeah, this guy said, "Come to Reddit.
We'll go for a little piss up." Yeah.
What do you know about? Do you know
about Southampton, Dusty? That's one
place I've never been.
They're formers as well. That's formerland.
Yeah. No, that's farmerland.
[snorts] Southampton's former land, lad.
Bristol's [snorts] farmland.
They all talk like that. That's how they
talk like y
like a firmer. That's how they talk.
Yeah, Dusty. I was born in Leighton Stone,
but I wouldn't say I'm Cockney.
I wouldn't say I'm Cockney, though.
Maybe I am, but I don't think I am. No.
No, I'm not. I'm just from London.
Do you know what's so [snorts] weird
though, Dusty? You know Brighton, they
don't have an accent, do they?
I've noticed that Brighton don't have an
accent, do they?
No, they don't. I notic that.
No, they actually don't. No, I've been through there.
I've been through Peter, bro. They're
farmers as well.
Yeah, they're farmers. That's near where
Macarelli is from, isn't it? Like there.
Yeah, but they they haven't got an
accent, do they Brighton?
No, not really.
I got a friend from Bristol with their
accents. Mad, bro. The Bristol accent's
kind of [ __ ] up, isn't it? No.
That's where it is is from.
That's where Isabelle from. Isabelli. [snorts] >> [snorts] >> No,
no, I never been. Yeah.
I just can't stop thinking about my bad experiences, Dusty.
So, [snorts] you're saying that if I get
better photos, I'm still not going to
get luck on the dating apps. >> [snorts]
>> You sure about that?
Reading is Red in near London, Dusty,
would you would you say it's near London?
kind of is it?
Nope. I'm never approaching again. I
shouldn't have to.
never again, bro. Nope.
Why try when you already know the result?
Why would you try when you already know the result
and you're hopeless?
It's never going to change. So
never again, lad.
I should need to approach. I should have
found someone by now.
That's the way I see it. Yeah, bro.
It's bad, is it, bro?
People, they go on dating apps to get sex. Dusty. Yeah.
Nope. I'm standing her up for trying to scam me. [sighs]
No. No, bro.
I'm [snorts] going to have to somehow go
to the dentist tomorrow. That's going to be hard.
That's going to [snorts] be hard when
you've given up in with life. Uh,
best life in it. Yeah.
bad because of the dating scene.
Just bitter every day, lad.
Yeah, I'm just bitter every day.
Yeah, bitter every day, lad.
Bitter and annoyed at the world.
I need to go in a minute.
[snorts] I was yours. >> [snorts]
>> I'm just watching some negative videos, bro.
It's bad, is it? Very bad life we live.
[sighs and gasps]
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> M it dusty.
I like Sheffield, Dusty. I like Sheffield.
[sighs and snorts] Sheffield's a cool place.
Do like Sheffield.
If you've ever been,
it's class. It's a class night out.
They got a little brothel as well.
[snorts] Sheffield's good.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> Yeah, pretty much. And sexless as well.
There's nothing you can do to change
your situation either.
That's the worst thing. There's nothing
you can do to change your situation.
How mad is that?
Just lie and rot.
Move out of London, mate. I can barely I
can barely get out of bed.
I can barely get out of bed.
Yeah, I was at my sisters and I was
getting these mood swings. Dusty. I was
on Reddit and I got these mood swings. I
had to come home.
I had to come home and go to bed.
I was thinking of my bad experiences. Yeah.
It's a sad life, you know.
Sucks to be hopeless, isn't it?
Grieves. Sucks to be hopeless.
Nothing you can do to change your
situation without making it worse.
That's really bad, Greezy.
[snorts] The only time I have a break
from it is when I'm asleep.
The only time is when I'm asleep.
I get a break from it.
Oh, when I'm eating good food.
Oh, when I'm eating good food. Yeah, greasy.
[sighs and gasps] People on Reddit tells
me stuff happens, but nothing changes.
People on Reddit says that stuff
changes, Grezy, but it doesn't. Nothing happens.
No good food like Indian.
I like Indian food. Greasy. I like [snorts]
Yep. And it's not going to change either.
Yep. And it's not going to change now.
If it hasn't changed then,
it's not going to change now. [snorts]
Isn't that right, Grezy? If it's not
changed, then it's not going to change now. [snorts]
That's the way I see it. [gasps]
I had a vindaloo
uh not yesterday, did I? Oh, yeah.
Yesterday. I had a vindaloo yesterday.
It warmed me up. [snorts]
Yeah. I had a vindaloo yesterday, lad.
[sighs and gasps] Yeah.
I can't believe this life never changes.
It's so depressing, man.
Really is depressing.
[snorts] Yeah, just in bed depressed.
Mike, thinking about my bad experiences
and how nothing's going to get better. I
got the dentist tomorrow, so I need to
go sleep in a minute. But yeah.
Hey, I hate having to be up for stuff
when I don't want to get out of bed, you know. Yeah,
I only eat once a day.
Yeah, I only eat once a day.
I like vindaloo me in this weather
especially January it's so nice vindaloo
yeah Mike it's depressing man this life
people on Reddit says cuz it gets
better. But it doesn't. Sucks.
It really does suck. Yeah.
Need better experiences. That's what you need. Yeah.
Slower the better. Isn't that right, Grezy?
Mike, people on Reddit keep trying to
tell me I'm going to meet someone when I'm not
cuz it would have happened by now. Yeah.
They say that you don't know what's
around the corner, but you do. When it
comes to women, you do know what's
around the corner cuz it's been it's
always it's always the same.
They tell me to use dating apps, Mike,
and I can't even get a bloody match. And
when I do, they don't respond, Mike.
And they keep dismissing my struggles.
Grieve Z. They keep dismissing my struggles.
I'm very bitter nowadays, Mike. I don't
really do much.
I wake up, think of my bad experiences, get demotivated.
Even money doesn't motivate me, bro.
Even money don't motivate me.
Nothing motivates me, bro.
I can't watch horror films anymore,
Grezy, because of the sex scenes.
Well, at least I don't have to worry
about that if I watch Spongebob, the new Spongebob movie. Yeah.
And I don't need help. I don't need to
go to the doctor's geese because it's a
normal way to feel after my bad experiences.
After the bad experiences, I think this
is normal to feel this way. [snorts]
So, I'd be very worried if there was no
if there wasn't a reason, then I would
go to the doctors. But this is normal to
feel after the bad experiences and
you've been wronged all your life. So, yeah.
the horror movie that it's very triggering
the sex scenes in the horror films.
That's why I can't watch them anymore. I
think I'll be all right with Scream
though. I don't think there'll be sex
scenes in Scream. The new Screams out next month.
[snorts] That sucks, you know. Yeah.
What a life. Hey, Grezy. What a life.
You don't really come on here much,
Mike, do you? No.
I can't believe I was speaking to you
Wally for [ __ ] seven hours.
Why do you think these people stalk and
harass me every day, Mike?
Do you think they're just bitter people or something?
I can see why you don't come on here
though, cuz it's always the same [ __ ]
Yeah, it hurts my head as well, lad.
Just stay away from LJ's channel. You
should be all right.
Why do you think they stalk me every
day, Mike? They even stalk me on Reddit.
I think they want my ass.
No, I'm not back full time.
They're weirdos, man. They stalk me
every day and stuff. Oh. [snorts]
I see. I see.
Yeah, that's sad though, isn't it? [snorts] Yeah.
Yeah. Just life sucks, Mike. I give up.
I give up with life. [snorts]
Too many bad experiences with women and
stuff, leaving [snorts] me single and sexless.
I haven't been motivated to try now for months, Mike.
So, I finally gave up in the end, didn't I?
Reddit lied to me.
Laney told me I'd meet someone. Greasy.
Laney said that we'd meet someone. Oh,
I'm getting hungry now.
You know what that means, Grezy? It means McDonald's.
I'm only joking.
I can't have McDonald's.
My belly's rumbling. You could probably
hear a grievy.
[sighs and gasps]
Laney told me I'd meet someone.
Grezy Laney lied.
Have you noticed that, Mike? All of the
things all of the things that's happened
in the years, yeah,
your dating life and your sex life has
stayed the same. And by you, I mean me.
I've had different amounts of money.
I've had different amounts of luck.
But have you noticed your sex life and
your dating life has been the same for
[ __ ] years? So, I'm not sure why
people think it's going to change. It
will never change. It's just like what
Ant-Man says, it will never change. It
Everyone would be more surprised if it
did change than, you know,
surprised people think that if they went
for over the years.
I'm surprised they think it will change.
I'm surprised that to be fair.
Yeah, I've done lots of things on
YouTube, haven't I, Dusty, over the
years, like lots of traveling and stuff.
Yeah, it makes me bitter, bro. Thinking
about my bad experiences
makes me bitter, full of hate every day.
Do you reckon it will go away? The mood
swings greases you. I don't think so.
I don't think so. I think it's there forever now.
It's a permanent part of my life. S
I should have been born like Daniel Thompson
without a dick. What's the point of
being born with a dick if you can't use
it? I might as well just be like Alen.
I might as well just be I might as well
just be like Alen.
Daniel Thompson Sullivan.
He's got a manggina. That's what I
should have been born with. What's the
point of being born with a dick if you
can't use it? It's like being born with
a mouth if you can't and not being able
to eat nice food
just or taste food. It's pointless.
That's the way I see it, Grezy. You know,
I've lost my taste buds before and it's
very annoying. I've actually lost my taste buds.
It's like It's like buying expensive
nice food, but you can't taste anything.
What's the point of that? That's just
defeats the object.
Yeah, but you Yeah, but you Yeah, but No.
Uh, but the thing is even if you pay for it,
you have to use a condom.
No, I'm not feeling sorry for myself.
It's I should be feeling this way. It's warranted.
That's why I said I was going to try to
join the porn industry.
put it to good use. You know,
they're looking for porn stars.
No, I wouldn't want to bang an escal
without protection. But I'm just saying,
you can't have proper sex. Proper sex is
without a condom.
So, unless you meet someone naturally,
you can't have proper sex. So, you
basically can't have sex, basically.
That that's depressing, bro. I think
about that every day.
How you're in your prime. You should be
getting sex. You should be getting sex
all the time.
Or just at least once a month. Well, not
all the time. No, not all the time. Once a month.
Just to keep you stable. So yeah. Yeah. Yeah,
it's not good, is it?
It's not good, bro.
Lack of lack lack of intimacy can cause
can cause um mental health problems.
Griezy, do you know that?
I'll think about it.
[sighs and gasps] Yeah.
You never get a depressed person in Thailand. [snorts]
You'll never ever get a depressed person in Thailand. [snorts] Never.
Yeah, that's what my porn star name is
going to be. Prolific Pete. Yeah,
that's what my porn star name was going
to be. Greavesy. I said my That's what
my porn star name will be.
So Greavesy, so did you actually really
know straight away it was a copycat
statement with the Cheryl Cole thing?
Why did you hear about it before then?
You must have heard people talking about
her before then.
Ah, you must have knew from years ago.
But I bet you didn't know back then that
they were all copying each other, did you?
Yeah, they were copying each other.
You used to do it with Beyonce as well. [snorts]
Really? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. 1213. Yeah.
What What were they saying?
Yeah. What were they saying?
Yeah. So, what was [laughter]
Yeah. So, why was they saying that, Grezy?
Why were they saying that? Yeah.
Really? Did Did that Did Did that actually happen?
Yeah. That's what my my sister said it
with Beyonce. She said that you got to
screw loose if you don't find her
attractive. She looked at me weird once.
Yeah, she looked at me weird.
yeah, they done it. They done it with Beyonce.
I think they done it with Emma Watson as well.
It was a thing basically, Greavvesy.
They It was basically a thing back in
the day to put average celebrities on a pedestal.
It was just a thing back then to do it.
Just to put these random ass average
celebrities on a pedestal.
Silly really. It is silly really if you
think about it. [snorts]
Do you remember Bqu Quest little account for Macdonald?
Oh, we miss Bquest, don't we? I know his
little account McDonald Fiona McDonald
account isn't it?
There was an account before Gravesy
called Isabelle Eldridge. >> Yeah.
I like them little accounts. Do you, Greasy?
See, I used to get these mood swings
last year, but I used to be able to get
better and stuff. Now I don't even get better, Grezy.
Even when I get money and stuff, it
doesn't make me happy.
I think I'm royally [ __ ] I think I'm
royally [ __ ] bro.
Feel like just I should just gamble my life away.
Thinking of just going back to gambling. Dusty
You used to like the gambling videos, Greezy.
Did you like the gambling videos? >> [sighs]
>> Did you slide the little roulette rage?
Oh yeah. Everyone loves King.
King is a cutie.
Everyone loves King.
Cinema. Oh, I haven't done cinema videos
for ages, bro. You must be talking years ago.
Oh, well, I'm Peppa Pig. Oh, you like
the Peppa Pig one? >> [sighs]
>> The roulette's fixed in the casino,
isn't it, Grezy? It's fixed.
Yeah, roulette's fixed, isn't it? >> [sighs]
>> Do you reckon if I won money right now,
I'd be happy? We nah, [snorts]
I still wouldn't be able to let go to
the let go of the resentment.
I'll just be depressed.
No, I still wouldn't be.
I was out last. >> [sighs]
>> Have you been watching Ed Matthews?
Have you seen that other guy? Hick tick
tockie. What's it? H tick tockie.
That guy seems like a clown, bro.
I think his name is Hates
Tick Tocky or something. He sounds like a clown.
I'm sure you've seen him.
Crazy. It's like hates Tik Tocky. He
hangs around with Ed Matthews.
hates tick tocky or some [ __ ]
Yeah. Oh, bless you, Grezy. You and your little DVDs.
I wish I could just be like Grezy, you know?
I might start getting some DVDs.
I might start being like greasy.
[gasps] Yeah, I might just start being
like grievy from now on. [laughter] [sighs]
Yeah, I might start getting some DVDs.
What's your opinion on that, Grezy?
If I started being like you, huh?
[sighs and gasps] [laughter]
What? So I could copy you then?
So what? [snorts] I could copy you.
So what would that make me if I copied you?
Yeah, I love horror movies.
>> I just don't like the sex scenes.
So what you call this a copycat community then?
Greavvesy. So, so you think this is a copycat community?
What makes you say that? [laughter]
What makes? [laughter]
What makes you say that? That's [ __ ] hilarious, bro.
Why is it a copycat community? Coffee cat [snorts]
was fit. Yeah, they mention that in the
in between users, isn't it?
Yeah, they mentioned she will call it in between us.
Yeah, it's a copycat community.
They all copy.
Yeah, it's true.
It's like LJ. He started copying He
started copying my meals like the pork
and that and the curries.
Yeah. My holidays started getting
copied. Yeah. It's a copycat community.
So what if you didn't find Shive? They
used to look at you funny
but call you gay.
So they would look at you funny and then
just call you gay is it?
What? So that what they give you like
evils and [ __ ]
Yeah. Gave you like dirty looks and that
in it. Yeah,
they done it with Rihanna as well.
Yeah, I remember them doing it with Rihanna.
Definitely done it with Rihanna.
Where did you hear them talking about it
like at school then? Grezy were they in
a classroom and they started talking
about her? [laughter] [gasps]
What? And they started talking about her
like what? like sitting down in class or
something or like the playground. [sighs]
What? Really? Are you joking or did they
actually used to talk about her?
really. Are you actually Are you
trolling? Are you actually being serious?
Yeah. [laughter] Yeah. That's her. Yeah. Yeah. Bro.
Yeah. X Factor.
I brought I brought her up to Nonss and
he said that if you don't find her
attractive, you're gay. I said I'm not
gay. She's just not my type. She's just
not for me.
He's trying to backtrack what he's
saying, but he definitely definitely did say that.
He definitely did say that, man. I swear
to God he did. It's weird.
So, how long does it take for a copycat statement, Greavvesy?
Every couple of days.
It's a big fat stinking copycat community.
It's a community where they all copy
each other, is it? Yeah. Yep.
I might start collecting comic books. Grievy
Superman comic books.
Okay with you, boss.
Now, you know, Superman
got the old comic books and stuff.
Maybe even Marvel.
Did you watch the new Superman, Dusty?
It was good. I think it was a couple of
months ago. The new Superman in the
cinema. I liked it.
Yeah, I like Superman.
Greavvesy, why can't I get attached anymore?
Why do I have attachment issues?
Yeah, but that account kept coming in
mocking me. Grievy,
you know the account I'm talking about.
It hasn't been on for a while.
I think it's pissed off for good, isn't it?
And you know it's the same person every
time, isn't it?
They repeat my sayings.
Looks like the virgin [ __ ] I put the
cat up on my photo, bro. And they wrote,
"Looks like the virgin fucker." [laughter]
[snorts] Funny, is it? Crazy.
Where have they gone to reckon I count
Grezy? They'll be back, won't they?
Do you reckon they're just busy at the moment?
Look at him just picking their moment. I
remember that on Family Guy. Look at
that tree just picking its moment. Yeah.
They're waiting for the approaching
video, isn't it?
And then they're going to mock me.
[sighs and gasps] >> [snorts]
>> It's time to find a woman soon, Greavvesy.
Are you looking forward to it?
Finding someone to share your life with
You're looking forward to it, Grezy.
You'll like it down here, son. You'll
never have to grow up. Grezy, remember that?
never have to grow up.
I love that
there were some questions on a quiz show earlier.
No lad, you can't follow me on
Instagram. You can add me on Snapchat if you want.
Yeah. Anyways, there was a thing on a
quiz so greasy and it was talking about
American abbreviated states and I got
all of them right. I know abbreviate. Do
you know what that means?
Yeah. They abbreviate their states.
It's actually quite weird.
They actually abbreviate their states.
It just sound It just looks so weird. Yeah,
I know about abbreviation states, but I
know a lot about America. I'm good at
geography, Greavvesy. I'm very good at geography. Yeah. Yeah. Anyways,
I need to go to bed, lad. So, I'll talk
to you tomorrow. [snorts]