Oh [ __ ] [ __ ] hell, man.
The [ __ ] happened there? Two of me [ __ ] joined. Madness.
Yeah, two of me joined, bro.
I feel he's updating, bro. It's [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
Yeah. So, at least you know you don't
get banned in the bookies. That was a
load of uh bollocks.
Yeah, that was a load of bollocks. That never happens.
Yeah, that never happens. Yeah, [snorts]
people are not pulling out thousands for
machines, lad. And that was literally
today, just as I come back from the
dentist. So, that's [ __ ] bro. That
was literally today.
I lo I lost uh 50 earlier than 100. So,
I lost 150.
So, I actually lost 150.
Yeah, I lost 150. They saw the white man
coming. That's all I can say.
No, it doesn't matter what happened. But
anyways, yeah. See, it's [ __ ]
Yeah. 150. Yeah. [clears throat]
I don't want to go today. I don't want
to go out today if I had to. Yeah.
Same old [ __ ] never changes, isn't it?
You can't even win any money in your own
country. What a life, eh? What a [ __ ] life.
I lost I put 50 in I got it to 90, lost
it, and then 100 to 40. Gives you It
gives you It gives you money. It gives
you money to take it back. I don't see
what the point is. What is the point of
giving a win if you're just going to
take it back? It defeats the whole object. >> Yeah. So, yeah.
[sighs and gasps]
M just to give it back. I spat on the
machine anyways. Not in that one. The
other one, the William Hill earlier.
I spat on the machine earlier as well.
Not that one. The other one in my area
when I lost 50.
What? I I'm going to take 40 up. Really?
Really? I'm going to take 40 profit.
Really, bro? Really? When I when I put
100 pound in?
>> Yeah. Okay. Yeah, man. Whatever. Hello.
>> Yes, lad.
>> Yeah, I told you you don't win on him
like that, bro. And I also lost another
50 earlier as well.
>> Yeah, I watched the video. I watched all
the way at the end. Yeah, you're right.
It's 10 to one all the time. And
>> And you also don't And you also don't
And you also don't get banned for filming.
>> Yeah, you don't. That's true. Yeah. Um
at the end of the day, you put that
video up and Yeah. You do not win. Like
you don't win on them machines. Nobody
wins on them machines. [snorts] Load of
[ __ ] 10 to one all the time. 10 to one.
>> Yeah. I was 150 in. Yeah. Well, I put 50
in early. I got to 90 lost it. Then 100
to You just get like 40 50 pound win.
You think, oh, your lux and then you
lose it all.
>> Oh, what it does, Peter? It gives you
like a 40 to one or 50 when you've got
like coppers on it. That's what it does.
>> Yeah, it's [ __ ] bro.
>> Yeah. You showed the reality the
faulties on that um video lad.
>> And it was today as well by the way.
Your boyfriend was saying this the other
day. No, it was actually today. Today
I'm talking about the dentist. So yeah,
stop making stuff up.
>> What's going on, lad?
>> Nothing, bro. Just chilling, man.
>> Oh yeah, that was in. Yeah.
>> So what do you think that you even said
it's not adding up with that Joe is it?
>> Yeah, it's not. There's no way he wins
as much as he does. I don't agree with
it, but [snorts]
>> I don't know. He doesn't I don't know.
plays 100 let him doesn't he? He's
[ __ ] probably that's probably even worse.
>> Obviously it's 100 numbers in it. Yeah,
you would think but
>> somehow jump you coming up. Jump jump
jump on the box lad. We'll have a talk about it.
>> But he's scared to talk. So how's that
going to happen bro?
>> Dusty showy. You're right. That's all it
does. When I played it the other day it
was 10 to one 20 to1. Obviously I got
lucky with number two for 100 to one but
I was playing on it.
>> England whis. That's typical England. It
will never change.
>> You can't get a win on woman, bro. We stay.
>> Yeah, you got you got to put a lot in. No,
>> not necessarily. >> No,
that was more than enough.
Anyways, is what it is, bro.
>> What did you feel like after losing a
150 then? It just
>> No, it didn't piss me off. It didn't
piss me off. It pissed me off. The first
50 pissed me off, but then when I lost
that, I was just doesn't care to be honest.
Exactly. Dusty's right there. Stick the
foot back. Yeah.
>> [ __ ] bad lad. Jump on.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Link up.
>> I've seen that you just missing after
missing that bar as well. >> Yeah.
Look for what did Seaside Mark used to
say? Hey, look for what you ain't got.
>> Yeah, he did. Jack, remember that? Yeah.
>> Look for what you ain't got.
>> Exactly the meaning. That's to the left
hand side of Zero. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Don't say that you'll get banned
for bookies either, Joe, cuz that excuse
has been thrown out the bin today,
hasn't it, Triple?
>> Isn't that right, Triple?
I mean, I don't gamble. Well, I mean
that I mean I don't really gamble to be
honest. This is like a one-off to be fair.
>> I I had a gun on it the other day. Lad
[ __ ] that was first time I played it
in [ __ ] ages. Like
>> yeah, I was trying to hit the 17.
>> Oh, I seen 17 was your jackpot. Another
one. It went nowhere near or by
>> and I bet if it went on it, it would
have been 10 to one. I bet you it would
might give you 20 to be generous, but
would have been more than 10. Want to be
more than 20? >> No.
>> Too much money on it. I thought it
>> Yeah. Even if it was 50 to one, that's
all right. Is it?
>> 51 would have done. You'd have been 200,
wouldn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. Even 40 to one would have done, Pete.
>> Yeah. Even 30 really.
>> Yeah. It's not 10 or 20.
>> Yeah. That was the worst.
>> Imagine if that 17 that was 10 to one,
man. It just sickened you. I've done a 40 quid.
>> I think I would smash the machine.
>> Yeah, lad. Is it in it?
>> Yeah, bro. [clears throat]
>> If I blow rule it online, if you get
Yeah, you do, Dusty. That's it. Like
that. That bar's [ __ ] scandalous. Like,
>> that bad to [ __ ] get a spin. >> Madness. Yeah.
Who would have changed it?
Never change your life.
>> I was laughing at that account. I was
laughing at that account earlier when I
was on the bus pre-owning McDonald.
>> That's a back rest.
>> Yeah. It's a weird name, isn't it?
>> Yeah, lad. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, well
take away later, I think.
>> [ __ ] lad.
Just going to get a takeaway later. I
was already in a bad mood when I woke up
to be fair. >> Yeah.
>> So like it won't even like Yeah.
Just going to have a takeaway later I think.
>> What you going to get?
>> Probably an Indian.
>> Do you not get like Chinese food or
>> sometimes? Yeah, but it's not open
around here today.
>> It's open tomorrow. Obviously I can get
one but there's a certain one I like
going to and it yeah I do
the reality of faulty
>> you you going to gamble today
>> yeah we going to put a foot back on later
>> I just knew everyone jumped straight on
that video when it was up
>> yeah I got the notification me
>> was picking my moment in it
>> yeah lad Yeah. Madness.
>> I'll be M man. >> Yeah.
>> Really? What's up?
>> I wonder if Joe gets a win a day then.
>> Probably. He always wins. He's the only
one that always wins. [laughter]
>> He's the only one that always wins. It's
mad, isn't it? [laughter]
>> Yeah. He he does win a lot like yours.
>> Makes you wonder, doesn't it?
>> Yeah. Just waiting for the upload of Jo.
>> I'm not subscribed to him to be fair.
>> Cuz she's just another obsessed one in
it. So I just unsub. >> Yeah.
>> You know them ones. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. You can't hit that [ __ ] and
even if he gives you a 4050£50 win, it
takes it back trying to get the next
spin. That's what annoys me.
>> Yeah. Yeah. He can't hit a photo toffee lad.
>> Who used to say that?
>> Mark won it.
>> Timmy Eldridge.
>> Oh, was it Timmy? Was I thought it was Mark?
>> No, it was Timmy. Oh.
>> Oh. Well,
>> so what's your plans today like lad?
>> Nothing. Yeah.
>> Um today I'm going I'm learning bed now
at the minute. Um a bit bad but I'm
going to go for a battle. I'm going to
play a darts and that later I think.
>> Yeah. Nice man. might have a couple of G eyes and yeah
long mind back now quit while I'm ahead
and then do the same a few times a month.
>> Yeah, I've got a drink today. I never
bothered I just [ __ ] bothered.
>> Nah, you only won the one Samuel
Jackson. That's 1,600 but he gave 200
quid to the faulty. So
>> he didn't win, 1600. He won,200.
>> I thought it was 16.
>> No, the game got postponed in it.
>> Oh, I did that. I didn't know that last. Right. Right. >> Yeah. >> It
do do you do that over one 1.5?
>> No. It's a [ __ ] mugs bet. [snorts]
>> He has [clears throat] about He takes
too many aims. He's lucky he got that
many. He won't get another one then. I don't think. >> Yeah.
>> Block takes too many teams. Most I do a trouble.
>> Yeah. And even that's hard. Two teams
maximum I like to do to be fair.
Anything more than two, you always seem
to lose when you do more than two.
>> Small pinches of the way forward, lad.
>> Yeah, man.
>> But give credit where credit's due. That
was a good little bet banger. Don't lie
to be fair.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Yeah. So, you win 40 pound and then you
lose. How do you lose all that money,
bro? on the two pound roulette.
>> Start off well, low pet, didn't it? It
start off well, lad. You got loads of
>> But I knew it was coming. I knew it was
coming, didn't you?
>> But you knew it wasn't going to last forever.
>> Yeah. Never. That's what they do. That's
what they do, bro. They'll let you win
4050 pound and it will [ __ ] you. Do you
not understand how just had to get
people addicted to something?
>> Yeah. Like when you put that 100 and you
got to 140. If you had that 50 go down,
you could walk with that 40 bar pinch.
>> No, but I was 150 in it.
>> Yeah, but that's what I'm saying. If you
didn't lose 50. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I won't be gambling anymore
anyways. So I could be during all I
want. I won't be gambling any anymore anyways.
>> Is that it? Why not?
>> Yeah, man.
>> What about the [ __ ]
>> Yeah, maybe that. But not the machines
and that. You know what I mean? No. Yeah,
fair play it
[ __ ] is, lad. Yeah,
[ __ ] fair. You will win. You've not
you haven't won for a while. Like to be
fair, Joy's right. Yeah, you used to
always win on you. You used to always
get a few little fppy touches, man. You
used to always eat your big numbers on
there at one point. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, man.
>> I might have a go later, mate. Can you record it?
>> I could upload your hair later. I'm
going to have a little look. You know, I
won't be gambling again, bro. I
shouldn't have even done that to be fair.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> You ever feel guilty when you're doing it?
>> Guilty? Why would you feel guilty?
>> Cuz you're like, damn, it's bad in it.
only bad if you depends if you can control it.
>> It's bad though.
>> I can control gambling. I'm not dedicating [snorts]
feeding chasing the losses. That's when
that caused bad. >> Yeah.
>> You reckon Timmy would have saw my video? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I don't know. Actually, Tim would
have seen that Tim was on here. >> [laughter]
>> It's funny, is it?
>> They got that mark off, didn't they? >> Yeah.
>> Got that mark off.
>> Yeah, they did. They did.
>> You reckon he'll come back?
>> Say that again.
>> You reckon he'll uh come back? I sp the
machine, Joe. You know the the one
earlier before that? I spat on it, bro.
What did they say to you?
>> I just walked out. I sp and walked out.
>> This is what I mean. >> Huh?
>> You shouldn't be gambling. If it's me,
you should mach.
>> Think I'm going to You think I'm going
to You think I'm going to punch you and
hurt my hand and not hurt your hand?
That's ridiculous, isn't it? Spitting is
the worst thing you could do as well.
You know that?
>> It's [ __ ] rotten. Yeah, it is.
>> Yeah, man. [snorts] Joe, what's the most
you've lost on the FOB? Truthfully, I
know you always winning that, but like
what's the most you've lost on a FOB?
>> I am full of cold me. Me [ __ ] you
know killing me. Me s you need to get a
C down you man.
>> A vindaloo.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm getting.
>> What was the crack with that John?
Didn't you say to him not to have one of
them vindaloos? But he wouldn't listen, would he?
>> No, I might. Do you know what? I might
go for a mill today, bro. I'm not sure.
just a city
>> maybe. Bro, I'm not sure.
Don't know what I'm doing. >> Yeah.
>> So, what what did Monty go live on Christmas for?
>> Just to see what saddles were on here.
>> Was there anyone on there?
>> Apparently, I did wasn't on Christmas
Day, but said there was five people in.
>> He said that's five people without a
family this Christmas. Is it
>> right Monty? I lost 1.2K once and never
again, but I've lost 6 or 700. Yeah,
it's too easy to lose big big money on
them properties. Join it.
>> UK asylum. Fill him the meal. Yeah, fill
>> I think I'm just going to go for a mill
to be fair, man.
>> Just to get yourself down to waxies, lad.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] that.
You know, I'm just going to go for a
meal, I reckon, cuz by if I order it,
it's going to cost like 30 something. I
might as well just go for a meal, bro.
[ __ ] it. [clears throat]
Go for an Indian is it?
>> Yeah. Are you going to uh
take any money for me? Like,
>> yeah, man. At some point. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Um I need to go to dentist
tomorrow. Get a tooth pulled out.
Back to it.
I thought you were there.
>> I was there today, but it's good. They
said, "Yeah, one of your back teeth and
he's pulling out."
>> Probably going to get pulled out tomorrow. Nothing else. >> Oh,
>> the back one is it obviously happens,
isn't it? Yeah.
>> Yeah. Them [ __ ] your [ __ ] mouth
anywhere, man. You can't look on.
>> Well, you you had it in my back, man.
One of my back to out. Yeah. [ __ ]
>> what? They took it out.
>> Took it out. Yeah.
>> Well, how long ago?
>> 225 actually lost that to be honest.
Wasn't the best.
>> How long How long How long ago?
>> About two year ago. Doesn't hurt, you know.
>> But then after you
>> losing losing a losing tooth all the way
at the back, though, there's a big
difference between losing your teeth at
the front and losing one tooth at the
back at almost [ __ ] you know what
I'm saying? At 30 years of age, there's
a big difference. You know what I'm
saying, bro? Like that [ __ ] odds has
actually got missing teeth all around
his mouth. Like they're actually missing
teeth. How the [ __ ] is you have you got
missing teeth at that age?
Yeah. Too much coke. Yeah.
I need to cut back on that as well. I am
cutting back on it.
So you say we're going by what you're saying.
I want to go for a meal, but I don't
know if I've got the energy to even go
out. Bro, I woke up today angry as
[ __ ] bitter, bro. But I didn't want
to miss the I didn't want to miss the dentist appointment.
Yeah, but I didn't want to I didn't want
to miss the dentist appointment
cuz it's taking it for granted, is it?
So, I was so angry. I woke up bitter and
angry today, bro. [ __ ] It's not even a
joke. as I do every day.
They will never change. So,
I think I'll just order it to be honest.
I can't be bothered to move.
No, I can't be bothered to move, bro. [ __ ] that.
Only thing I was just bad experiences in
life as you should be as you should be
bitter and angry. You should be.
You [ __ ] well should be.
The only reason I was thinking of
getting a meal is because obviously the
meal is um it's going to be the same
price as the delivery. So, but I don't
think I can double it going to the city
to be honest.
>> No, it's not it's not about a doctor.
You need better experiences.
That's what you need. You don't need
help. You need better experiences. Big
difference. Big big big difference. Yeah.
So get in lad. >> Yeah.
And I started it
get a meal as you struggle to read
tomorrow. It's true that from asylum
actually. Yeah. Yeah. Your [ __ ] mouth
go your jaw that goes massive in that
man when you to
talk like spasm man spazz for a bit horrible >> really
>> it's not funny really is it [laughter]
>> the way you're saying it is funny is it
>> you should tell the doctor your mental
health isn't too good
>> yeah Joe that's what you need to tell
your doctor your mental health's not good [snorts]
>> why are you so bitter and angry
>> you know what I
I don't know if I can stop it.
[cough and clears throat]
>> Nah, just tell him you want little numb
all your mouth and that's all. You'll be
all right. You won't feel the fell.
>> How did you lose yours? Same thing in it.
M was all crack. The back my back one
was cracked. I've only lost one but
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Right at the back.
Can't really do say I [ __ ] off. No.
Well, at 28, you should have had better
better experiences, Joe. And you need to
realize life's not all about money.
That's what you need to know.
Are you on the fed today? Like, Joe, are
you playing today? [snorts] me, lad.
>> You got what?
>> I've been off this tab cigarettes for
[ __ ] over two year now. >> Yeah.
>> Smoke them vapes.
>> Nice, man.
>> Does your mom still smoke like pay?
>> Yeah, cigarettes. >> Yeah.
Does Charlene smoke? >> Yeah.
>> Oh, does she? I didn't know she smoked
it. All right.
Yeah. Do you do it? You smoke vapes, you
said, is it? Yeah.
>> Vapes, mate. Yeah. [snorts]
>> I like to hang around with people that
think the whole world is against them.
>> Some people like Yeah. There's this guy
called Oreo Man. I like them kind of people.
>> It's called
Oreo Man. His name is Black Guy.
>> I've never smoked in my life ever, you
know. That's one thing I've never done.
>> Never. You done coke with Tim?
>> I tried obviously I've tried it but I
haven't done it. It doesn't make sense.
>> Yeah, I thought it was Samuel Jackson
but I got went on the vape for me mate
and [ __ ] easy.
>> I used to vape socially like every two
months but nah I don't do anything like that. >> Yeah.
>> Oh god.
>> Damn. Not good though is it? No. That's
a mug of game in it realistically like
but everyone [snorts] does it. >> Yeah.
On tonight like I'm be doing a better day. >> Yeah.
>> What are you going to eat?
>> I'm [snorts] having a beef dinner. Really? Hi
When I get back later, I'll be on the
beef dinner. [snorts]
>> Bless you then. >> Yeah.
>> I went for breakfast this morning. Like
got like a breakfast rappers. Look,
>> I done a video dedicated to you, Grezy.
You poor [ __ ]
>> Oh, is that Gravesy? Honestly, get in, Gravesy.
>> Poor Grevy said this is a copycat
community. I was thinking of some of the
things he said. Yeah. When I was in
public and I was laughing, people was
looking at me.
>> Say that again. Sorry.
>> We said that
we said that this is a copycat community.
>> Yeah, he's right. It is.
>> So when I was So when I was uh So when I was chilling,
>> so when I was ch So when I was um when I
was chilling in public earlier, I was
laughing my ass off, bro. People was
looking at me in it. It's a copycat community.
So, is that what you done? You've done
something like this before though,
didn't you? On the train, you were
laughing at something all the way.
>> Yeah. People's looking at it. Yeah. When
Oh, yeah. I was laughing at one of Do
you remember that account that come in
and said Peter Benny can't get attached
anymore? He's he already found his mama.
>> Yeah. People's looking at me in it. [snorts]
>> What just laughing in public? >> Yeah.
>> I agree. I'm gonna start copying Grevy,
you know, like with the DVDs. I'm going
to start buying DVDs.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Grievy didn't give Grezy didn't
give me his opinion on that.
>> Is that what you done, Tiger? Tiger, I
tried them patches, mate, and they
didn't seem to work. And then I just end
up getting on the vapes and then never
>> I don't need a doctor. I need better
experiences. That's what I need.
>> Get in.
>> That's what I need. >> Peter,
>> that's what I need. Joseph, better
better experiences. So yeah, Grezy, I'm
going to start getting I'm I'm going to
start like getting some DVDs. Is that right?
>> You're getting some DVDs, Peter? >> Yeah.
>> The problem is with that, you won't be
able to watch them.
>> Why? Cuz Xbox
>> You're always on here.
You're always live on this YouTube.
>> I might I might get some I like
digestive biscuits. Triple H. [snorts]
>> Yeah, I don't mind them actually. Yeah,
to be fair.
>> You like that?
>> Anyone? I like barb bons.
>> Yeah, I like I like digest I like uh
digestives. It's your fol bastard.
Yeah, I like digestive me.
>> Oh yeah, Tiger.
Nah, I give them a go, mate. And just
there didn't work. Like, so I just end
up got the vapes. I've been the vape for
two. Yeah. Like I need your ease off
these. I'm bang on the vape.
>> You remember when I said you should go
drinking with Ant and Deck and you told
me to be realistic?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
What should I do I need to really be realistic?
>> Well, yeah. The [ __ ] celebrities aren't there.
It doesn't matter. You live in the same
place. You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. But you live in the same But you
live in the same place, isn't it?
>> You have Yeah. Yeah. You'll have to dip
your discus now that the dentist is
>> I don't watch porn anymore. I don't watch porn. [laughter]
>> Yeah. He used to watch the old vintage
porn, didn't you? >> Yeah.
>> What did that man say about that?
>> He said that's strange. He said, "What?"
He said, "You watch porn from the 70s?
That's weird." Yeah. A bit scared that like
>> said he's ever heard of that before. Yeah.
>> Not good. Pete
>> from the 70s.
>> I think it's because it was it looks
more realistic than it does now. Triple.
You know what I mean? That's what why.
>> Where are you?
>> You get what I'm saying? >> Yep.
>> And you think with that Johnny Sims in
it just looks too fake. Which it is
fake, but do you get me?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. [snorts]
>> You know Johnny Sims, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> Well, you you you've watched him.
>> No, I'm watching. I know he is now.
>> How do you know who he is then? Aren't >> I? [laughter] Yeah. Yeah.
>> Some of them are either granny's or dead
now from Jo.
>> Yeah, they are. Yeah.
So, you giving that uh
that cold approaching a rest for a bit
now, are you?
>> For the rest of my life on Yeah, cuz you
meant to go out on New Year, weren't
you? But you said you're not bothering.
You can't be asked with the same sad song.
>> Yeah, it's boring. It's very toxic. It's
very boring, bro. It's very, very boring.
You didn't go out New Year's Eve either. >> Who?
>> You didn't go out New Year's Eve, is it?
>> Yeah, I did. New Year. New Year's Eve. Yeah.
>> New Year's Eve.
>> Yeah, I stayed in.
>> Um, what's Tiger? Tiger saying. I have
stopped smoking. Oh, boy. I still for a
smoke. Yeah. Saying that, Tiger. When I
have a drink, I have a tab on the drink.
Like, I'm not going to lie. I I buy tabs
when I'm on the drink now. [sighs]
PJ pull this tiny plunk of some old
granny from Jo.
>> Why does Why does So, why does Monty say
it's the same faces?
cuz it's the same people in it. [snorts]
You've gone John Lavy. It's the same
faces that sat there all Clinty. You've
got the likes of Cho Time V. It's the
same [ __ ] on there.
>> Hopefully it will change one day. Is it?
>> Only way it'll change is when they die.
>> And even then they'll still be on there.
Monty said he said even when they're
dead, they'll still be on here.
>> Yeah. Monty's an idiot.
>> No, it's true. They'll never get off in
it. Well, how come they be on here if they're dead?
>> That's what he said. [laughter]
>> Yeah, he's an idiot, man. But yeah,
sometime it'll end with these people. [laughter]
>> Well, so they'll be on their deathbed
still doing it until they like drop dead.
>> More than likely, lad. Yeah. Yeah. >> Yeah.
Makes sense, isn't it? I think it's mad
how cuz um before I went out New Year's
Eve I'm sure I was on someone's live and
and it was the same face like you think
they go out and that wouldn't you like
they haven't got a life most of these
you know here
>> no mad man
>> they ain't
a got a life
>> that been fair what he said was
>> same people same story next year
>> he took the air off as well didn't he Yeah.
Yeah. I'm going to go for a meal, I reckon.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yeah, man.
Probably have to shower before Yeah. I'm
going to shower cuz I don't Yeah. [snorts]
>> Yeah, man.
>> What time you going out, lad?
>> I'm not sure. I'm going to have a
shower, brush my teeth again, and Yeah.
do an Indian. Nice Indian.
>> Cost you when you go out like Peter?
>> A lot, bro. Well, up up north up here
right on a Sunday you get
>> I mean I go to the city in it. I go to
the city so it's like it was more
>> they do special do specials and that then
>> like where you get to [ __ ] start the
main rice and for so much. >> Mhm.
>> It's going to cost a bomb.
>> It's going to cost a bomb. Mate, [snorts]
>> stupid that price, man.
>> They were so nice.
>> Just get the special. It's cheaper.
>> How much [snorts] do you pay for it?
>> [ __ ] 14 quid or something for this
bad guy special. >> Yeah,
>> that's any any starter, any man, any
rice, any nine and pop it on.
>> Yeah, when I go it's like 40 pound me
when I get everything.
That's [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> But that's Yeah, but no, for an Indian.
Yeah, a nice Indian. I'd pay that. But
not for a [ __ ] roast dinner, bro.
That roast dinner. When I last went for
a roast dinner, it cost me £44. Never
again. But I would pay for a nice
Indian. I'd pay it for a nice Indian,
but not for a [ __ ] roast dinner, bro.
It didn't even have lamb on it.
>> I remember that roast. Yeah. You paid
for that, didn't you?
>> Yeah, but I pay it for an Indian. I
don't mind, bro. Paying for an Indian. I
know, but 40 quid for an Indian outrageous.
>> We get a lot.
>> Yeah, you might get a lot, but you can
get the special for for 15 quid up here. 14 quid.
>> But you live in the northeast.
>> That London's prices are ridiculous in it.
>> Yeah, it is. But you live in the
northeast that's why. I mean, if I go to
where I mean I go somewhere else, but
like it's I just like it where I go in
it. It's like um Yeah, I just go to a certain place.
>> Yeah. Yeah. is uh are you going to brick like
>> that's London prices it? Yeah man.
>> So where you going to go ladder?
>> Yeah that's where I always go.
>> What what you going for? Vindaloo.
>> Yeah man.
>> Why don't you go for a foul?
>> I've already had it. Did you see the
video where I done that when I done the challenge?
>> I kind of done. No. No.
>> No. I tried it. It wasn't It was hot but
it didn't defeat me, bro. There's only
been one thing that's defeated me.
That's that car like Reaper burger.
Oh, that was that was talking.
>> Where was that from?
>> Uh, Slim's Chicken.
Dave's Chicken. Have you seen Do you
have it there? You must have one in Newcastle.
>> What a Dave's Chicken. >> Yeah.
>> Not seen one about Eli.
>> It's like red and white. Yeah, bro. That
is hot. That's hot.
>> Did you finish it?
>> Killed me, bro. No. Three bites was
enough for me, bro.
>> Was Charlie being able to handle it?
>> [ __ ] no. You can't even have a mad dress
that skint one. [laughter]
>> You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. But yeah, but you warned him about
the vindaloo not to rather cuz he
wouldn't be able to handle it. But he
done it. He done it to fit in.
>> Yeah. Yeah. He didn't listen in it.
>> What happened? Did he go on? Was he on
the toilet all night?
>> Yeah. The next morning.
>> You did warn him though, Pete? >> Yeah.
>> It's nice though, is it? A nice meal.
What? What's You've paid hundreds for a
meal before though in it. I swear you
have on a date.
>> Never paid hundreds for a meal ever.
>> I'm sure you paid a good money once before.
>> Say that again.
>> I'm sure you paid good money once
before, haven't you?
>> I've been for a nice steak and that but
never been when I first met our last
[snorts] like before we split up and
that [ __ ] I went we took I went to a
nice Italian me. I got um
>> I got steak
>> got carbon past [clears throat]
50 60 quid for us both to eat.
>> That's all right. So I would have spent
over So with this meal I probably would
be spending over 200 pound today. >> Yeah.
>> Gambling and food.
>> Yeah. [laughter] [snorts]
>> That's mad is it?
>> [ __ ] ridiculous life. Yeah, London is
expensive to be fair, bro. All of it's
expensive, you know.
>> I don't live in London like I'm up
north. It's quite cheap to be here.
>> It is. It is. It is, bro.
>> The rent's cheap as well. Rent rent
houses is cheap as [ __ ] as well. >> Yeah.
>> I don't think many people can afford to
live in London nowadays unless they're
[ __ ] celebrity, bro.
>> Most people, you know, most people in
London, most people London, they either
live with their parents or they live in
a room. They don't have their own place, you know.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Which you can see why in it.
>> Yeah. 100%. Yeah. I'll get me own place
soon, mate. Just [ __ ]
[ __ ] too much money when you got all
your bills and all your [ __ ] you
[ __ ] rent. [ __ ]
>> How how much are you left with every
month after you've paid everything?
>> I don't pay I've only got me phone. I
[ __ ] I'm back at my mom's. So I don't
pay no [ __ ] all mate.
>> You don't pay anything? I don't. Yeah,
>> for me, man. [ __ ] cussy here. But I'm
nearly 30, man. I need to [ __ ] move out of
>> You're single in it. So, it's like
what's the point, bro? If you're single, then
>> I know, I know.
>> You know what I'm saying? It's like It's
not like you're with someone. You know
what I'm saying? I would just I would
just stay there and just like go
traveling if I was you or something.
I'll just enjoy it as much as I can.
>> Yeah. I don't pay no lo, you know? All I
have to pay to pay for phone bill every
month. That's it. >> Huh?
>> I just pay me phone bill every month.
It's only director. But I've got a phone
bill and the rest of mine. >> Yeah.
>> So I drink all
>> I don't really drink much anymore to be fair.
>> Are [snorts] you having a drink with
your Indian or probably not?
>> Nah. Nah.
>> Yeah, I am having a drink a drink of Coke.
>> Yeah. You like a Coke, lad, don't you?
>> No. I need to cut down on that though
100%. So that will probably be the only
one I have today. I need to really cut
down on that, bro.
>> Yeah, it's no good for your teeth. That
fizzy pop that tooth and that is it.
Yeah. No, seriously. Seriously.
>> Yeah, I would have a nice
>> You can have one. You can have one a
day. You can have one and reduce it and
and you know what I mean? But you need
to stop drinking like it like that, bro.
And but you know, it's bad.
>> It's bad, bro.
>> Yeah. It only happens as you get older
as well. Like you know when you're 18,
19, you could it doesn't catch up with
you until you're older.
up when you the thingy. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Like our way in it. Like you know
what I'm saying?
>> I didn't expect you you to say you had a
tooth pulled out though.
>> I right at the back. The back one had
[ __ ] wasn't rotted or was just all
[ __ ] was cracked and that man. >> Yeah.
>> Just took it out for us.
>> Was it the right side?
>> Left side lad.
>> I brush my teeth three times a day. You
said you brush your teeth for two weeks.
Maybe that's not helping us.
>> I brush I brush I brush my teeth three
times a day.
>> No. So when I when I have a shower, I'm
going to brush my teeth before going out
and then when I go to bed later. >> Yeah. >> Yes.
>> You get me?
>> All right.
I brush on the morning on the night
mate. Like two hours a day.
>> You said you said you can live up. You
said you can't live a £500 a month in it.
>> Obviously not. [laughter]
>> I spend [ __ ] I spend 60 week mate.
>> You what on your vapes?
>> On me b That's about me ving me [ __ ]
me fueling all that. >> Yeah.
>> Fueling that [ __ ] Yeah.
Impossible. They're not vote going for
any food or anything not getting popping
in that it's [ __ ] But now these
people live off that [ __ ] UC a month,
mate. What is it? 300 quid a month.
>> Yeah. [ __ ] that.
>> [ __ ] that lad. [laughter]
I wouldn't dare. [ __ ]
>> No, bro. >> No.
>> Is that what Sean gets?
>> No, I don't know what he gets, bro.
>> He's [ __ ] skint. That's all I know.
It showed 13 grand in mil, you know.
>> Yeah. After losing my pip. Okay, bro.
Well, I'm going to do video later
anyways with my meal.
>> Did you get your leg paid?
>> I've had money, bro. No, I didn't get
any money today. I have money, bro.
These people don't know anything. You
see what I mean? They don't know
anything about anyone. That's why they
don't they don't affect me, bro. You understand? Hi.
>> They don't know anything, but I just let
them keep guessing.
Are you meet I thought you meet that
Terry today lad.
>> Yeah if he comes to Stratford I'll meet him.
>> Oh yeah yeah.
>> Well he can come to Brick Lane if he wants.
>> Well you smash your head in fire. Have you Indian >> 100%.
Don't show 20 notes or skin. This is
really this is really boring bro. These
people are really boring bro.
>> They've been doing this for years though.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Really? Really, really, bro? years.
>> Just show them 20 quid later.
>> Show [clears throat] them 20 quid.
>> Yeah. If they show me 20 quid, I'll show
them. I've already shown you more than
20 pound today. I showed you £100.
>> That's true. Yeah.
>> So, what did you do? Go to cash point.
Have another 100 quid out for the fault. >> Yeah.
>> I lost 150 today.
>> Them floppies are [ __ ] man. Aren't
they? Yeah. [snorts]
>> Anyways, I'm going to get going.
Anyways, I'm going to have a shower and
get ready and be back later. All right,
lad. Right. Catch you later. Yeah, man.
All right. See you.