Yo. Yeah.
It's landed back. Oh, not long. Yeah,
that was lush. Oh,
[ __ ] full up.
I was just talking to someone.
To be honest, it was all right today. It
wasn't that busy.
Probably because it's January.
Yeah, probably because it's January.
There was some people out, but obviously
I didn't approach because I don't
contradict myself. I don't contradict
So, when I say that they're all evil and
they're all scum in the earth, I meant
it. I don't contradict myself.
And obviously me approaching this contradicting myself.
So, I didn't approach cuz I know they're
all the same evil.
>> Yeah, but there's still people out, but
it was quiet. Yeah. Heat.
I don't know why people to tell I don't
know why people tell people to get money
then money doesn't change anything.
I'm a clear example.
I'm a clear clear example.
No, money doesn't mean anything. We're
talking to this guy, bro. Money don't mean nothing. [clears throat] surprised
why so many people talk about money.
That's something that people should get.
It doesn't mean anything, bro. I'm not
sure why people do.
Maybe, like I said, it's because I've
done so much in my life already. I don't know, but
I mean, it doesn't make me happy.
I'm still [ __ ] you know,
Oh, I lost 150 pound gambling today
after I come out the dentist
cuz I was getting mood swings all day
and thinking about women and how they
[ __ ] me over for years and [ __ ] Getting
them nasty, nasty mood swings. So, I
gambled 150. Uh, didn't win anything. Yeah,
I went to Liverpool Street. I'm back now.
God, I hate have to go back to the
dentist tomorrow, bro. It's [ __ ]
annoying, man. I hate have to go to places.
It doesn't matter, bro. I've got money.
I've got money that it's not it's it's
not even a loss. That's how bad it is to
me because I've got money. So,
to be honest, no one actually said anything.
Yeah. I have to have my tooth pulled out.
Don't remind me, bro.
I hate having to be somewhere, you know?
I can never sleep when I have to properly
Yeah, I've heard of that. I've actually
heard of that before. Now you say it.
That That's been going years. I have
heard of that.
Yeah, I was up I was in Brick Lane
today. There was not many people out.
There were some people out, but there
weren't that many people considering London.
Yeah, I was thinking about my bad
experiences with women. You can't escape
it, bro. And then I got depressed again.
It's never ending, this, isn't it? It's
never ever ending, bro. Is it never ever
ever ending? I woke up in a [ __ ] mood
swing. I woke up in a mood today having
mood swings. So, the only reason I went
to the dentist is cuz I'm not going to
waste a dentist appointment.
They're so hard to get, you know? It's
taking a piss. So, I I I didn't want to
like waste it and that, but I was I've
been in a mood all day, bro.
I've been in a mood all day.
It was a bit better when I had the food
and that, but I've been in a mood all day.
Sad, sad, sad life, bro. And I need to
have to start coming off YouTube as well
cuz Laney doesn't want me on YouTube and
want to respect Laney's wishes and stuff. So yeah,
sad life, isn't it? Sad sad sad life.
There was women out about there was
women about today as well, Mike.
Obviously I didn't approach cuz all
women are the same.
They're all evil. So obviously naturally
I didn't approach. I saw some people out though.
Yeah. If I didn't have to go dentist I
would just stay in bed all day.
I would just stayed in bed. Done nothing.
Yeah. I'll just be off you. I'll just be
in bed all day anyways. I won't be doing
anything when I'm off here.
But it's just Lane doesn't want me on
that in it. So, probably for the best,
but I'll just be in bed. I'd just be
doing nothing to be fair, just like always.
Yeah, I'll try it sometime, mate. I I
bet you I could take it. It's not worth
It's not worse than a Carolina Reaper
burger. I've had the Carolina Reaper
burger and that's the only thing that's
been able to defeat me. And I'm telling
you that that Bangalore Village is not
worse. It is not uh
I think I was in Bangalore village
today. Sure that's what the place was called.
I'm sure that is the place I was in today.
No, it's not worse, mate. There's
nothing worse than that Carolina Weber
burger. I'm sure I was in that place today
thinking of it.
I'm sure I was in that place today.
>> Yeah. I'm sure that was the place I was
I was in today. I'm sure it was.
I read the napkin. I'm sure it was that
that was the place I was in today. I'm sure
that was it. I'll have to try it.
I wish I could just stay in bed
tomorrow, but I can't sadly.
Got to get tooth taken out. Ouch.
I'll be depressed.
I'll be depressed tomorrow like every
day. Thinking about my bad experiences with women as always
and how nothing changes in your life.
Bad, bro. Bad,
bad, bad, bad, bad, bad. It really is bad, lad. [snorts]
I don't like going out, bro. I feel like
the whole world's against me. I don't
like going out. I don't like being in
public. I don't like nothing.
I just like staying in bed.
To be fair, yeah,
because I've got anxiety. Never had
anxiety in my life.
Anyways, I'm blocking you. Anyways, you troll thingy.
No, I don't have anxiety.
Never had anxiety in my life.
No, cuz every time I'm in public, I just
think of my bad experiences.
I've got anxiety. You're telling someone
like me, I've got anxiety. Really?
Yeah. That's typical self projection.
Yeah. So, as I was saying, it just gets
worse over the years. I don't think I
was as as bad last year. I was still
bad, but I'd eventually calmed down.
This is not changing, bro.
I told this guy in Belgium earlier as
well. This life is not changing.
It's really, really bad when you've been
wronged all your life. I mean, I've come
out I come out of Liverpool Street and
I'm seeing these people vaping. So
westernized. So westernized. Nothing
about this country ever changes. So
westernized, you know, so westernized. Yeah.
And that was bad today that I gambled,
bro. You need to try to nip that in the bud.
It's just a cycle, isn't it, bro? isn't it?
I should have really gambled today, but
I was just having mood swings and that
in it. So,
The reason I don't tell my friends about
this as well because uh I don't want
them to think I'm weird cuz they won't
understand. And that's another thing as
well. Uh here's another thing. I saw
some uh uh uh account called Pooh. I
shouldn't even be addressing this
anyway, but the account's called um
the account's called Pooh. And he was
saying, "Oh yeah, after all these years,
you would have thought the common deminator.
I can't even pronounce it. It's me."
Again, I have shown messages. I have
shown approaches suggestion that it's
showing that it's women and you're still
blaming me. Well, have you got
selective? Have you got selective eyesight?
because I mean I don't know what more
evidence people can show you to prove
that it's them, you know. So yeah,
but I don't care about any of that stuff
anyways cuz like I said, once you
realize it's a gender thing, it doesn't
bother you. Once you realize people are
just sexist and biased, I'm not even
just talking about YouTube, I'm talking
about Germany, then you know it doesn't um
it doesn't bother you
when you know how sexist and biased they
are. You know, you just Yeah. don't care.
No, I hate England. Can't get dates. You
can't get sex. You have to wait around
for everything. I had to wait 20 minutes
today for a train in London.
The weather's [ __ ] Everything [ __ ]
about this country. Everything. Mainly,
I tell you what mainly ruined it is the
people in England. It's actually mainly
the people, the men. They're just [ __ ]
And then obviously the waiting around
for things, the weather, the way the system is.
But the people are the number one thing
in this country. There's so many [ __ ]
Me and Antman just said the same thing. Nah.
Yeah, I was bitter all day today, Joe. I
don't calm down anymore. You know when I
used to calm down, I don't calm down
anymore. There was people out today. I
didn't approach them.
No, I wouldn't do that, bro. I don't
contradict myself. So,
I was actually talking to someone in a
shop that was from Scotland cuz I've
been to Scotland, but I never asked them
out obviously cuz we know what they were
like, but it was just a normal conversation. Yeah.
We'll go to the shittiest shitty dentist
tomorrow. [ __ ] sake. I hate having to
be at places.
[ __ ] annoying that is, bro. Don't
like that stuff.
Yeah, I am bitter. And it's never going
to change until the experiences change.
I'm never going to change.
And that's that's good, man. Uh, until
the experiences change, I won't. And I I
think that's fair enough to be honest.
That's fair enough.
I'm in every right. I'm in every right
to be better.
Every right. I've got every right to be.
Every single right to be. I could have
carried on drinking if I wanted to.
There's loads of bars around. I mean,
even though there wasn't really people
out, I could have if I wanted to, but
nah. No, no, no, no, no.
>> I told you, bro. I'm done. You didn't believe me.
>> Yeah, I would hate it
then. I would hate it. Simple.
Do you have your Do you have your donut?
Did you have your donuts?
I bought some donuts.
Yeah. Yeah. We need to nip that gambling
in the bud as well, bro, because that's uh
that's not good, you know.
No, thank you. I'd rather give up.
See, year a year ago or two years ago,
I'd eventually calm down and be like,
"Yeah, okay. This is just a phase. We'll
go out again. We're just being silly.
But not anymore. Not anymore.
You know, I knew I was done. I knew I
was done from last month. I already knew
I was done forever. Yeah.
I knew it, bro. I [ __ ] knew it. I
[ __ ] knew it. It's just like you're
28. It's not getting better. So why I
don't know why people still tell you
it's going to get better.
You know, at the end of the day, I don't
know why people on Reddit tell you that
you're going to meet someone. Why do
they lie to you? You're never going to
meet anyone. You're never going to meet
anyone. You're never going to have a sex
life. I don't know why people keep
feeding people false hope. I really,
really, really don't understand why
people keep feeding people false hope.
I really really don't know why. I don't
know what people get out of feeding
people false hope.
Seriously, I don't, man. I really don't. Oh, yeah. So, yeah,
that's where we're at basically. Yeah. >> [snorts]
>> It's a It's I was just wrong. I was just
born in the wrong era.
Yeah. You can't get dates. You can't get
sex. What kind of life is that?
What kind of life is that? You might as
well been born Timmy Eldridge. You might
as well just been born in a wheelchair
without a dick. Really?
And I'm not even laughing when I'm
saying that. I'm generally generally
generally being serious.
He might as well been born a [ __ ] to
be honest. Like Timmy Eldridge. I'm not
even trying to be nasty. I'm being I'm
being serious. I really really am. [snorts]
I really am. You know,
it's not good, bro. Is it? It's not good.
Yeah, I don't think my mood swings are
going to stop. No,
not really. But
yeah, I saw some women out today.
I saw some people out today.
I'm trying to think what we could
actually do to better our life and I
can't think of one thing.
Well, obviously I need to stop gambling as well.
That was a one-off today. But it's not good.
It ain't a good life really, bro.
Regarding certain things.
It is everyone else's fault. Yeah, man.
Yeah. I mean, I've tried more than
anyone in the world. So, it is everyone
else's fault in my in my circumstances.
Yeah. It is everyone else's fault. But
if you go on like someone else's channel
that's complaining about stuff, I mean,
you'd have a point. I mean, they don't
try anything, but they still complain
all day on the internet. But with me,
yeah, I've definitely got a point. I've
definitely definitely got a point with
what I'm saying.
I definitely got a point because I've
actually tried. You see, whereas these
other people that moan and winge, they
don't try anything. So, they can really
blame themselves. I can't even blame myself.
And there's also nothing I can do moving
forward. And there's been evidence as
well of approaches and messages. People
act stupid. People act ignorant when
when it's women doing wrong things. I
don't know why, but they do.
Even though they're showing black and
white evidence, they still were like,
"Nah, it's you." They're they're just
they're they're um what's the word? They're
what's the word? They're just um
they just can't be helped, these people. Yeah,
but yeah, I need to be coming off
YouTube soon anyways, Joe, cuz Elanie,
so I won't be on him. Uh, yeah, cuz
Elani and [ __ ] I only really come on
here and use it for therapy sessions, to
be honest. I'm not interested in the
community. I'm not interested in people
on the community.
you if I if I found another community
with loads of people watching me, I
probably would never come on here again.
And that's that.
Everyone's addicted to it for different
reasons, I guess.
But yeah, I'm bitter every day. There's
nothing I can do to change my situation.
It's a madness, bro. I've never known
anything like it.
Oh, what's that? He's talking [ __ ] Just
another one of these immature rumors. Yeah.
Yeah, it is everyone else's fault. I've
had bad bad bad experiences.
I've documented them as well. So, yeah,
it is it is everyone else's fault when
it comes to me. Yeah, it is. Yeah. Yeah, >> [snorts]
>> It was only ever going to get worse. It
was never going to get better. It was
always going to get worse. It was
always, always, always going to get worse.
I knew it deep down. People said it
would. I always knew it was going to get worse
because it's obvious it was going to get
worse, isn't it? like, you know,
it's bad. It really is bad. What's that? Yeah.
I'm not sure, bro, what you could do.
But yeah, I can't tell my friends and
stuff because they'll just think I'm
weird. So, obviously, I don't tell
people I've met in real life because
they're not going to understand and
they'll just think you're you're just a
complete weirdo. So, yeah.
Because they've not been through what
you've been through, cuz they've not
tried as much as you, they wouldn't be
able to relate. So yeah,
bad, bro. It really is bad.
Should be able to meet people. Green cabbage
should be able to meet people. Should be
able to have a sex life.
Should be able to do all the things that
you're supposed to be doing in your
prime prime years.
But nope, you can't do nothing,
>> brother. I've shown approaching videos.
I've shown messages.
Uh that that proves it's not me. But you
keep saying it's me all you want, bro. I
mean, that's on you. If you want to
dismiss messages and you want to dismiss
approaches, that's on you, lad. I put
them out there for a reason. I put my
approaches out there for a reason. I put
my messages out there for a reason. And
if you're too ignorant to dismiss them,
that's on you, bro.
I'm not explaining myself again. That's
your fault. You know, at the end of the day,
what you're saying does not make no sense
because if you I'm sure you've seen my
approaches. I'm sure you've seen my
messages. So, you would know the answer
to that. You would literally know the
answer to the question that you're asking. >> [snorts]
>> Well, it is Well,
it is [clears throat] normal, but it's [ __ ] up.
It is It's not normal, but it is normal
because it's the West and it's never
going to change. So, I mean, no, it's
not normal, but at the same time, it is
normal, if that makes sense. [snorts] So, yeah.
But you've seen messages, you've seen
approaches. So, I'm not sure why you'd
keep blaming me when I mean, the
evidence is out there.
But [snorts] you still would rather just
make stuff up.
Like, it's in front of your eyes.
Messages and approaching videos have
[clears throat] been in front of your eyes.
They've been all in front of your eyes.
So, why are you trying to find other
stuff? It's It doesn't make you not
understand, you know? Okay. Okay. It's
like, you know, when somebody calls
someone an incel, right? You know, if
somebody calls me an incel, Joe, that
wouldn't bother me. You know why it
wouldn't bother me? If say if someone
right now come and said that you're an
incel, do you know why I wouldn't react to it?
Do you understand? Do do you know why I
wouldn't react to it and it wouldn't
bother me? It used to annoy me, but it
doesn't anymore. Well, it hasn't for
ages because I know that they don't
they're not meaning what they're saying.
That's why I wouldn't give a [ __ ] if
anyone said that. Like, you're an
insult. That wouldn't bother me
cuz they don't mean what they're saying. You see,
and what I mean by that is if it was
women complaining, everyone would feel
sorry for them. So when you realize it's
a gender thing and they're just sexist,
then it doesn't that that's not going to
affect someone. Do you understand?
Because it's a gender thing. It's not an
actual it's not a personal thing. You see?
And that is the truth.
That's the truth.
Well, well, yeah, you won't progress.
I've had too many bad experiences to
progress. And like I said, I actually do
think of revenge a lot. I actually do
think of revenge.
Proper proper proper revenge on people.
It does cross my mind.
I do actually think of like bad bad you
know. I think if I really really did get
revenge on someone bad, I think I would feel better.
I think then I would generally generally feel better.
someone that's made it scooted or [ __ ]
me over. I think I'd really, really,
really feel better then. That's the only
way I think I can move on.
And that's sad, you know. But yeah, so yeah,
and that's that. You know,
I've even thought about starting that
America [ __ ] up again. I can afford to
go there. I've got the money to go
there. I've got the money to go there.
It's It doesn't bother me. I've got the
money to go there.
Just starting up madness. It's not even
an individual person. It's just anyone
that's done me over. Like that Muslim
that was using excuses, the one that I
spent four hours was walking around
[ __ ] what was it called? Hide Park.
I've had thoughts of [ __ ] messaging
her and telling her about herself.
And that was a friend.
And that was a [ __ ] friend.
I even [ __ ] feel like messaging that come.
You know, I've got a friend in Reading
and he's a cool guy. I don't tell him
about any of this stuff cuz he's not
going to understand it and he's going to
think you're weird. I've got a friend in Red.
He's a cool guy, you know, but I
obviously I can't tell people like this, Dad,
cuz you know, they're just going to
think you're [ __ ] weird, lad. You know,
you know what I mean?
It's madness how this this is the way it is.
I hate women. I hate the double
standards. I hate everything.
I hate everything about it, bro.
Yeah, I saw your email. And to be honest
with you, I can't be bothered, bro. I'm
not going round and round and round in
circles. I've gone to his area and he
didn't come out. Simple as that. I'm not
going around in circles.
So, that's that, bro. Keep your 100 pound. Yeah.
I ain't going around in circles for another year.
So that's it with this. Anyways,
just going around in circles, bro. It's really boring.
I actually forgot about that today until
I saw your email when I come back. It's
actually really boring this, bro.
Really, really boring. I'll be coming
off here soon anyways cuz my mom don't
even want me on here and I don't I don't
want to feel like I'm disrespecting
someone in their own house.
Brother, call people out, brother. He
was calling me out. Yeah, if you
actually saw the conversation yesterday,
I'm not even going around in circles
again, bro. Yeah, I'm not going around
in circles again. [ __ ] this.
Yeah, I went to his area. He didn't come
out. End the story.
Simple. End the story. He called me out.
I went to his area. He didn't come out.
Just like Mark Samson.
Yeah. talking like the guy didn't run
away when I went to his area last time.
No, I don't need to get out of I don't
need to get out of ladies. I don't need
a job either.
I get money. I make money. I don't give
a [ __ ] about money anyways.
I don't give a [ __ ] about money, bro. I
seriously don't give a [ __ ] about money.
As long as I can eat and do what I want
to do and stuff, I don't give a [ __ ]
bro. You understand?
I don't need to get a job.
When I need a job, I can work. I can
work. I can work, bro. If I needed to
work, I'd work. Yeah. Simple.
You know, people get money. You know,
people make money, Joe. But people don't
tell you little brasses anything on here.
You do realize that you're never going
to know how people get money and that
you think that people get this and that.
You You won't know, bro. You'll never
never know. Too many glasses on here.
You would never even knew if I worked.
Even if I worked, you would never know.
You would never know that. You do realize that. you know.
Yeah. Meet people. I'm not interested in meeting people.
I hate people in England. I [ __ ] hate
them, mate. I meant dealt with enough
[ __ ] when I used to work.
I like the Oreo man out here. I actually
like the Oreo man.
I like that Oreo, man.
But he's he he has no right to complain.
He has no right to moan. I do. There's a
big difference between me and him.
He's like there is a big difference.
See, a lot of these people, they gave up
like when they were like 23, 24. I know
a guy in America. Yeah, I talked to him.
He gave up. He's 23 and he's given up.
And I'm thinking, bro, I only gave up at 28.
Well, kind of 27, but it was 28. And
it's like, what the [ __ ] bro? Like,
they're they gave up way before me, and
they never tried no as much as me.
That's mad. So, everyone's got like different levels.
No, I had my own account, brother. It
was work. I had my own account. Yeah, I
used his account years ago, but last
year I had my own account and it got banned.
So, I mean, I had my own account last year.
So, you're talking about years ago with
the other one. I had my own account last
year, mate. So, it definitely definitely was work.
It definitely definitely was work, mate.
Cuz it was my it was my own account
going into my own bank account.
You're talking about years ago when I
used a tenants account. That was years ago, lad.
Yeah. Okay, bro.
You're not going to have kids. You're
not going to meet a woman. So, how are
you going to have kids when you can't
meet a woman?
You're never going to meet anyone. Not
in this country. Been there, done that,
won the t-shirt, bro.
That's never going to happen, lad. So, yeah.
And I never need to work anyways, LT.
I'll never need to work. I get money,
bro. I make money. There's always little ways.
There's a way I'm getting money, but
that's for me to know, and you should
never find out. Yeah.
Bro, you know it's impossible to meet
women. So, I don't know why you're
bringing up women when you know it's
impossible and you know what they're
like. I don't know why you're bringing
them up. It's like that poo account. I
don't know how what more I can show you.
I've shown you approaches. I've shown
you messages. There's there there's no
getting through to some people, bro.
There's no getting through to some of you people,
which is strange. It is It is odd. It is
That's the way people are in this day and age.
Even when you're shown like certain
things, you still deny it. I don't how
know how that's possible, but you you do anyways. Yeah.
But yeah, I need to come off YouTube cuz
Elanie and that
he doesn't want me on YouTube and I
don't want her to feel like she doesn't
have rules in her own home, you know.
So, and it's for the best anyways, you
know, even if I moved out not to be on
here to be honest. So, it's a good
thing. I should really use that to my advantage. Yeah.
Reddit is banning quite fast, aren't they?
I need to [clears throat] actually
really come off it. Bro,
you need to ask yourself this question,
LT. If this Terry is such a bad man, why
didn't he come on my door when I was
living with the tenants?
Like, think about it. Okay, so I go to
his area. Yeah, listen. Listen to me.
So, he's called he's called me out. So,
he started it again. I've gone to his
area and he's not come out. So, if this
guy was really about it, why didn't he
go live outside the house? Why didn't he
come on the door? See, he doesn't You
see how it doesn't make no sense? And
then I'm happen to go to his area again
to do the same thing. I've already went
to his area. He doesn't come out. The
guy literally does not come out. He
doesn't come out of his area, bro.
So, I'm surprised that was even a
[ __ ] thing, you know?
No, I'll never be homeless, bro. It
would never happen.
Yeah, but he didn't come outside.
Yeah, but he didn't come outside when I
went to his area.
Yeah, but he didn't come outside.
But he didn't come outside either.
And I did go outside for him.
I did go outside for him, mate.
I am addressing it. But I am I am
You're the one that dismisses people's struggles, lad.
Cuz dating apps don't work.
I've used dating apps. They don't work.
Another struggle dismisser.
Yeah. Well, you're not meeting anyone in
this country, Bob Bills. No, that's not happening.
Okay, bro. Whatever.
whatever, bro. Just go around in circles. You're 36.
You're not going to get a girlfriend.
You can't even get a date. So, I don't
think you're going to get a girlfriend,
lad. And by you, I mean me. It's a
figure of speech. You're not going to
meet anyone, bro.
You need to start a new life in another
country or something.
It's never happening. Nothing's ever
changing in this country.
You know, I even went to the dentist
today. I'm thinking, "Oh, waiting around
for a train. 20 minutes. Still waiting
around for things. Still the country's
full of dickheads."
Nah, it's not more chance, mate. You
can't even get matches on dating apps. I
mean, me, I don't know about anyone
else. And even if you do, they just
troll you. No, you ain't got more
chance. If I didn't approach, I'd be a virgin.
So you don't have more chance. Maybe you
do. I'm not saying you don't. I'm just
talking by by my experiences. I would
never get into it all again. If they
weren't for you, bro. They work for you
in it. That's good, man. I mean, I don't
know about you, but they don't work for
me. And they never really have to be
honest. Not for years.
Yeah, it has a few times actually.
Yeah, a few times.
Yep. Few times
more than the dating app ever did. Yeah.
I mean, I was on Instagram. It doesn't
work. It just has worked. It doesn't
work. But it has worked. Nothing works. now. No. 150.
Yeah, I lost 150.
Well, I don't anymore cuz I don't
approach anymore. But yeah.
Yeah, I had approached for ages, bro.
I don't think I've got it in me anymore. >> No.
You think of this community grievy is this?
You can't believe it. I can believe it.
I can believe it, lad. It will never change.
Oh, I take you saw my videos then. [laughter]
Doesn't matter, bro. You're never going
to meet anyone.
This is what I'm saying. This is why I'm
bitter every day.
Thinking of getting revenge and [ __ ]
Mood swings every day.
I take it you saw the videos then, huh?
Before I deleted them.
Yeah, you can't meet no one, mate. You
can't meet no one. I've not had a date
since April or March. I keep forgetting.
There's no hope, sadly.
Don't know why people keep telling you
there is, but there really isn't.
There is no hope, lad.
Nope. Not at all.
So, I take it you saw my approaching
videos and on my other channel, huh? Yeah.
And I can't justify trying again cuz in
my head I shouldn't have to try again.
I'm 28 and I shouldn't have to try
again. So, that's in my that's in my
mind. I've had enough bad experiences to
last me a lifetime. I don't need to try
again. I'm not trying again.
Simple. It's not being difficult. It's
being real, bro. I should have to try again.
So that's why I don't try again. I
should have to
Yeah, I do know who it is. Yeah.
I wish I didn't have to go to this
bastard dentist tomorrow, lad.
So annoying. [snorts]
That is so annoying, bro.
what I have to do. So,
well, I can't do it because I don't I've
already proven that I can't do it.
So, anyone ain't me because I can't do it. Not me.
I've already showed my bad experiences and [ __ ]
and yeah, the messages I put out
messages as well. So yeah.
No, it's never going to change, lad.
Never going to change. Never.
Never in a million years.
But people on Reddit still tell you it
will. No, it won't.
Yeah, I had someone uh blocked me on
Instagram, then they unblocked me, and
then they followed me. And I'm thinking,
"Oh, okay. Maybe they listen to some of
the stuff I said, then they blocked me again." Huh. Impossible.
Not ever changing, lad. >> Yeah.
So, yeah, I'm bas I'm basically screwed user.
Yeah. They're kind They're cheap enough.
Nothing, bro. Just depressed as usual.
Bitter as usual. Nothing new.
I've already been up north millions of times.
Still didn't meet anyone.
You must be new on this channel, lad.
You must be very new.
No, it isn't. I've been up north
millions of times. Same [ __ ]
You must be new to the channel. I've
traveled all over the country.
Multiple multiple times.
Yeah, I've been all over.
Yeah, you must be new to this channel, lad.
I've been Manchester, Liverpool,
Leadeds, Sheffield, Nottingham, Birmingham, Scotland,
Bristol, Cardiff, Brighton, [snorts]
[ __ ] everywhere, bro. Everywhere. Bournemouth.
Yeah, I've been to a lot of places,
multiple times as well. Newcastle, I've
been there as well. Did I mention that? No.
They all stuck up there as well. Yep.
What a life, mate. What a [ __ ]
[ __ ] stinking life. [snorts]
Yeah. Not good, is it?
And I should have to try again. User.
That's how I have it in my head. I
should have to try again.
I've already tried more than anyone in
the world. So, I should have to try again.
Oh, it is bad. It's very bad.
You should be shagged in your prime
years. You shouldn't be single in your
prime years. You should be shagging. And
if you're not shagging, it should be by choice.
It's very, very, very bad. Not
financially, it's not bad. Not like, not
anything else is bad.
It's just you should be getting sex and
women at your age with the amount I've tried.
You, you know, you shouldn't be going without.
And that's and that's that.
That's the way I see. That's what makes
me bitter every day thinking about that.
That is really bad. That is depressing.
I wouldn't care. I don't care about money, bro.
I don't care about money. So,
I mean, I just would I just wouldn't go
out, would I?
I don't give a [ __ ] about money, bro. So,
a lot of people do. I don't care,
you know. I don't starve and that. So, I
do right. So, yeah. You know what I
mean? That's it.
Should have met someone by now, matey.
Should have met someone by now.
And I just think about how I was wronged
every day. Bad experiences. Bad
experiences. Bad experiences. Bad. It
drives me mad, bro. I can just sit
there, keep thinking about it. It drives
me [ __ ] mad. You know
the dickness. The dickness. to dickness.
Do you know what I mean? Yeah.
Oh, I've given up a long time ago, bro.
I've definitely definitely given up.
I've tried more than anyone in the
world. I I I'm I'm
wave my white flag.
I've definitely definitely given up.
I will never be trying again. I haven't
for two months. So, and the last time I
went out is cuz I was forced to go out.
So, more than two months, actually. I'm
definitely giving up.
So, that's that. I should have to keep
trying. [ __ ] that.
So, I've definitely given up, lad.
Yeah, I've given up, bro. 100%.
You should be getting sex at this age,
user. You should be with someone at this age.
It's not normal, lad.
That is depressing, bro. I think about
that every day. That is so depressing. Yeah. So bad, it
know. I gave up a long time ago, bro.
It will never change. It's the same
thing every time you go out. That's why
I gave up. It's the same thing.
It's the same exact thing. So, yeah. Yeah.
[sighs and gasps]
No, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, I give up, bro. 100%. I haven't
had a date since April, by the way,
user. I haven't had a date since April.
Yeah, it's kind of strong.
I went for a meal, bro, cuz I was
getting mood swings and I was getting
pissed off, so I thought, oh, let me
just go out for a meal.
Uh, they've got to pull a tooth out tomorrow.
Yeah. I got to go dentist tomorrow. Back
to dentist tomorrow. Yep.
And I need to get a fill in the next
week and then that's it.
Got two things that need doing.
It's all right though. It No, it's a
back one. It's all the way at the back.
Yeah, just one.
So, I've got to be somewhere tomorrow. I
hate having to be somewhere. I [ __ ]
hate having to be somewhere, bro.
It could be anything. I hate that man
having to be somewhere
cuz you know you can't lie in and it's annoying.
No, it's right at the back.
Had it as well
and then just a pin at the bottom a
little one. That's it. That's all it is week after.
Yeah, let's not let's not talk about
that anyways, bro.
Well, they offered me it in it, so I had it.
But I'm not going out drinking or
nothing like that.
I'm not doing nothing anymore, bro.
Nothing. I shouldn't have even gambled
today. That's really bad.
I shouldn't have gambled today, man. I
should have just gave Laney that 150. >> [gasps]
>> Back to this [ __ ] again. Is it
back to this shitty life again?
What the [ __ ] bro? What the [ __ ]
Bro, what the [ __ ] bro?
Hopefully I don't wake up tomorrow.
That' be lush.
Yeah, you can't get sex. You can't get women either.
Basically, there was no point being born
with a dick if you can't use it.
And that's what I was thinking about
today as well. What's the point of being born?
You might as well been born a [ __ ]
Really, if you think about it, you might
as well been born Timmy Eldridge.
without a dick.
That's the way I see it.
Yeah, that's the way I see it. Me. Don't
know how you see it, but that's the way
I see it. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't know how you see it, but
that's the way I see it.
You know, if you had a sex life, all of
this [ __ ] would go away. You do realize that
if you I think it's this horror film
that triggered me. You know, it's that
horror film that triggered me a couple
of weeks ago. You know, if you had a
normal sex life that you're supposed to
have at 28, this wouldn't be happening.
You do realize that?
So should be having a sex life at 28 and
better experiences at 28 as well.
Yeah. [ __ ] that, bro. >> [snorts]
>> I don't know. It's a sad life.
It's a sad depressing life. E,
you can't get it. No one's interested.
You can't get it. You can't get anyone.
No one's interested.
Is that right, Stephen Howard? Yeah, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. They're not interested Steven Howard
in this country, lad.
Sad, isn't it, bro? Sad life.
Sad, sad, sad life, eh? [gasps]
Yeah, I woke up with like these I woke
up with some mad mood swings, bro.
Really, really dirty mood swings, bro.
It's not even a joke.
I woke up thinking of my bad experiences again.
[sighs and gasps]
like every day.
[sighs and snorts] Yep.
Never changes either. Never changes.
I'm completely [ __ ] now, bro. It will
never get better. My mood swings will
never change. I'll never try again. I'm
[ __ ] bro. I'm actually really [ __ ]
I'm actually really really [ __ ]
Really really really [ __ ] because I
used to be able to I used to be able to
calm down but now it's constant bro.
It's constant and constant and constant
build up of bad experiences. It's
constant, lad. Constant.
It's no good, man. It's no good.
It's really no good.
So, I'm [ __ ] basically. Yeah.
There's more to life than sex. To people
that get sex.
Yeah. To people that get sex. Yeah.
But not to people that don't get sex
that should get sex.
Yeah. There's more to life to sex than
people that get sex. you know. [snorts] Yeah.
That's the way I see it.
Yeah, that's the way I see it.
Who's got clinical depression?
[snorts] No, bro. Cuz last January, last
I think I still went out. I still had
hope. I think I still went out, bro.
Even Even even when I was bad. But now I
don't even go out. So So yeah.
So So now I don't even go out.
No, I would say it's just bitterness. I
would say a lot of it is just
bitterness. cuz I still brush my teeth
and stuff. I still shower and that.
I think it's just bitterness.
I don't know what it is, but
it's never going away. It's never going away. So,
What do you think of this community, Greavvesy?
And I feel sorry for Lady as well cuz
she has to see it every day.
Me being miserable
and having a mood
every day, bro. It can't be nice to see,
you know, every single day, you know.
It can't be nice to see every day, [snorts] you know. So
I feel sorry for lady either way, you know.
That's why I'm coming off this YouTube thing.
I was live for 8 hours yesterday and I
don't even know what the [ __ ] I was
talking about where that time went. Yeah.
It's what it is, isn't it?
I think I was trying to win money for an
escort cuz I weren't going to pay for it
out of my own money.
Greavves. Yeah. I was trying to win
money cuz I didn't want to pay by out by nobody.
But I also got [ __ ] I also got [ __ ]
royally with that. So they saw the white man coming.
Yeah, there was the black guy in the
bookies. Yeah, they saw the white man
coming, lad. They saw the white man coming.
Greasy. They saw the white man coming today.
in the bookies.
You missed the videos where I used to
spit in the spit on the machines.
They saw the [ __ ] white man coming, mate.
They saw the white man coming.
If I was black, they'd probably let me win.
What do you think of spitting on
machines, Grezy? I like spitting on the
cuz if you punch them, you hurt your
hand, you see. So,
nice bit of spit all over the machine.
I've done it quite a few times, you know.
I've done it. Yeah.
Sucks, isn't it?
Anyone would think you're depressed,
Grezy. The way you go on.
You don't leave your house. You don't
leave your house, ma'am.
Yeah, the Indian was really nice.
He got me out of the house.
Grezy. I like sevil cozy.
I spent over200 pound today [ __ ]
giving you content.
I like Chev cold greasy.
Yeah, I weren't going to pay for it out
of my own money.
I didn't need a win. I could pay out my
own money. I've got money.
But I don't want to use an escort. I
should have to use an escort.
I weren't going to [ __ ] I weren't going
to [ __ ] them either. I was only going to
get a [ __ ] but I weren't going to uh
I'm not using an escort anyways. I'm not
using an escort. So, I left you. I don't
look like Timmy Eldridge. I don't look
I'm not a [ __ ] in a wheelchair.
So, yeah, that's the way I see it. I I
haven't not tried. So,
Yeah. No reason for it. So I won't poor [ __ ]
grieves you. I like shovel cole.
I hate this community, mate.
I hate it because it's full of copycats
where they all copy each other,
you know, where they all copy each H. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't know what to do, lad.
What a life, man. What a life.
They saw the white man coming in the B
shop. They saw the white man coming.
What do you think, Grezy? They saw the
white man coming.
Nah, [snorts] I don't watch porn anymore.
Why don't I watch porn?
Grey, was you lying when you actually
said that? Like when you was 12, 13,
people used to talk about Jevil Cole and
they used to look at you weird if you
didn't find her attractive.
That's funny as [ __ ] bro. Really?
Are you actually being serious? Bye, Virgin.
Wait, you was actually being serious, Grezy. >> [snorts] >> Really?
So why why was they doing that then
Greavvesy? Why was they talking about her?
Why were they doing that then?
That's weird, bro. That's seriously
weird. I don't know why people do that.
I got a donut, by the way, Greavves,
from Crispy Creams.
Going to have that in a minute.
What time do you wake up, Grezy?
So I'm leaving. Monty's left. Sees
Mark's left. Squeezy.
So you're [ __ ] now, is it?
I'm leaving. Monty's left. Mark's left.
You're [ __ ] now, aren't you?
I hated these standards. I hate the accent.
Yeah, I hate the accent.
I hate that cockney accent, bro.
What do you think, Dusty? You hate it.
Yeah, I hate that accent.
I hate Greavves's accent. His little
northern accent. Bless him.
I watch David Dickinson. Dusty, have you
ever watched David Dickinson?
Dickinson's real deal.
I sometimes watch that with Laney. Yeah,
please edit a video. I could have walked
a 90 up.
No, I couldn't.
Yeah, David Dickinson.
You know David Dickinson's a cockney.
He's from Stockport.
Yeah, he's a cockney. He is [snorts]
Yeah, he's cocky.
Why are you laughing, Grezy? It's not funny.
The worst accent is the [ __ ] is
Dudley. That's the worst accent. Dudley
[ __ ] war. That's the worst accent,
man. That black country accent is [ __ ] vile.
And Scouse, they're the two worst. [snorts]
Yeah, they're the worst. I think they
are actually the worst. Huh? Yeah.
Better than being on YouTube for one like you.
Better than being alone on YouTube like
you with no dinner. Eh,
I'll take it, lad.
Yeah, I lost 150.
I lost one.
I always feel guilty, you know, when I
gamble. I don't know why. Long story.
Long story, lad.
I actually went to the house today.
I actually went back to the house today.
I shouldn't even be on this YouTube, you know, bro.
But who else would I have to moan and complain to?
But I am leaving though. I do actually
have to leave cuz a lady. So I will have
to actually leave. Sorry, Greasy.
I'm going to have to, bro. Really? At
least for a long time.
Sadly, cuz lady doesn't want me on here, son. Yeah.
Dusty, I don't like Sher Cole.
[snorts] She's ugly. No, never.
Yeah, I'm gay, bro. Definitely. Yeah, I
like walk out.
I actually walk out.
Mad, isn't it?
So many women vaping today around
Liverpool Street. So westernized. Yuck. [ __ ] yuck.
sounds something that I'd like to watch. We >> [snorts]
>> But women aren't innocent.
Women aren't innocent.
Ruby, you said people dismiss my
struggles because you said people
dismiss my struggles because it's about
women, isn't it?
You say that if it's a woman doing
wrong, they dismiss it in it.
You say they they dismiss it in it.
I'm so tired, bro. That food knocked me out, lad.
That food knocked me out.
Just really knocked me out. That food. No heat.
I'm so tired, man.
Whenever you eat the food in a
restaurant, greasy, it seems to knock
you out. It seems to hit different when
you eat in. It seems to fill you up for
longer and make you sleepy. I can't
explain it. Like, it's I don't know.
It's hard to explain it.
Maybe because the sauces are thicker and
the texture of the curry is thicker. and
not as watery when you take it out. I
don't know. It's weird.
It is really weird, bro.
Reddit still says that I'm going to meet
someone, Greavvesy. They said, "You
don't know what's around the corner."
I know what's around the corner because
it's been happening for years. They keep
giving me false hope. We see
No, you will never meet anyone. Never.
I like negative people.
I know. Don't remind me, bro. is
depressing. I hate have to be up for things, man.
I know. I know.
You never know. But I know.
Yeah, I know. Don't remind me. I got to
be up for that tomorrow. Oh, it's annoying, bro.
So [ __ ] annoying. That is
to be somewhere.
No, it's fine, bro. Go. I'm not scared
of the dentist, bro. I just don't like
having to be up for stuff.
No, I'm not rearranging it, bro. I'm going.
I'm going to go.
It's just annoying.
I to be up for stuff.
I don't need him to hold my hand, mate.
I'm not scared of the dentist.
He doesn't need to hold my hand. I don't
need anyone to hold my hand.
If I don't turn up, yeah, they'll ban me.
cuz it'll be the second time. Yeah.
I'm not scared, bro. I just don't like
being I don't I just don't like go being
having to be somewhere.
I'm not scared, bro.
It's just annoying. It's just effort, you know.
You need to hold my hand, mate.
The anxiety doesn't get to me. I went to
the dentist today.
I'm not I haven't got anxiety.
I don't have anxiety, bro. I went to the dentist today.
I'm not scared of the dentist, lad.
Anyways, moving on. Oh, yeah.
No, [snorts] he's black.
No, he's black.
No, it's not a wisdom tooth. Yeah,
I'm not scared of the dentist, lad. I've
always been to the dentist by myself as well.
I just want to lie in bed and be depressed
all day every day.
Nothing to go to the dentist is a nuisance.
It's like anything that used to happen
like police stuff I don't like happen to be somewhere.
The court thing I just don't like happen
to be somewhere. You know
it's hard to explain it. Cuz I have to be somewhere.
I like sh.
Yeah, that's not going to happen, lad.
It's not going to happen because I like sh cow. Dusty.
I like cow. [snorts] No.
And I just need a fill in on my bottom tooth
the next week after and then that's done.
So it's only two things. Uh Greavesy, Yeah.
No. Never fill me in. Someone like that
could never fill me in. [snorts]
No. Guy's a [ __ ] Yeah.
You can stay in these little nestles to
my lucky [ __ ]
Yeah, in a bit, bro. The food knocked me out.
The food was £40. That weren't that bad
to be fair.
Considering the area it was in and I got
a free shot and that, I didn't think it
was that bad to be fair. So, yeah.
No, it's not a big day tomorrow.
It's not a big day at all. Matey,
the anxiety [snorts]
doesn't get to me, Greg. I'm not scared
of the dentist, lad. It's just an inconvenience.
Yeah, it's just an inconvenience, mate. That's all.
And I hate being around people,
women, and stuff because of my bad experiences. So
it's just I just hate it. So yeah,
you're what? Scared of the dentist?
I'm not scared. I'm not scared of the dentist, bro.
Are you scared?
A lot of people I think half people are
scared to be honest. I looked it up. It
says four out of 10 people are scared.
So yeah, that's almost half. That's
basically half people or they've got
anxiety about it.
I like the dentist. I don't mind the
I've gone whenever I've needed to.
I don't mind them, bro.
Laney doesn't like them.
Laney hates them. She would never go.
Yeah, it's my back tooth. It's a back tooth, bro.
It's only a back to it. So,
it's only a bat tooth, bro. Yeah.
I'm not scared of the dentist.
We I'm really I'm just depressed. I
don't want to get out of bed, you know?
Well, have you had a tooth out, we
have you had a have you had a group have
you had a tooth Oh, really?
So, it's not uncommon to have a tooth took out.
It only happens as you really get older,
you know, tooth problems. It only
happened to me the past year and that
I never had any in the old house. I
never had any um tooth problems in the
old house. It's as you get older, is it
What would have happened if I done some
cold approaches today? Greasy,
what would have happened?
Would have I met anyone? You reckon?
Yeah, but Reddit Yeah, but Reddit says
that I will meet someone. Ko.
Yeah, but people on Reddit say that I
will meet someone.
They say you don't know what the future holds.
That's what they say on Reddit.
Oh, that woman in Scotland blocked me by the way.
I told her my experiences and [ __ ]
and she blocked me.
But she used the word mate.
Women that use the word mate, I I I'm
done with them. That's so cringe. Women
using the word mate is so cringe. It's
so so cringe.
They are all the same. These women isn't
it? Truly are all the same. Evil.
Yeah. I told her my experiences and then
she blocked me. Greezy.
Yeah. had a wisdom tooth problem when I
was like 19, 20. Yeah, you get an
infection. A wisdom tooth infection. I
think everyone gets that in it, Greasy.
And they give you antibiotics.
Yeah, I think everyone gets that though.
Wisdom tooth infection.
Yeah, I think everyone gets that. 19 20
then you take antibiotics. Remember
Greavves, don't let them [ __ ] women win.
We can't let these [ __ ] women win, Grezy.
Like that count said, is it? No, we
can't let them [ __ ] women win, Grezy.
They need to pay
for what they've done. You know,
that was weird of that Scottish woman blocking me.
I will never move on, mate. I will never move on. Never.
For all the bad experiences they've gave
me over the years. No way.
I'm never moving on. [snorts] Never.
Never, bro. Never.
My sister also told me to not go on YouTube. Yeah. Uh,
I spoke to some woman from Scotland
today. Greavves in the All Saint shop. I
just said, "Oh, where Scotland are you
from?" I still hate women and that. I
never tried hitting on her cuz women are
evil, but you know, just uh wanted to
know about like the It reminded me of
you a little bit.
There's a lot of Scottish people around
Liverpool Street for some reason.
They're an African. No.
When you've had bad experiences like me,
you become bitter, don't you, Greasy?
You become bitter at the world.
You start hating people and hating
people around you. Well, at least me anyways.
Dusty. That's how I get.
I like Liverpool Street.
I like I like the Indian food. I like
the Indian places.
Yeah, I do. [snorts]
I'm going to have a donut in a minute
with a Coke. I have cut down on the coke, but
I just had a bad day today.
I just love people that think the whole
world is against them. Like, oh, man.
He still posts videos, Oreo, man.
He still posts videos, Oreo, man. You know that?
Yeah, he still posts um every day.
He's got some videos.
No, I I said to the dentist, I'll cut
down. He just says cut down for now and
just try to give up it up.
Yeah, this guy's been posting videos
since 26, Grezy, and he's 36 now, 37.
And he still does videos talking about
women and stuff and loads of things. Yeah. [snorts]
That's mad. He's actually 37.
Peter Belly can't get attached anymore
because he's already found his mama.
Because he's already found his mama. Remember Greavvesy.
Did I bring that one on myself? Greasy.
Be honest. Did I bring that one on myself?
Was that the same person that that
called you a po [ __ ] Grezy, that said that?
Do you reckon that was the same person?
I think so.
I don't know who it is. I don't know who
it is, but
they come here and they mock me.
[ __ ] She blocked me and the other one
unblocked me and then blocked. She
unblocked me and then followed me and
then blocked me again.
Probably shot. So I wasn't fully white.
So yeah, nothing nothing good's
happening. Same old England.
Same old depressing [ __ ] Never change. [snorts]
I did it really, really bad. Yeah.
It's so bad in it, bro.
It's bad gra.
I'm [ __ ] tired as [ __ ] I am, lad.
You like Joseph Fery? Okay.
Do I judge it for all?
Yeah, it was.
They're [ __ ] That's what they're like,
I wonder [snorts] if they've got
dentists in Reen.
You reckon they've got dentists in Reen or no?
What about Southampton?
Do you reckon they've got dentists there or no?
I wonder if they've got dentists in Southampton.
What do you reckon? [snorts]
I don't even know if I can be bothered
to go get this donut, mate. I'm [ __ ] knackered.
I can't move out of bed, Grezy. [snorts]
That Indian knocked me for six, lad.
Knocked me for six, mate.
I can't believe you got you can't get
sex or relationship in your own country.
Sad times, isn't it? Sad times. Greasy. Yeah,
but it'll get better. They say
you'll meet someone. They say, "Yeah,
I don't think I'll ever have sex again,
to be honest."
Well, I know because it's been this way
for years, so
I mean, I know.
I 100% know.
I know for [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah,
if I close my eyes, Greavves, I'll fall to sleep.
Nah, not with women. It never changes
with women. Things might change. Things
might change, but women won't change.
And your m mortal stat your marital
status will never change either.
Things might. Women won't. Dating won't sadly.
[snorts] But things might. Yeah. Just
not dating on women. Sadly. [snorts] Sadly not.
No. Things will never change.
What do you think, Steven Hour? Do you
think things will change?
Very unlikely. Very, very, very
I can't see it personally,
Look at that finish Izzy. She was a [ __ ] as well.
Yeah, she was a [ __ ] too. They're all
[ __ ] what they do.
I remember I spent a lot of money that
Sunday as well.
No, it will never change. But it will
Yeah, I remember that. I do remember that. Yeah, just [ __ ]
She was a [ __ ] as well. Yep.
You reckon I'll get a date this year? Steven Howard
nothing about sick. I haven't spoke to
her for years.
I haven't spoken to Sig for years.
Graves. I like several cars.
I like Cheryl Cole Gy.
What's your opinion on me like in shovel car?
Why are you meowing?
Why was you talking about Sig bend over
Stig's old is
seems old news, bro.
>> She said she wanted a serious
relationship. sink. So if she wants a
serious relationship, why is she [ __ ] people?
You're not Why is she [ __ ] Why does she
[ __ ] me if she wants a serious
relationship? That don't make sense.
People that are looking for
relationships don't do that, you know? She's strange. Very strange. No,
she doesn't even live near me, bro.
Why is it better than USA? Is he?
Why is that?
No, I don't talk to Sig.
Do you remember Greavves? You sing was
never your mama. That's what that
account says to me. It comes on and
[ __ ] with me in it.
Signal Peter Belly's mommy. Mama.
She'll be waiting longer than the guy in the shop. Yeah,
no more no more content for Greasy and Pucker.
What a [ __ ] I'm tired.
I'm so tired, bro.
Not for long.
Wait until I find out who he is. Dusty,
he will be getting messaged.
He will be getting messaged.
Oh, he'll be getting messaged, lad.
You'll be getting messaged. Yeah.
You remember the dad?
Oh, I need to go to bed in a minute. I'm
tired. I won't be back for a long time, sir. [gasps]
For the sake of Laney. For the sake of
Yeah, they in shape.
Yeah. Wait until I find out who he is. Dusty.
I'm protecting people from narcissists, you know,
protecting people from narcissistic people.
Is that right, Steven Howard?
Bro, I'm not coming live tomorrow
cuz a lady,
she's sick of saying stop going stop
being on YouTube and that and that's not fairy.
Yeah. If I if if you found out who her
boyfriend one was, would you message
him? Greavesy, I would message him. Yeah,
I would. Yeah, if I if I found if I
stumbled across him, I would message him. Yeah.
Would you message USAD's boyfriend
if you knew who he was?
No, he won't be. I brushing my I brush my teeth.
Yeah, that's what I would do.
Yeah, I would message him as I message him.
has a right to know it. Yeah. Yeah.
People like that should never be with
anyone in it, Grezy. They deserve to die
alone and be alone.
People like that.
No, I would never. I won't leave them
be. If I find if I stumble across him,
I would I would message him. I would
If I stumbled across him, I would
message him, bro.
You want to be, you know? No way.
Did you like the content today, Grezy?
Did you like the content?
Hope you liked it. It cost me a lot of money today.
Yeah. You don't really like gambling, do you? So, uh,
Big day. I'm not nervous, bro. I'm not
scared of the dentist. You're saying it
to the wrong person.
I'm not scared, bro.
I just don't like being up for stuff. I
just like staying in bed.
I'm not scared, lad.
Saying it to the wrong person.
Yeah, I need to go sleep in a minute, man.
I want to be on Reddit all night. Grievy
complaining, but I can't.
I want to be on Reddit complaining. Yeah,
I message random women on Reddit.
Like random women on Reddit. I find I
messaged them to tell them about the experiences.
I've even asked some women to get a sex change.
I said, "Could you get a sex change
so you're not a woman anymore? So you're not evil."
That's what I've said to some people before.
When they used to message me about the
house, I said when I was subleting the
house, I said it's double for women cuz
women are smelly. And I actually did say
that as well. I said it's double.
It's double the price for women.
So if the room is 400, it will be 800.
uh double prices unfortunately
for women that give people bad experiences. Oh gosh,
I'm under my little blankie. Yeah. Oh.
You like Laney Grezy? Laney and uh
Lane and King Maybe.
is a little copycat.