seem to be missing a piece here.
Do this Lego.
We seem to be missing a piece to this Lego.
No, it's definitely missing, is it?
Oh, I'm [ __ ] blind.
But no, it's missing. This is definitely
missing. I am missing a piece to this [ __ ]
to this [ __ ] Lego, man.
Yeah, I'm missing a piece of I'm I'm
missing it, bro. Definitely missing a piece
cuz I have not lost any pieces, bro.
Trust me. Cuz I kept it all. I'm
definitely missing a piece. It's a black
I'll show you where I'm at with this.
See, I'm here and then I'm doing this
other wing. Yeah. Look. And then we need
this piece here. And it's missing. It's
black and it's missing.
No, that is definitely definitely missing.
I'm sure it is. Let me look over it one
more time again.
It's for 8 years plus. It's not for 8y
olds. Oh, I just had to block that b
man. He started trying to like uh
he's he started he started trying to
project his [ __ ] onto me again on my
community post, bro.
He's another self projector. I thought I
had him blocked, bro. But no,
it could be No, this is the same one,
bro. No, it's the same one. No, he's a self projector,
bro. I had to block that self projector.
Calling me Py. Have you seen yourself
self projection with these people, bro?
Come on, man. It's 2026. Give it a
break. It's boring now.
No, bro. I don't chase women.
Nah, [ __ ] that. That's a mug's game. I'd
rather that that just tells you how it is, lad.
Yeah. And you're in your And you're in
your 40s on YouTube watching me. So,
what does that make you, bro?
I'll never be as fat as you people, bro.
I'll never be as fat as you people.
When I'm as fat as you people, I'll
start worrying. No, no, no. Fat as you
people, bro. When I'm 1% like you, self
projectors, I'll start worrying, bro.
I'll seriously, seriously start
worrying, bro. You're in your 40s and
you're watching me on YouTube on a
Saturday night. So, what does that say
about you people, bro?
That's even worse than if you're
watching me, isn't it?
No, there's a piece that is definitely
definitely missing on this thing and I
don't lose anything. So, yeah,
yeah. Bye-bye. Self projector.
See you later. Bye.
So many self projectors on this
community. E. Ah, here we go. Got it.
That's how [ __ ] tiny the [ __ ] things are.
It's hard to see the black ones cuz
Yeah, it's hard to see the black ones,
bro. There we go. Got it.
It's where it's black, it's harder to
see them. Not to be racist, but it's
harder to see than um
Okay, here we go.
That bit was hard to see, bro. For some
reason, I actually thought I lost one. I
start getting worse.
Okay, just just shut up a minute. Yeah,
cuz I need concentration when I'm doing this.
I really want to complete this by
tonight or at least 90% of it.
Okay, so we need two of them. That's
easy. It's just the same thing on a different wing.
I'm not [ __ ] going out drinking in
January, bro. That's dead.
That is dead, bro. [ __ ] that.
What's Where's that piece now? Here we go.
It's hard to see the black ones, bro.
So, what you're saying is one gets left there.
No, one second.
No, we're skipping it again. Okay, we're
going to ahead again. That's what
happens when you're trying to rush
That's what happens when you're trying
to rush the [ __ ] [ __ ] Okay. Um,
that's why you don't try and rush the [ __ ] thing.
Where does that one go?
I'm trying to see where it goes.
Okay, it goes there. See, the lighter it
is, the easier it is to see. The black
ones are [ __ ] hard.
Anyways, why you people are out drinking today?
You say you got a life, you got all this
money and [ __ ] Why you not out drinking
today? You ask you the same thing.
I can get into this whole rant about V,
but these people are not even worth
talking about, bro.
They're not even like worth even
mentioning. They're just absolute
wasters. They're not even They're not
even worth it, bro.
Just self projectors.
So, they're not worth entertaining. Self projectors. Yeah.
I think it's sad they're still doing it
in 2026 though.
I do think that is sad to be fair. Well, it Okay,
there we go. That's on. Okay.
The black ones are so hard to see, man.
This one you find them in seconds. [ __ ] thing is No more. Oh no.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Getting there, bro.
I'm getting there.
That's nice. Spray. Spray in the room.
You can smell that, bro. L.
Yeah, when I was a kid. I can't remember it though.
Which one is this piece?
Oh [ __ ] man.
Where's this one?
Yeah, I'd much rather doing this than
[ __ ] drinking, dealing with stuck up
women on a gen in a genu, bro. [ __ ] hell
yeah, bro. I'd rather be doing this any
day of the week. Oh, here we go. I found it. Yeah,
we're almost at the end of this wing now.
That's two wings done. It's just the
same repetitive [ __ ] just a different wing.
I should be able to get this done quick though.
Oh my god. Why has that come off? See?
Oh, it's gone back in to be fair. No,
no, no, no, no. One sec. No.
One sec. Hold on. [ __ ] stupid.
One dot in the middle. One sec.
He's a sad bastard. He's a grass as well. A sad
a sad bastard and a grass.
One second please. Man, I'm trying to do something now.
your concentration on doing this. No,
because he's called the police on me, bro.
That's how he's a grass. Because he's
called the police on me. Yeah.
Yeah. Who started that Porky thing, bro?
This is not real life. So you got people
that are fatter than you calling you
Porky. How does that make sense?
People that are literally fatter than I
will ever be. Not only just am, but will
ever be is calling me is calling me
Porky. People that are fatter than me
and uglier than me. I don't think so,
bro. That's why these people are just
literally something to laugh at, bro.
Cuz they all get found out in the end anyways.
I'm sure this is right, bro. But
who [ __ ] knows, mate?
I'm sure it is.
Porky B, you need to stop projecting,
bro. You're obese.
You're the obese one, bro. Not me.
Nothing porky about me. Nothing poverty
about me. You're just talking about
yourself. See you later. Anyways, lad. Um, yeah.
You just get you got yourself banned for that, lad.
You're talking about yourself again,
bro. Mike, this is 2026,
bro. I was in your country and you had
nothing to say and this is 2026. So,
time to grow up, mate.
You're talking about yourself, lad. And
I was in your country and you didn't say
nothing when I was in your country. So,
behave, man. Actual age, not your shoe size. Um,
think this is right. I'm sure this is.
We can't do it with you lot. Um, okay.
Yeah, this has got to be right. Yeah,
it's got to be right.
Yeah, it is. I want a bit more.
Yeah, I've had more women than you'll
ever have, bro. And you're not in a
relationship. You're not in a
relationship. Stop projecting, lad.
Nothing you self-reflectctors say bother
me. So, you're wasting your time, mate.
You might as well go on someone else's channel.
Cuz everything you say is about
yourselves. We all know what you people
look like. We all know the people that
show their face. So, like I said, you're
you're something to laugh at, lad.
We know that you're wasters. We know
that people like you, Michael, on
YouTube 24/7. We know that I've come to
your country and you've done nothing
about it. You're embarrassing yourself.
You literally are embarrassing yourself.
You're You still You're still projecting in 2026.
What does that say about you, mate? A
lot more than it says about me.
You've been doing this for about 5
years, by the way. Huh? You've been
doing this for about five [ __ ] years. top five.
You know, you've been doing this for five years.
Yeah. That's funny though cuz you call
other you call other people disabled but
you've been doing this for 5 years.
Does the truth hurt? Yeah, the truth
hurts a lot.
Why don't you come in, bro? Come in the
hangouts. I'll put link out for you,
man. You should show your face. Show
everyone what you look like.
Oh [ __ ] There we go.
You should do that, man. Show everyone
what you look like, man. Show everybody what this
one second. Why is that not going in?
Oh, bro. They're all obsessed with me,
bro. He's not the only one. They've been
doing it for years. That's why I just
laugh at them. This [ __ ] is wrong, bro.
Yeah, they've been doing it for years, bro.
They've been doing it for years, man.
Obviously, I'm younger than them. I'm
better looking than them. I expect it, bro.
Okay, that's why. shut up.
I'm trying to put this I'm doing this
[ __ ] wrong now. You dirty bastards.
Yeah, they they're all disabled here,
bro. Their life's rejects. That's why I
laugh at them, bro. They don't bother
me. They think they bother me, but
seriously, they don't, bro. They just
embarrassing them. They just embarrass themselves.
The thing is with these people, Ding,
you need to look at these people and
what they look like. the ones that get
exposed and the ones that are showing
themselves now. That's why they don't
affect me, bro. Because they all they
all just self they all just
self-reflect, bro. So, I don't really care, man.
Okay, now we need to do this last bit.
And I've actually built the I've
actually built the wings now.
Yeah. Sorry, YouTube, bro. Like I' like
like I'll say to you one more time, this is 2026.
Uh yeah, this is 2026 now and it's
boring. So come up with something new.
I know it's because they ain't got a
life dig own bro. They've not got a
life, bro. They're just sad little
rejects of society that's got nothing.
They got no They got I'm not even going
to say they've got no friends because to
me that's not an insult. They've got no
money. They've got no life. They've got
no family. They just sit on here all day
doing this. They've been doing it for years, bro.
Oh, [ __ ] man.
Oh, one second.
I've just I've just done this wrong somewhere.
No, I haven't.
No, that's supposed to go there, isn't it?
Yeah, I have done it wrong somewhere, bro.
I'm sure I have.
No, I haven't. The only thing I haven't
put is just here.
You know what? And you know what they're
trying to say now, D? They're trying to
The projection is so unreal with these
people, bro. Now they're trying to call
me Porky when I'm literally
not even fat. They're They're the fat
ones. Like, what the actual [ __ ] bro?
They ain't got no life. They've
literally got nothing, bro. They're just wasters.
Like I told you, bro, I don't give a
[ __ ] about them.
I must have forgot to put that that long
thing on there.
I must have done. There's no long thing
on there, is there?
Let me go back to the very
Yeah, I literally missed a part here. I
didn't even realize it, bro. So, you
need full concentration when you're
doing this [ __ ]
I only missed one bit. Uh, no.
Yeah, it's cuz they're jealous, bro.
Thing Joseph Ferrar does the same thing.
LT's know better. He's biased.
LT is another biased one. I'm sure you've s
I'm sure you've seen the video. They
ain't got a life, bro. They got nothing
but self projecting.
Yeah, that's it, bro. You got to
understand, bro. These people are uh
Bro, they're rejects to society, bro.
I can't even believe. I didn't even
realize I missed that part, bro.
It's just a streak. I didn't put the
streak on the on the on on the thing.
It's because they're rejects to society, bro.
I lady was like, "Oh no, it's going to
be the same people. It's going to be the
same people." And I was like, "Nah,
2026. It's going to be different." But no.
So sad bastards, bro.
Who knows? Eh,
where's this [ __ ] thing as well?
Oh, that's where it is. It's [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] stuck together. This was
the [ __ ] that's stuck together. Yeah.
This was the [ __ ] that stuck together.
Yeah. That's It's stuck on top of each other, bro.
Porky Pete and Poverty Pete. Oh, that's
hilarious, bro. I love that because
you're just talking about yourself, but
I love I love the rhythm, bro. I love the rhythm.
That's funny as [ __ ] bro.
I'm living under poverty, yet these are
the people that sit on YouTube 24/7 with
no social life. They don't even leave their house.
Oh my god. This is bad, bro. This Lego
Yeah, cuz it only got be open. Yeah, this [ __ ]
Right, I'm going to try get they need to
do this. One sec.
There we go.
To split a part up, bro. I had to split
apart up. I don't need to show you anything.
That's self projecting. You asking me to
show money? Why don't you show us 100 quid?
Here we go. Oh, lovely. I can't believe
I missed that part. Why don't you show
us 100 quid, lad?
We love to see 100 quid from you. [ __ ]
Yeah. Why don't you show us 100 quid?
Yeah. Why don't you show us underground? Huh?
And why you calling me a M when I'm
better looking than you, lad?
What's going on?
This is weird, bro.
Ah, there we go. That's the [ __ ]
There we go.
Yay. I built the wings. Big up Peter belly.
I'm getting this done tonight, mate. Look. Ooh,
making progress here. I told you I'm
doing this today, mate. Now, this is
where it's going to get hard.
What the [ __ ] are them things?
So we need
what is it? What is that?
Oh, it's them [ __ ] Okay. So, okay.
At least we made a [ __ ] wing. So,
we're getting there. It
Yeah. Why do you want people to show you
100 pound, bro? Why don't you show us
100 pound, lad?
Oh, it's just [ __ ] It's just [ __ ] there. One second.
Yeah. So, it's the backup. Okay. Okay. Right.
Okay. So So
you need two
Oh, that's easy. Oh, it's just two of
them [ __ ] ones, isn't it?
Yeah. So, it's okay. So,
This better not split, bro. I will go
[ __ ] mad if it does. No. Wrong piece. Let's go. No,
it's got to be a similar piece, but just
not that [ __ ]
I guess I know. Um,
I will find it.
I will find the [ __ ] thing.
Okay, I think it's this one.
So it's saying what's up
Yeah, man. So,
two of them.
Two of them. They go there.
I got a little ship now.
Still building, building, building. Bro,
with this you want to make sure the leg
goes on properly cuz if any splits [ __ ] it up
getting a bit hungry, you know, what I ate earlier. Okay.
So, we need four of them. Yeah, this
bit's easy, bro.
These bits are easy.
Well, probably all easy to [ __ ] most
people to [ __ ] be fair.
It needs to be on the right bit.
What's up going, bro?
What is that up? That is upwards, isn't it?
Why it going? That's weird.
That should be going in. Man,
you can't. Can you Can you twist them
and turn them?
Is that It's not going in. And it should be.
There we go. What the [ __ ] bro? Okay.
Oh, now we're getting on to the little uh
do other bits. Okay, I'm gone anyways.
I'm going to finish this Lego set and
hopefully I'll be it'll be finished by
the morning. So, yeah. See you.