One second. [sighs] [gasps]
I don't want to start emailing back and
forth, right? Let me Yeah. Yep. >> [snorts] [clears throat]
>> One second. Yeah, bro.
Yeah. Oh, I've seen it again. I'm being
I'm [ __ ] I'm [ __ ] being called a
virgin again, bro. Where the [ __ ] is LT,
bro, when I'm being called a virgin?
That's not fair. I feel very very hard
done by it.
I've just had to send him another email.
You're fast enough to suck up his dick,
you little gay boy, when I'm calling him
a virgin. So why why you not talk about this 19year-old?
Why are you not talking about this
19year-old? Why you not talking about
Sig, bro? You're fast enough to white
night and suck up his dick every time I
call him a virgin. Start crying, having
a panic attack. Oh, don't say that about
him. He's got a girlfriend. [ __ ]
funny. I called him a funny in the email
as well. your you biased little fatty.
Trust me, bro. I'm going to get on this
guy's nerves today, bro. Cuz do you know
why, bro? Cuz I'm not scared of him,
bro. That's the thing with me, bro. I'm
not scared of him.
One second, bro. Yeah,
I called him a biased little fanny. I
called him bias and I called him a
biased little funny. He's so biased,
bro. You know, everyone Yeah. that don't
believe that this guy has gone to these
places. I don't believe it now, bro. I I
think it's a re I I think it's a
pre-recorded video. I literally think
it's a pre-recorded video, bro. I agree
with all of these people now. You know,
Shagger, all of them people. That's what
I'm going to start doing. I actually
believe it, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I
actually believe all the times. Yeah.
That he was supposed to go places. He
hasn't been anywhere now, bro. I I don't believe him.
No, no, I don't believe him, bro. Yeah,
I don't believe him.
Yeah, I don't believe in me, bro.
No, I don't believe him, lad. Does any
of you believe him? Yeah, man.
He's not fast enough, bro. And it's not
his boyfriend being mentioned.
Wow, this Jamie Thompson is so jealous
of me. I still keep hearing about this
fat waster. I still keep hearing about Peter Griffin.
We're still hearing about these fat ugly
people in 2026. [ __ ] hell, bro. These
wasters. We're still hearing about these
nobodyies with no life in 2026. I just
emailed him. Bro,
tell me what I'm saying is wrong, bro.
It's not even wrong what I'm saying, is it?
Why is this guy not on his channel, bro?
He's fast enough to keep cutting me off.
And and I'll say to him on the phone as well.
You're fast enough to cut me off every
[snorts] time I defend myself. Oh, he's
got a girlfriend. Don't say that about
him, bro. like proper sucking his dick
up and that
cuz he's probably a virgin like him,
bro. That's probably why.
It's probably because he's just a virgin
like him. Anyway, sorry about that, bro.
Sorry about that. Yeah,
by the way, this LTF, he's another Jo, bro.
He's another Jo, bro. That's what he is.
He's another Jo.
He's another Jo, bro. Don't let him tell
you any different. He's another Jo. Trust me.
He started saying we again. He's the
same as them. I knew it, bro. Anyone
that starts sucking up this guy's dick
like he does, you know they're all the
same, bro. You know they're all the
same, bro. You literally know they're
all the same. Anyone that starts doing
that, bro. Yeah, you know that they're
they're all the same. Soon as they start
defending their boyfriend, you you know
straight away. And this LT is no
different because he's probably a virgin
like him. That's probably why he takes
offense to it, bro. You know what I mean?
[ __ ] cut me off enough times, you
[ __ ] [ __ ] You know what I'm saying,
bro? When your boyfriend's mentioned,
who the [ __ ] yeah? White Knight's
another [ __ ] man, bro. Like it's bad
enough. Yeah, it's bad enough white
kning a woman. Yeah. Like that is
embarrassing. But imagine white
knighting a man, bro.
Imagine that, bro. Like you're white
knighting a man, bro. Imagine that.
White kning a man. I I emailed him again, bro.
I emailed him another two times. He's
embarrassing, bro. He's another Joe F.
He's another Ly.
He belongs on this community, bro. He's
not someone that's just stumbled across
these people, bro. He proper belongs in
this community, bro.
Yeah, man. I said your boyfriend's um
Well, I think I said your boyfriend's
calling me virgin. Do you not want to do
you want Do you not want to say anything
about that? Do you not want to talk
about Sig? Do you not want to talk about the 19year-old?
Nah, bro. Just some crisps. I just said
to him, "Oh, do you not want to talk
about that?" No.
I imagine if I said, "Do you not want to
talk about it, bro? I can link to it if
you want." "Since you got so much to say
about your boyfriend."
Since you got so much to say about your
boyfriend. Uh LT, bro, I just emailed
him. I said, "Uh, your boy is calling me
um a virgin again. Do you not want to
talk about the 19year-old? Do you not
want to talk about the [ __ ] video? Do
you not want to talk about all the women
I kissed? Do you not want to talk about
the women that admitted to sleeping with
me? Cuz you're fast enough to do it for
your boyfriend. I'm starting to get left
out now, bro. You're fast enough to be
sussy about your boyfriend. Oh, he's got
a girlfriend, bro. Don't say that about
him. And bro, I'm I'm literally like, do
you not have anything to say? You
[ __ ] little white knight. You white
knighting your boyfriend. Oh, boyfriend.
He's got a boyfriend and he bro. Yeah.
I said, "Do you not do you not have
anything to say?" Why? Because I'm not
your boyfriend like a certain person.
You [ __ ] biased [ __ ] I called him a
biased [ __ ] again.
I called him a biased [ __ ] again, bro.
Stop sucking up your boyfriend's dick
every time I'm saying something about
him. Yeah. Don't even try to cut me off
again. Cuz I tell you what what will
happen, bro. If this [ __ ] tries to cut
me off again, I'm just going to keep
talking over him and over and over him
and over and over him. That's what I'm
going to do, bro. Yeah, that's what will
happen, bro. If he tries to cut me off
again, don't cut me off when I'm talking
about your boyfriend, cuz next time
you're going to get emailed. I don't
care about some fat, ugly girlfriend. I
don't care. So, don't ever bring it up
to me ever again. Yeah, you've got
nothing to say with this clown, you biased [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm going to go along with these
people now, bro. I'm going to go along
with these people now, Dusty. All of
these people that say that he hasn't
gone to this place, he hasn't gone to
that place, he hasn't gone to this
place, he hasn't gone to that place. I'm
going to agree with them now, bro.
That's what I'm going to do. I'm going
to agree with them.
No, it's just LT's biasness, bro. It's
just his biasness again. I just emailed
him. I said, "Bro, your boyfriend is
calling to me a virgin again. And do you
not want to talk about the 19-year-old?
Do you not want to talk about the
[ __ ] Do you not want to talk about
Sig? Do you not want to do you want to
start Do you not want to start talking
about these women I've been with? Cuz
you're fast enough to when it's your
boyfriend. Don't say that about him.
He's got a girlfriend. You're fast
enough to suck his dick. So, I just
wanted to know, did you not want to say
anything about that? Cuz you're very
touchy about your boyfriend. And then
you started saying the word we again.
You're no different than these people.
Don't act like you're different than
these people in this community because
you're not. And every single person that
has acted biased toward you. You deserve
it. You deserve it, bro. All the people
that said that they don't they didn't
believe you went there. They don't they
didn't believe you went there. Good. I'm glad. Good.
Good. Just like you then. All of these
people that don't believe you. Good. Do
you know what? I used to feel sorry for
this guy, bro. I used to feel sorry for
this guy, bro. I generally used to feel
sorry for him because I could I could
relate to the biasness in it. But no,
no, [ __ ] it, bro. If he wants to stop
being biased, yeah, [ __ ] him. [ __ ] him,
bro. [ __ ] him in it. [ __ ] Let these
people say what they want to say now. Is it
[ __ ] idiot? Who white knights over a
man? Who the [ __ ] white knights over
some [ __ ] man they don't know, bro?
Who white knights over some man that
they don't know? Tell me that. [clears throat]
Yeah, [snorts] man. Who the [ __ ] Who the
[ __ ] white knights over a man that they
don't know, bro?
[ __ ] pathetic, bro. Pathetic.
[clears throat] Yeah.
I'm I'm I'm I'm in my right to say what
I'm saying, bro. How many times have you
cut me off, bro? three or four times.
You have cut me off three or four times.
No, you've cut me off about three or
four times every time I've used this word. Yeah.
So, why why is someone else allowed to
do it? But I can't.
Come on, explain yourself, bro. I put
the link up. No, no. I put the link up,
bro. I'm not even trying to rage anyone.
I I want I want I want to explain him.
Yeah, the link's up, bro. He can join if
he wants to join. I don't give a [ __ ] bro. Simple. Yeah, simple.
[ __ ] hell, lad.
Yeah, man. That's all I've really come
on here is to get the answers. I'm I'm
off this [ __ ] bro. Seriously.
with these weasels. These jealous
weasels on here, bro. Yeah.
These little weasels. Have you seen that
fat Peter Griffin? Jamie Thompson.
[laughter] Have you seen the guy, bro?
Still stalking me. Little weasel. Little jealous weasel.
Yeah. So, anyways, the link's up there,
bro. So, you gonna are you going to are
you going to come in? Come on, bro. Mad, bro.
[ __ ] madness, bro. [ __ ] madness.
Yeah. Tell me about this girlfriend,
bro. And I'll tell you about the [ __ ]
that I've shown. I'll put it back up on
the channel if you want me to. I've
still got a [ __ ] video. I know you've
all seen it, but I'll put it back up if
you want, bro.
I'll put it back up if you want, bro.
Come on. I'll put it back up if you want
me to. I've got it. I mean, let's let's
have it out, bro. I want answers.
I want the [ __ ] answers today, bro. Come on.
Why am I not allowed to wonder that? I'm
allowed to wonder that if I want. You
know what I mean? [clears throat]
[ __ ] idiot. [snorts]
[ __ ] absolute idiot. Absolute idiot, bro.
Proper proper idiot. Sorry, I just seen
it, bro. And even though Yeah, they
don't bother me what they say cuz it's
just self projecting. But like, can this
guy be [ __ ] writing on these people's channel?
You know what I mean?
You know what I'm saying, bro?
Bro, this community is starting to weird
me out again, bro. I've noticed that.
Yeah. You can be on it for a day, two,
and then three days you're like, "It's
getting cringy again, bro." And that's
when we come off of it for like 2, three
weeks. The same fat stalking weirdos.
It starts getting creepy again, Dusty. Yeah.
I was going to do a long video, Dusty.
Yeah. Explain replying to this email
about the whole M thing and everything,
bro. But I couldn't be bothered as a
[ __ ] I can't be bothered. Yeah.
I just want to know why is it okay for
me for people to call me, but I can't
call them back without this guy butting
his nose in.
Why can't I say anything back without
this guy butting his nose in? Dusty,
I can't say anything back without this
guy butting his nose in.
I'm all right, man. Yeah, I just I just
emailed LT. I've asked him again, has he
not got anything to say about people
calling me a virgin? Cuz he's got a lot
to say when I call other people a
[ __ ] virgin. Oh, girlfriend. Don't
say that about him. Don't say that about
him. He's got a girlfriend. So, I just
emailed him saying, "Oh, um, do you not
want to bring up the 19year-old? Do you
not want to bring up the [ __ ] Do
you not want to bring up Manchester? Do
you not want to bring up all of the
women that I was kissing? Do you not
want to bring up all the dates I've
had?" I just emailed him simply asked, I
mean, do do you not want to do that?
No. I just don't like biased people,
bro. I just don't like biased dick
suckers. I just don't like biased
[ __ ] That's all I don't like,
bro. I just don't like [ __ ]
Oh, don't say that about him. He's got a
girlfriend, bro. [ __ ] off, bro. [ __ ] him. Yeah.
But I was I was going to get really
nasty on the emails, bro. I was going to
get really disgusting and nasty, bro,
and prove to everyone on this YouTube
that this guy's not about nothing, bro.
You know, but for my mom's sake, bro,
it's not worth it. Trust me. Trust me.
And I would show everyone that this guy
is not about nothing, bro. today. I
swear to God, I would do. I don't care,
bro. I'm sick of this guy sucking
people's dick every single time I go for
them. Sucking up their dick. You know
what I'm saying, bro? It's annoying,
bro. Do you know what I'm saying?
[ __ ] [ __ ] cutting me off every
single time, bro. Every single [ __ ]
time. Defending his [ __ ] boyfriend.
Like, get married to the guy, bro. Like,
if you want me to give you the money, I
will give you the money. You can get
married to the guy. If you want to get
married to your boyfriend, I'll fund it,
lad. It's not a problem. Just just just
say the word and you can get married to your boyfriend.
Yeah. You can get married to your
boyfriend and I'll come to the wedding,
bro. Like, that's all you got to say. Do
you know what I'm saying? That's all you
got to say, bro. Yeah, they do have
their own agenda. But Dusty,
Dusty, this guy says he doesn't like
biased people. This guy says he moans
that every single place that he's gone
to, bro, people have said, "Oh, he has
not gone there. He's not gone there."
So, why are you doing the same thing?
Why are you doing the same thing? Why
are you by your boyfriend's side every time? Boyfriend.
Come on, bro. Like, tell us.
Tell us, bro. Tell us.
Madness, bro. Trust me, I can get
really, really nasty, bro. Trust me. But
it's not worth it. It's not worth it,
bro. It's not worth it, bro. It really,
really, really is not worth it. Trust
me, bro. Trust me. Yeah.
[ __ ] idiot. [ __ ] clown.
Who was emailing you to go to the pub,
bro, and then you started backtracking
when you was last on here? Who was
emailing you telling you the pub that I
was in before you started backtracking
and then you started backtracking? Who
was it, bro? Do you remember during the
Euros? Then you started backtracking
again. Tell us who who was Tell us who
was emailing you.
Tell us who who was emailing you, bro.
Tell us who was emailing you. Who Who
was it? Who was emailing you, bro?
You should let everyone know who it was.
instead of starting to instead of backtracking
and you're telling people they ain't got
a purpose. I've got more than a purpose.
You don't know what I do in my daily
life, bro. You don't know nothing about
me. People are allowed to tell you what
you are and have a purpose in life.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
[ __ ] clown, bro. Absolute clown.
Penny Wise the clown. Yeah. [clears throat]
Yeah. They have got their own agenda.
Well, you should have known that with
Pat Mustard to be fair.
You should have known that with Pat
Mustard about the agendas, lad. That's
been going ages, bro. Even before him,
that's been with like Pat and Yeah,
that's been going years, bro. The agendas. Yeah.
Just let me know if you want to get
married, bro. Like, I'll help fund it.
It's not a problem.
Next thing I'll be asking is when the
[ __ ] when is the when is the baby
due? You know what I'm saying? [ __ ] me. Madness, bro.
Mad. Absolute madness.
Absolute [ __ ] madness.
Yeah. And I was going to go over that M
thing, but then I couldn't be bothered,
bro, cuz it's like one ear and out the other. Yeah.
Come on, bro.
So, yeah. I don't know if that was Did
Did that L Did that LT go to Scotland to
meet Shaga then? Was there any is there
any proof that it was him?
Nah, I don't believe he went, you know.
No, bro. I heard a lot of rumors that wasn't him.
I don't believe he went to be honest
with you, bro.
Nah, I don't believe it. Me? No, cuz he
didn't go live, did he? So, no. No, I
didn't. I I don't believe he went
anywhere out of London to be honest.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Two can play that game. See, now two can
play that game. If you want to start
being biased and keep defending your
boyfriend, I can do I can do exactly the
same thing. See, I I can play exactly
the same game. Do you know what I mean?
Who Jaws? I emailed him, bro. I emailed
him, Hu Jars, like about 15 minutes ago.
I said, "Oi, bro, your your your man's
talking about me being a virgin again.
Do you not want to talk about the
[ __ ] and the 19year-old and the sig
and the Manchester? Do you not want to
start talking about these things, bro?
like you're fast enough to keep
defending your boyfriend when I open my mouth.
Come on, bro.
Like, do do I want to go on his channel
and start talking the truth, bro? Like,
do you not want to start writing stuff
or what's going on, bro? [snorts] [laughter]
Nah, of course you wouldn't, mate. Of
course you wouldn't. Of course you wouldn't, mate. Nah. Mad.
I can't even open my mouth without [ __ ]
getting jumped down my throat. Having
someone jumped down my [ __ ] throat.
[clears throat] Yeah.
And then he comes out using these words
that these people use. I was like, I
knew you was one of them. I knew it,
mate. All you the easiest way to tell
with these people on here yet is as soon
as they start having an agenda,
I'm going to prison. You wish I You wish
I was. Um you uh as soon as they start
having an agenda, you know straight away.
Yeah. Going to prison. You w you wish I was. Yeah.
You know, bro, straight away. It's easy to spot.
Going to prison. You wish I was, mate.
You wish in your wet dreams, lad. You wish.
Anyways, I'm I'm going to be coming off
this [ __ ] anyways for a couple of weeks
minimum tomorrow. Defo, bro. What's
today? It's Monday tomorrow, isn't it? Yeah.
It's getting weird again.
It's getting freaky again, bro.
Am I going to jail? Uh, well, no.
What kind of question is that, bro? What the [ __ ] [clears throat]
I would. I'll tell you what I'm doing.
I'm coming off this [ __ ] That's
what I'm doing, bro.
I'm joining Monty. Yeah.
Yeah. They wish, bro. They wish.
Yeah. Well, then you should know it's
[ __ ] then, isn't it, bro? If people
are putting up stuff, then you should
know it's [ __ ] then, shouldn't you?
I'm scared of LT, bro. The only one
that's scared of LT is you, Harry.
And I'm not even offending him anyway,
so I'm not even going to say the reason
why. [ __ ] that. If he wants to be
biased, I'll be biased as well. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't want to I don't want to
[ __ ] myself up there. Yeah. Yeah. Well,
I I don't know anything about this guy.
Yeah. Yeah. He wants to be biased. I'll
be biased as well, then.
But yeah, no, honestly, I am coming off
this [ __ ] anyway from tomorrow because
it's just the same people just doing the
same [ __ ] and we've we've seen all of
this last year. So yeah.
Yeah, bro. It's just the same people
doing the same [ __ ] that they were doing
last year and the year before and the
year before and the year before and the year before.
It's not about agreeing. I've already
explained this multiple multiple times.
Go away Lavy Lavy follower. It's not
about agreeing. I've explained it
multiple multiple times. So,
well, I've got enough evidence pack,
mate. I've got enough evidence pack.
I don't even I don't even need anymore.
We're not talking about agreeing. I'm
not explaining it again.
>> [clears throat]
>> So yeah, it's got nothing to do with
agreed or disagreeing. What are you
talking about? [snorts] You're biased,
mate. You got your own agenda. Go away.
Every what I'm saying is is correct.
Anyone with a brain cell would know it's correct. Simple.
But yeah, I'll be coming off here anyway
from tomorrow. So yeah, you might want
to come and speak your mind now, bro,
whilst the link's up. Yeah,
bro. Have you not seen these people on
there as well? Look at that Jamie
Thompson, bro. Look at the state of what
these people look like.
Look at the state of what these people
look like that are doing this, bro. What
the [ __ ] lad?
Jealous. You can tell he's jealous. Look
at him, bro. He looks like Peter Griffin.
It's It's straight up jealousy with
people in this community, lad.
It's straight up just jealousy. I knew
that. Anyways, with these people, bro,
it's just straight up jealousy with them
because what it is with these people
where they're It is real. It is real,
bro. He's come on camera and he's Come
on. where these people's lives are
ruined. Yeah. They've got nobody.
They're sat on YouTube 24/7. They try to
bring other people down. Do you
understand what it is with the people in
this community, bro? And it is real. It
is real because he's been on camera on
live streams. It is him, bro. This This
is the kind of people that you're
dealing with. This is literally the kind
of people that you're dealing with on
here, bro. That is him. That literally
is him. That's But to be fair, bro, you
know, that's what a lot of the people on
here look like.
It's jealousy with these people. Like,
it's And what I'm saying to you, they
have failed at everything in life. Their
their lives are at the pits. This is why
they do this [ __ ] bro. And to be honest
with you, I shouldn't even be on here.
I shouldn't even be on here, bro. To be
honest, I'm I'm off tomorrow, bro. Day
tomorrow is Monday. I'm off of here
tomorrow, lad. 100%. I am off of here
tomorrow, bro. On my mom's life, bro. No
courses included. I am off of it for a
very very very very long time.
100% because we seen all this [ __ ] last
year. I shouldn't be on it, bro. I
shouldn't be to be fair. It's full of
glasses. It's full of bias people. It's
full of idiots. Yeah. It's full of It's
full of self projectors.
Yeah. It's true though. It's literally true, bro.
It's true. Am I Am I lying, bro?
I'm not lying though. Am I, bro? Am I
lying? No, I'm not lying, bro. I'm
telling the truth. It's the truth.
It's full of biased people as well. Like,
you know what I mean, bro? Yeah.
So, what some of these people on here
look like, bro? [ __ ] weirdos.
Weirdos, bro. Right. Actually, look,
bro. Look at them, bro.
They try to ruin anyone. Then you got biased people.
Biased people, bro. They're not even
worth the time of day. They're not even
worth [ __ ] They're not even worth the
time of They're not even worth anyone's
breath, bro. You know, that's how bad it
actually is. Why do you think I wasn't
on for weeks, bro? What? cuz I couldn't
go on YouTube. No, cuz I couldn't be
bothered with the [ __ ] These people
are not even worth it, bro.
Simple, lad. That's why I'm doing it again.
[ __ ] me, lad.
So obsessive. So weird.
None of them look good.
Have you noticed that ghost of ducks?
None of these people on here that do
this look good. Have you noticed that?
Have you noticed all the people that
have shown their face? All of the people
that have been exposed, have you noticed
that none of them have looked good?
Isn't that telling you something, bro?
None of them have looked normal. None of
them have looked handsome. You know what
I mean, bro?
Have you seen Have you seen what these
people look like, lad?
Bomb. Uh, bomb. Sorry, bomb. Nonss
[ __ ] There's been loads of them, lad.
There's been loads of them. Look, look
at what these people look like, bro.
These are the people that are doing it.
Look, look at what they look like, bro.
Try and tell me something, bro.
Look at this, bro.
Get your answers very quickly, Dad.
You get your answers very quickly.
Nah, not moaning, bro. Not at all.
Not moaning at all, man.
Yeah, man. So, you see why they doing
You see why they do this, in it, Ghost
of uh Ducks? You see why they do this
[ __ ] in it, bro?
It's basically where their lives are
ruined. They want to try to bring other
people down with them. Like L's
followers. Yeah. They're all just
rejects of society. Nothing going for
themselves. That's why they sit on there
calling other people that are better
than them. Do you don't understand it?
They're all alike. Miners think alike.
Do you not get it, bro?
Why? Because because they can't afford gas heating.
[laughter] Cuz it's jealousy, bro. I'm
better looking than them. I've had more
women than them. I've got more money
than them. You tell me one person that
sits on the internet, bro, for god knows
how many years doing this to someone
that they don't know. By doing this, I
mean being obsessive and stalking, you
get what I mean? [ __ ] It doesn't
bother me, bro. Me telling you people
what you are, that's not bothering me.
It's telling you what you are, bro. It's
an opinion. Everyone's allowed an
opinion on what you a lot of the weirdos
on here do, lad.
No, I only got one of them. I'm getting
the other one in a couple of days. Yeah,
man. It's the same thing with that Jo.
Look at him, bro. Look, look at this guy
that's talking about me.
You know what I mean? Come on, lad. Come
on. This one come today. I'm not sure
why it was fast delivery, but yeah. Look
at the state of the people that do this
that have shown their faces and then
look at me. Yeah, man.
It's just It's just It's just saying it,
bro. It's not even reacting. It's just
It's just saying it.
Who's the worst follower? Um, sorry bro,
I'm trying to keep up. Uh,
in terms of what obsession,
probably Jo. That guy is obsessed with me, bro.
His whole channel was dedicated to me.
That's why I unsubed. I unsubed from him
two weeks ago and never went back on the
channel, bro. He's another jealous one. Jealous freak.
Nah, bro. It's got to be that Joe F.
No, he's he's really bad, bro. This guy
was trying to call me Porky. I was like,
are you mad, bro? Two weeks ago, I was
on his channel, bro, before unsubed. I
was like, you're you're calling me Py,
bro. You're calling me that.
You're calling me that, bro. You're you
are calling me. No, bro.
because they want to. Why does that
concern you? Who lives with their mums
or not? Bro, lives with their moms, who
lives with their dads.
Okay. What's that? What's that got to do
with you, bro?
Why? Why do you care who lives with
their mom and dad? Do you live with your
What's what's why do you care, bro?
What about your own life? Oh, Timmy, you
haven't got a life. My bad.
But yeah, I'm definitely coming off of
this tomorrow, lads. Um, for a very,
very, very, very long time. So,
yeah. So, in case anyone tries to like
make up rumors and stuff, I've told you
I'm I'm coming off, lads. So, um, so
you'll know why. So, simple as that. I
don't know who that is, bro. I don't
know who that is.
I'm not proving nothing to you. Don't
even try [ __ ] showing on my channel,
lad. It's not going to work.
Yeah. When you people start showing your
faces like I've asked you to do, then
I'll do what you asked me to do. Simple
as that. I don't need to prove anything
to you, bro.
So, um, when you people when you start
showing your faces and prove my rumors
wrong, I'll do exactly what you asked.
Shake on it. Shake our should we shake
on it? Virtual handshake. Shake hands.
When you start proving my rumors wrong
about you people being the way that you
look like, then I'll then I'll then I'll
um destroy some of the rumors that have
been made about me. I think that's fair.
Come on. That's fair. Come on. Come on.
That you would never do that. And that's
another thing, Ghost of Ducks. You
notice that on that L J channel, the
amount of people that watch that uh the
live stream and no one joins. Hardly anyone joins.
Like maybe one person does very rarely.
But have you noticed none of them join
and none of them ever ever come on camera.
They never put their cameras on. Um they
never even talk.
Why do you think that is, bro?
Why do you actually think that is? Like
it's no one joins and no one no one
shows what they look like.
Um rarely, bro. Like really they they
actually don't. They really really
[ __ ] weird, bro.
H and then they tried to talk about me
and you know when these people keep
calling me a M. Yeah. I was going to
explain this to LT in a video. I was
going to do a video to LT and I was
going to I was going to destroy that
once and for all, but then I couldn't be bothered, bro.
Like, cuz there's no point even
explaining to these people because
they're not even going to understand, bro.
I was going to say I could explain
exactly why, bro. Like, but it's like
there's no point. There's literally no
point, bro. You know what I mean?
I don't I don't know. I don't rate my
looks. I don't care about what I look, bro.
I don't really care. I just know I'm
better looking than these people. Miles
better looking than them. That's all I know, bro.
That's all I know. I'm just miles better
looking than them.
But who knows? I don't know. I don't care, bro. Six maybe
since you're asking. 6.5.
But yeah, lad like it's um
I can explain the M thing if you want me
to, bro. If you really want me to. I
come across somebody that's got daddy
issues four years ago and they wanted to
project their insecurities onto me.
Somebody that I didn't even approach.
Good for you, bro. Good for you bringing
up the four or five. The only reason I
got called I got called a month or four
years ago, mate, is cuz I've actually
got a life. And you know how entitled
women are and how rude they can get and
how they can project their daddy issues
onto you. Good for you, bro. And what?
What about all of the women that called
me good-looking? What about all of the
women that I slept with? What about all
the women I pulled and didn't even have
to pay a penny? What about them women?
Good for you, bro. Some women projected
her insecurities onto me who I didn't
even approach [ __ ] uh four or five
years ago. Good for you, bro. No one
cares. And guess what? You can't even
par it because I didn't even approach her.
I didn't even approach her. So, do you
think I care? I weren't even [ __ ]
with her. Now, if I was [ __ ] with her
as in I mean like trying to talk to her
and that then then it'd be different.
So, I come across somebody with daddy
issues that wanted to self-p project.
Oh, no one cares, bro. That's that's
that you know that was four years ago.
Somebody wanted to project their
insecurities onto me. Okay, good for
you, bro. And what's happened in the
past 3, four years,
LT, what's happened in the past 3, four years?
Like, do you know what I'm saying? What
the [ __ ] Do you think I care that some
woman's projected her insecurities onto
me? Because let me tell you something
for a fact. Yeah. If somebody actually
did find you ugly and they had any wits
about you, they wouldn't even say that.
They would not even say that. Someone If
somebody generally found you ugly and
they had something about them, they
would not be saying that. The reason
they said that out loud, bro, is cuz literally
um they were self- projecting their
their issues onto me. Good for them,
bro. I don't care. I don't like them. I
won't I You know what? It's so long ago.
I can't even remember what they look
like, bro. I can't even remember what
they look like.
I can tell you what. Look, I'm going to
give you some ammo here. Yeah. I
approached somebody in a shopping center before.
Uh, I approached somebody in in in a
shopping center before.
I I approached somebody in a shopping
center before and do you know what
happened? There was somebody that come
beside me and they said my hair was
greasy. Do you know what this person
looked like? Do you know what this
person looked like? Yeah. I don't think
you want to know. So, bro, that happens
in these westernized countries where
entitled people like to be [ __ ] cuz
they've got issues. Good for them, bro.
I don't care
about we've seen a woman call you a
manta. We've seen me have more women
than everyone on this community
combined. We've also seen that as well.
You know, there's no point starting an
argument with me cuz you're not going to
win, bro. You're never ever going to
win. Trust me, you're never ever ever
ever ever ever going to win. And it's
not because I think I'm right. It's cuz
I know it. You know,
no one cares about someone self
projecting, bro. 4 years ago, I
approached her friend. I approached her
friend and she was probably jealous I
didn't approach her.
No one cares about that month of [ __ ]
bro. Serious. Come on now.
This community gets very, very weird.
Ghost of ducks. Yeah. The longer you
stay on it, the weirder it gets.
the weirder it gets. You know, that's
why Monty don't come on here anymore.
She could have been jealous or she could
have just been like could have her own issues, bro.
Yeah. Whatever the reason is, bro. Like
that is I I I I've seen it. Yeah. Where
where people have approached women and
they've turned around and said, "Oh, you
look like a guy I friendzoned." Or
they've done some mad or they've said
some mad stuff to them, bro. Like that
will happen, you know. I just got
unlucky and dealt with somebody that was
really rude. That's all it was, bro.
That's all it really really was, bro.
Getting happy over that about four years
ago, bro. And you're still getting happy over that.
Maybe I'm Maybe I'm the only one that's
still living in 2026.
You know, maybe I'm the one that's
living in 20 Maybe I'm the one that's um
only I'm the only one that's only living
in 2026, bro. It seems to be that way. You know,
you know what I'm saying?
It's madness, bro.
But yeah, I'm not I'm not ever defending
LC ever again, bro, with these biased
people. He can [ __ ] off, bro. He's by
himself now. Simple as that.
the year of the fight.
No, I don't want a Vindaloo, Dusty. You
know, the thing is when you order it,
when you order the Vindaloo's, they're very watery.
It's not like eating it at a restaurant.
It's very watery. So, I probably won't
eat again today, bro. I can't be
bothered. I don't think I'm that hungry
to be fair.
Could do a cutting down anyways, but no,
it's too watery.
It's too watery, bro.
It's not the same as when you eat in a
restaurant. It could be any restaurant.
It don't need to be um Liverpool Street.
It could be anyone. It's just not the
same, bro. It just don't hit the same
way. It's so watery. Every time you
order it, it's always watery.
The mint sauce is watery. It's just pointless. [sighs]
Yeah, maybe, bro. It depends. If I'm
hungry, maybe. I don't know. I don't
know what I'm getting yet, bro. if I get
anything to be fair.
Yeah. Calling me Porky, bro. People that
are that are [ __ ] that are bigger
than me calling me Porgi. What the [ __ ]
Come on now, bro.
Yeah. Who do you know who started that?
It was that Jo, bro. It was that it was
that self projector.
That Jo self projector.
I used to think he was all right. Um but
Ghost, I used to think he was all right,
but then he started defending his boyfriend.
Um, so I was like, he's giving weird
vibes now. And I and I was right. He was
another he was another Ly.
Yeah, he was another lovely lad. But yeah. Yeah.
No, I [ __ ] did not. No, I [ __ ] did
not, bro. What? Maybe what? 10 [ __ ]
what? Maybe 12 years ago, bro. No, I
[ __ ] did not.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. I did not, lad.
No, no, no, no, no. It was weird because
[ __ ] Yeah. And then you can't And
then he started self-projecting his
virginity onto me and [ __ ] And he
started being weird about Cheryl Car and
that, bro. That's why I cut contact. He
started self-projecting his virginity
and started talking about dead
relatives. And I don't want to hang
around with a coward.
I don't want to hang around with, bro. I
met him because I felt sorry for the guy, bro.
Like, people used to bully him on
PlayStation. Yeah. And I thought I was
young and I was like, "Okay, well, okay,
this guy, you know, maybe he's all
right. Maybe people are just, you know
what I'm saying?" And then he started
being weird with the shovel thing and
projecting his virginity onto me.
Yeah, it was so weird, lad. So so so so weird. yeah.
Yeah. So I I couldn't hang around with
someone like that. I just could not hang
around with someone like that
unfortunately. So I had to cut contact.
And he started talking about dead
relatives as well. So yeah. Yeah, lad.
Yeah, he's projecting, lad. Projecting.
How Why Why is this guy so obsessed with
me, bro? After all of these years. Oh,
it's so weird.
[snorts] Gives me the creeps, bro.
Oh my god. You wouldn't even be obsessed
with somebody that you was in love with
this long, Dusty. Do you know how weird
it is? I stopped that you I stopped that
USA thing. Yeah, I stopped that USA easy
thing after [ __ ] God knows how long.
You don't see me still do anything. You
don't don't see me still go on about it.
[ __ ] weird, bro. Is it [snorts]
so weird, isn't it?
It is strange, isn't it? probably. Yeah,
Yeah, I need to complete this one and
then Yeah, should be good.
I just want a channel where Greavvesy,
Steven Howard, and a couple of other
people. I don't want these people
following me anymore.
I'm being deadly serious, lad.
I'm being deadly deadly deadly serious.
No, I'm not looking hch, bro. I just
been eating a lot of food lately.
Well, I mean, Legos for everyone.
Well, I haven't been doing it straight.
Well, I haven't been doing it straight, have I?
I haven't been doing it constantly. You
do realize that. I've only been doing it
when I can be bothered.
Nope. Elaine doesn't want me out. Elaine
just doesn't like me on YouTube.
So, that's what I'm going to be doing,
lad. I'm going to be uh I'll be I'll be
I'll be living my life with Laney
after today. No, no, no, no. See, I saw
this guy's rumors two weeks ago. Jo, an
old woman controls my life. No, an old
woman doesn't control my life. I just
don't want to react to you little
weirdos. You little jealous weirdos that
ain't got a life.
Yeah, I can do what I want when I want,
mate. I'm on it right now on the one
that I unsub from. Yeah, bro.
Weird weird people in here, Dusty. Very weird people. H
weird people, lad.
Yeah, you do that.
Am I skinn again? Well, I'm on YouTube
24/7 and I'm never skin. So there's no
again to it because I'm never skint
and I'm not on YouTube 24/7. Big difference. So
no nothing skint about me. Bro, you need
to stop the ski thing. It's getting
boring now as well. Leave that in 2025.
It's boring now.
See, I can actually I can actually sound
serious when I want.
You know, it's very very boring now.
Leave it in 2025.
Very, very, very, very boring. [gasps] [clears throat]
How can I be skint when I want a [ __ ]
football bet and a hand buddy? Anyways,
do not use your brain, bro.
Do not actually use your [ __ ] brain.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
That's [clears throat] their life, isn't
it? And it's more than 5 years. They've
been doing it for over 10 years. So,
yeah, they've been doing it since 2012, I've heard.
been more than five years. Yeah.
I don't really understand the point of
this community, you know, cuz you know,
communities are supposed to have points
to it. This doesn't have no point. No
one puts gambling videos up.
Everyone just talks about the same
thing. They just self-project. I don't
really see the point of the the the whole community.
I don't see the point of this community
ghost. No one puts gambling videos up.
No one puts content up. They just all
self-reflect and no one even joins
[ __ ] panels. I don't get the point of it. Weird.
I'm not sure, bro. I don't know what the
point of it is.
That is weird, bro. Do you know why I'm
on it today? Because I've got nothing to
do today. I'm I'm chilling today.
I've literally got nothing to do today.
I'm bored. I was watching Ed Matthews. I
need to continue watching something. Yeah.
Yeah. I got my other channel as well.
I got I got I got three channels, bro.
>> [clears throat]
>> I'm going to make a tea in a minute. Simple.
Nope. One one channel is just my approaches.
When I've gone out and approached women,
I just show it to people on like Reddit
and stuff. Oh, that's another thing.
Ghost of Ducks. They also stalk me on Reddit.
Yeah. Well, they can't do that anymore
cuz I use different subreddits, but they
used to stalk me on Reddit as well
pretending to be women.
Yeah, bro. But they've actually stalked
me on Reddit as well before pretending
to be women and [ __ ] They dedicate
their whole life to Peter Belly, but
they've got a better life than me apparently.
I don't think so.
Yeah. They'll actually like post
pretending to be women in hopes that you
message them and show them your
approaches so they get your new channel.
They are literally obsessed.
Obviously, they can't do that anymore
cuz they don't know the subreddits I go on.
Strange, isn't it? You know,
but that's Yeah.
No, I'm being deadly serious. They do.
They stalk me on Reddit as well. [clears throat] Yep.
No, I'm not.
Poor PJ has no luck in life. I still not
been laid, bro. Self-projecting comments
don't bother me, lad. Don't even waste your time.
28 not been laid, lad. That's self
projecting. That doesn't bother me.
Uh, and no, I'm not joking you. That's
what they do on Reddit, bro. They stalk
uh they stalk me on Reddit.
who done it pretending to be a woman.
Um, a few of them. A few of them have
done it, bro.
>> Yeah, a few of them have done it. That's
how you know they're jealous, bro.
Because they dedicate their whole life
to stalking me. That's how you know
you're doing something right, bro.
That's how you know you're doing
something right, bro. That's how you know.
Don't need a part-time job, mate. Got
enough money. Ah,
little part-time job. I suggested that
for someone else before you, little copycat.
Little part-time job at Macked. £50 a
day. Why not? Nothing wrong with that.
£50 a day.
But no, they they they do stalk me, lad.
They do stalk me.
Yeah. Mad, is it?
Oh, that's their life though, is it, lad?
If they're so intelligent. Yeah, I don't
keep falling for it. They can't find me
anymore. O, if they're so intelligent, um,
Ghost of Ducks. Yeah, like they say they
are, why do they repeat the same [ __ ] every day?
Ask yourself that question. Yeah. Yeah, man.
He was on here earlier.
Nope. He was on here earlier.
Well, it's not normal. You're on YouTube every day,
but you don't see me say anything.
You're on YouTube 24 hours every day.
I'm coming off here tomorrow, so don't
believe any rumors. Yeah.
I should have took that advice that that
person gave me, bro, like a year and a
half, two years ago. To be honest, I
should have took that advice.
Stupid of me not to, to be honest. It
was right all along.
I should have took the advice really,
bro. To be honest. Um,
I don't know, bro. Loads of people. A
lot of them are a lot of them. Um,
uh, loads of them, bro.
90% of the people on here do.
So, there's no point naming them because
90% of them do. >> [whistles]
>> But yeah, most of the people in here
were just nerds.
Nerds without a life. Isn't that right? Um, Dusty.
This has got to be the most weirdest
community, bro, I've ever come across.
Yeah, definitely, bro. Definitely.
Definitely made up my mind, bro. These
people are little grasses. They're
little self projectors. Why do you think
I wasn't on for two weeks, bro? It's not
because I couldn't go on it. It's cuz I
just didn't want to.
Definitely. Definitely. Definitely. I
have to leave. Nope. Not worried about
prison. I'm not going to prison. Why
would I be going to prison, bro?
[snorts] Bro, use your [ __ ] brain. Seriously.
Nah, it's just I don't want to entertain
these little self-protting little
stalking weirdos. I'll just go on my
other channel. Simple as that.
Nah, you definitely won't see me
tomorrow, lad. You definitely definitely
won't see me tomorrow. You definitely
definitely definitely won't. Bro, at the
end of the day, you're talking to
someone that has been off of YouTube
longer than weeks, bro.
Nope. Don't have a trial coming up.
Not for years.
Oh, I was speaking to my solicitor about
that the other day, Dusty, and he
basically said that, yeah, basically
he's [ __ ] because where I've got all
the evidence of them harassing me, trust
me, it will count. Trust me, it will
count. and where I've got the crime
reference numbers where the police
haven't done anything. Bro, trust me, he
doesn't have a leg to stand on. Funny
you should mention that. Um I've
actually got um Yeah, he's [ __ ] bro.
He's really really [ __ ]
Yeah, I got You don't need to see a
solicitor to not get arrested, you [ __ ] idiot.
Yeah. Yeah, you can see a solicitor
without getting arrested.
And uh Yeah, bro. He basically said
um he basically said as well that yeah
because of all the stuff I've got he
asked me what I had. He says no chance.
So yeah, that actually did come up actually. Yeah.
Yeah, definitely definitely definitely.
Um and I explained as well. Trust me,
bro. You're all welcome to come. I'm
that confident, bro. I'm that that
confident. Um when I get the date, yeah,
you can all come. You can all come and
you'll see, bro. Trust me.
Trust me, bro.
You you never with things like this,
bro, you never win in the end.
It doesn't matter, bro.
Yeah. People like that, they never ever
win in the end, Dusty. So there's I
don't even know why they even why they
even do it because they're never ever
going to win in the end.
I got several I've got so much [ __ ] on
my phone, bro. So much [ __ ]
Like so much [ __ ] bro. Trust me,
it's not ever going to work, lad. Trust
me. Trust me. So, anyways, I'm not
talking about it anyways. So, yeah.
Messed up, bro.
I need to make a cup of [ __ ] in a minute, lad. Um yeah, basically
cut down on all that, bro. Yeah. So, yeah.
I can hear someone.
Yeah. So that's that. Basically, [gasps]
these people on here don't know the
amount of [ __ ] I've got on my phone,
bro. They really, really, really, really
don't. They really, really, really,
really don't. Because me and Kieran was
talking about this like save everything
that they do. And that's it.
They always go to the police in the end,
the losers. Anyways,
that's how you know they're losers. Only
losers go to the police over YouTube, Dusty. Yeah, bro.
I don't really give a [ __ ] to be honest with you.
Yeah, I might start going out from next
week drinking I think. Probably. Yeah,
who knows? Maybe, maybe not. [ __ ] knows
what I'm doing. I'll be doing something anyways. So,
no. Trust me, it does matter. Anyways,
I'm not talking about this anyways. I
don't really care, bro. So, you're the
ones You're the ones that brought it up.
I really don't care, bro, to be honest.
Yeah, you will see that I'm right when
the day comes. Simple as that. So,
that's all. Yeah.
Yeah, man. No, I don't want to talk
about it, bro, because it's pointless.
It's pointless and it's boring,
you know? I don't want to talk about
these irrelevant people and I am coming
off tomorrow anyways. I'm not even on
them much anyways. So
they're irrelevant people, bro. I don't
want to talk about boring, jealous
people, lad. We want to talk about
different things, you know,
and that's that. Um, weird,
you know. Yeah, but all I was saying is,
yeah, more people's obsessed with me
than they are with Timmy.
And I'm just looking on this and I'm not
going to give them a reaction. They're
still trying to get a reaction in 2026.
Madness, bro. I'm on another channel
that not Joe for anyone's
still trying to still trying to bother
people in 2026. But like I've always
said, bro, I don't mind it, bro. It's
fine. It's good because
it's all right, bro. These people doing
this because it proves what I'm saying
is the truth. That's why I don't mind
them doing it, bro. It doesn't annoy me.
It doesn't make me rage. I I love them
doing it because it shows the jealousy
that I was talking about is correct.
So, I don't I don't mind. Like, it's not
going to make me stop [ __ ] swearing
and [ __ ] punching up [ __ ] [ __ ] all
that, bro. It just proves what I'm
saying is the truth. Timmy's got a lot
of stalkers, but I've got it worse than
him. Obviously, I've got it worse than
him, though, bro. I'm younger. I'm
better looking than these people. You
know, you expect that. You expect that, bro.
But yeah, Timmy, he's got haters, but he
doesn't have as many as me.
So, go figure in it. And he's been
longer than me. Yeah, [snorts]
I've actually got channels that are
dedicated to me and I don't think Timmy has that.
So, yeah. But I love it anyways cuz it
proves what everything I say about them is right.
The more they post about me, the more
they waste their time on me, the more it
proves I'm right about them. I'm saying,
nah, that's not that doesn't a wash that
doesn't wash in the washing machine.
That's just an excuse, lad. That's just
an excuse. Because think about it, bro.
Yeah, think about it. This is the way I
use it. I use this analogy. Yeah. So,
say, okay, um, let's just say a random
person. Yeah. in case you try and say
that I'm biased. They use that as an
excuse. Say someone comes on here right
now and says they want to do this to
kids or they want to do that to kids.
Like say they say like mad stuff,
whatever. So, do you think I'm going to
stalk them 24/7 for 5 years or do you
think I'm going to get on with my life?
Cuz I know the answer. So, that excuse
it doesn't wash in 2026
that it really really doesn't wash in
2026, lad. Um because so what? because
someone has said something about kids,
you're going to har you're going to
you're going to waste your life. The
only life that you've got stalking
someone every day. No, bro. That doesn't
wash anymore in 2026.
So, no. I mean, if if you said stuff and
and they thought you was a wronging,
they would actually be doing the
opposite. They would actually be
avoiding you. They would be avoiding
you, not dedicating their life to you.
So the fact that they dedicate their
life to you Yeah. Yeah. No, I know what
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I know, bro. I know
that's what they say. Yeah. But that's
not the reason, bro. Because if if that
was the case, bro, they would just like
not talk to you. They would not have
anything to do with you. Because the way
I see it, bro, if if I'm better than
someone, Yeah. I'm not going to waste my
time on someone. If I'm better than
someone and I know that they're jealous
of me and I'm not jealous of them, I'm
going to do the opposite of what they're
doing. That's why I don't make videos
anymore or reacting to anyone. I just
said to the LT that he's biased.
Yeah, exactly. It's jealousy, bro. It's
jealousy. It's nothing to do with
[ __ ] uh what people have said about
kids, bro. It's It's nothing to do with
it that they are jealous. It's nothing
to do with any of that stuff. Believe
you me, bro. It's nothing to do with
what people have said
because a normal member of the public
would not act the way that these people
do. They like they would avoid you. They
would literally avoid you, bro. They
wouldn't dedicate their life to you.
So yeah, it's jealousy. It's not because
of what you've said. It's cuz you're
younger than them. You're better looking
than them. Their lives are over. So the
only thing that they can try to do is
drag you down with them.
And like I've said before, UK asylum,
why has none of these people been better
looking than me? Why has none of these
people had more money than me? Do you
not think that's fishy? Do you not think
that's a bit fishy in the sea? How if
that isn't it isn't it a coincidence?
Right. Is it Is it a coincidence?
Is it Is it a coincidence that every
single person that does this that gets
caught out seems to be worse looking than me?
Why do you think I don't bother with
them anymore? Why do you think I don't
go back and forth with them? Cuz that's
me giving them my time by arguing with
them. You see? Because um
think about it. How hard can it be?
Doesn't do this. Charlie doesn't do
this. Ben Furry doesn't do this. Kieran
Like it's no one could ever make me
waste my life on on someone on the
internet I don't know, bro. Every day.
Look how long I done that thing to USA
for, bro. And that was someone I met
that I got with. That was someone I
actually met and I gave up after a
while. I gave up after a while. I gave
up after a while and they actually
[ __ ] with me. So, and then I gave up.
You don't see me doing this to them
every day. Don't go in their profile.
Don't message any of their family cuz I
can't be bothered, bro. Simple. So, if I
if I can stop when someone's, you know,
someone who I've actually met, then why
can't they stop?
Simple, bro. Why can't Why can't they
stop? Ask yourself that question. See?
So, yeah. [sighs] Yeah, man.
I don't know.
I mean, who do you like on this
community, bro? Like who do you actually
like? I thought L2 was all right until
we started being biased. So
yeah, man. It just shows that not many
people on here are all right. Yeah,
I don't mind limbs, bro, because at
least limbs don't selfject.
No, no, no, no. Do you know what it was,
bro? Yeah. It's because he when I used
to um when I used to go to these places,
Yeah. he used to say, "Oh, yeah. You've
gone, you've gone there. You've gone
there. You've gone there. You've gone
there." So, I was like, "Oh, yeah." Cuz
he was the only one that backed up with
the Seaside Mark thing. Uh, sorry,
Seaside M. The Arsenal Mark. Do you
remember? He was the only one that said
it. So, I was like, "Okay, you're not
biased." But then he he started saying
about um about the virgin thing. He said
it on the phone in it and I thought,
"Oh, maybe he just said it once and then
he said it again." I was like, "No, he
is biased though because that is being
biased." Yeah. He might have not been
biased about like, "Oh, you've turned
up." But no, he literally is being
biased because how can he butt in every
time you call someone a virgin that's
got this girlfriend, but every time
someone calls you a virgin when you've
literally proved you've had sex, he's
got nothing to say about it. How is that
not biased? That's completely biased,
bro. That's completely biased,
in every way. No, that is biased, bro.
That's why I call him bias. It's not
even about opinions. It's facts. That is
biased, bro. [snorts] Because you're
sitt there saying, "Oh, it's immature
that I find someone with a girlfriend a
virgin." But it's not immature that
somebody finds me a virgin, who's had a
[ __ ] on camera, who's been in women's
beds naked on camera, who's kissed women
on camera, who's women admitted to
sleeping with me on camera, who I've
literally pulled to the hotel room on
camera. How that is biased. That that
that is literally biased. But that's not
immature. But that's not being for real.
No. So what is it then if it's not biased?
So, and he done it a few times as well,
bro. I think he's done it about three
times. The same thing with that Jo, he's
done it as well, but obviously I
expected it from him because he's a Lav
um fan. So, you know, I expected it, but
when he started doing it,
I was like, "Yeah, that is weird." But
no, it is it is it gen No, that is biased, bro.
Cuz if he wasn't, he would say that and
then he would also he would say, "Shut
up. None of you are virgins. Shut the
[ __ ] up. So, no, he is biased. Definitely, lad.
That's all, bro.
[snorts] Pretty much. He is, bro. Do you
know why? Because the last email he sent
me, it started it started um being like these people.
Yeah. He started talking like these
people. I was like, "Oh, you're one of them now."
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He's one of them, bro.
He started using the same [ __ ] that they
were saying. Oh, we this, we that. I was
like, "Oh, so you're one of these people now." Okay. Yeah.
Yeah. He started saying the word we Okay.
Yeah. Thank you, man.
Yeah, I need to make a tea now. Anyways,
to answer your question, it was a good
question to be honest with you. But
yeah, they are they just use kids as an excuse, lad.
These people don't a lot of these people
don't even [ __ ] have kids. So yeah,
they use that as an excuse.
Yeah, they use it as a as an excuse to
be obsessed and [ __ ]
It's not supposed to make sense. This
community is not supposed to make sense.
So, don't try to, you know,
make sense out of it because you won't get me.
It's [ __ ] full of idiots. That's what
it's full of.
It's full of idiots. Mhm. Yeah. Yep.
[ __ ] [clears throat]
Yeah. Rattle. No, that's YouTube. These
people don't rattle me. Selfjectors
booming self projectors selfjectors
bouncing off their own lives. No,
>> Timmy. Why do you keep calling people a
virgin when you are a virgin yourself?
And that's not me being triggered.
that's asking you a question. It's 2026.
Same thing goes to you, ladies.
The only one that's the virgin is you.
So, I don't know why you keep trying to
trying to call me lad when you are
literally a virgin and that's not being
triggered. That's literally telling you
on the level.
What the [ __ ] bro? What the [ __ ] bro?
You're calling me a virgin, bro. What
the [ __ ] man? You don't even make sense.
>> And you're not winding me up either.
You're just embarrassing yourself.
Yeah, I spoke about women to me 32
times, not 62 times. And I've also shown
women in my bed. And I've also shown pornos.
Yeah. What's the point, lad?
And you're not triggering me either.
You're just you just make yourself look stupid
by calling me a virgin. You just look
stupid. That's all you're doing is is is
look look you're making yourself look really silly
by calling me a virgin. You're not
bothering me. You're not making me rage.
You're not making me rage. You're just
talking about yourself.
I'm just making a cup of [ __ ] weirdly.
Is that okay with you, boss?
Okay with you, boss.
You like Little Yoda illustration H
uh I put two sugars in that I can't help myself.
Two sugars. [laughter]
I bet Grezy would love to see a be LT
fight in it.
We usually would love to see him be an
LT fight in it.
You'd be getting your popcorn in it.
[laughter] I bet I bet you'd like to see
that with you [ __ ] Huh? [laughter]
Huh? Would you
could you imagine? Would you get your
popcorn out? [laughter]
Yeah. Would you [laughter]
would you make a DVD of it? [laughter]
I'm going to have a super. [laughter] Nah, bro. [ __ ]
Imagine what that guy looks like in real
life. The guy that was saying to poor [ __ ]
You never know what he looks like. Is
it? That's really weird, is it? It could be anyone.
That could literally be anyone. It could
be an old man.
I'm just making myself a cup of [ __ ]
It could literally be an old man.
Imagine that is an old man. You don't
know who it is.
E a s. Es
a wild s appears.
A wild s appears.
Oh, wow. Simply
Well, I was just watching Ed Matthews.
I was just watching Ed Matthews and it
seems to me from what I'm watching that
it's definitely the women and I've not
tried for a very long time.
Yeah. I was watching Ed Matthews and
this this woman was on on his lap. Yeah.
on on on his lap and he was he was in a
he's in a he's on a mobility scooter and
then he asked and then he asked for her
number and then she's like, "Oh, I've
got a boyfriend." I was like, "Oh, do
you really?" And that's and I was
watching it, bro.
No, it's definitely the women, bro.
Definitely definitely the women. I was
just watching their Matthews. They've
all got the same attitude. Anyone that
disagrees at this point is a s any is a
white knight. Sorry. Anyone
anyone that disagrees in 2026 has got to
be a white liro with all the evidence
that's out there now then [snorts]
is watching me. I need to tell her to stop.
I need to tell they need to stop
watching me. I can hear myself in the
other room. Greasy.
I can hear myself in the other bloody room.
Yeah, I can hear myself. But yeah,
anyone anyone now in 2026, bro, they've
got to be they've got to be they've got
to be delusional, bro. Yeah,
they've got to be del They've got to be delusional.
And I don't even care, bro. I'm just
watching this guy cuz it's good content, you know?
They're better than Cory. Yeah.
I don't know what I'm going to eat
today. I probably won't, to be honest.
I'd fancy a curry, but nah,
the curries are not good. She eating.
>> Yeah, probably nothing to be fair.
Stop watching me, Laney, if you're watching. [snorts]
Yeah, he can miss me all he wants. I'm
never going back to that [ __ ] Do you
remember that, Frankie the [ __ ]
Never. Never. Ever. Ever. Ever ever ever ever ever.
I'm not going back to that [ __ ] And I'm
not going back to ruler either. No. Never. Never,
never, ever, ever, ever, ever. Thankful
lady. Laney owns L J and all the
followers in it.
Laney owns them all. She says that they're morons. Laney.
Everyone simps over these people in this
community. It's weird, isn't it, Steven
Howard? He's got a lot of simps, bro.
It's like what you said earlier. A lot
of white a lot of simps white knights a
lot of people white knight him.
No he didn't mate I'll never go back to that [ __ ] Never poor [ __ ]
I agree you remember poor [ __ ]
I want that account to come back.
He used to repeat my little sayings, in it.
He used to repeat my little sayings.
No, I don't.
I stopped gambling for 9 months. Uh-uh.
When I gamble with Christmas, that was
the first time in like three months.
No, I don't.
[ __ ] damn Limbo.
Unless it's a football that's different.
When I play roulette, Greavesy. When the
ball spins, I'm no longer in control.
When the ball spins, I'm no longer in control.
I'm in denial. Really? Okay, that's nice to know.
That biscuit was nice.
Why have you ever had that hippo
biscuit? That kindo um hippo biscuit.
It's lush. I had two today.
Or did I only have one? I think I had
one. I got two.
Oh, they're so nice, bro. The happy
hippo biscuits. Yeah,
they're so nice, bro.
Yeah, the hippo biscuits.
I'm a bit hungry, but I don't know what
to get, but
yeah, the hippo biscuits. I like the hazelnut one.
Oh, I just realized what you've said
there. You've said something different.
You like my Lego, Steven Howard?
Is so is Joe F is one of the brothers? Steven Howard.
Joe is one of the brothers. Is he [ __ ] mate?
He's a little white. He's He's a little um
You know what? White Knight.
No, it's only non It's only nonsy to you
people that have got something to hide
because you got sick minds.
Now, it's only nons to people like you
that's got something to hide because
that's why you'd think something like
that. But nah, not to normal people.
Nah. Nah. Lego is for any age.
It literally says it says kids and
adults on it. I mean, it really really isn't, mate.
No, it really really isn't.
You think you you only in your mind you
would think that, look, cuz you got
something to hide. You see, that's where
projection comes into it.
No, I've got one I've got one toy, which
is Crash Bandicoot. Yeah.
Do you like my little Crash Bandicut tie? He's cute. [snorts]
Yeah. So, Lego. So, anyone that So, if
you if you play with Lego, that's Nonsi. What? Lego?
No, that's that's that's what you people
think. Oh, that's projection, lad.
That's why you've never worked a day in
your life, brother. That's projection.
We don't have this on this channel.
We don't have self projection on this
channel, lad. If you want to project
your life, your waste of life onto
people, bro, please find another channel
to do it.
Don't don't do it on this channel. We
don't have self projectors on here.
We just want normal people that can have
that can have a chat.
That's self projection, lad.
You should have left that in 2025. Yeah.
Got to be careful. Mommy's listening. Uh,
all right. They put more GTA videos on here, Grezy.
When's the next set? I'll probably get a next set.
I don't know.
Probably for next week. The next set is
£120 Grezy. It's more expensive. This one.
This one's more expensive, but it's got
Jojo on it. It's got more characters.
That one's got more little characters on it.
But it's £120 that one. This one was £40.
That's one [ __ ] 60 on [ __ ] Lego. Jesus.
Bye-bye. [snorts] No virgins on my channel. Uh, all right.
Wait, let me get it up. I think it might
have went up.
Oh, it's actually gone up, bro. One is $134.99. for $34.99.
This is definitely adults. This is
Oh, it's got all the little characters.
It's got the Oh, it's got all the little characters.
134. That's gone up. That has
It was cheaper, but now it's gone the [ __ ] up.
Yeah, this one's uh
Oh, look at Georgia.
He's cute, ain't he? Jojo,
do you like Jojoy?
It says gift for 10 year old for 10 plus
year old boys and adult fans.
So obviously it's adults as well, isn't it?
Oh, you can get Jojo just by himself,
but he's £45 as a minifigure.
No, but your mom did. Mine never. But yours did.
>> Yeah, your mom did, but not mine.
You know, there's um
I swear there's a Home Alone Lego set,
but you can't buy it anymore, can you?
Oh, this is definitely definitely all
This is definitely this money mic, you know, bro.
Oh, this is this is definitely
definitely money mic. I could I could
Yeah, it's him, bro. This is money, Mike, bro.
Yeah, that's definitely definitely him.
I can spot him a mile off. See, I'm very
good at spotting these people.
Stop giving it the big, bro. I've met
you in real life and you're not about
nothing, mate. You're scared when you
come to London.
There's a lot of Lego Harry Potter, but
I don't like Harry Potter.
I don't like Harry Potter Gre Grezy. I
only like Dobby. I don't like the whole
I wouldn't get that.
Yeah, Game Boy. That's old, bro.
That's very old.
That Home Alone set is like full [ __ ] weird. Yeah.
No, no, no, no. [snorts] Oh,
I'm just looking at the little sets.
[clears throat] Crazy. I'm looking at
the little sets.
Oh [ __ ] there's one here. 587.
Oh, [ __ ] me, bro.
Collectible gifts for teenage boys and
girls. No, no, no, no, no.
That's got to be for adults as well at that price.
Look how many little characters there is.
is. No, there's got to be more than Oh,
the Y. Oh, Chewaca.
I want Chewaca.
I love these little caves.
Who's your favorite little Lego Star
Wars character? Greavves.
I like Jojo and Chewacca. [sighs]
There's a set here. 150.
What's your favorite Greasy?
You're going to love my Spider-Man
t-shirt, Gregy. It's It's Spider-Man
with its ba with a baby on it. So, it's
Spider-Man and Spider-Man with the baby.
I'll show you it when it comes. I said,
"What's your favorite Star Wars Lego
set?" Uh, Lego character,
like the actual Lego character.
Oh, I remember that [ __ ] Poor [ __ ]
I wonder where's gone.
The poor [ __ ]
Yeah, I don't think you can get him in a Lego cavatar.
You can't get the Home Alone set
anymore. The Lego one is it. I want the Simpsons one,
but they don't sell Yeah.
That's not Reddit. Yeah.
Listen, you're boring, Mark. This is
2026. See you later, lad.
Um, you're boring, mate. You're a joke. Um, anyways, Greezy,
this woman on Reddit is dismissing my
struggles again. I've told her three
times and I've showed her my experiences
and she keeps uh
she keeps ignoring my um
she keeps dismissing all the bad things that's happened.
This mission struggles are getting it lad. Yeah.
Yeah. But you said if it was men they
wouldn't dismiss it, Greavvesy or
something, wasn't you saying like two
months ago? So you were saying that if I
was complaining about men, they wouldn't
make excuses or something.
Yeah, we'll just ignore this uh Arsenal
Mark. He's just a fool.
Yeah, this Arsenal Mark is just a Fanny.
Yeah, we don't respond to little fannies like him. [snorts]
I can't believe this is 2026 and you're
still you're still at the big man.
I mean, no one even likes you on here.
Why do you come and not even not one
person likes you on here, man?
Not one person likes you on here. They
all Even the people that don't like me.
So why are you on here, bro? You need
you need serious serious help, bro.
Serious serious serious help.
text LT. Why would I text LT when I
don't like LT?
H I think he's biased. So why would I
why would I run to LT? I don't need to
run to LT. Mate, I've tried to meet you
twice by myself.
Why would I run to LT? I don't even like LT.
texting LT when I don't like him and
I've tried to meet you two times by
myself. Okay, bro. Stop it, man. Just stop it.
The big man The big man act doesn't suit
you, Mark. Give it a break, will you?
Give it a break, mate.
Give it a break, lad.
Very boring. Very very boring.
You're a [ __ ] grandpa on YouTube
trying to act big, man. Grow up.
Pathetic. Absolutely pathetic you are. Jesus Christ.
What the actual [ __ ]
What the [ __ ] bro? [gasps]
All night, mate. You're talking about yourself, lad.
No one else. That's enough for talking about yourself. So
look at my credit score really.
Why do you always go to these cheap um destinations anyways?
What am I having for food? Probably nothing
to be honest.
I can't be asked.
I don't know. Probably nothing, bro. I
ate earlier, so
yeah, it is cheap.
So was Turkey. Your little 300 pound holidays,
your little cheapest chip holidays. Yeah.
Yeah. Your little cheap holidays.
Nope. Even Greavvesy doesn't like you,
Mark. Even Grey doesn't like you.
You know, everyone knows what you're
about on here now. So, I don't know why you're
I'm skint really. You need to come up
with some new comebacks, lad. It's 2026.
You say that you're smart. Yeah. Oops.
You say that you're smart and that's why
you don't show your face. Yeah. So, how
about you come up with some different comebacks?
Come up with some new stuff, lad.
Yeah, you should come up with some new
things, man. You should come up with
some new comebacks.
It's all very regurgitated.
If you're smart, why do you repeat
yourself every day then?
If you if you're smart, then why do you
why do why have you used the same comebacks
for 5 years?
Because you're not smart.
That's why. Because it's obvious.
Because you're not smart. Because if
you're smart, why do you keep repeating
the same comebacks? You repeater? Cuz
you ain't got nothing because you're not smart.
Yeah, man. Remember when I come to your
country, you didn't come out two times.
Yeah, I do remember that. I also
remember when I went to your country two
times, you didn't come out.
I remember that time.
You don't know everything about me,
though. That's the thing. You really
really don't. What color boxes am I wearing?
Okay. So, what color boxes am I wearing?
If you know everything about me, what
color boxes am I wearing then? Go on.
No one cares about your messages, lad.
Literally, no one cares about your
messages. No one bloody likes you.
People hate you more than they hate me.
Why? No one likes you, Mark. Everybody
knows that you're not about it. Go away. Go away,
Mike. You're very, very boring, lad.
You're sending me to sleep now.
You're sending me to sleep, lad.
It's like taking sleeping pills. You're very boring.
If you're trying to trigger me, you're
doing a very, very bad job. [snorts]
You're doing a really bad job. You're
actually very boring.
Um, was you are you able to um are you
able to afford an iPad yet? I remember
you couldn't afford an iPad. You got the Amazon tablet.
I remember you couldn't afford an iPad.
I remember that. Yeah.
Couldn't afford an iPad.
And what is it with you always going to
[ __ ] Turkey and [ __ ] Spain? Why
don't you go somewhere different this time?
Why don't you go somewhere different
this time? H
I pull my old iPad. I've never pulled an
iPad in my life, lad.
I have never pulled an iPad in my whole life.
Never in my life. I've tried to pull an
iPad when the police gave my iPad back,
but they broke it. [gasps] I've never
pulled an iPad, lad.
Why don't I go anywhere?
I have been
pulled a shitty TV.
I've never pulled the TV either. You got
the wrong channel. I've never pulled a TV.
Have I? I'm trying to think a TV. No,
I've never pulled a TV either. Never
pulled an iPad. Never pulled a TV.
Bro, do you even know whose channel
you're on? Because I've never pulled a
TV. And I I've never pulled an iPad.
You got the wrong person, lad. Cuz I've
never I've never I've never pawned
anything to gamble.
No. When did I pull a bro? I had a TV at
my old house and it stopped working.
I have never pulled a TV.
No, I definitely definitely didn't. So,
what year was this then? Because I've
only had two TVs.
I can't ever remember pulling a TV. I
don't know. I've definitely never pulled an iPad.
You're You're very unstable, lad.
Did I? Well, I know. I've definitely
definitely never pulled an iPad.
See where you people bring up such old
[ __ ] People don't even remember it.
People don't even remember it because
it's literally so old. I can't even
remember doing that.
That's how that's how much you live in
the past, bro. But I've never ever sold an iPad.
Never sold an iPad. I know that for a
fact. I've never pulled an iPad.
Yeah. Anyway, see you later, lad.
You get kicked. Yeah. Really, bro?
had a gamble. Yeah, I won a football bet yesterday.
Yeah. God, I could do with a laugh.
Yeah, I had I don't know. I put 20 pound
on five teams and I won 220.
I'm going let this guy on because it's funny, bro.
Yeah. And on five, both seems to score.
They all won. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
I lost 50 on Friday though on the property.
Wasn't having it for toffee.
My roulette days are done anyways. Yeah,
[ __ ] roulette, man.
[snorts and sighs]
This Arsenal. Who remembers this Arsenal
Mark clown? Steven Howard.
He's a [ __ ] idiot, ain't he? [snorts]
God, he's so embarrassing, bro.
He's a [ __ ] embarrassment. [gasps] >> [snorts]
>> It's the same old [ __ ] in it, bro. Same
Same old crap.
Yeah. It's so boring, isn't it, lad? Why
do you think I don't react to them, bro?
They're [ __ ] clowns, lad. They're
They're [ __ ] clowns.
I don't know what to eat today, bro. I
run out of coke cuz I only buy two cans
of Coke. I only have two cans of Coke a
day cuz obviously I cut down cuz of the
teeth and that in it.
I run out of coke.
I don't know what would
Yeah. You know, you just can't be bothered. Yeah.
Marks ran off, bro. He's done this
millions of times, bro. Do you know how
many times this guy has done this? He's
disliked more than me,
[laughter] bro. He's done this a million times.
It's just usual with this guy, bro. He's a clown.
The guy is a clown. I know. I can't be
bothered either, lad. I can't be [ __ ]
I'm under an electric blanket. I'm so cold, bro. Jesus.
>> Yeah. What do you want? What do you
>> What do [snorts] you want?
>> Yeah. What do you want, man?
What you want, man? Listen, what's your
problem with me? Keep my [ __ ] name
out of your mouth. Yeah. >> No.
>> And get on with your life.
>> I'll mention you whenever I want.
>> You're [ __ ]
>> I tried meeting you twice. You haven't.
This is so boring. Right. I tried to
meet you twice. I tried twice. I tried
meeting you twice. You come to my
[ __ ] area. Listen, you always overeat
people. You always over people.
>> Let me put I'm going to stay quiet. Yeah.
>> So, can I talk without you interrupting
or or do you just do you want to waffle?
>> Yeah. What's Yeah.
>> Can you turn Can you turn the music down
so I can actually hear you?
>> Excuse me?
>> Can you turn the music down so I can
actually [ __ ] hear you?
Oh my god, you're so sad. I got Roman
Virgo on like free volume. You can't
even [ __ ] hear this.
>> Yes, you [ __ ]
>> I can [ __ ] hear it. I can [ __ ]
>> Oh, but you can hear me though. Yeah.
>> Am I Am I Am I Am I Can you hear me? Can
>> I'm not a cokehead like you. So, no.
>> Okay. How are we going to work this? How
we going to work this? Right. You can't
hear me. You can't hear me. You just
said I'm on drugs, which I mentioned. Roman Virgo.
>> Mark, why are you in 2026?
>> Because you are a sad creep.
>> Going to meet You're never going to meet
anyone. So, why are you still doing it?
>> That is the reason you got the uh a good
a good thing that I'm on your live,
right? But the thing is with you, PJ,
can I say one thing or are you going to
interrupt me or block me like you
normally do when you don't get the
answers that you want?
>> Can I speak? >> Yeah.
>> Thank you. Thank you. Finally. Cuz you
block LT. I spoke to him. I've been
emailing all this stuff. Right. Listen,
you are a [ __ ] weirdo, right? You're
going to interrupt me. You're going to
say this, you're going to say that. Let
me give me two seconds. Yeah.
Can you hear me, PJ?
>> Yes. Go [clears throat] on. You said
you're talking. Go on. Listening.
>> What? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Tomorrow, Monday. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Go on.
Where are we eating? >> What?
Where are we meeting tomorrow? It's Monday tomorrow.
>> Mark, you're not meeting.
>> You're going to say I You're going to
say I don't want to meet people on
anybody. I've gone to your area you now.
>> You're not meeting no one. Shut up.
>> Stop talking [ __ ]
>> Why you laughing?
>> No one takes seriously anymore. It's funny.
>> I'm going to meet you tomorrow.
>> Yeah. Good for you. And I went to your
area twice. You didn't come out.
>> Oh, [ __ ] you. I was 27. I was having a wonderful morning.
>> We're not doing this in 20.
>> Can I speak? Can I speak or not?
>> Yeah. Go on.
>> PJ, you got a big problem. Yeah.
[screaming] You call people out that you
know ain't going to meet you. Right. I'm sitting here.
>> I've gone to your time and you didn't
come out live.
>> Everyone's so embarrassed. Everybody saw it.
>> I went to Can I speak to the park?
>> Can't ask him. Can I speak? Can I speak? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. See, you get interrupted again.
Yeah. Again. Yet again. I'm offering you
out face to face straight up right now.
Meet me tomorrow.
>> What do you got to say about that, big man?
>> We done. We've done
>> you take it before. Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh. You come to my area twice. Yeah,
without me knowing you. No,
>> I'm asking you one second.
>> No, no, no. One second. One second. How
did you not know when I was No one
second. No one second. No one. No one
know. No one. No one. No one second. No
one second. No one second. >> Untic
attacks. You've got anxiety. That's
another Yeah, that's actually true.
>> Yeah, that's true. That's true. You know
what? I've got You know, I'm so [laughter]
I've got like anxiety. I'm I'm I'm
Yeah. But PJ, can you hear me now? Yeah.
Can you hear me now? [laughter] Yeah.
>> Right. You going to let me speak again?
Are you going to let me speak again? [laughter] Yeah. >> [music]
>> Mark, you're not about that life. Why do
you do this? Why do you do this? You're
not about that life.
>> You know what I'm about?
>> You are a coward, a creep, and a weirdo. Right.
>> But you don't let you don't let people
speak. You don't let people speak on your
I am. And you're going to do nothing
about it. I'm going to do nothing. Yeah,
I'm going to do nothing. Okay. Right.
Can you let me speak then? [laughter]
>> Yes or no? You see on your life?
>> And that that window. By the way, by the
>> by the way right now.
>> Why do you meet me right now?
>> Right now? >> Yeah.
>> Uh 6:45. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Let's meet.
>> Let's meet halfway. Let's meet right now.
No, I'm I'm chilling.
>> No, no, let's meet right now. Come on.
>> All right. Where abouts?
>> What you What are you scared of?
>> What am I scared of? Where abouts, mate?
>> I'll meet you in Statford. >> Statford. >> Yeah, halfway.
>> It's Sunday night. I've got work
tomorrow. I just told you where to meet
>> Excuses. Excuses. Excuses again. It's
always excuses with you.
>> I'm not I'm okay. Okay. No, hang on,
hang on, hang on, hang on,
>> hang on, hang on.
>> Well, let me sort this um live out here
just so I can see where I'm [laughter]
>> still there. [clears throat]
Oh, you still there?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, let's meet.
>> Have you found anyone or text anyone? No.
>> Who Who would I be texting when you know
I don't like Ali? I've literally had my
own arguments WITH HIM. STOP.
>> OH, you mentioned that.
>> I know what you're getting at cuz I know
what you're getting at. You do it every
time. Listen, mate. When I went to your
area, when I went to your area by myself
by myself scared of you scared of you.
>> Oh my god.
>> No one is scared of you. Just come and
meet me today. Come on. I
don't don't leave don't stop
where it's at right
me a headache bro.
>> Okay. Okay. You know what you Stratford.
You said Stratford. I'm not going to
[ __ ] Trafford. Right.
Stratford and Miland is one stop away. Yeah.
>> Uh, I'm not going to Miland. I'll meet
you in Stratford.
>> Now, [ __ ] you, Stratford.
>> See, this guy's not about. See what I
mean? It's the same.
>> What time?
>> No. No. Hang on. Hang on.
>> Whatever time you want.
>> Right. It's It's uh 10 to 7. Yeah. Yeah.
>> 12 to 7 to be precise. But yeah,
>> [ __ ] Bradford. You're in [ __ ] Essics.
>> You're going to I'm going to go there. I'll
>> meet you in
>> Can you shut up for one minute?
>> No, Stratford is not one way. Stratford
is your [ __ ] dog.
>> I said halfway. I said halfway. [ __ ]
go to now. Okay. I'll meet you in I'll
meet you in Reen. Read.
Yeah. The awardion
puts you in control.
>> Yeah. I meet you on.
>> How about that?
>> Oh, you're a [ __ ] joker.
>> You're a joker.
>> Listen. Okay. So, why didn't you meet me
when I went to area twice? You saw it.
You did see it. I was a little You hear
me speak? You won't hear me speak.
You're going to talk to [ __ ] right?
>> Griezy, is it the same argument? Oh, Grey,
>> oh, Grey, please put a little thumbs up
on my channel. You're a [ __ ] weirdo.
>> You know what?
>> Okay. Why do you beat me in red? >> I'm
[clears throat] reading.
>> Yeah. Why do you meet me?
>> Christ, you're [ __ ] weird.
>> Mark, get off of your
>> I'll beat you in. Come on. PJ is not
meeting. He's supposed to come to Belfast. Well, >> this Mark, [singing] you're offer.
>> Oh my god. Oh, there we go. There we go.
That's um Lord J.
>> I knew people were >> PJ
properly. He can't even talk.
>> He's not going to meet you. The same way
you're not going to meet him. No will ever meet.
>> The thing is, hold on. I've actually
tried to meet him twice.
>> No, no, no.
>> I went to his area twice. [laughter]
>> Mark, get off a cheap ball. It's not
good for you.
>> Oh, why did you never bring that up
anyways, Lord J? Why didn't you bring
that up when I went to his area life twice? PJ,
>> I was 5 minutes.
Can you give me
>> Remember you were saying you're proud of
me, Lord J. Proud of me?
>> Yeah, I'm Can you hear me?
>> Yeah, we can.
>> Okay, shut up for one minute. [laughter]
>> Both of you.
>> Let me just talk for one minute. Right.
I'm in London.
>> [ __ ] you.
>> Because I'm trying to talk and you don't
shut the [ __ ] up. Right. You're a punk.
>> [ __ ] you. Oh, he sound like a [ __ ] weirdo.
>> Right. Okay. Right. Guz,
buzz. Are you [ __ ] serious? [laughter]
[ __ ] me. You You You begged me. You
begged me. You begged me for gear the
other week [laughter] from London. So,
don't [ __ ] tell me.
>> You did. He said, "Uh, Mark, Mark,
please, please send me some decent gear
up into Belfast." You in Belfast,
>> is that real? >> Okay.
>> Okay. Okay.
Right. Can Can I ask one thing now?
Right. Let's sort this one thing out.
Right. Lord Jay, are you there? And PJ,
>> Oh, cool. You want to say what they said?
>> Right. BJ PJ
I am in Hatne
uh it is
6:52 say 7:00. Yeah. Right. I'm going to
meet you now tonight. So where do you
want to meet? I'm I'm going to go. [laughter]
>> I told you I told you I'll meet you.
>> Two clans could be next door to each
other and you're never going to meet.
>> You know what? Do me a favor, PJ. [ __ ]
this [ __ ] off. He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] weirdo.
Absolute [ __ ] weirdo. [laughter]
>> Get rid of that [ __ ] and I'll meet you. All right. [ __ ] weirdo.
What a strange man. What a strange man.
>> Okay. I'll beat you in school. >> Stuffford. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Where?
>> Anywhere you want. But the train station.
>> Get yours before it's
>> You mean Yeah. But the train station.
>> Okay. The Olympic Park.
>> Can I ask you a question if you don't mind? >> Yeah.
>> You know you're going to get [ __ ] battered.
>> You're not going to batter me, man. Not
Not a chance. Not a chance, mate. You're
an old man.
You are so what?
>> You're an old man.
>> You are so deluded. You're so deluded.
Okay. Right. Right. It's um Right.
Nearly seven. Yeah.
>> No. Steen Alward. He's not right because
I've tried meeting this guy.
>> I can't see your messages. Listen. Hey.
Oh, please let me speak. [ __ ] Why do
you speak over people so much?
Can I speak please PJ?
Thank you. Right. It's nearly 7. Yeah. >> Okay. It is
I really got out of Straford. We're back
in Stratford. You know the um I'll meet
you at I'll meet you in Olympic Park. They're
in Pig Park. >> Yeah.
>> Can't you just go one more stop to my land? >> No.
>> So, you're making me go to Straford to
meet you to beat you? I'm going to
[ __ ] rip I I swear to God, I'm going
to [ __ ] rip your head off your shoulders. [laughter]
>> Like, [ __ ] Will you?
>> Okay, let's go live. I can't go live, by
the way. [laughter]
LT, I spoke to LT. Let me finish. Let me
finish. Let me finish. Right. [laughter] Last night,
um LT said, "Oh, he he emailed me saying
I'll go live." I can't go live,
but you're live now, isn't you?
>> So, do me a favor. Stay live.
Stay live. I'm going to leave now. What?
Yeah, leave now. No,
>> you you you show me a video of you
leaving, then I would end this live
stream and leave. Simple. We know what
you're like, man. Come on.
>> What's my channel? [laughter]
>> We know this is We know what you're
like. Stop it.
>> You're laughing. Yeah. You're laughing. [laughter]
>> You something to laugh at this Mark. You know that
>> PJ my friend I'm
>> going to get myself sorted
by 7:00 I'm going to Stratford and you
know where he is. You know the um tell
me where to meet in Stratford.
I don't know that place where opposite.
Oh for [ __ ] sake. Grow up PJ. Where
are we meeting? I'm I'm going to fight
you right now.
Half an hour. I'm going to go there.
>> Olympic Park.
>> Yeah, the Olympic Park by by West
Stratford Station. Yeah. [laughter] >> Yeah.
>> Opposite that.
>> Yeah. You [ __ ] idiot. West Ham Stadium.
>> West Ham. >> Yeah.
>> Well, you know what? Oh, [ __ ] hell. Just
give me a [ __ ] postcode.
>> What do you mean give you a post? Okay.
Well, yeah, I was thinking that as well,
Dusty. Okay. Mryland station. Mryland station. Yeah.
>> [ __ ] Mland.
>> Uh, it's one stop after Stratford.
>> Oh, mate. Listen, I mean like
you know Bryland station. Do you know it?
>> Elizabeth live I don't go to [ __ ]
>> Oh gosh. You You guys You guys
PJ, can you hear me?
>> Dusty. I I lived 5 minutes away from
Midland Station. Albert, that's my
>> Dusty. Right. Listen, Dusty. Greasy.
your friends, the only people you have
in your life, right?
Can you just sort something out, please?
Can you sort something out? Where the
[ __ ] do you want to meet me right now
within half an hour? I'm going to be I
swear to God, I swear to God,
>> I'm going to film it. I'm filming it.
>> Mary stationary. Maybe then. [clears throat]
>> Yeah. What time? >> Now
you mean now? I'm [ __ ] at home.
>> Oh, this guy, bro. He I'm going to have
to kick him, bro. He's a waffler, bro.
He's a proper waffler.
Proper proper waffler, bro.
Bro, that guy is an idiot, bro.
Proper proper idiot, isn't it?
This guy is an idiot, bro.
You're on your way. You're not going anywhere.
This guy is so boring.
You're so [ __ ] boring.
>> One second. One second. What? What do
you mean we're not meeting each other?
I've actually tried to meet this guy
twice. What are you on about, bro?
>> You went to an area once and you were
saying, "Lord J, are you proud of me?"
>> I went to twice. I went to a park twice.
>> I don't know. I just remember you going
once saying that uh like you were asking
me was I proud of you for some weird reason.
>> And I remember there was a siren on in
the background and you ran down the
street screaming they're after me.
>> Yeah, cuz I thought people called the police.
>> Yeah. Anyway, Mark, if you're listening
in the background, if you still have my
phone number, if you message me, I'll
give you PJ's mom's address where he lives now
>> cuz he doesn't live in Straford anymore.
>> And he probably already knows it anyways.
>> Well, we're going to find out if he
messages me, then I'll give him your
mom's phone number and then he
>> he's not going to meet anyone anyways. So,
>> okay. I mean, I don't think he will, but
in case he is snipped enough gear that
he might want to, I'll give him your
mom's address. Then we'll go from there.
There we go.
Simple as that, bro.
Right, this guy's I'm trying to speak to
someone on Reddit and I've got this guy
talking utter [ __ ]
Utter utter utter [ __ ]
He talk so much [ __ ] bro.
I'm going to order some food soon, I think.
Is this [snorts] guy This guy is an idiot, bro. God.
Look, look, look.
>> Yeah. What? What we looking at?
What? What? What do you mean what I'm
looking at? I'm getting ready to [ __ ]
meet you at Straford.
>> Yeah. What?
You're sat down.
>> And when I get there, when I get there,
when I get there, you're going to say, "Oh,
blah, blah, blah. Are you going to meet
me or not? I'm not wasting my [ __ ]
time. You're a [ __ ] weirdo. You are
creep. You are a creep. You are actually
like the weirdest like man I've ever met
on YouTube or any online thing. Are you
going to meet me or not?
>> Yeah, I am.
>> Don't [ __ ] laugh with your weird
[ __ ] baby laugh. Yeah,
>> this guy is weird, bro. This guy is a
weirdo, man. I swear to God.
>> I'm a weirdo. I'm a weirdo. I'm a
You know what? You know what? Please, to
all your followers, three people,
1,000 people watcher,
two people watch you and respond to you
cuz you are full. You are so entertaining.
Yeah, PJ PJ. [laughter]
Oh, is it
>> I'll meet you. I'll meet you at Maryland Station.
>> Autistic love. Autistic love.
>> Autistic love. Mark, listen. You've been
acting hard on the internet for now for
5 years. You've not met no one.
>> Let me do [clears throat] me Let me do
you a favor. Let me do a favor.
>> Let me do you a favor.
I met the person that pushed the bin over. Go. What?
I have met anyone that calls me out. You
said to me, "Please don't interrupt me."
You come to an area, you piss,
you have a little laugh, you joke, you
do what you got to do in someone's area. Yeah. [laughter]
>> Doesn't even make sense, bro. I swear to
God, he's an idiot. It doesn't even make sense. Oh,
>> he got a very strange laugh. Okay.
Right. Listen, I go to Mike Tyson's finished. >> Yeah.
I go to Mike Tyson's area. Yeah.
Oh, meet me. Meet me. Meet me. And guess
what happens? Next day he wakes up. He's
going some little weirdo tried to meet
me. Yeah. [laughter]
Oh, bro. I swear you got to just laugh
at him in it.
>> Do you actually think you're like about
it or what?
>> I'm more about it than you'd ever be. Sunshine.
>> Sunshine. Okay. Well, okay. Where we
got? Where we got? Where we got? Um [cough] 7:00, right? [laughter]
I told you I'm in Maryland.
>> Maryland? Why you Why are you laughing?
Why are you like [laughter]
does this turn you on? >> No.
>> Is this Does it turn you on when you get
like a little bit angry with people?
Like you're I think you're like a
pedophile like a weirdo.
>> Honestly, look look
you the one you showing up. Wasn't you
the one who wasn't you up? Is he?
Do you want me to answer that? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Okay. I didn't shut up. Is he?
>> Yes, you did.
>> Yes, you can.
>> I spoke to him.
>> You have sexual.
>> Can you let me speak?
>> He was having sexual chats.
>> Can you let me speak? What are you doing?
>> Sexual chats. >> Yeah.
>> Okay. Peris Mark.
>> Yeah, I ba
have my Mark. Do you still have my phone number?
>> L. Um, what's your mom? >> Mark,
>> listen. Mark, I'll give you PJ's mom's
address. If you still have my phone
number, message me.
>> I am not going to [ __ ] Essics. All right.
>> Of course you're not. You're not going anywhere. [laughter]
You're full of cheap balls talking
absolute [ __ ] bollocks as usual. Why
are you still Why are you still [ __ ] lurking?
>> So yeah, why didn't you talk dirty to Izzy?
>> Because I want to explain to you what
happened, but you're not letting me
because you you keep interrupting me.
>> Do you want me to say it to you? >> Yeah.
>> Okay. I spoke to um he misses me, right?
Sorry, that's a lie. I me first. Yeah.
After you. Cuz you're a creep. You're
like a widow.
And then what happened after that was we
just spoke and then about a week went past.
Can you hear me?
>> Yeah. We're listening. I'm listening.
>> Yeah. And um I left it, ignored it,
whatever. And we spoke again and then
she phoned me and it come from um
[ __ ] What's it called? Yeah. Atlanta.
>> Oh, come over here.
>> I heard you. I heard you. You two have
done the business.
>> Yeah, we did. We did.
>> Yeah, we did. And you know what the
funny thing was? You know what the funny
>> That makes you the pedophile then, DOESN'T IT?
>> YEAH. AMAZING, MATE. You're amazing. Oh,
amazing. You're so clever. How old is she?
She was a lot younger than you, mate. A
lot younger than you. [laughter]
>> [ __ ] boy. [ __ ] weird.
>> Two questions, PJ. >> Yeah.
>> Right. Number one. When we mean tonight. >> Mland.
>> Mryland. Where the [ __ ] is Maryland?
>> In Stratford.
When? What time? Give me a time. I'll be there.
>> Right now.
>> Yeah. Right now. Right now. Give me time.
>> Yeah. Go on.
>> Yeah. Right. Show me. Right now. Give me time.
>> When you're leaving. Show me when you're
>> Well, then listen. Listen. If if Li Jay
or someone is watching, I I will film
the [ __ ] old thing. I'm
Why you laughing?
>> I find this all funny. Dusty to you. I
think it's funny.
>> Why are you dusty? You dusty greavesy,
your only [ __ ] friends on YouTube.
Yeah. PJ, I'm asking you straight out
now. What time will you be at Mary Land?
Wherever the [ __ ] that is. I'll find it.
I'll be there. What time? What time? [laughter]
>> When When you're there. when you're
>> No, no, no, no, no. It don't work like that.
>> It works like that.
>> Works like that with me. It works like
>> Right. 7:00 now. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Half eight.
>> Yeah. Meet me. Come on. Yeah, that's fine.
>> You won't meet me. I'm going to [ __ ]
I'm going to [ __ ] strip your head
from your [ __ ] shoulders, you [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Stop talking and and do it. Stop talking.
at Maryland station. >> Yeah.
>> Okay. I'm going to video it.
My journey. I'm going to be there. I'm
going to be walking you at Mary. I'll
meet you at Maryland.
>> And you know what? Let me ask you one
more thing. Yeah. >> Yes.
>> If you message or text your little
boyfriend. Yeah. You know what I'm talking about?
>> I smoked him last night. I spoke to him
last night and you know what? I got to
say one thing, right?
When I'm finished with you tonight, he's
going to [ __ ] [ __ ] Oh, you don't
even know, right? Mland.
>> Wait, you're going to you're going to what? >> Mland 8 >> tonight.
>> Why was you speaking to him?
>> Can we confirm?
>> Why would you speak half? Why was you speaking?
>> Half eight tonight. Can we confirm yes or no? >> Yes.
>> Yes. Yes. Right. Someone clip that. Yeah. [laughter]
>> Right. What was the other question?
>> Why you laughing?
>> Why was you speaking to L?
>> None of your business. Um
Lord Jay was the better one. He He has
his [ __ ] talk sense. That guy. You're
a [ __ ] weirdo.
>> Yeah. Just Just meet me. Just Just
leave. Stop talking [ __ ] and leave and I'll leave.
>> What do you mean leave? >> Leave.
>> Mland. You know what? Go one more stop
to Stratford. Is it got to be Maryland?
>> I'll beat you. I'll beat you. I'll beat you. Maryland.
>> Yeah. What time? Halfway. Yeah.
[singing and music]
>> Why are we laughing? Listen,
are you leaving or not? [music]
>> Hey, one minute.
>> I'm kicking him, bro. We're just going
round and around in circles and the
guy's not leaving, bro. I just kicked him.
[ __ ] hell, man.
This guy is so boring, bro. Is he
leaving or not, bro?
It's the same [ __ ] with this guy, bro.
Every every [ __ ] couple months.
Every couple months. >> Right.
>> Are you leaving or not?
>> Listen, Mryland is next to Stratford.
It's not even that far. I just Googled it.
>> Meet me. Meet me in Maryland. Oh, stop
[ __ ] stuttering, you [ __ ] I'm
meeting you there. I'm going to be
there. We've got our
>> You're a very weird looking bastard. [singing]
>> You really um 81.
>> Yeah. Really? You're in your 50s. You're
in your 50s in it. [singing] All
right. Do you want to?
>> Right. Truth or dare time. Truth or dare? Yeah.
>> Are you going to leave or not?
>> Mate, listen. Maryland is 33 minutes
away by car.
Someone is picking me up now. They're
going to drop me. They are going to drop me off
and film it. And by the way, can I say
one thing to you? Yeah,
>> I'm holding my phone with your left hand
and going to bat here with your right hand. >> Really?
>> Yeah. Really? But you know what's going
to happen? You're not going to turn up
again. You're going to say the same
thing with like
>> Mark, you never turn up. You've never
turned up anywhere.
>> Oh, don't make me laugh. PJ, listen.
Oh, PJ, you are talking B, right? You're talking.
>> That's me now.
>> No. Well, let's prove it tonight then. [laughter]
>> Yeah. Okay.
>> What do you mean?
>> Is that Lord Jay there? No, it's not.
It's me. Sorry. Okay. Sorry. My
apologies. Right. Okay. I'm going.
Right. Half past 8 Maryland station.
Wear pads, mate.
>> It's outside the station.
>> Perfect. Are you going to call LT?
>> No, I I don't like LT. You know this.
>> No, I don't know this. What I know is
>> you do know this cuz you seen the cool.
>> Can I Can I just say something? Cuz I'm
recording this. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Do you mind if I say this? >> Yeah.
>> The he he he he laugh. Yeah, I'm
recording this. You called me out. Me
and you, manto man are going to meet at
Maryland station in 1 hour
and 14 minutes. Yeah. Where weapons at
their station? No. No. Don't do the he
he [ __ ] Where's at their station? Do you agree?
Where weapons? Yeah.
It's agreed with both of us.
>> Yes or no? >> Yes.
>> Leave and stop going on.
>> Just leave. Just leave.
>> Stop stuttering. My content for my content.
>> Answer my content.
>> Oh my god. Just shut up and leave
when I b
that would never happen. But yeah.
>> Are you serious? It was Mark. I was in
your area twice in the park. You did not
come out once.
>> Yeah. Well done. Well done. Well done.
>> Stop making You're saying
>> Let me speak for Let me speak.
>> Stop talking and leave. You should be on your way.
>> For half an hour.
>> You should be on your way now.
>> You should be on your way.
>> Leave. Let me speak.
>> No, you should be on your way. Stop talking.
>> I said something wrong.
>> No, you should be on your way. No, you
can't. No. or it I can't say something. Can I
>> No, you can't talk. No, leave the house
and get on your way. We've heard enough
of your [ __ ]
>> We get on your way. I'm getting We've
heard enough of your We've heard enough
of your [ __ ] Mark Simpson.
>> It's Samson.
>> No, Simpson.
>> No, it's Simpson. You're one of the Simpsons.
>> You look like a [ __ ] home.
>> I'm wasting my [ __ ] time moving you.
You're not going to turn up. You're not
going to turn up,
>> mate. Just leave now and you'll see who
will turn up. Stop making excuses and leave. Simple.
>> Yeah, which I'm going to do. But another one minute
>> before I leave.
>> No, just leave.
>> And then how how am I going to prove
that I'm there and you're going to [ __ ]
cut off like you normally do? You're you
in a really [ __ ] creep in the world.
>> See See, he just wants to talk. He just
He's a talker. He's a talker, man.
>> Talker. I'm a talker. Yeah,
>> he's a talker.
>> I'm a talker. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. How far Mland? Yeah.
>> Yeah. Leave.
>> Let's see what happens.
>> If you don't leave in the next minute,
I'm blocking you and I'm not letting you in.
>> I'm not.
>> So, you're going to leave or
>> I'm leaving. I'm leaving. What? Just >> No.
>> Yeah. Turn me off this thing.
>> No. Leave.
>> I'm going to pick you up in a minute.
>> I'm leaving. I'm leaving. I'm leaving to meet you.
>> Leave and stop talking and leave.
>> Yeah, but I'm going to have to turn this
[ __ ] stream thing off.
>> Just leave. Stop talking and leave.
>> Deal. You know what's going to happen?
>> Yeah. You're going to you're going
[clears throat] to look a [ __ ] fool
when you don't turn up. Okay. Yeah.
Yeah. See you soon.
>> [ __ ] prick. >> Yeah.
The guy is not going nowhere, mate. He's
a talker, bro. Anyone who's new. Yeah.
He's done this about 50 times.
Anyone who's new, he's done this about
50 times. [laughter]
He's an embarrassment. Why does he do
this, bro? Why? Why does he do this?
Like the guy gets panic attacks and
anxiety and he's come and he's coming on
here doing this embarrassing, bro.
[ __ ] mad, bro. No, he's not showing
up, bro. I've done this I've done this
with this guy for years, bro.
So, nah. When he shows me him leaving,
I'll leave. Simple as that. He's not
leaving, bro. He's all talk. I'm not
doing this. I'm not going around in
circles with these people, bro. I've
already got the W. I don't need another
Ah, [groaning] my brain, bro.
No, bro. When he shows he's left, yeah,
when he shows he's out on the road, I'm
leaving, bro. Simple. Until then,
[ __ ] I'm not I'm not I'm put the
link back up as well. So he can't say,
"Oh, you did let me in."
Duping me, eh? Yeah, man. Yeah.
Chase, listen. I'll be coming back to
Cardiff soon anyways, lad. So, you can
say all of this stuff to my face.
Yeah, man. You can say all of this stuff
when I'm in Cardiff. I'll be coming back
to Wales soon anyways, lad. You can say
all of this stuff to my face. Yeah,
I've already gone to his area two times.
I don't need to go anywhere. If he
proves to me he's on his way, I will.
Again, biased. This is what I mean with
bi Oh [ __ ] This is what I mean with
people being biased again. I've already
gone to his area two times live. I've
already won against him.
The [ __ ] bro. Again, Mr. biased.
Anyways, we're moving on from this clown
anyways until he shows he's he's he's
going anywhere. But yeah, Chase, you're
not you don't bother no one, lad,
because I'll be going carding soon anyways.
Like I said,
what should I have for my dinner?
Let's have a look.
I'm not going nowhere, mate. I've
already been to your city enough times,
lad. I've already been to your city
enough times, Jason. You've not shown up.
Yeah. Sorry, man, but you are biased. I
won't say it again, but you are. >> Hey. >> Yeah.
>> So, are you going to meet Mark tonight then? >> What?
Yeah. When he shows me he's leaving,
I'll leave. Yeah.
>> What do you mean show he's leaving?
Might show him walking out of the house. >> Yeah.
>> So there
>> joins the panel as he's leaving the
house. You're going to go to Warriors
meeting in Maryland Station.
>> Why do you sound nervous?
>> No, I'm not nervous. You're the one that's nervous.
>> Why would I be nervous? >> No.
>> Why would I be nervous? The guy doesn't
show up anywhere. You turn me nervous.
>> Why did you turn in the timler? >> No,
>> you do sound a bit nervous.
>> You were doing that.
>> The only one that's nervous is you, lad.
Not me. Why? Scared of what?
>> I be nervous. No one's Why would I be nervous?
>> There's none of you who's brave enough
to come to Belfast. Why would I be nervous?
>> Brave enough to Why would anyone go to Belfast?
>> Yeah, but then why would I be nervous?
Why would I be nervous when this guy
doesn't show up anywhere?
>> Because if Arsenal Mark leaves his
house, it means he's obviously on his way.
>> Yeah, but he's not going to, so why be nervous?
>> Mark just joined the panel and shows
just walking out of your house.
>> Then PJ is live and on his way there.
>> Oh, this is so boring, bro.
>> You know this is you know this is 2026, isn't it?
>> Yeah. You're still And you're still
doing this [ __ ] Oh,
>> I'm not doing anything. I'm not meeting you.
>> You know I'm still doing the same [ __ ]
in 2026. What the [ __ ] man?
>> He just sent me a message there saying
he's on his way.
>> Yeah, tell him to come and show us then.
>> Yeah, hold on. Right. Hold on.
>> There you got blocked. [laughter]
>> Listen, Chase, you and your boyfriend
bottled it from a fight, lad. Yeah, man.
And you're banned. See you later.
No virgins on my channel, Chase. It's a
no virgin zone. We don't have virgins here.
We don't have virgins that only target
disabled dwars. This has no policy.
That's the policy, lad.
Seriously, Chase, I know he's your
boyfriend and all. He's your boyfriend,
but sorry, lad.
No virgins. It's a strict policy.
No virgins and no skin people.
Sorry, lad. Love to let more people in,
but that's just the way it is. I don't
make the rules. Ask Grezy.
Um, who's my boyfriend? Can you
elaborate by saying the name? Yes, the virgin.
That's his name. See you later, lad. Um,
see you later, lad. Anyways, Mark, um,
what are we doing, lad?
I don't know why this guy does this,
bro. Really? He's never ever ever Oh,
[snorts] I need to get a drink.
Oh, I did get the same one, didn't I? No.
Can you Can you say by his name? Yeah.
The skin version. [laughter]
That's his name. All right. Tell me that
was a good one, isn't it? [clears throat]
Right. I'm going to wait for this guy
before I order this um food
cuz I don't have any excuses, lad.
You're not coming in your skin, virgin.
You're banned. Nice try.
[sighs and gasps]
Yeah, you're not coming in your skin,
virgin. Bye-bye. Hey, hurry up, bro,
before I order this food. Lad,
so bloody expensive now. holding these bloody takeaways.
All right. Right. I'm waiting.
>> Yeah. I told him uh to join. So he start
he was texting me here. So he says he's joining.
>> Yeah. You better do otherwise I'm going
to order this takeaway.
>> Well, how long are you giving him, man?
>> Like a while. 20 minutes.
>> Why have you in that voice again?
>> Because I like it. >> Yeah.
>> So why don't you play Why don't you do
any gambling videos anymore? Is it cuz
you've gone skin?
>> Uh, we're not friends, so I wouldn't ask
answer any questions from a na like you.
>> Oh, you you're calling you're calling me
a na? Didn't you hang around with a na mustard?
>> Again, biasness.
Come on, bro. No, I'm going to give him
some time. Don't worry, bro.
Bro, anyone I assume there's a lot of
people in here that's new here. I can
only assume. So basically what this guy
does is whenever he's had a drink or
well in East case does drugs he will oh [ __ ]
he will um
basically act a hard man. This is what
he does. So I assume there's a lot of
people new on this community that
doesn't uh know what this guy does.
Yeah. And then he just gives it the big basically.
He's been doing it for years. He's been
Um, absolutely. Yes. He doesn't meet
anyone. I've gone to his area twice
live for 3 hours. He's not shown up. Uh,
I done it on a Friday and I think I done
it on a Saturday. It was a Sunday. It
was two days. Did not show up. He's He's
been doing it for years. This guy has
literally been doing it for years.
Absolutely years. And he's never met
anyone like unlike me. He's literally
never met anyone. So yeah,
I don't know why he does it to be honest.
Sad, sad, sad [ __ ]
You're banned. See you later. The only
one living under poverty is yourself.
See you later, lad. You got yourself
banned. Anyways, Mark,
I feel like I've changed, you know,
since it hit 2026. I've noticed that I
don't even react to these people anymore
cuz they're just self they're just self
projectors in it. So I don't I don't
they don't get me angry, bro. These people
they're very predictable as well.
I'm still waiting. [applause]
What's going on, bro?
It's always the same [ __ ] bro, with
these with these people on here, man.
It's always the same people.
It's always the same [ __ ] It's always
the same [ __ ] with him, bro. Mark
[ __ ] Virgin Boy. It's always the same
[ __ ] with him, lad. Every single one of
them. Every single one of them, bro.
It's always the same [ __ ] with them, bro.
I'm going to order some food in a bit, bro,
cuz I'm hungry. So,
I know, bro.
All but seriously. Yeah. Steven Alier on
a real yeah me, you, Greavves, and a
couple of others. I am actually going to
make a new live account like going live
and that bro. And it's just going to be
us and none of these other people.
I don't want anyone else like I'm being
deadly serious, bro. Like serious
serious. Like it's okay for today and
that, but like I can give you my email
and that, bro. And we're going to have
to set up like a whole another thing cuz
I don't want these weirdos watching me.
I don't want them recording me. I don't
want to have to keep blocking accounts.
So, even if it's just 10 genuine people,
bro, I'd rather it. No, seriously, I'm
being deadly serious, bro. I mentioned
this earlier. Seriously.
Nah, Greavvesy won't tell you. Grievesy
doesn't tell anyone anything unless I
say it's okay. That training video, he
weren't going to tell anyone, but I just
said, "Oh, you know what? Just tell
everyone." No, he won't. He won't.
Trust me, bro. It's better. I don't want
these weirdos watching me
like the skid virgin and all of them
people. I don't want them following me
about I don't want them watching me. So
I am actually going to make like a whole
different um live channel, bro.
It might even be my approaching ones.
I don't want them watching me, bro.
Serious. No, seriously. Seriously,
seriously, bro. There's too many grasses
on this community. There's too many
stalkers. I'm deadly serious, bro. This
time I really Cuz
there would be no Mark today. There'd be
no Virgin boy today if I had already
done this. Do you get me? So yeah.
How I'm going to do it, I'm not sure.
me. You greasy
other people. Lad,
bro, I rarely gamble. What you talking about?
When was the last time I went out?
A long time ago.
Yeah. Yeah. I was deadly serious about
stop going out and I haven't gone out. I
went out Monday cuz I was playing pool
when I had a couple of drinks. I didn't
plan it. Yeah, I haven't been on a night
out for months.
Yeah, good, bro. They could go. Yeah,
they good. Good. That's a good thing,
mate. I've not been on a night out for months.
So, yeah, I didn't go out New Year's
Eve. Didn't go out Boxing Day. Didn't go
out for months.
So, yeah, I was serious about that. Yeah.
You won't find me, lad. You was never
able to find my channel with the approaches.
The only reason you found it is cuz I
linked it by accident.
Oh, you had Nandos, man. Lucky bastard.
I'm going to get a curry in a bit.
Yeah, I'm getting a curry in a bit, lad.
Yeah. Every time I go Nando, I just get
a whole chicken and rice, bro. Just yam it down.
Yeah, that's what will happen. Yeah.
Yeah. I think I'm going to do that, bro. 100%.
Oh, you [ __ ] Yeah,
that way they can't find you. You will
never find me, bro. You never found my
approaching channel. The only reason you
got it is cuz I linked it by accident.
You can't find me, bro. You won't find me.
Yeah, Bryan's nice, bro. Chicken ticker
biryani. I tell you, the best biryani
Yeah. is a homemade one made by people
that could do it. Yeah. I used to have
tenants, bro, and they used to they used
to cook the biryani. Oh, it was another
level. Oh, it was so good, bro. It was
so good. You'd eat it and then you just
fall asleep like a chicken ticker.
Sometimes it was lamb. Oh, with jalapenos.
I'm I'm leaving. When he when he shows
me he's leaving, I will leave.
Simple as that. When he's proved to me
that he's left, I will leave. Simple.
Because I know what he's doing, bro.
He's not going anywhere. It's the same
[ __ ] with this guy. It's the same [ __ ] different year.
It's the same [ __ ] with this guy, bro.
Wait a little bit. [snorts] Yeah.
He's an idiot, man.
Why is he talking about LT as well? Why
does he keep bringing LT up when I've
gone to meet him by myself two times and
he knows I literally don't like LT? So,
why is he Why does he keep using LT as
an excuse? He's such a cow with this guy, bro.
He always uses LT as an excuse to get
out of things. Have you noticed that?
He's always used that as an excuse. Uh
LT, bro, it's embarrassing, bro.
[ __ ] so embarrassing.
He is. Oh yeah. Yep. He's doing it
again, bro. You missed it. He come on a Hangouts. Yeah.
Again. Again, bro. Again. Again. Yep.
You sure is. Mhm.
He's pathetic, bro. Pathetic.
Anyways, let me put another link up. No, no. What?
Is this guy coming or Oh.
Oh, [ __ ] thing is live. One sec.
Right. Here we go. Still here. [sighs] Still waiting.
L show trainers or skin. I just nipped
on to L J's. Bro, it's literally just
the same talking, isn't it? The same repeating people.
What the [ __ ] did they just say? L show
trainers or skin. It's just the same
talking, the same people. Have you
noticed that, Dusty?
Yeah, I read a comment here. LT's email
to PJ was ruthless tiger planting your
big nose into a dirty mattress. Yeah,
but that's not what happened, was it? I
slipped. That's not what happened,
though, is it?
But yeah, funny thing to say,
it's the same talking. If you go on the
channel, Dusty. Yeah, it's the same
people doing the same talking, lad. and
I'm still waiting. >> [sighs]
>> Yeah, I'm still waiting, lad.
He's still not left, has he? No.
Go J. Go Lord. >> [laughter]
>> uh Alra, I've already shown up about it,
lad. I'll repeat myself for the third
time. I've gone to his area twice live
and he didn't show up. I've already
proved that I'm about I'm about it. I
don't need to prove anything to anyone.
I don't need to prove anything to anyone, lad.
Just have to make you uh correct on one
thing. A, I've already gone to his area
twice and he's not shown up when I was
live for several hours. And B, I don't
need to prove anything to anyone.
So, I don't need to prove anything to
anyone. I I when he shows me him
leaving, I'm going to go and meet him. I
said I was going. I don't need to prove
myself to anyone. Otherwise, I'd be
doing that every day. I don't need to
prove anything. I've already proved that
I've gone out and he's not shown up. So, yeah.
Bro, he he does these fake call out or
you already know what he does. He just J
just I've gone to the guy's area twice.
He's not shown up. So when he's proved
that he's meeting,
I'm going to give him 10 minutes. If he
if he doesn't come in 10 minutes, I'm
ordering my food. So
yeah, I'm going to give him 10 minutes
now. Already been enough time, lad. Yeah.
Put the link up them. Oh [ __ ]
I'm going to get slapped up by you. Okay, lad.
What? By an alcoholic that's not even
leaving his house. Yeah, I don't think so. [sighs]
You a proper boring on this community in
it, bro. Especially Mark, right?
I said I'll give him 10 minutes. Yep.
Cuz once I order this food, I don't care
what you're doing, bro. Simple.
Yeah. He's leaving soon. Well, he's got 10 minutes.
cuz I'll be ordering food. I'm on top
order food. I'm not going back out. So,
yeah. And he's not showing up anywhere
anyways. I don't even know why we're
having this conversation. The guy's not
showing up anywhere.
He's not showing up nowhere, man.
Probably going to get an Indian to be fair.
Give it some more time. Yeah.
Waiting. Waiting. Waiting.
I don't know why this guy does this.
You get a chicken coma. [ __ ] off.
[ __ ] you. Get Yeah, I'm watching it
right now, bro. I'm watching it.
See what I mean? You see what I mean,
bro? I'm watching it. I'm watching it.
Don't worry. I'm watching it, bro. [laughter]
The government went prison. What did the
go to prison for? No, he never >> [laughter]
>> The GV. Do you not remember the guy from
you? Oh, it was before your time, Steven
Howard. It was before your time, lad. >> [laughter]
>> This guy's a [ __ ] idiot, bro.
He's not leaving anywhere, bro. Right.
It's B. It's [ __ ] bro.
I'm going to order this food in a minute, bro. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, [ __ ] this, bro. I'm giving it
until 8 and I'm delete and then I'm ordering it. Yeah.
No, I'm going to give it until 8. This
guy had more than he had like half an
hour, bro, to leave.
No, I'm going to give it five minutes.
I'm going to give it four minutes, bro.
So, this guy don't have any more. He's
likes to use excuses, you know. [laughter]
There always excuses with this gun, you know.
[ __ ] pair of [ __ ]
now. Next time next time he comes on.
Yeah, we just ignore him in it from
tomorrow, bro. If he comes back on, we
just ignore we just ignore him. Is it Steven Howard?
We just ignore him in it.
I'm going to get Indian lad.
Yeah, I'm just going to get um I'm just
going to get Indian. I know I said I wasn't, but um
what did you say? Um,
What did you say about um people on
here? Are they Are they Are they Are
they um nonsleg simps? Steven Howard,
who's a nonsleg simple? Why not?
I don't know, bro. One second. Right.
Let me I'm going to order from somewhere
I've not ordered before. Oh, chicken coma.
Yeah, that's nice, bro. Yep.
I want to order one I've never ordered from before.
Yeah, that shocked me with LT, bro. I
thought LT was all right.
I thought he was a good [ __ ] but no.
Lamb Rogan Josh
Lamb address lamb ka that
they don't have a vineloo.
Why don't they have vindaloo here?
They don't have vindaloo here.
I'll just get a dress. [ __ ] it. >> Strange.
Need to get I'm going to ask Laney if
she wants anything.
250 for a [ __ ] coke.
Take a lamad dress pillow rice coke. What?
That's the madness, bro. [snorts]
Better be normal coke as well. It better be.
Yeah, my dress is is good enough.
>> [clears throat]
>> Laney doesn't want anything. The uh
onion bar. Yeah, it comes up here. I'm
not getting that. I'm just going to get
an address. did enough in it.
So expensive these takeaways, bro.
I need to cut down on him. Really?
I really need to cut down on these takeaways, lad.
Really bad for you.
Nah, she said she didn't want nothing, bro. So,
that's [snorts] that in it.
Oh, it's cold, isn't it?
I think I'm going to put my dressing gown on.
I take my B Simpson top off.
>> [sighs and gasps] >> Uh,
I thought you liked LT me.
Yeah, I thought you liked LT.
Even I would [clears throat] Luke.
>> [clears throat]
>> order some lost food.
Yeah, I'm I'm staying in there now anyways.
>> Oh, they're virgin now's life.
>> Jimmy, the only virgin is you, lad.
>> No, bro. You're the one who goes on
about women breaking your heart. Don't
break my heart. My achy achy [laughter]
heart. But I can't get over you. Go on, mate.
>> You know, you know what? You do you know
what year we're in?
>> What year in? Yeah. 2026. So what's that
got to do with the cost of her being you
being you being a virgin?
>> It's because it's time to stop
projecting your virginity on the wall
projecting. You're the one who comes on
YouTube and go these people got no
money. These people are all skit. These
people you live with your [ __ ] mom.
>> I think you should get yourself a part-time job.
>> I've got one broke. It's called a
full-time one. You should try to preach in it.
>> You give yourself a little part-time job.
>> Anyway, when you get When are you going
to get laid?
>> Uh, never, bro.
>> I think that's true. Actually, at least
you're speaking the truth.
>> When are you When are you going to get
When are you going to get your first kiss?
>> I had that about 25 years ago. Peter,
>> your Timmy, your mother doesn't count. Come on.
>> Oh, Peter, that's a little bit harsh,
isn't it? How do you know I've kissed my mom?
Anyway, Pete, anyway, Pete, can I ask
you a question? I was watching one of
your videos the other day. Why did you
ask for a refund from a bottle of wine?
You got rejected by an Australian chick.
Or was it was it Italian or one of them
or or or Polish? I don't know. I'm
autistic. But, you know, you lie that
you say you haven't got autism. You have
got autism. If you haven't got autism,
I'm going to come down and give you a
good kicking because you've offending
people with autism like me. So, I
>> Well, Timmy, come and do it then.
>> I will, Peter. I will, Peter. And you'll run away
and and you'll get owned again by running away.
>> I think you were tiger together.
>> Peter, you couldn't beat yourself out of
wet paper bag. You [ __ ] you. Okay.
It's like Peter in 2025.
>> Let's have a serious chat. Tell you
heard this in 2025. And you were like,
"You broke don't do that. You don't do
that." You get stuck IN AND GO, "YEAH."
>> Anyone else? Anyone else falling asleep?
>> No, you're not falling asleep. Do you
know what they used to? You know, they
caught the fight with you in boring me.
You're very boring.
>> So, so are you. Oh, I'm not a virgin.
Oh, I've got money. Oh, I live in my
mom's box room. Okay,
>> Timmy. When are you going to stop this, man?
>> When are you going to [ __ ] get laid
and grow up and stop crying on YouTube
for 4 hours a day?
>> Jimmy, I've I've shown me getting I've
shown me getting a [ __ ] on YouTube,
bro. How can you show getting a [ __ ]
on YouTube when it's against YouTube's
terms and conditions to do pornography?
That don't make any sense.
>> Uh because it got banned a minute after
me putting it up there, but everyone saw it.
>> So So everyone seen it within one
minute. So you're telling me everybody
>> Everyone Everyone saw it. Yeah, everyone
saw it. Well, I'll send it to you. Well,
if you give me YOUR NUMBER IF YOU GIVE
ME YOUR NUMBER, I'll send it to you.
>> I'll send you What the [ __ ] bro?
>> What the [ __ ] is you?
>> I think you need to calm down, man.
I think you need [laughter]
>> I think you need to I think you need to
calm down, lad.
>> I think you need to get [ __ ] live and
stop self. Timmy, you're the one. Timmy,
you're the one that's the virgin, not me.
>> You know, everyone, you know, when
you're saying that, everyone's laughing
at you. You're not You're not
laugh. The only one that's a virgin is
you. So, you're just making yourself
look silly now.
>> Have you got the evidence? Have you got
the evidence, Pete? I'm a virgin. Yes, I
do have the evidence. I do. I have the
evidence when two women when two women
went around you before and you started bluffing.
>> Yeah. You started blushing to me.
>> So that so that's evidence. Yeah. >> Yes.
Yeah. Anyway, Peter, I'm glad to hear
that you're not playing pub roulette cuz
it's the most bent roulette in the planet
>> mate. Online roulette is fixed.
>> It's all bricks, mate. The whole
industry's gone. Have you ever heard that?
>> Did you s Did you see my roulette video
the other day? You cited it?
>> Yes, I downloaded. I'm going to upload
it. It's mine. I'm going to say man on
pip and his bollocks and his
>> So why did it kept go? Why did it kept
going on my news and numbers to me? It
kept missing numbers
>> because PJ, right? If it's a Magnum
roulette, let me hear me out. If it's if
the roulette is air, right, they can put
enough air to miss you. You do know
that, don't you?
>> Yeah, but you didn't watch the video I
made, did you?
>> I've got a call coming in right there.
I've just canled it. Go on, mate. What you saying?
>> Yeah, but you Yeah, but you didn't watch
the video that I put the other day, did you?
>> Yes, I did. You hit [ __ ] 17 and then
it [ __ ] landed on [ __ ] was it um
not number four at 19 and it land on it
you took me£100 £115 spin and it fed you [laughter]
like that it looks for what you ain't
got in it.
>> Well, I've got 15 PJ I've been I've done
an £800 spin this month in the casino.
>> No, you bloody didn't.
>> Oh, yes I did.
>> Did it win? I just said it lost. I felt sick. And
>> where did you get £800?
>> PJ, I'm not telling you where I get my
money from, mate. I don't All you All
you need to know is me and Smokey Beer
doing well in life as you're living in
your mom's box room moaning over trolls.
>> You don't have £800 your name.
>> Where's the evidence, PJ? Where's the evidence?
>> You didn't do PJ, you can listen to your
trolls as much as you want because you
believe anything what tells you. You
believe in [laughter] so many
if if Harry Fraud told you that the sky
is purple, you'd believe it. PJ,
>> I don't talk to Harry F. So,
>> but he's he's on your chat constantly
giving you advice.
>> I don't f lad. So,
>> what what's your views on Harry Ford?
>> I think he's a [ __ ]
>> Do you think he's a skimp bold [ __ ] scouser?
>> I think he's a bit of a virgin like you.
>> You know, he lives with his mom like you.
No, I didn't know that, man. Well, he's
a smart guy then, isn't he? Saving all
that money living with his parents. What
a smart man.
>> But he's got 10 grand and you've got [ __ ] all.
>> That's good then. I've got more money
than you, Timmy.
>> No, you haven't, PJ.
>> Timmy, my Lego that I bought the other
day cost more than what you've got now.
>> Wow. So, how much is your Lego, PJ?
Let's have a CR. >> £300.
>> 40 quid.
>> And you think I haven't got 40 quid? You
>> How much do you have now then?
>> 9 million. Mhm. >> No.
>> No. Seriously, how much you have?
>> Do you think I'm going to be telling you that, Peter?
>> Just say Just say a roundabout.
>> Put it this way, Peter. I've got more in
my bank account than what you get from
DWP per year.
>> No, you [ __ ] don't me.
>> And you know, I'm freaked out. Anyway,
can I ask you a question? Serious
question. Why is Albert Square been
boarded up? Because I wanted it to be boarded up.
Why don't you mind your own business?
Oh, he left.
[ __ ] lies. Why does this guy lie
about everything? £800 spin. He's never
done an £800 spin in his life. He's such
a liar, bro. What the [ __ ]
I'm waiting for this food to come, bro.
[ __ ] hungry, lad.
I hope it's the real Coke and not the fake coke
cuz that would be [ __ ] in it.
[clears throat] Do you reckon Monty man
will ever go live again? No. Um, Indian bro.
Do you reckon Monty's going to go live again? Ever?
Can't imagine it, bro.
All right. Do you know Do you want to
know why I emailed LC?
I emailed him at 4:37. Yeah. Today I
said, "How comes you keep white knight
in non-legs every time I call him a
virgin?" Question mark question mark
question mark. Is he your boyfriend or
something? when he's calling me a
virgin, why don't you talk about the
[ __ ] and sig, etc., you fanny. And I
said, you're biased little fanny. And he
and he didn't reply back.
Didn't reply back, lad.
Did you like that email, Steven Howard?
Did you like that little email? What? [snorts]
Can't wait to have this food. Steven Howard, lad. Oh.
What's up, bro? [laughter]
Yeah, he hasn't. Yeah, he hasn't replied
back. I don't know why he white.
Why is he white lighting another man?
That is That is weird.
Why is he white?
I should have said no. I think I did say
it. I did say to him why you defended
him and I think I did say it, man.
But I didn't put it that way cuz I
couldn't think of an answer quick enough.
I said, "Why did you talk about the
19year-old? Why didn't you talk about this?"
Imagine white in a man, bro. That is embarrassing, bro.
And don't even try and say that you're
you're you see it how you see it because
you don't see it how you see it, lad.
Because if you saw it how you saw it,
you would have a lot to say about me.
You'd have a lot to say about the women
that I've been with. Simple. [sighs]
[snorts] Yeah. It's weird, bro.
Yeah, there is no real answer. The white knight.
If if if someone can call me a virgin,
someone that's been with all of them
women, why can't I call someone with a
girlfriend a virgin? What's what's the answer?
Yeah. What's What's the answer to that?
What's the answer to that? There's no
answer. There is literally no answer.
What can you really say?
>> So weird, bro. It's so weird. Yeah,
mama. Mama, just waiting for this food now. Bro,
I feel like I've got bigger, you know, Steven Howard
feel like I've got taller even though
you do stop growing at a certain age. I
don't know. I feel like bigger and taller
for some reason.
H must be all the piggies I eat. Yeah,
I'm about 510, you know, bro.
Yeah, I'm about 510. I don't know how
tall you are.
Don't tell LT that, bro. He'll start
getting mad. He's got a height complex.
Don't tell him that you're that you're 510, bro.
I'm about 510. Yeah.
Pretty sure, bro. Either 5'9 and a half or 510.
Sure. It's 510 now, though. Someone I
know is 5'9 and I'm taller than them. So,
Yeah, the guy didn't leave as we knew he wouldn't.
Well, he's not leaving. So, no, I'm not
ready. I've just ordered some food.
Oh, who's that?
>> Oh, there Pete. How's it going? Sorry,
bro. I had to take a phone call. The M phones.
>> So, yeah. I've I've got a problem with
LT, man. What's he done now?
>> He's just I just find him very biased to me.
>> Well, I watched your video and to be
honest you LT has given you some sound
advice. You two fell out overnight. I
don't get this
>> because because he was he's being biased.
>> What do you mean he's being biased? Explain.
>> I'm not explaining it again, bro. I've
already explained it multiple times.
>> Well, I can't watch a 14minute video.
You going about LT? 3 minutes is enough
and I get heart bleed.
>> Well, it's not important enough, is it?
But he's just biased as well. That's it.
>> Basically, him saying that you're you're
Pakistan and saying that you're useless
and you live with your mom and all this
and all that.
>> Nah, bro.
>> That's what being is.
>> He say he said you got a small penis. >> No.
>> Did he say that you're an autistic fix plastic?
>> No. You suffer with anxiety to me. Is it?
>> I suffer from autism, Peter. But I'm not
a liar like you. I don't give a [ __ ]
what people think. If people want to
bully me like Winchester and that I've
got autism, my day still goes on. I'm
autistic. Not ashamed of it. I was born
that way. I've got no shame for what I
do on here. If Dibos can't handle it,
come and meet me and I'll spit in your face.
>> I am not I I [laughter] am I'm not like
you, Peter. I don't explain myself to no
one. And I mean no one.
>> Timmy, you should quit gambling this year,
>> bro. I'm not gambling at the moment. Do
you realize I've lost two?
>> Did you see Did you see Did you see the
football better one?
>> Yes, Peter. I thought you should have
got more. I think you should have got
>> I should have because it's because the
odds are [ __ ] now in it
>> because the gambling industry I've had
this chat with you many times.
>> I know. You don't need to explain it. I
know it's finished. I know. I know it's
finished. I already know this.
>> Right. They've turned the APR down on
the pub machines, which is basically the
percentage, right? King Konger, you
could used to do well on that four years
ago and it got worse and worse and worse
and now it's diabolical, right? Even I
mean I've noticed no one plays pub
machines anymore because pub machines
the days have gone now, right? I only go
around and play old blueprints now which
is the old 2016 ones with the cracking
and Patty's payday and all them because
these new ones are shight [snorts] as
[ __ ] I put 600 quid in one day. And I
got bonus on Fishing Frenzy,12.
And then I got a bonus for eight quid.
Then I got a bonus for [ __ ] 35. Then
I got one for 49.
>> You know what annoys me? Oh, do you know
what annoys me? Yeah. You don't listen.
You know, you know the bar roulette in
the bookies. One second. Yeah. What?
What? I don't understand. Listen. Yeah.
He gives you
>> He gives you a 20 spin and it cost 20 to
get the next spin. What's the point of
them giving you a win to take it back off?
>> What you on about? I put in the other
day in that bar roulette in the pub one.
Right. And I' I'm going to when I in
February because I ain't got to edit the
videos at the moment. I've got a bad
losing video going up in February
because I've already edited like
December's video for January and you'll
see on that one. But you'll see how big
these pub machines are, mate.
>> No, but you know the bookies. Listen,
the bookies. Yeah.
>> It gives you a win and it takes it back
trying to get the next spin on a bar
roulette. You get it?
>> Because Yes. Because P I mean PP PJ
they've lowered the at the ATR I think
it's called. I don't know what it's
called at the top of my hand. They've
lowered the percentages. Why blueprints
are up to something illegal. Xinox is up
to something illegal. And the um the
what they call Xoxes the the what's it
called? Prismatics. They're up to
something because I don't know if you
watch Bucket's live stream he put over£700
in without one premium spin. when I saw that.
>> No, he did. If you go back on [ __ ]
Bucket uh channel, right, the live stream, right,
>> watch real talk. Watch the end bit. If
you still got the stream up, the end
bit, he put £740
and I think it was about one premium
spin. Real talk.
>> Timmy, you're going to die. You're going
to die over YouTube one day. Peter, I'm
not the one who does [ __ ] 10our
streams moaning about bomb, moaning
about [ __ ] this money. I laugh at
this, right? Because I tell you why I
laugh at you. I laugh at you all how
[ __ ] childish you are.
>> Yeah, but you like it.
>> Like what? How childish you are. I find
it funny that grown men act like
spastics. Yeah, I have to admit.
>> What are you having for dinner today, Timmy?
>> Stir fry.
>> Well, you cook it.
>> I'm just cooking it now. I'm going down
the pub for a few after. But but but
[laughter] the thing is Pete, right?
There's no there's no point there's no
point me telling you this because you
ain't going to listen. Every time you
tell that someone's skin that someone's
got no family and all this and all that,
the troll is laughing at you. Right. The
best way to defeat a troll is silence.
You do know that, don't you?
>> Yeah. But Timmy, you react to these people.
>> I don't react. I've been in the
background for three weeks and I've read
all the rumors. I've been arrested. I'm
racist and all this. And I laugh at it, Peter. I
>> Wait, no. You lost all that money,
Smokey B. [ __ ] off. Wait, [laughter]
that that that money. One second. That
money that you the money that you won
that what the thing that you put up, you
want you lost all that money?
>> What the [ __ ] [laughter]
>> [ __ ] hell. Why do you What? What? Can
I ask you a serious question? Why are you bothered?
>> Why are you bothered about Smokeoky Bee's money?
>> Because we're talking about gambling.
Yeah, but if the Giza wins, why can't
you be happy for him? Even if he's an
enemy abused, why can't you,
>> bro? Do you even understand anything
we're talking about? Why are you getting
involved, bro? Just shut up, man.
>> I know. I've been watching it in the
background. And you are jealous of
Smokeoky Beam's bank roll.
>> Yeah, bro. I'm extremely jealous, bro.
>> But why do you I'm so jealous of you,
man. Be careful. I'm so I'm super jealous.
>> Yeah, but I'm not trolling you here. I'm
trying to help you. But why do you go on
about somebody else's gambling? How does
it how does it affect your life?
>> I told you the only way is football are
the casino now, Smokey. I told you this.
I I said the same thing.
>> Yeah, it's mad.
>> But but the thing is I mean I mean PJ,
why are you bothered about other
people's gambling and bankroll? Why
don't you focus on yourself?
>> Well, I am focusing on myself. I just
ask a question.
>> Because you're triggered if someone skin your
>> Okay, I'm going to have to kick Timmy
for a second, bro. He's hurting my
brain, bro. This guy's actually hurting
my brain. Stop it, bro. You're hurting
my brain, bro. You're really, really
hurting my brain.
Yeah. Well, I won a 223 pound football
bet, Smokeoky B. It was a five both
teams to score. Now, that should have
been a lot more than that, but the odds
are just [ __ ] now. But to be honest,
they pay the money instantly, this lad Brooks. So,
I mean, there's that in it. Yeah. Yep.
That should have been more than that,
bro. [ __ ] We're not going to complain.
200 off 20, but still should have been
more than that. Sure. It should have
been more than that. [snorts]
I think the only way to win now is a
double both teams to score.
That's where I've had all my wins. Even
though they've only been like 260 pound,
260, 270, but
I reckon that's your best bet, you know,
a double both teams to score. I've won
so many of them, bro. So, so many of them.
But the odds are the odds on it are [ __ ]
now. So, if you put 150 on it, you get
400 back. But, I mean, yeah.
Yeah, he was trying to troll me earlier. Yep.
One day I'm going to put 500 pound on a
double both teams to score, man.
One day I'm going to do it.
Yeah. But is that true though?
groping some old lady. [snorts] Really, bro?
But how did you know about this though?
How do I know if it's true or not? Yeah,
someone owes me money, bro. I've not
heard from him all day. Yeah. Uh
so what is he going to go jail or what?
I remember I got a [ __ ] Yeah. In the
alleyway from this American, bro. And
she was drunk, but I was drunk as well,
bro. And I didn't I didn't force myself
on it, bro. I mean, she was coming on to
me in it. So, I thought, [ __ ] it. I've
been drinking as well. But it always
scares you with stuff like that in it
because you never know when they can
just lie and [ __ ] in it. [snorts]
That never happened to me, bro.
[sighs and gasps]
So what do you do? Just grope someone? What? Randomly?
That's mad, bro. What the [ __ ]
So what did she do? Like
Yeah. So when I got a [ __ ] bro,
obviously the thing is like I was I was
drinking. Yeah. And the next day,
obviously, I used to get anxiety from
the drinking in it.
And I was thinking, "Oh [ __ ] what if
they went to the police?" Obviously, I
know I hadn't done anything, but you
know what they you know what they're
like in it, bro?
You know what I mean, bro? You can never
be too um
You know what I'm saying? You can never
be too um Yeah,
but I was drinking as well. It just gave
me a [ __ ] in the al anyway, bro. It
was funny as [ __ ]
Um, so how did they find So what
happened then? Did she report him? How
did they So how did they know how did
they find him then? So she reported it
to the police and what they just went to
his address or what?
So is that what happened or what?
But what I'm saying is how did it come
about then? How did the police catch him?
That's what I'm asking. Yep.
I might do online again maybe in two
months or three months.
Who knows? But I I don't really like
gambling, all that [ __ ] bro.
Now, the reason I was live all day today
is cuz I'm not doing anything today. So,
my food's out for delivery now.
Mad, bro. Mad.
So, do you think he's going to get sent down then?
Madness. That is, bro.
Everyone's got cool cases. [ __ ]
Monty, [ __ ] him. Me in two and a half
years. But mine's probably going to get
dropped to be honest before it even
comes to that.
But either way, that one them ones are
quite serious, isn't it?
These ones is one is serious. Money. Do
you remember Money? He was [ __ ]
himself in it. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, Monty was [ __ ] himself in it.
He was [ __ ] himself, bro. Yep.
I've been to prison before. It's not that bad.
Yeah, I've been to prison before. Me,
Harry. I've been to prison before me, lad.
Yeah, I've been to prison for two years. Yep.
I don't know why Monty always used to
say to me, "Oh, you're single. Oh,
you're single. Oh, you're single." I'm
thinking, bro, I could have had Natalie
G before you had Natalie G. I could have
had Natalie G when she looked a lot better.
Now, remember, do you remember Monty
always used to say that? I was like,
"Bro, I had my chance with her."
And I was a virgin back then. Well, I
Well, I mean, I had escorts, but I mean,
I hadn't had anyone but escorts when I
was like 21, 22.
So, think about it, bro. Think about
this. I didn't even get with her when I
was a virgin.
When I was a [ __ ] virgin.
So, I mean, think about that, bro.
Think about being a virgin and still not
getting with them. And you're a virgin, bro.
Never get with her. Huge ass. I'd never
Never. And I had chances as well, lad. Yeah, man.
They still haven't put a deposit limit
on my account. Yep.
What do you mean for what?
Oh, the casino. I tried to put a deposit
limit on my account and close my
account. They wouldn't close it. I won't
be going back to it anyways.
I hope these Cokes are English, but
they're probably not going to be
English, so they're going to taste funny.
I love Curry, bro. I love curry, man. I
love curry. I ordered it from a
different one this time, so hopefully
it's not watery. I just love curry, bro.
In the winter,
in the winter. I love curry, bro. [snorts]
Can smash him every day, man.
My [ __ ] belly wing.
Is this stuff about money, Mike? True.
What stuff are you on about? Go on. This
[ __ ] No, it's not true. I know what
you're going to say. I mean, Pete,
>> this is only stuff I've been hearing.
>> You got to you got to stop listening to
rumors, mate. At the end of the day, you
know, it's like people say rumors about
me. And if anyone's stupid enough to
believe it without evidence, then
they're [ __ ] thick as [ __ ] At the
end of the day,
>> you still do you still talk to Tiger?
>> I talk to everyone. Peter,
>> what do you mean to me? And I'm talking
to you then I so I talk to everyone.
>> Does Tiger ever mention me?
>> Well, he thinks you're a [ __ ]
>> No, he don't really. I'ming you up. Did
you Do you want Do you really want to
know Tiger's opinion on you? He says
that you're YouTube dependent like
banger and your life is tragic.
>> But he's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Yeah, you're a [ __ ] but got a life and
you haven't cuz you're triggered over
[ __ ] names on a screen.
>> O Timmy, be honest yet. I'm taller than
Monty in it.
>> I reckon you could outdo Monty in a
fight. I don't know why. I reckon I
reckon if you actually had your evil
streak and you turned and I think
somebody pushed you at the wrong moment.
I'll be realistic. I think you could film Monty.
>> But I reckon I reckon nons could have you.
>> No. Oh, come on. I'm not even Mini me
out of Austin Powers could beat up nons.
>> Yeah, but you don't know, man. He could
knock you out. Oh,
>> for [laughter] [ __ ] sake. I've been
around for 41 years. I can tell you
someone's going to knock me out or I'm
gonna have a competition or not.
>> Jimmy, Jimmy, do you reckon you could
have London Tail on now?
>> Do you know what? I'm not scared to go
against him, but I think he would dab
me, mate, cuz he's done more boxing
training than me. I'll own it. I reckon
he would flatter me, but I wouldn't be
scared to confront him, though. [laughter]
>> But I've got a reason to start on London
Taylor who's physically made who Yeah.
imagine dying over YouTube. Imagine
being killed over YouTube. That's funny, isn't it?
>> You could have died over YouTube.
Imagine you being in all the people you
sublect to turning at you like the Roth
David Rockefeller got eaten by tribes.
>> Think about that. Dying over YouTube.
Think about think about that though,
bro. You think it's funny? Is it to me?
>> You could have died over YouTube. You
could have got eaten by the [ __ ] by
your tenants and you know they could
have put you in a stuper. Imagine you
being in the house and then you just got
thin. Imagine your [ __ ] the people
you submitted to who turned on you and murdered you.
>> Yeah, but Timmy, I'm I'm prepared for
that. I'm not scared. I'm not scared.
I'm prepared for that. You know what I'm saying?
>> You got You got to look at life, PJ. If
it's your time, it's your time. You
can't control it. But the one thing I
will say to you is if you don't know
Jesus Christ, you will be going to the
lake of fire.
>> Okay. Okay. If if LG broke into your
house, what would you do?
>> And you was in the house. [laughter] But
where's your initiative? would stab him.
>> Yeah. Are you sure? Are you sure about that?
>> No, I would. If anyone come in my front
door and it's either me or them, I would
do my best and if I lose, it's my time
and I'll say, "Jesus, I've sinned. I've
fallen short the glory of God. Please
don't send me to the lake of fire."
>> Yeah. If if the tent was in that day
with the windows, they would have died.
>> But if somebody comes through your
house, you've got to defend yourself.
You got no choice. You can't be living
on naughty land and run away.
>> Timmy, you're lagging. I have to kick
you, bro. You're lagging. Oh, you know,
if I was in that veh, I could have got
killed, you know? Like on on all
seriousness, I could have actually got
killed. Like, imagine I was actually in
that day, bro.
I would have been woken up to violence over YouTube.
Imagine that, bro. It imagine that.
That's actually quite That's actually
quite scary, bro. It [laughter]
That's actually quite scary, is it? Yeah,
that's actually quite scary, bro.
Could you imagine though?
Do you not think, huge, that's actually
quite that's actually quite scary.
But now if it happened, bro, I wouldn't
I wouldn't run or nothing. I wouldn't
give a [ __ ] bro. I wouldn't give a
flying [ __ ] I wouldn't care. Trust me, bro.
Yeah, I wouldn't care, bro.
Yeah, I wouldn't give a [ __ ] if it's
something's going to happen. It's going
to happen in it. I really don't give a [ __ ] Yeah,
but yeah, you could have died over
YouTube. Yeah, it's true. It
So, do you reckon that day if I was in,
do you reckon I would have got killed?
Do you reckon I would have got killed?
Maybe not killed.
That's [ __ ] madness, isn't it? It's
not even anything to laugh at, but like
it's not it's not funny, but like the
whole thing is um [ __ ]
But it wouldn't happen now, bro. It
would never ever ever happen. It would
never ever happen, bro. Now it would never happen. Trust me.
Trust me, that would never happen, bro.
I was a [ __ ] back then, bro. Trust me.
Four or five years ago and that.
And I kind of had stuff to live for. I
still have stuff to live for now,
obviously. But I was younger then, in
it. Obviously, I've still got stuff to
live for. So, like, it's it was a case
of, do you know what it was, bro? Do you
know? Do you know? Do you know a lot of
reason why I didn't do stuff even back
then as well is cuz I thought about it.
I was like, "Bro, you're making money
from the house. Yeah. You don't want to
do anything that's going to put you in
prison. You don't want to do anything
that's going to make you lose income."
That's what it was, bro. As well. A lot
of it was that as well, you know? And
it's like, what's the point over some
[ __ ] idiot? Yeah. Losing everything.
That and that's that was a part of it,
bro. It actually was a part of it,
you know, cuz obviously like why am I
losing income from [ __ ] the house,
bro? Yeah. Um, you don't understand when
you've got a lot to when you've got
stuff to lose, bro. You don't understand
what I mean?
Do you understand? Like when you've got
stuff to lose. Yeah.
And I had stuff to lose. I still do now
obviously, but like I had a lot more to
lose back then, bro. Trust me.
because obviously I had a responsibility
in that. That's why I had to curve it
with the YouTube as well, bro. Because I
didn't want to go [ __ ] you know what
I'm saying? Like to jail or anything,
bro? Because who's going to look after the house? But yeah,
that's what a lot of people don't realize.
That's what a lot of people don't
realize, bro. When you've got stuff to lose,
it's different. You know what I mean? But yeah,
which I'm surprised he done all of that
[ __ ] if he had all that stuff to lose.
To be honest,
I'm surprised he done all of that if he
had if he really has all of this [ __ ]
that he says he does. That doesn't
really make sense, does it?
Yeah. Lucky they weren't in that day,
bro, cuz they would have got killed.
They they would have um they would have
been they would have been injured from that.
They would have been injured, lad.
That's horrible. Oh, lucky they weren't in.
Yeah, I'm skinn. Okay, bro. Like I said,
this is 2026, lad.
Yeah, it's 2026, lad. Change up the
insults going now. [snorts]
Yeah. So, yeah, that's what would have
happened because Yeah, if the tenant was
in, bro, it's not good. Oh yeah.
But that's mad though to do that over
YouTube. I don't think I would have done that, bro.
Nah. Nah, bro.
That is mad, bro.
That's a bit extreme, isn't it?
That is a bit extreme, bro.
Do you not think that's a bit extreme,
bro? Honestly, like, let's have all your
opinion. I think that's proper proper extreme.
Yeah, you might have said stuff about
him and he's But but at the end of the
day, bro, like that's a do not think
that's a bit extreme.
Yeah, it wasn't my bike. It wasn't my
That's another thing. That wasn't my
bike, but obviously he thought it was.
Trust me, that nothing for mine would
have ever been stolen, bro. Cuz I would
have personally got it back no matter
what it took. No, it would never happen,
bro. Even back then.
Yeah, cuz obviously they thought it was
my bike in it. That weren't my bike, bro.
That definitely definitely wasn't my
bike, bro. It would never be my bike.
That would never be my bike ever. No way.
So yeah, bro.
That's a bit mad to do that over YouTube
though, is it?
That is a bit mad, isn't it? It's a bit extreme
because the bike was in the the bike was
in the hallway
and then he just took the bike.
Yeah, bro. And what? And I already told
you why I did nothing about it. Cuz I
wasn't going to end up in prison a and
lose the money for the house. [ __ ] that,
bro. I'd rather be labeled as a [ __ ]
And I was actually a [ __ ] back then as
well. But I'd rather be labeled as a
[ __ ] that done nothing and kept getting
over three grand a month for the house
for not working. Of course I did
nothing, bro. Of course I did nothing.
I didn't need to do nothing, bro. I
didn't need to do a damn thing about it.
There was no way I was losing that money
from that house for some for some loser
on YouTube. There's no way, bro. I
wouldn't give a [ __ ] who it was.
I wouldn't give a [ __ ] who it was.
That's why I was moving the way I was moving.
That's literally why I was moving the
way I was moving,
you know, because then it what is it?
Then I I do something and then I could
end up in prison and then I lose the
house and then the money from the house.
Nah, bro. Trust me. Nah.
It wasn't worth it. Was not worth it.
No way. Was it worth it, bro? No way. So yeah.
So I knew what I was doing, bro. I knew
what I was doing.
Yeah, [snorts] I know it is.
Yeah, I know it is. Yeah.
But what was I supposed to do, bro?
[snorts] If you actually think about it
logically, you know,
but it depends on the situation and
who's doing it. You know what I'm saying? Like,
so yeah, that's another thing. But if I
was in my own own house. Yeah. So I'm in
my own house now. Don't make money from
the house. It would never happen, bro.
It would never ever happen. It would
never ever happen. Trust me.
Trust me. [snorts] It would never ever happen.
So yeah. So then it's like, what do you
do? What do you do in that situation?
I'm not losing money from that house,
bro. No way.
So yeah, I kind of had to do that.
Yeah, I kind of had to move like that to be fair.
But that's [ __ ] [ __ ] anyways, bro.
Smashing windows and that. That's all
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. All of that is just
Really is, bro. Really, really is.
But that's weird because if someone No,
it's coming out 3 minutes away. If
someone actually has stuff to lose like
he claimed, why would he even be doing
that? Do you know what I'm saying?
Why Why would someone even be doing
that? Do you get me?
No, he did not. Has he smashed any
windows here? Has he come on the door?
No, he hasn't, bro.
No, he hasn't. Because then you would
know what time it is, bro.
In 2025 and 2026, you would know what
time it is.
Trust me, none of these windows are ever
getting smashed. No one is even going to
try to knock on the front door.
That that that is not happening. That
literally is not happening. So, yeah.
Yeah. What? He went he went outside it,
bro. Good for him. Yeah.
No, not in my mom's. Never.
He went out with a grand. I don't need a
grand. I had my own money.
I don't need a grand.
But yeah, there was no way I was going
to do anything to jeopardize that money,
bro, from the house. No way. I'd rather
be labeled as the [ __ ] Trust me. Trust me, bro.
Trust me, that's all it was. That is all
it was, bro. No one was scared.
It was the same with everyone. No one
was scared. Not one. Well, I wasn't [ __ ] scared.
And then when And then and then that
whole [ __ ] nonsex thing as well. I
was like, I need to be careful what I'm
saying now. I need to be careful with
what I'm saying now.
You know, because
I didn't think they were going to let me
out of that [ __ ] police station. It's
not because anyone's scared, bro. Not at all.
Literally not at all at all.
And I'm more bad now in my head, bro.
Like, you see how I am with gambling and
that. Trust me. You see how I am with
gambling and that?
Trust me, bro. It would never happen. It Yeah. Trust me. Yeah, bro.
I can't even remember what I said, bro.
No, I think he was singing over the
battles, wasn't he?
I think he was singing over the battals
or something, was he?
Yeah, it was something about that. Where
the [ __ ] is this? Yeah, that's what it
was, bro. I remember.
Yeah, I remember, bro.
>> Yeah. Or something like that.
There we go, bro. What's this?
Yeah, we just coming out, bro. Yeah, man.
Hopefully this is nice cuz I haven't
ordered it from here, man.
>> Everything for you. I see the message. I
>> Yeah, it doesn't, bro. That was uh
another restaurant before, is it?
>> But I didn't uh I forgot to change it.
It's for Nando cuz you know Nando
sometimes they make it dry, but it
doesn't apply to them.
>> Give me two number. Uh 16.
>> Yeah, man. >> Yeah. Okay.
The ticket is orange, but it can be orange.
I haven't had this one before.
Yeah, the Coke is always foreign, bro.
It's always Oh, no. One second. That
one's not. That one's English.
Look, man. Yeah, I just got curry ticker.
Sometimes it's orange. It's either red,
This is not
will be though. It [clears throat]
prime bro. He could never ever grab me now, bro.
You could never ever grab me now. I'm a
big [ __ ] bro.
You You could You wouldn't even have the
strength to do it, bro. Yeah.
What makes me laugh here is LT, he calls
you He calls you a troll. Yeah. Stephen
Howard. Yeah. But we don't see you white
knight in nonsense. We don't see you being biased.
You know what I'm saying? We don't see
you being biased, bro.
So, how can you be the troll? That don't make sense.
>> [clears throat]
>> Not one.
But then he calls you a troll. How could
it call you a troll?
when you're literally not the one that's
white knighting, bro. So,
yeah, it's still a little bit watery,
but this is always the way. Whenever you
order it, it's always watery.
Building me up. Yeah.
A lot, bro. I need to stop to be fair,
man. I need to stop. I need to be saving
money, bro. [ __ ]
A lot of [ __ ] money, bro. This [ __ ]
ain't cheap anymore like it used to be.
Don't depress me, bro. Don't depress me. Yeah. Yeah. 100%.
I don't need more income, bro. I've got
more than enough money.
I get money. I make money, bro.
I don't tell my life story on here, but
I get enough money, bro.
I just need to save money not spending
lot [ __ ] takeways. You are no
shouldn't be wasting money on food.
Well, we already know about the
gambling. You can't win on anything but football. So
I get enough money, bro.
The only thing is you're
you don't understand this yet
that you seem to think if you get more
money you you got a better life, but
that's not necessarily true because when
you get more money, as soon as you get
more money, you will just spend more
money. So you don't it doesn't even
necessarily equal a better life and then
you get a costume to that money that
you're getting. It doesn't always equal
better life. You know that when I was
getting £1,100 a month, I was more
sensible. I was living a better life
than when I've had different amounts of money before.
When you get more, you'll probably
gamble more and spend more. Unless
you're disciplined, so it doesn't really
matter, you know.
Unless you find a way to somehow
be disciplined, you're just going to
spend more if you get more.
Trust me, bro. You live You live any
amount of money you get.
Yeah. Well, as long as you're not
starving and you got no money, it
doesn't matter. Yeah.
you get. Trust me, bro. When I whenever
I get extra money, when someone gives me
extra money, I I just thought I was I
found myself gambling more than I wasn't doing before.
Trust me, bro. If you get more, you will spend more.
Trust me, Dad. It's no different.
Trust me, lad. Doesn't matter what you
get. You adjust to whatever you get to
an extent. Obviously not 300 pound but
you know if you got 11200 pound you would
Yeah. You ask him that. Mhm.
You asking that?
Yeah. [ __ ] lad.
You get banned for that, man. That's weird.
This cover is nice. They could have at
least gave me a [ __ ] free pop for buck sake, but no.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, man.
Can't say it's too much.
[clears throat] Do you reckon you'll
ever get life?
You reckon you'll die once?
Can't tell you, bro. I can't tell you
the app, lad. We have so many stalkers.
I can't tell you.
There's certain things I can't say,
unfortunately, lad. Obviously, it's not
best better than the ones as well. Yeah.
Sorry, I can't say that, bro. I have too many stalkers.
All right. You know what's so mad about
LT? Yeah, Stephen is at He talks about
USA, is he? But what I was saying
earlier when you wasn't on here is that
you're talking to me. You're messaging
me, bro. You're not talking to someone
on YouTube that don't know more than
you. You're talking to someone that
knows more than you. I know they went
running to the police three times. I
know they'll never meet me. I know
they'll never say anything to my face.
So, you're talking to me, bro. Someone
that knows stuff that you don't know.
So, it doesn't work when you're talking
to someone that knows more than you. You
understand, bro? You get me?
But it will never be as good as the
restaurants. It will never be. But
obviously, takeaway is never as good no
matter where you're there from.
I'm saying to the dude there that you're
talking to me, bro. You're not talking
to no one else. You're talking to me,
bro. How you going to f How you trying
to How you going to try and kid someone
that knows more than you about the whole
thing? You're You're actually mad in your head. Yeah.
And it's wrong of you to be [ __ ] serving
when the person is not about anything.
Whether I was a man, whether I was a
woman, this [ __ ] is never going to say
anything to my face. So you [ __ ] storing
to someone that's not about it, you're
only causing them problems really.
You will never ever
you're trying to come because we know
the we know that we know the story
because the thing is you can sit on
YouTube and try and [ __ ] stir and try to
go and try and make out that this person
is about something but bro if they were
really about something they never goed
me once. They will never ever say
anything to my face. They have not goed me once.
You get me?
Yeah, because they're not about anything.
What will happen, right?
Two two things will happen if you go
there. If you go there, bro, two things will happen.
You'll either get stopped by the customs
and they're going to let you in the
country, which is probably what will
happen, or someone's going to come and
try and shoot you. That's literally all
that will happen, bro.
Yeah. Stop [ __ ] stirring about people
cracking jokes and that, bro.
You're not about that, guys. Trust me.
Trust me. You're really not about that life. Yeah, man. Stupid [ __ ]
This is nice though, bro. It's quite
nice to be fair.
I'm enjoying it.
Oh, it is ping, isn't it? Yeah, man.
This coke is foring. That's the thing.
When you buy it from the takeaway
places, they're forbining Cokes and they
taste different. But I wasn't going to
go back out today, but I was tired. I'm
tired and I can't be bothered.
You get me? Yeah, bro.
Can't beat your belly full of co.
Yeah. Why have you got a picture of me, you weirdo?
You look weird on that.
Oh, I'm a good looking man. Why don't
you put yourself up then? H
tell Cole come up the TV today. She come
on the TV.
She come on the TV.
Yeah. I thought his coat tastes nasty, bro.
But it's better than nothing, is it?
It's better than nothing.
You want my life?
Why, bro? I'm skin. I don't leave the
house, man. I'm skin.
Why Stephen Albert? Do you remember the
people on Reddit making excuses for women?
Like when I saw them leading me on and
stuff, they make excuses for them.
Funny, is it?
>> Yeah. But that's just that's just
normal. I know
they make excuses.
Yeah, that's been happening, bro.
So, Dusty, listen. Answer me this. Yeah.
So, if I go on Reddit today slagging
about men, slagging off men, are people
going to make excuses for them like they
make excuses for the women that lead me on?
I still haven't done the experiment yet.
I got a VPN now, so I can do it. I hope so.
Equality will be nice.
I'm going to be I'm going to say that
I'm bisexual and I've been trying to
date men and they keep being [ __ ]
So, do you reckon they're going to make
excuses for the men like they do women?
I'm hoping they do. So, it's better, isn't it?
What do you think, Dustin?
What's your money on that? Yeah.
What do you think, Dy?
Yeah, they do make excuses. I've showed
them my approaching videos where I've
tried to speak to someone and they said
they have a boyfriend and they make
these excuses up um for them like, "Oh,
you come on too strong." Or
it's always an excuse, bro.
This is nice curry.
Nice enough, bro.
I don't know.
I don't know the answer cuz I've not
done the experiment yet.
I don't know the answer because I
haven't done I haven't actually done the
experiment yet. I'm just going to moan
about men and complain about men.
from the people make the same excusion
for them like they do women.
>> Oh, they were being nice.
>> I was I was talking to this gay guy in
America from years ago and I showed him
the women leading me on. He said, "Oh,
they were just being nice." I said, "No,
they weren't. They were leading me on."
People have a tendency, Dusty, to act
stupid um when you show women [ __ ]
you over or them leading you on or wrongdoing you. um
they have a tendency to start acting
stupid like they don't know what you're
showing them and yeah
well yeah as an experiment I'm going to say that
I'm going to say to them that oh men are
leading me on men punts and see if they
start calling me an insel and all of the
things that they would call me if I was
saying about women
I want to I want to see if they make
excuses for men the same way as they do
women. So, I don't know. I hopefully
I'll find the answer. What do you think
is going to be, Dusty?
Cuz when you say about women, they make
excuses for women and go to their rescue
and say they were being nice and stuff.
So, we'll see if if I moan about men.
We'll see. We'll see if we get the same thing.
I don't know. What's your money on, lad?
Should we do a bet? Who wants to do a
bet, Steven Howard? Me, you, Dusty?
Let's see if they make excuses for men being [ __ ] We'll see.
I don't know the answer. How could I
know the answer if I've not done it?
Who knows that?
What's your opinions? Mhm. Yeah, man.
Remember I can't date you cuz I'm a Muslim.
Oh, I can't date you cuz I'm a Muslim.
Okay, I'll convert to Muslim. Oh, I'm
not looking for anyone. You
agrees. Listen, man. What do what does
you what do you people think? So if I if
when I go on Reddit and I say I'm
bisexual and I start complaining about men,
are they going to make excuses?
Will they make excuses for the men like
they do the women?
What's everyone's money on? I want to
hear I want to I want to see if they
make the same excuses for men doing
wrong than as they do women when women
do wrong. M
[sighs] what's everyone's opinion
with with women they say oh they're just
being nice or you're coming on too
strong or it's always you. So you know
hopefully if we if we wor about men we
get the same answers
you know cuz they're not technist or
anything. But you know what do you think
Steven would lad
what's your opinion
talking to can I'm making a cup of can so what
I'm going to What's up, man?
Yeah, but what do you reckon the result will be?
You can't even say anything about women
without being called in.
But it's okay for them to be punts. It's
okay for them to pretend they've got
boyfriends. It's okay for them to leave
people on. And they never get no backlash.
But they want to be equal.
I'm not sure how that's going to work. Yeah.
Yeah. But you did answer the question, Dusty.
Are they going to make excuses for men
like they do women
or are they going to take my side? Cuz
on Reddit, you can't even say something
without being called an insel.
Women are shallow. Incel. Intel. You
can't even say anything. They call you
an intel. Not fair.
Well, what do you think is going to
happen? What's your prediction?
I've already beaten me, Elijah.
I've already done it, so I don't think I
I don't reckon I can.
I'm only doing it if you give me your
predictions what you think will happen.
If I start slagging men off or people
going to make excuses for them on Reddit
like they do women,
I'm going to do it. But you need to give
your Yeah, but you need to give your opinion.
Are they going to make excuses and not
take accountability or [snorts]
No, I don't think you you get the point
I'm trying to make, Steven Howard.
No, I don't think you get the point I'm
trying to make, lad. Right. What I'm
trying to say is, right? Okay. So,
when I show my bad experiences with
women, them pretending that they've got
a boyfriend, them having attitude, them
leading me on, them playing games, them
coming out with 101 different excuses.
People always make excuses for the
reason that they do it. Like, oh, you're
coming on too strong. Or, oh, they
changed their mind. Or, oh, they were
being nice. and they will just
continuously make excuses for them. So,
what I'm wanting to know is if I pretend
that it's men doing the same things that
women are doing,
um will they will they make the same excuses?
Yeah, it's weird that though, bro, because
Yeah, they side with them like they're innocent.
That's why I do know, bro. That's one of
the reasons why I quit the dating game
because of the double standards.
That's why I quit it, bro. That's why I
quit it, bro. Because of the double
standards and [ __ ]
That's why I quit it, man. Well, that's
one of the reasons I quit it
cuz it's like whatever they do, they get
away with it. So, I was like, what the
[ __ ] is the point of it then?
They just make excuses for them and
what's the point now?
That's why I haven't tried, bro.
And anything that they do, it gets
justified. So pointless. Yeah.
So then it's a gender thing there, isn't
it? Isn't it? All you know, like I said
to you, Steven Howard, when someone ever
calls me an incel, all I say, all I
reply back is,
all I reply back, right, is
um all I reply back is
all I reply back is, all I reply back
is, would you say that if I was a woman?
And that's how you always win the
argument, Dusty. I would say if I was a
woman complaining about men, would you
say that? And to that they never they
can never answer. So I pretty much rest
my case. It's a gender thing. When you
realize it's a gender thing, lad,
then you realize you know the game,
isn't it? Um, let me read what you said.
So you're going on as a by guy slagging
off other guys for not wanting a
relationship. Yeah, pretty much. Yeah.
Yeah. And basically the point of it is
to see if they if people are going to
defend them and blame me like they do
with women or are they going to agree
with me and basically call the men out
for doing what they do.
So that's why like if you Yeah. So all
you got to say is well would you call me
that if I was a woman? And then the
answer is no. So it's a gender thing. You understand?
Obviously, I'm not by, bro, but I'm just
doing it as an example.
When a woman complains, everyone feels
sorry for her. When a man struggles for
years and has to deal with nothing but
crap, no one cares.
So, that's why I quit the dating game, lad.
And the excuses. Oh, why do you think I
I don't get depressed anymore? Um,
Steven Howard, why do you think I'm
stable? Why do you think I'm never
really fed up? Cuz I quit dating, lad.
Do you remember when I was waking up
every day with mood swings? Every single
[ __ ] day. Waking up with mood swings
for like two weeks, bro. That's cuz I
was dating, bro. That's why I gave up.
Never felt better, bro. Never felt better.
It's so toxic, bro.
The excuses, the [ __ ] the mind
games. I watch Ed Matthews, bro, and
that's enough for me, bro.
I watch some of these Tik Tockers
um and well Tik Tockers. I watch some of
these kick streamers and they get the
same thing. And what makes me laugh
Dusty right is why do you when I'm
watching this guy yet when I'm watching
this Ed Matthews
and I'm watching other people deal with these women
being [ __ ] I'm thinking to myself,
how are people defending them?
But I was watching one earlier where one
was sitting on his lap. He was he was on
a mobility scooter and she's saying that
she's got a boyfriend when she blatantly
don't. I mean and and the attitude to
some of these women. I don't understand
how there's people defending them, bro.
And you got them [ __ ] being defended
by a million and one white knights.
Weird, isn't it? [sighs] >> [snorts] >> Yeah.
So, yeah, I that's why I gave up on the
dating scene, lad.
I done two approaches on Monday, Steven
Howard, cuz I was out and it kind of
escalated, but nothing happened. So,
I just thought it would have maybe been
different because it was 2026, but no.
But yeah, I've not been on a proper
night out for months, lad. So,
don't think I ever will again.
Do you remember that one? Oh, I can't
date you cuz cuz you're not a Muslim.
Oh, I'll convert to Muslim. Oh, I'm not
looking for anyone anyways.
Yeah, right. You just laugh at it now,
bro. I'd rather watch other people deal
with it than deal with it myself. So boring, lad.
So boring, bro. So boring.
Yeah, he does, bro. But [snorts] yeah,
I like the approaches and that cuz I
used to do [ __ ] like that.
told you to [ __ ] off.
Yeah. Oh, he's still there, Dusty.
that LT said on his email. Do you know
what LT said on my email? Oh, we heard a
female call you a ma. I said, "Yeah, you
heard a female call me a ma four years
ago. Someone that's got daddy issues."
A, she's got daddy issues and B, I
didn't even approach her. She just got
jealous because I approached her friend
and she's got daddy issues. Yeah. What?
And what, bro? Who cares? Someone that I
wasn't even [ __ ] with. You see, it'd
be different, bro, if he was actually
[ __ ] with a person.
I told who to [ __ ] off? What are you on about, bro?
I've dealt with so many toxic entitled
people, bro. That's [snorts] just I was just unlucky.
You think that matters, bro? some some
woman that I wasn't [ __ ] with with daddy issues
calling me a month or four years ago.
What about all the women that call me
good-looking? What about all the women
that slept with me that call me cute?
Come on, bro. Seriously, we live in
London, bro. London's full of [ __ ]
You can easily be working and and have
an entitled person just want to insult
you for no reason. We live in London,
bro. Come on.
That's why that M thing is so boring.
That's why I don't even explain it, bro.
Because it's just
It's just [snorts] silly, isn't it?
What are you talking about? [ __ ] off,
bro. I don't know what you're on about.
There's this guy that approached a woman
and she was like, "Oh, you look like
some guy that I friendzoned."
So, you know, you get it from any every
most people get it from women, bro. One
one time in their life. All you got to
do is come across somebody with daddy issues.
And then they say stuff like that. I've
seen him be rude to loads of people.
Yeah, LT was trying to make excuses for
that one as well. Yeah, I saw it, bro.
I'm watching some of his stuff.
Um yeah, he also made excuses with that
one as well.
The Weather Spoons video. He's got loads
of buyers. He's got loads of excuses,
doesn't he, bro? Yeah.
Yeah, they've got their own.
Yeah, he made excuses LT with that video
with the bouncer and the other people. I
said, "Bro, them other people did not own me."
And then he said, "Oh, what about the
woman on the train?" I said, "I told the
woman on the train about herself as
well." Again, somebody with an agenda.
them people in the Weather Spoons did
not own me, bro.
That was sat outside. That did not
happen. Only in your world that happened, bro.
Only in your little world that happened.
Not in the real world. That never never never happened.
Do you know what's so bad? Yeah. You
could actually win a fight here and
they'd say you lost.
You could actually grieve on this
community. You could actually win a
fight fair and square and they tell you
that you lost.
They'd be like, they'd be like, "Nah,
you lost, lad."
You could literally be in a boxing ring.
Yeah. You could actually knock someone
out the first round, then they'd be
like, "Nope, never happens." Nope. Nope.
What do you think of Little Yoda,
Steven? How would you like him with his
little hands? He's cute, isn't he?
Have a little go on roulette. Steven Howard. Nah. Never. Never, bro. Nah, bro.
All right. Nothing.
Good old Rud, eh?
Yeah, he's cute, isn't he?
So, what happened, Grevy? How did I used
to get my vitamins? Grievy,
how did I used to get my vitamins?
I'm all right now without the vitamins in it.
I [snorts] just get it from like curries and stuff.
What did you say, Grezy? What did I used
to latch on to? Greavvesy.
Mark was calling you a mong earlier that
Arsenal Mark was coming on at tonight.
the big man.
>> Yeah. And I defended you, lad.
>> Yeah. He's pissed up. How did I used to
get my vitamins, Grezy?
So, is that why I used to go to like
clubs and bars like every like twice a
week then to get my vitamins?
So, is that why for the vitamins, bro?
Bro, I literally couldn't go without I
couldn't go without like a woman for
more than two weeks, bro. When I was
younger, like without kissing and
touching and stuff. I couldn't do it
grievy. That's why I used to go out
Thursdays and Saturdays
to get my vitamins and stuff.
But obviously, I grew out of that phase
and saw [snorts] them for what they were
and that. So, I get vitamins from other places now.
yeah, I used to go out Thursdays. I had
sick. I had a one night stand on my birthday.
You remember I was really depressed one year. Greavvesy.
I think it was two years ago.
I was like, "Oh, I'm not going to go
out." It was my birthday and I ended up
going out and having a one night stand
on my birthday, Grezy.
So I I was I got my vitamins, Greavesy.
Yeah. I used to not I wasn't nice to be
around without my vitamins, was I? You know.
Yep. And I got my vitamins.
Yeah, I need my vitamins.
I used to like to be hugged and kissed. Grezy,
you know, a couple of years ago, I used
to like hugs and kisses and stuff.
Is that cute, Grezy?
But now I've got Yoda. I've got my Cries
at least. And I got Crash Bandicut, so
they don't they're loyal, you know.
Yeah, I got my little Yoda.
He's so cute. Love you. [snorts]
Do you know what? I reckon the virgin's
going to get laid this year, though.
It's his birthday soon. Hopefully, he
gets laid. Fingers crossed.
Anyone that brings up the girlfriend
now, Steven Howard, we will just ignore
it, won't we? So, whenever we say that
he's a virgin, anyone that brings up the
girlfriend, we will just carry on as normal.
Until they have stuff to say about the
19year-old and the [ __ ] only fans and
the Manchester woman, we will just
ignore it now. it.
I'll say come back when you go on his
channel and you start talking about what we've shown.
That's what I'll do now, bro. I won't
even like get into arguments with it. [snorts]
You just carry on as normal. Is it?
Oh, you've not seen Crash.
I won him in the arcade.
Yeah, I run him in the arcade. Look, he's official.
He lives up there.
Yeah, he just lives at the top.
>> Yeah, he's cute. I want him in the grab machine.
He's He sits at the top.
watching over me.
>> Uh, I'm not sure.
Do you know my birth date? Steven Howard,
do you remember when I was born?
Crash is older than me. Yep.
Grezy, I want some digestive biscuits. Greasy. Grezy. Yeah. [sighs]
Oh, do you remember that Jamie Thompson
Steven Howard? All I've got to say is
look at the way the guy looks. I say no more.
Another jealous stalker.
Another jealous one.
Another jealous stalker, dude. Um,
Ste Oen Albert, what do you think of Jamie Thompson? Jesus Christ.
How can someone look like that, bro?
Did you like when I used to get my little vitamins? Greasy.
Yeah. He's still stalking me, bro.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> He's another stalker, lad. Another stalker.
Yeah, someone reported me to the police
the other day. Greavvesy, I already told
you, isn't it? So that's why we need to
um we need to go on another channel at some point.
But Greasy, you better not tell anyone
the other channel, lad.
I'll give you and Steven Howard it and that
and I'll find a way you get it, but you
best not tell anyone, bro.
Cuz obviously we don't want grassing and [ __ ]
Oh my god. Look at this Jamie Thompson guy, bro.
[ __ ] Have you seen what he looks like,
bro? You sure this guy is not in a wheelchair?
I'm pretty sure this guy's in a wheelchair, bro.
What the [ __ ] I'm just on his channel, man. Jeez.
Jesus. Imagine looking like that, bro. That's mad. [gasps]
Yeah, because of the grassing and stuff.
Ain't it greasy?
Don't want grasses. I don't want people
watching me. I don't want grasses
Five live five hours, bro. The [ __ ]
So, do you want me to unbox the Lego Grezy?
When I get some new Lego, do you want me
to do you want me to do an unboxing of it?
To be honest, my favorite is the little characters.
So, you know that t-shirt I got, that
Simpsons t-shirt, Greasy, would you wear it?
You would wear it, wouldn't you?
You'd wear it, wouldn't you?
You'd wear the B t-shirt, wouldn't you?
It's an adult's t-shirt. Would you wear it?
What about a Spider-Man one?
I want to show Can I show you the
Spider-Man one I got? It's not here yet,
but I'll show you it.
Yeah, I'd wear the [clears throat] Bart
Simpson one, bro. They're just I just
wanted casual t-shirts. It weren't cheap
as well. It was 14 pound, bro. Wasn't
cheap. That t-shirt wasn't cheap, bro.
You'd wear this t-shirt though. One second.
I bet you you're going to wear you'd
wear this t-shirt.
I'll show you exactly which one it is.
One second. It's coming.
Yeah. The t-shirt. It's just casual
t-shirts cuz I didn't have any t-shirts.
Many t-shirts. So, I bought a couple.
Crazy. You'd wear this one though,
wouldn't you? One sec.
This is the one I've got coming. I like
it. I think it's cute. Yeah,
I think that's pretty cute. Me.
So, you got Spider-Man and he's had a baby. Look.
[sighs] Sat on his lap.
You wouldn't wear it. I'm I'm [ __ ]
wearing it, bro. [ __ ] you. You can. By
wearing it, I don't mean going on a
night out drinking wearing it. I mean,
wearing it around the house, wearing it
out, but not like going out drinking. I
don't mean like that.
I don't know. I thought it was cute. [gasps]
Yeah, I wear I don't mind me, lad.
So, where what t-shirts do you wear, Grezy?
You You wouldn't wear it now.
Well, I'll wear it.
Beepy shirt. You don't like it?
I like it me lad
smart button up ones. No.
Yeah, but what do you what do you wear
for bed? Greavves. I just wear boxer
shorts for bed.
>> Yeah, Simpsons one. Yeah.
Yeah. The Simpsons one was £14. It's
good quality though, bro.
Well, obviously it wasn't cheap, was it?
So, I just wear I just wear boxes for bed, bro.
What? You sleep in socks? I don't know
how people can sleep. I hate socks. me.
I wear like the thinnest socks possible.
I wear thin ankle socks. I hate socks.
But obviously you have to wear socks
with trainers obviously and it shoes and
that. I hate socks, bro. I can never imagine sleeping
sleeping with um socks. Nah.
[sighs and gasps]
Nah, I don't think I ever have. [ __ ] that, bro.
I just sleep in my I'm Do you know what
boxes I'm wearing, Grezy? I'm wearing
Stits boxer shorts right now.
I'm wearing Stitch boxes right now. box.
Yeah. [snorts] Stitch boxer shorts.
What about a t-shirt of Stitch Queezy?
Would you wear that?
[sighs and gasps] [sighs]
Yeah. [clears throat]
Greavves thinks about women every day, isn't it?
From the time Greavvesy wakes up to the
time he goes to bed, all he thinks about is women in it. Bless him.
Like I said, lad, I get vitamins from
other places now. So, yeah,
I don't need them. I I get vitamins from other places. So, yeah.
Do you remember Greavves? You glue your
glue your dick to someone's mouth. Remember,
Greavvesy, glue, glue your dick in it to
someone's mouth. Is that cute, Greavvesy?
You come out with that one, didn't you,
Greavvesy? Yeah. As long as someone's
got a mouth, then they're good enough, isn't it?
Yeah. They just need a mouth, isn't it, Grezy?
Yeah, I was messaging that woman I had a
one night stand with on Manchester. She
doesn't she doesn't um
No, he didn't leave, bro. She didn't
reply back. She actually swallowed my
sperm. Greavves. Is that disgusting?
The first one that stand I had, she swallowed it.
Was that you?
That's kind of gross, isn't it, Grezy?
Well, maybe they need vitamins as well. Yep.
Yes, she swallowed it. Yeah.
[gasps and sighs]
Obviously [snorts and clears throat] in
her mouth. Where else would have been Yeah.
Yeah. That was Chinese, Izzy.
She's so lucky I had a bath, bro. Yeah.
I can't believe she done that. That is disgusting, bro.
That's [ __ ] vile, isn't it? Yep.
Oh, I'm in my little bed. [gasps]
What about USA? Is he Steven Howard? Do
you like USA? Is he?
There's loads of different Izzies.
I don't like the first one. She was a meanie.
Greavvesy. Do you remember Izzy? The
first Izzy? She was a meanie. Yep.
She was a big nasty meanie. [sighs]
get on the panel.
Well, I agree with you. Did you ever
watch Star Wars the Phantom Menace?
The Darth Did you ever watch Darth Maul?
He defeated one of the Jedi.
One of the Jedi Jedi got killed by him.
He was a nasty bastard.
that Darth Maul,
[sighs] he killed one of the Jedi
and then the other one survived. I
played that in the Lego version as well. [gasps]
Yeah, she she play the Lego version.
How do you remember it, Grezy? What did
you watch it? >> [gasps] >> No. [sighs]
Yeah, I used to watch them. They used to
come on every Sunday. Griezy the Star
Wars. I used to love Star Wars, but I
used to have all the lightsabers.
Yeah, I used to, bro.
Rate all the isies.
There's so many of them, bro. Yeah,
I like Georgia. I like Georgia Blinks.
I love Star Wars. I like Yoda. I like Jojo Blinks.
I like um I like the black man with the
purple lightsaber. I like the purple Yeah.
Oh, Star Wars is not shy. Yoda's a
lovely little character.
Isn't that right?
Star Wars is a lovely little character.
Did you like Harry Potter, Dusty?
I didn't like Harry Potter. I think that
was [ __ ] But I did like Dobby. I like
Dobby. I just don't like Harry Potter.
I just don't like Harry Potter, bro.
Like the actual um I just don't like it. Harry Potter. [snorts]
Space Balls. I've never heard of that one. Dusty.
No, I've never heard of that one. Dusty,
what's Yoda doing right now? Grezy,
my little Lego Yoda. What's he doing?
Space balls. I'd have to watch it.
Oh, I remember that Looney Tunes basketball.
Dusty, do you remember the new era hats
in Wolf and Stone Market?
There used to be a shop years ago, about
18 years ago,
and there was a place in Wolfenstone you
could have pink panther jeans, new era hats.
I'm having a go. Nah,
you remember it though, is it? In
Morenstone Market, there used to be this
shop, bro. I don't know if obviously I
don't think it is still there. And it
used to be called um I don't know what
it was. It lot 69 and [ __ ]
Yeah, I used to watch that [ __ ] bro. I
wear that [ __ ]
Do you remember the Telean scarfs, Dusty?
Do you remember the Teleban scarfs?
I used to have a gray one.
I was in Leighton. Do you know a place
called Leighton? That's where I was. I
used to live. I was there um the other day.
Why no roulette? Uh
cuz roulette's [ __ ] rigged.
Why would I do that? Why would I waste
130 150 on on that when I can just buy some Lego?
When I can just buy some new characters.
Why I do that, bro? When I can just buy
some little characters.
No, I'm not playing roulette, bro.
Roulette's too addicting, bro. [gasps]
What do you think?
Why don't you look at your own money?
How about you look at your own money, lad?
How about you look at your own money?
That's nice. You should look at your own
money then. [sighs]
No, I don't even know what that is.
Why [snorts] do you remember uh do you
remember football stickers, Dusty?
Back 16 years ago. I used to connect I
used to collect them, lad.
Uh to talk to Steven Howard and
Greavvesy. And honestly, I'm bored
today. I didn't even leave that. I
didn't even leave. But I did leave the
house earlier. I had nothing better to
do today, bro.
I'm busy tomorrow. I'm doing stuff
I literally done nothing today, bro.
So, I didn't mind going live. Only day I
didn't do nothing.
O, do you remember the football stickers, Dusty?
Bro, I used to like the football stickers.
We used to go to school and set. Oh,
bro, them them 20p football stickers.
I used to love them here. Yeah.
What do you think I do when I wake up?
The first thing I do when I wake up,
what do you thinking the first thing I
think about when I wake up? I can tell
you. I make a I make myself a cup of tea
and Yoda a cup of tea.
Me and Yoda has a cup of tea together.
>> No, I don't. Wank. No, bro.
Where? Wait, what are you talking about?
Nope. [snorts] That's definitely you,
bro. And Lord J's followers.
I don't even go on my phone as soon as I wake up.
Nah, I can't tell you, Dusty. Sorry.
Nope. I don't even go on my phone as
soon as I wake up.
No, that's you people, lad. No. Uh, Reddit.
to be honest.
Oh, I watch a quiz show. There's a new
quiz show on Greasy.
I watch it, bro.
Wasting my life away. I'm not wasting my
life away, bro. I'm out every day.
I'm out every day. I've done a lot in 3
4 years. I'm not wasting my life away on
here at all, lad. There's weeks where I
don't come on here.
Definitely definitely not wasting my
life away, lad.
[sighs and gasps]
Definitely definitely definitely not.
Definitely not. I was out yesterday
out. Done a lot in four years.
Definitely not wasting my life away,
lad. I've done more in my life than
you've done in your life. And you're
older [snorts] than me.
Believe you me, I've done more in my
life than you've done in your life. Um,
[sighs and gasps] the housemaid
Yeah, good for you, bro. No one cares
about that Skint virgin.
I don't know why you keep bringing the
Skint virgin up. No one cares.
What he needs to go to is a [ __ ]
dentist and sort them missing teeth out.
Is that a good one, Grezy? That was a
good one, wasn't it, Grezy?
That was a good one.
How about you go to a dentist?
I like that one. I added that one in
there cuz people should be going to the dentist, you know. Yeah.
Go to the dentist and sort them [ __ ]
teeth out, you skin [ __ ]
But I need to be careful what I'm
saying, Steven Howard,
cuz LT might pop in again,
and start crying. So, I need to be He's
very touchy with his boyfriend, is he? So,
I need to be uh
I need to be careful, lad.
Isn't that right, Greavves? He's very
touchy with his boyfriend. I don't want
to don't want to say anything untowards
cuz he will start crying about this
girlfriend. So, I need to be careful
what I'm saying in it, lad.
[snorts and clears throat]
I'm not wasting my life on YouTube. I've
done a lot in 3 years.
Been to loads of places. Been to loads of restaurants.
Like I said, today I didn't go out
except once. So, if I wasn't on YouTube,
I would just been in.
Brother, what did I tell you about self
projection in 2026, lad?
What did I tell you? What wh why do you
why do you white knight over some
lanky skint virgin anyways?
Yeah, of course they're jealous, bro.
They're skinn. They're low life. They
got no money. Just like this guy, bro,
right here. this little self projector.
He's white knighting. He's Do you know
why I think a lot of the people white
knight this guy? Because I I think a lot
of the reason they white this guy is cuz
they're ugly like him. That's another
reason. It's like what you were saying.
He has a lot of white knights. Steven
Howard, I think it's because they see
themsel in him.
That's why they get like assy when you
talk about him and [ __ ] bro.
They proper all white knight him as well.
It's jealousy, bro. I'm better looking
than all of them, bro. Trust you.
I'm better looking than him as well.
Yeah, I'm a lonely virgin. Bro, listen.
What did I tell you about self projecting?
Yeah, he gets disabled with he gets sex
with a disabled girl. Yeah, I don't want
sex with a disabled girl. I don't pray
on the vulnerable.
And I'd rather live with my mommy than
live in a cancel shitty bedsit.
I'd rather [snorts] live with my mom.
Yeah, I'd rather live with my mom than
live in a cancel bed with a disabled
girl. But [snorts] yeah.
Yeah, of course they're camera shy, bro.
They don't even leave the house delayed. Yeah,
proper proper white knights, bro.
Proper proper white knights.
L2 does it as well.
[snorts] No, never in my life have I
lied about sleeping with anyone.
Anyways, you can get banned now. See you later, lad.
Go back to your boyfriend's channel.
Let's see if I got an email back from LT.
He can't even email me back cuz he knows
I'm right, lad.
Hey, Dusty. I emailed him. Yeah. I said,
"How comes you keep white knight in non
legs every time I call him a virgin? Is
he your boyfriend or something?" when
he's calling me a virgin. Why don't you
talk about the [ __ ] and sig, you bias
funny. He He didn't reply back. I said,
"You're a biased Fanny."
[laughter] Cuz he knows that's his boyfriend.
All right. That's his boyfriend, Dusty.
I'm going to end up getting in trouble
again, you know. Bro, I'm going to end
up getting This guy's going to end up
beefing with me again, bro.
You know that Greavesy,
how many times you know this guy has got
a lot I've I've got into a lot of
arguments over this guy. I've got into
it with Jo. I've got it to it with LT.
This guy has got a lot of boyfriends.
No, I'm not going to end up nicked. Why
am I going to end up nicked?
They've got a lot of um he's got a lot
of boyfriends, don't he? Steven Howard.
He's got a lot of boyfriends, bro.
He's got a lot of boyfriends. Strange. Yeah, man.
No one cares about a girlfriend. Come
back when you showed what I was showing
me getting a [ __ ] Come back when you
show you in bed naked with women. Then
come back to me. When you can come back
and show something other than a girlfriend,
then come back to me, bro. I think
that's a fair analogy, isn't it?
Yeah, [snorts] bro.
That is mad.
Of course they're from the same sim
skill score, bro. Yeah.
I don't know why somebody would simp
someone that they had problems with
and try to get them in [ __ ] It just
doesn't make sense. Why would you simp
someone like that? That don't make no
sense, bro, when you've had problems
with them yourself.
Like, okay, the guy's got a a girlfriend
with disabilities. That's not sex. The
same way as a [ __ ] is not sex. If a
blowjob's not sex, then a girlfriend
with with disabilities is not sex.
You literally don't know if they've had
sex or not. You literally don't have no
proof. If you're if you're if you're
turn around and you're saying to me that
my my [ __ ] video and my kisses and my
bedding naked with women ain't proof,
then bro, how is that proof then?
Yeah. So, you can't answer it. So, we'll
move on now anyways cuz you know I'm
right, bro. Simple.
How was that proof then? Simple.
What are you? Are you their love life or
something? Are you a fly in the wall
madness? Is it bro? See, people on here
don't like to admit the truth.
It's the same thing with the money
thing. Steven Howard, I've shown more
money than than all of the people on
here. They still talk [ __ ]
Nons has not shown more money than me.
That is he has not shown more money than me.
That was his daddy's money. Um, and he
has not shown more money than me. And
that was years ago. But again, they
pretend that he has. That's like
everything on here, lad.
It's going all right, man.
>> [snorts and sighs]
>> No, that's you, bro. Self projecting.
See you later, lad. Get kicked. [sighs] [snorts]
Yeah, it's going all right, bro. Yeah, dude. do.
Yeah. And I showed more money than them
and they made their own excuses up.
[gasps] Oh, you can't show it now. You
What the [ __ ] bro?
[gasps and sighs]
Yeah. It's the truth, is it?
But like I said, if they ever bring up
the girlfriend thing again, we just talk
over it, Steven Howard. We won't pay no mind, lad.
For the reasons I mentioned in it, so we
will just keep doing it either way.
We just pretend that we didn't hear it in it.
That's [snorts] like, do you know that's
like calling, bro? That's like calling
me calling someone like me a virgin is
like calling Johnny Sins a virgin.
It doesn't make sense. It's like calling
Johnny Sins a virgin.
Pretty much. Someone calling me a virgin
is like calling a porn star a virgin.
Doesn't make any sense. Yeah, literally.
And he's like, "Oh, we bully you, LT.
You have never bullied no one." Just
like the people on here have never
bullied no one. Like I said, we all end
up seeing what you people look like.
There's no we, bro. There's no we.
There's literally you we had to
continuously say to this guy, "Bro, I'm
better looking than you." I don't know
why you keep calling me clapped.
But I'm better looking than you, lad.
I'm better looking than you will ever
be. So, I don't know why you keep
talking about people being a mon when
when they're better looking than you, lad.
You need to stop getting excited.
Just cuz you was caught defending your boyfriend.
Sick of women. I don't deal with them anymore, bro.
So, I I can't relate. I gave up months ago.
I know she can't.
Anyways, let's move on from these
wasters now. Anyways, bro, we know that
they're biased and that. Anyways, um I'm
going to be setting up a new channel,
lad, and I'm going to
comment it and then delete the comment. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Yeah. He's another He's another one of
these people, lad. Yeah, exactly, bro.
And also remember Steven Howard when
they used to call Monty man a grass
but yet when this guy talks about grass
and he gets thumbs up
that the money the virgin thing like I
said bro it's multiple things.
It's multiple things. It's also like
with police and money as well lad.
It's like [ __ ] stupid LT.
Um, I said multiple multiple multiple
times, "Oh yeah, like the coach told me
to report him." He's like, "Oh, don't
grass, bro. Don't grass."
I said, "Bro, your boyfriend's been
grassing." Why don't you go and tell
your boyfriend that he's a grass instead
of telling other people
instead of telling other people about
them being grasses? Why don't you go on
your channel? Why don't you go on your
boyfriend's channel once in a while and
call him a virgin? Why don't Sorry, call
him a grass. [ __ ] virgin. Why don't
you call him a grass?
You know what I'm saying? Instead of sing
for this little [ __ ] waster, right,
bro? I need to calm down, bro. Because I
if I start this [ __ ] I will finish it,
bro. This time I will actually finish
it, bro. This guy is literally not worth
getting locked up over, bro. Trust me,
he's not worth getting locked up over.
Believe you me, bro. Yeah, simple, bro. [snorts] simple.
But [snorts] yeah.
Yeah, it's weird, isn't it, bro?
Yeah, they literally all s for
you know that's the right word. You know
when you started saying that it's the
truth. They actually do
weirdo, isn't it?
But yeah, we're doing this new channel
soon anyways, bro. So, where are you um
where you going to be commenting on, lad? Um,
where are you going to be commenting on
so I can give you this channel, bro?
cuz we want to do madnesses and we want
to save like we want to get [ __ ] and
And obviously we can't have people
watching us and recording us, bro, when
we're doing this. We don't like little grasses,
you know what I mean?
[snorts] Little grasses
on here. So yeah,
they will not find it, bro. They haven't
found my They haven't found my
approaching channel. They will never
find it. They will never find it. I've
got a new channel, bro, where I do
approaches and everything. They don't
know about it. It's got no subscribers.
They won't find it, lad. Trust me. They
won't find it. [snorts]
I don't want these people following me,
bro. Simple as that.
They won't find it, lad. Um
because their priorities change. Bro, listen.
I'm being serious about this new channel, bro.
No, no, no, dude. I'm being serious.
I don't want to go back live on this channel, bro.
Because of the grassing the other day,
like to the police and stuff and whatever.
Yeah, I had to go to the police station
the other day. I didn't get arrested or
anything, but still, bro, I don't want
to entertain a load of grasses,
you know? So, that's what I'm saying to
you. Like, I we let's do it on this.
Let's go live and talk about football
bets and stuff on another channel.
They won't find it, bro. Seriously, they
won't find it. And I'll close this
channel down, bro. I'm serious.
So, we'll just carry on as normal, but
they won't know where we are.
Trust me, it's the best way, lad,
because there is some normal people in
here and that, but obviously, I don't want them
I don't want them on this. I don't want
them on this. I don't want them watching me.
You gave me that. So yeah, it tpjx@yahoo.com
cuz I don't want these people following
me like this. Jamie Tonson, uh Jamie
Thompson, Virgin Boy, Red Star, all of
these little grasses. I don't want them
I don't want them following me, lad.
And I'm dead. I'm I'm being serious, bro. Seriously,
I don't want these little creeps
following me. So, it could be me, you,
Great Grezy, a couple of other people.
We can talk about football and [ __ ]
bro. I might even do content on that
channel, bro. I will do content on that
channel. I just don't want these people
following me, bro. So,
yeah. Emma, everyone's got my email
anyways, bro. But yeah. [sighs]
Yeah. [snorts] And I don't want these
people following me, bro, as well. I
don't want to put any content on this
channel. I don't like these people
recording me, following me.
They proved what they're about multiple
times, lad. So that's what I'm saying
about the other channel. Is it
like these are the ones that are being
keyboard warriors, bro? I'm I'm not
being a keyboard warrior. Yeah.
Yeah. And Kieran will know about it as
well when he comes on. [snorts]
Yeah, he caused it. Bro,
these are the people that start. They
start on me, JNA. I'm not interested in
these little jealous keyboard warriors
like [snorts] Virgin Boy and Red Star.
I'm not interested in them, bro. I'm not
interested in these little weasels,
these little skint low lives.
And I will do content, but I'm not doing
content on this channel.
I don't want these people watching me. I
don't even want to give them the
satisfaction of even watching content videos. So
little stinky dirty grasses.
So and that's that bro it.
[snorts] Whoever done it, bro. Simple as
that. You want to go around being a
grass, you get deprived of content.
Simple as that. So yeah. So they just
defeat the whole object really. But
that's just part of their low IQ. Simple.
Well, no, it's in the wardrobe.
So, I'm not going in my wardrobe right now. So, yeah.
I need to go to bed in a minute. Did I
get an email or what? Let me see. Told
you my email. >> [snorts] >> Yeah.
We should make our own little community,
bro. Take some of the good people from
this community and make our own little
in it, Dusty. make our own little community.
Know what I mean, bro?
No LT, no Virgin Boy, no LJ,
none of them will know about the
channel, bro. None of them.
No Joe F. No, none of them.
They're not let bro let letting them run
me off. How am I letting them run me
off, bro? I've been on YouTube for
almost [ __ ] 6 hours.
They're not running me off. They're
keyboard wobbers and I don't want them
watching me. How is that running me off
when it's my choice?
No, bro. They're grasses,
bro. They're literally police informants.
They're literally grasses that never
meet anyone. What do you want me to do,
bro? Spend 30 years arguing with police
informants. Jealous little grasses. Why
am I going to do that, bro? But we can
just go on another channel and ignore
them and that will get to them more.
What do you want me to do, bro? Go live
every day arguing with them. Arguing
with jealous people?
Think about it, bro. Like, what what's the alternative?
So, like, no, bro.
Not at all.
What's the alternative, lad?
No, these people are not even worth it,
bro. Dusty, that's why you don't see me
on YouTube for weeks, bro. Cuz they're
not even worth it, lad. You think when
I'm not on YouTube, when I weren't on
YouTube for two weeks, I couldn't come
on YouTube, lad. No, I just didn't want
to waste my time with these people. They're pathetic.
They're pathetic, bro.
Pathetic low lives. Jealous low lives.
What the [ __ ] lad? [snorts] Yeah, bro. Anyways,
I'm gone, lad.
So, yeah. I'll see you later. Yeah.