Let's see if we have any luck today.
Closing this [ __ ] down.
If they don't close it, I'm just going
to get someone to change my password,
bro. Simples. I'll just get someone to
change the password on it like I did at
the old house. They whack me 8 pound as
well as well as rigging the tables.
[ __ ] dirty dirty [ __ ]
If you Oh, here's the thing. I'm going
to if you don't. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Yeah, that's funny as [ __ ] bro. All
right, one second.
Yeah, bro. [ __ ] hell, man. I should
have recorded it. Roulette's the same
rigged roulette. That never changes.
It's like at this point, you just kind
of expect it now, isn't it?
How people in 2026 can still deny the
fact that that shit's fixed. Um, which
is only the reason why I've come on here
basically to say that it's so so so
fixed. They definitely definitely do
control the outcome. Even when it's just
25 pound spins, it misses every number.
It literally there's no they might they
might as well just take numbers away
that you bet on because it doesn't go in
any number but the losers.
people £8 to deposit. What the [ __ ] bro?
Sorry, my shit's a bit laggy, bro.
But no, it's definitely definitely
definitely it is definitely fixed. Even
2025 pound spins, I thought, oh, let me
just let me just try and uh same thing
again. I haven't won since Christmas.
Isn't that funny? Do you not find it a
bit funny how you can put five teams on
a football and somehow you win, but then
whenever you play roulette, it's just it
just seeks out losing numbers. Does Does
anyone else not find that a bit strange?
Does anyone else not find that a bit
odd? I find it very very odd, but
everyone's got everyone's got different
opinions on it. It's so so fixed.
It loves that number 31.
It loves that number 31, doesn't it, bro? Yeah. Yeah, bro.
It is fixed. You don't even need to bet
big money on it. It's so fixed. It's so
so so so fixed.
It's so I've never known something so
fixed in my life. Yeah.
Something so fixed like that, bro. It's so fixed.
Right. Anyways, where we uh
That's hilarious, bro. Hilarious.
So, anyways, I'm going to get someone to
change his password anyways if they
refuse to close it. Um,
I'm thinking, what the [ __ ] More's come
out than £100.
Yeah, I'm gonna um change the password
if they don't um if they don't close it.
That's how we're going to do it. Yeah.
So yeah, you either close his account now
or um I'm just going to change the
passwords and I won't be able to go back
on anyways. So simple as that.
I'm going to try and get my cat out the
bastards before I do it though to be fair.
So so so so fixed.
It loves the number 31.
And you know what? The reason I'm not
getting mad today, bro, is cuz I just
can't be bothered with it. I can't be
asked with it anymore going bad and all
that. I can't be bothered, bro. I
really, really can't be bothered with it.
But I just want them to see what they
can give me. You know, I'm tired and it's cold.
But yeah, how people try to say it's not
fixed that that [ __ ] roulette is is
they got something wrong with them, bro.
They really have got something wrong with them.
Cuz the odds are better on roulette than the football.
You're not coming to see anyone. Shut
up. You're boring. See you later.
No retards on my channel. I've literally
only come back to talk about this quickly, lad.
No, I just thought I'd try with £100,
bro. Someone owes me money anyway. So,
like I just thought I'd try with 100.
No, not at all, bro.
No, it's not even about resisting the
urge. No, I'm just lying in bed cold. I
thought a try.
Not even, bro. Not even.
I can't even be bothered to be honest.
I really, really can't be asked.
It's madness, isn't it?
I was just playing roulette.
I'm just talking to someone.
I said, "No, I was just playing um
roulette." So, I thought I'd come and um
tell everyone how it's fixed and that
otherwise I wouldn't have been on it.
And I don't know why you're so bothered,
bro. I don't know why why you're so
bothered with what I say and what I do. Anyways,
like I said, I don't know why why it
bothers you so much to be honest. You
can't even take an hour off of YouTube
for [ __ ] sake, bro. Like, you
shouldn't worry about what I say.
That's my opinion. You shouldn't be You
shouldn't worry about what I'm saying.
I'm only come on here because of this
[ __ ] to talk about this [ __ ]
shitty thing, this shitty website, you know? Right.
Madness, isn't it?
So, yeah, I'm probably going to get this
bonus, see what I can get with this
bonus, and then I'm probably going to
just change the passwords on it. I'm
just going to get someone to change the
passwords on it. So, either way, I will
not be able to get back on it. So,
simple as that. I think this is the
first time in a week, maybe a bit more
than that. I don't play it often. I just
thought of trying it.
How they say though, how they sit there
and say it isn't fixed though is is
beyond me, bro.
How they sit there and say that is
and they charge £8 for the deposit as well.
They transfer the deposits as well, lad.
No, I won't be live for long. I'm just
talking about rig roulette.
That's all, man. I just tried a one on
it and nothing again. Same story. It
loves the number 31, doesn't it? It
loves the same rigged areas and the same rigged numbers.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] bro. is such
[ __ ] How anyone still defends that
is mad to me, bro. Oh, it definitely
definitely is rigged. Oh, no. It
definitely definitely is.
No, no, no. It definitely definitely
definitely 100% is.
I'm not I'm not even debating that. It
definitely is. 100% it is. I covered um
90 numbers and I missed four spins.
No, it definitely definitely definitely
is fixed. 100% it is fixed. I was
covering 80 90 numbers and it missed
four times or five times. [ __ ]
Absolute bollocks. You never get five,
six streaks in a row. It's [ __ ]
No, Roulette is definitely definitely definitely fixed.
It is 100%. I've played on this now
about six times over the past two months.
It definitely definitely 100% it is fixed.
My numbers don't come. So, stop trying
to stop trying to change the subject.
Oh, it definitely is fixed. It doesn't
matter if they're playing at the same
time. It's definitely definitely fixed.
Mathematically, it's not possible to
cover 80 90 numbers and keep missing.
You're not even going to try and justify
it to me. So, don't even waste your
don't even waste your time. Um, Coke.
uh two plastic bottles.
So yeah, let's see what they're saying. Anyways, uh
see what they're saying on here. Take
advantage of these um sites. But no, it
definitely definitely is. 100% it is
mathematically. It's not possible.
Trust me, bro. Like you're not you're
not going to try to justify to someone
like me. Trust me. Because I know more
than anyone. You know it is.
Don't you think I'd be putting more in
right now if I didn't think it was?
Don't you think I'd be chasing? If I
generally didn't think it was, I'd be
putting more money in, bro.
But obviously, I'm not going to do it
cuz it is fixed. I mean, there's been so
many videos on it as well.
It definitely 100 million% is fixed.
100% it is. It is.
It really, really, really, really,
really, really is. You can't miss that
many times. It's [ __ ] When you're
covering 80, 90 numbers and you've
missed four times in a row, would you
hit four times in a row? No, you would
not. So, simple as that.
Yeah, man. It seeks the loss in numbers.
And the site is dodgy to begin with.
Anyways, the site is dodgy to begin
with. £8 to deposit, won't close your account down.
No, I didn't record it. Proof or what? I
know it's fixed. I don't need I don't
need to record it for proof. There's
enough proof videos out there
where it keeps seeking out the losing
numbers and going on whatever you ain't
got. That's why I hardly ever play it.
That's why I God knows why I chucked 100
pound on it right now. It's [ __ ]
fixed as [ __ ]
God knows why to be honest.
But no, it definitely definitely
definitely is fixed. There's so many
videos out there showing magnets and
[ __ ] as well. is [ __ ] And it's not
even just that. It's the You can't miss
that many times in a row. You're not
even going to try justify it to me
because mathematically it's not
possible. Mathematically, you can't
cover 90 numbers and keep missing.
You're not even going to try and justify
it to me. You've covered more than one
area of the wheel and it keeps
continuously missing. There's no way in
hell's bells ever.
Simple. So, that's that.
It is fixed as [ __ ] Simple as that. So,
it is fixed. If you kept doing this
every day, every other day, or every
week, whatever, you would never ever
ever win. Trust me, that's the thing.
You never ever ever win.
How do people sit there and say that
it's random when it blatantly is rigged?
I don't understand that. Yeah.
But that's that in it.
So you tell me Greavves if it's not
rigged. How have you missed four times
in a row when you've covered 1890 numbers?
1890 numbers but you've missed four
times in a row. Really? What was it?
Just unlucky, was it? Just Just unlucky.
Nah, you're talking to me, bro. You're
not talking to an idiot. You're talking
to me, lad.
You are literally talking to me.
And then, and if it's not dodgy, then so
why Okay, then. So, why won't they close
your account down when you ask? When you
ask, why won't they close your account
down? And why won't they put a deposit
limit on your account when you've asked several times?
Yeah, because it is fixed. That's why
I have not seen a five, eight, 11 in any
of the sessions that I played. But I
guess it's just bad luck for the mill
time yet. When somebody covers five
teams on the football, somehow they win,
which is what was it? That was but yet
yeah yet yeah yet yeah yet yeah yet yeah
yet yeah yet yeah yet yeah yet yeah yet
yeah yet yeah yet when you bet on the
football which is what 100 to one was
that what was that better that must have
been 100 to one
no 100 to one [ __ ] 10 to one sorry
it was 10 to one you seem to win
something's fishy bro come on now let's
not play stupid you know
and I don't know how People lose and
they're so calm about it. Grievesy, I'm
I'm not calm about it. I'm just holding it in.
I'm just holding it in because I
literally just can't be bothered, bro. I
ain't got the energy for it. Yeah,
I ain't got the energy, bro. To be fair.
That's [ __ ] up, bro. Really [ __ ] up.
I don't know how people are so calm when
they lose. I'd love to know the secret,
Greavesy. I'd love to know the secret,
lad. You know,
I would love to actually know the secret.
And if I was going to react, I wouldn't
react on here anyways cuz obviously the
grasses and [ __ ] which is the whole
point of the new channel. So, I mean, even then,
people just seem to lose and they're
just okay with it. I'd love to know how
they do it, Grezy. They seem to just be
okay with it. Not me, bro. I see demons
in my head. I don't understand how these
people just get so they're just happy with losing
and they'll be like, "Oh yeah, you're
the one that done it." I said, "Yeah, I
did the I am the one that done it and
I'm now the one that's reacting to it."
So what does that even mean? You know,
see, I'm annoyed now, bro. But you know,
and that was £100. I've got more than
£100. I'm not going to feed. I'm not
going to starve. See,
doesn't matter what money you lose. Just
I think just losing on that is annoying.
Just losing because you know it's fixed
as well. That's another thing. You know,
it's not even a fair game, you know.
But my numbers don't come in. So that's
a silly question. They they don't come
in. It's fixed as [ __ ] Yeah,
it is fixed as [ __ ]
Why I even play that, bro? I should never know.
Could have bought a new Lego set with that Grezy.
Trust me, you'd have winning sessions.
If it wasn't rigged, you'd have winning
sessions. What happens is you either put
money in and you lose or
or you might win£120
and as soon as you up the ante it misses
everything. That's my favorite word, up
the ante. But it's not rigged yet. You
can literally win a football bet that's
10 to one with five teams quite easily,
but yet as soon as you go on that wheel,
you lose. Isn't that funny, mate? But
it's not R. It's not rigged because they
don't have to rig it.
Okay, bro. Whatever.
Yeah. And I ain't got a [ __ ] hole in
my backside if that's not rigged. Yeah.
You literally would hit some numbers.
It's really fixed, isn't it, Grezy? I
don't know why they rig it. They're
going to win in the end.
The odds are stacked against the player.
So, I don't know why they rig it. They
don't have to, but they definitely do.
They definitely do.
Am I meeting LT today? No. Why the [ __ ]
would I be meeting that clown?
Why am I meeting that clown?
I'm not meeting any clown from this
community, bro. Are you [ __ ] mad?
I'm not meeting that [ __ ] clown.
Yeah. I'm scared, bro. I'm terrified.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm so terrified, bro. You
got me. Yeah. You ain't making Why is
anyone going to meet anyone on this
community, bro, when you're all [ __ ]
grasses? That's another thing as well.
Why would anyone a waste their time on
people that are not even worth the time
a day and b your grasses? Why would
anyone waste their time on that? Truth
be told, Grezy, I'm only on here because
I wanted to talk about the roulette
being rigged. I wouldn't have come on
here today if it wasn't for for some
reason. Whenever you gamble, you feel
the need to come on here and rant. It's
always been a thing for as long as I can remember.
Yeah, I know. I'm scared, bro. I'm
terrified, bro. You got me, man. You
know me better than myself. Yeah.
The people in this community, they're
not even worth spitting on, bro. That's
how that's how bad it is. They're not
even worth spitting on.
They said they gave me a bonus. I want
to try and get some money from this bonus.
Right. Anyways, see you later, lad.
This is exactly why I don't come on this
community, Grezy. Unless it's other than
like, yeah, I've just played roulette
and that cuz it's just the same people
doing the same [ __ ] It's boring, bro.
It's 2026. It's literally boring. 2026, same wasters. Yeah.
Did you not see that Arsenal Mark thing yesterday, Grezy?
How long has this guy been doing this for now?
How long has this guy I don't even Bro,
they're not even worth talking about.
But I had to I had to bring it up, bro.
Sorry. Like, they're not even worth talking about.
But you get the point I'm trying to I'm
trying to make. Like, how how long have
they been doing this for now, man?
You know what I'm saying?
A very long time, bro. A very long time.
Anyways, I'm going I'm going to come off
in about 5 minutes anyways, lad. So, yeah. Yeah,
>> people lose money on roulette grezy and
they're just fine with it like secular slots.
They're fine with losing and then and
they somehow seem to be okay with it.
Not me, bro. I hate losing on that [ __ ]
As you know, bro, as as you know, you
like if I was to gamble before a night
out and I lost, I would just go straight
back home and go to bed. It's literally
that bad, bro. Really, really, really that bad.
I don't know how people are so calm.
I feel like I've been degraded and
disrespected. And I don't care if I if
I've done it. I don't care if I chose to
do it. I literally don't care. That's
the way it is. Simple as that. You know,
yeah. And you start feel like you're
losing your mind as well. I start
feeling like I'm losing my mind whenever
I play that [ __ ] bro. I don't know
about anyone else.
I feel like I'm losing my mind, bro.
Some people seem to be fine with it,
though. They don't mind losing. Oh, it's
just a game. Oh, better luck next time.
Nah, not with me, mate. Not with me.
Definitely, definitely. Definitely not with me.
Yeah. What's your opinion on it, Grezy?
I love the people that think, yeah,
because you've lost a small amount of
money or you've still got money left,
that makes it okay. I love that, bro. I
love it when people say, "Oh, well, you
still got money." Nah, bro. I could have
a million pounds and I don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah. You remember that car story the
other day, Grezy?
You remember the car story the other day
with with a person
and I was chasing the car and they drove off. Yeah.
But as long as you gamble within your
means, it's completely fine. That's what
they say, bro.
That's what they say to you, bro, on
adverts. That's what Secular [ __ ] says.
because you still have money. That's
fine. That's how they see it. No, it
isn't fine, bro. Nothing is fine about
any any of it. It could be 20 pound, it
could be £50, it could be £100.
You are playing like when people play,
they play to win. They don't play to
lose. Do you understand?
I don't know about anyone else,
bro. It's bad enough even if you didn't
even lose on it.
I've done it before where I haven't even
lost. I just got my money back and it
was giving me mood swings.
So yeah, and if you say it to anyone,
they just put it down to addiction when
you you're literally not addicted. They
don't believe that someone can gamble
responsibly and it affect them. They
don't seem to think that. They think,
"Oh, it's okay. It's money you can
afford to lose."
But it's not okay. Even if you're not
addicted, it's it's literally not okay.
You know, like I've literally ditched
people over it before, you know?
It's really, really, really, really bad.
And it's always been the same way as
well. Doesn't matter how much money you
have, it doesn't matter. Losing is not
an option. Simple. No one wants to lose
on it. Simple. And no one wants to even
get their money back from it either.
That's the way I That's That's the way
my mind works. I don't know about anyone else, but yeah,
maybe it's just me. Hey, so
it was so bad yesterday. I had to drink
Guinness to calm down, bro. I literally
had to drink a Guinness to actually calm down.
That's how bad it was. I think that's
probably why I started drinking on the
Monday to be honest because I don't
drink anymore. It's really really bad.
I don't know how people are okay with
it. I'd love to know their secret, you know. But yeah,
it's so [ __ ] annoying. It is so bastard annoying. Yeah.
I want to see if they give me this 30
pound. I can just straight I can just
withdraw it. I want to really [ __ ] these
people. I want to [ __ ] him over, bro. Yeah,
but I don't have the energy. Seriously,
bro, I really don't have the energy
and my mind starts racing as well, bro.
When it happens, it starts thinking of
bad things that any good, it will make
things bad. It literally is a fuel for negativity.
how people don't understand this. I I
seriously seriously seriously don't
know, you know.
They seem to be fine with losing.
Not me, mate. Not me. Not me.
Doesn't matter what it is.£10, 10 pound,
20 pound, 30 pound, 40 pound. If I was a
billionaire, I don't give a [ __ ] Um,
you know, simple as that. I'll make my
point across if I lose. It's as simple
as that, you know. And it's blatantly
rigged as well. It's not even like you
can win on it. It's not like you've won
and then the next day you've lost. It's
it's continuous with it. Even if it's
over a period of time,
there's, oh, your bonus has been added.
Thank you for that. I hope you get
lucky. Yeah, you hope I get lucky on a
[ __ ] rigged casino. I don't think
that's going to happen.
Yeah. One second. Let me see if I can
withdraw this money. Hold on.
They gave me £30. I'm just going to withdraw it.
I'm a [ __ ] aren't I, bro? I'm a proper
Let me see if I can withdraw this, bro.
Their little golden tactics are mad as
well, though, if you think about it.
Right. Let me let me put this spin on roulette.
This is money that they've gave me. Yeah. One second. No, no.
Yeah. Isn't that funny? It comes in when
you're using their money. Huh?
Yeah. What coincidence, huh?
Yeah, it comes in when you're using
their money. That's funny, isn't it?
Yeah, that's funny as [ __ ] That
all the numbers are coming in when
you're using their money. H, that's interesting. Yeah.
And there we go. The rig 16. Isn't it
funny how these numbers come in when
you're using their money? Huh? That's
strange. Very strange.
Yeah, I love that, man.
That is so fixed. It just took my bet
off and then went on 11. Oh,
it literally it literally took my bet
off and then went on 11.
I love it, bro. Love it.
Oh, there's a max limit on it on set.
Yeah, of course it would be. And it went
on 11 as well.
You got to laugh, bro. You got to laugh.
Right. Let me see. Anyways, I'll come
back. I need to concentrate on
Yeah. Isn't that strange how you start
hitting with bonus money? Huh?
That's a strange coincidence, isn't it,
Grezy? With bonus money, you seem to
start hitting money that you can't even withdraw.
But your buddy Oh, no. You miss
everything every time. Decline the bet
and win 11. Of course you did.
I have to wager £1,200.
Yeah, I've got a wager £1,200.
What the [ __ ]
So, guess I have to go in some slots then.
It's funny how it seems to play on bonus
money, but to be fair, that's been going
for years where it's done that because
you can't withdraw the money in it
because it's it's it's bonus money, you see. All
right, let's try
I'm just I'm just wagering on this [ __ ] slot.
This game should be good for ra
Sorry, bro. Just playing this slot.
Bro, you're on YouTube every day. You
don't need to worry about me, lad.
You're on YouTube 24/7.
Don't worry about me.
Yeah, I'm just playing this slot. You know
All All right, back to roulette now.
Yeah, I just tried 100 on roulette
and then they gave me a bonus. It's so
fixed that online roulette, bro.
They make it go on loing numbers.
Yeah, they make it go on loing numbers. Yeah, defin
Yeah, definitely fix that. Screw that up.
Distics and [ __ ] No,
nope. The zero section it loves.
Love that zero section on it. Wow.
It loves that zero section, don't it?
It loves that zero section, doesn't it, bro?
It loves that zero section. This was
only bonus money they gave me.
Huh? But people on YouTube still defend
it. Oh, they don't need to cheat. They
don't need to cheat. Yeah. All right,
mate. They don't need to cheat. Okay,
You keep telling yourself that. Anyways,
uh back to this [ __ ] now.
I don't know how people still defend it.
um trying to say they don't need to
cheat when they blatantly blatantly blatantly do.
They literally make it go on losing
numbers on purpose. They literally do. I
don't know how people can sit there and
and still say they don't when they they
[ __ ] well do cuz it always goes on
the same area of the table every single
time. This was just bonus money that
they gave me. It wasn't my own money.
[ __ ] that, bro. Anyways, I'm about to
try to close this account now again.
They literally make it go on losing numbers.
They don't need to cheat,
but they do. So, One second.
They might not need to, but they do. That's my Anyways,
I'm gone anyways. See you later.