Yo,
self projection earlier, man. I was
going to do a video on it, but I was
like, nah, they're not even they're not
even worth responding to.
Just self projectors, isn't it?
Or as Monty was calling, self-reflectors. Yeah.
We'll see how long it takes people to join.
See if they've got a live. Yeah, we'll see.
up. Two people already [ __ ] bro.
[ __ ] boring today, ain't it?
just chilling, bro.
Yeah, man. I went on L J's live earlier.
Well, I didn't go when he's I watched
the live back cuz it come up my thing.
Serious serious self projecting, bro.
Yeah, bro. You You would have thought
they'd get bored, is it? You would have
thought they would have got bored in
2026 of self projecting. But no,
self projecting, bro.
Proper proper self projecting.
I was going to do a video, but they're
not even worth replying to, bro.
No, not even worth replying to, lad.
saying that I've wasted my life on here.
I haven't and firstly I haven't even
been on here 10 years. I didn't even
know about Timmy 10 years ago. A B I
haven't been on here 10 years. And C I
have done more than you in 28 years and
you've done at almost 50 years of age.
So look who's talking. Sad bastard.
And they're very weird as well. Like
they're trying to say, "Oh, people have
got their big money today, bro. You
don't know what money people get and you
don't know when people get it. If you
actually had money of your own and you
stopped self self-reflecting,
uh, you wouldn't be doing this.
How is someone at almost 50 years of age
that's been on here longer than you try
to tell you you've wasted your life?
I've I've been on here for like seven
years and I've lived my life whilst I've
been on here. Something that you ain't
done. Stop self projecting.
[ __ ] bro. Yeah. There's like, oh yeah,
this person gets their big money today
and that. It's like, bro, you don't know
when people get money. You don't know
what day they get money. You don't know anything.
So, you must be talking about yourself.
You must seriously be talking about
yourself, man. But anyways, that's all I
wanted to say about that. Yeah,
proper proper Mongs, bro. Proper Mongs.
Yeah. Self projecting.
I haven't been out. I need to I need to
shave my I need to shave my beard, bro. [ __ ]
It's getting long, bro. It's getting
annoying. I was either going to buy a
razor today or go to the barbers, but
I'm not going out drinking for a while,
so I thought I'll just leave it.
But yeah, I don't know, bro. Needs to be
trimmed. It's getting really long. Madness
doesn't feel right, you know. Yeah. Yeah,
I know, but I need to get it trimmed.
Look, I need to get it trimmed, bro.
It's [ __ ] Yeah,
it's annoying, bro. Annoying as [ __ ] Yeah.
Maybe I'll go Bob this week, bro.
You know what I'm saying?
They'll never change, bro. Never change. Never.
Look at that beard, bro. Look how long it is.
People on here could never grow that beard, bro.
But yeah, I haven't even been on YouTube
for 10 years. So, how do you make that?
How do you work that one out? And the
years that I have been on YouTube, I've
lived my life on YouTube, unlike you,
you know? So, how do you work that one
out when I've not even been on YouTube
10 years? I didn't even know about this
community 10 years ago. So,
how do you work that one out?
Really, how do you work that one out?
I knew about Timmy when I was 19 and I
come on here when I was 21.
How would the [ __ ] is that 10 years, you [ __ ] idiot?
Get your facts right before talking about people.
Yeah, bro. Yeah. Yeah, man.
I'm not subbed, but it come up on um
sometimes it comes up and I'm definitely
definitely not sub to that kind. So, I
just scrolled through it. You see, he's
he's projecting, bro. That's what they
like to do on that channel. Project.
They love projecting for some reason,
bro. Year in year out.
Projection. Projection. Projection. It's embarrassing, bro.
talking about themselves every day. Like
I said, you would have thought they'd
got they would have got bored of it, but
yeah, telling me that I'm wasting my
life when I've literally lived my life
on here and I haven't been on here for
10 years. A and he's older than me and
I've done more than him in my life and
I'm younger than him
and I'm younger than him. Think about
it, bro. And I I've wasted He's been on
it longer than me. I haven't been on
here [ __ ] 10 years. I've been on here
since I was 2122. And what did I do since 2122?
Not what the not I haven't done what
your little followers have done. Sit on
YouTube 24/7 self projecting. I've
actually gone to places and live life.
What the [ __ ] bro? Guy's a [ __ ]
clown, man. He's a [ __ ] clown, lad. What's up? Anyways,
yeah, I was on Reddit earlier, bro. I
was doing a little bit of You know what?
It's funny, bro. Yeah. Earlier.
Yeah. Might go for a drink next week. I
don't know. Probably not.
But I need to go to the barber, isn't
it? So, I don't want to go barbers. I'm
not going out. So, yeah. I cleaned the
lens. Look at that, man. Look at that lovely beard.
Do you remember UK asylum? I can't get
over that, bro. I was thinking of that today
when I went on the celebrity crushes on
a different forum. Made me laugh.
I just can't get over that because
just bling copying
literally bling copying l copycat.
Oh, someone's typing. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, I'm having them kebabs today.
Yeah, definitely having them kebabs today, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, I did. It was nice.
I want to try the chicken one. Yeah, I
tried it yesterday with
Yeah. Give it a whirl. I would
I would give it a whirl.
I'm speaking to this person in India.
Yeah. You don't know how there's Oh,
yeah. If you come over here, we can get
married and stuff. You know how it works
in them countries. They just get married
like that. So if they like someone, they
will propose a marriage. It's not like
how it is here. You know, you're with
the person for a long time and then you
get married. Countries like that, you
you you just get married. So they say to
you, "Oh yeah, we won't have sex with
you until we until we get married." But
you get married very quickly.
Go getting married over there is like
going on a [ __ ] date.
There's a lot of countries that do that.
Yeah. Do you know what I put on Reddit? UK asylum.
I said, "Oh, I like to
I said I like to collect women and that
like a collection of women."
You should have saw the responses, lad.
You should see the responses
like a collection. A collection
like like Yugo cards like a little collection. Yeah.
Should have saw the responses, bro. It's
funny as [ __ ]
Yeah, it's funny. Is it, bro?
[ __ ] What? Like collect them. Yeah.
Like Lego in it. Collect them.
Well, I just put them all in a room and
that and just collect them. Yeah.
UK asylum. Do you remember the people on
Instagram that was making excuses for
the women and that?
No, bro. I'm not I'm not trolling, bro.
Here's my theory. Yeah. So, because
they're not people and they're not
normal and they're not to be trusted,
how else are you supposed to see them?
If they lie and they're full of [ __ ] and
they're and they're and they're
[ __ ] bro, how else are you supposed
to see them?
How else are you supposed to see them?
They're not normal. The stuff that they
do is not normal. So, to be fair here,
how how else are you supposed to see them?
That's what people say. Like this what
makes me laugh when people say oh you
know they're people but they're they're
not though because of the [ __ ] that they
do and that so why I don't get why you I
mean I was watching the Ed Matthews
again um I fell asleep during the uh yes
uh the last night stream I was watching
it again and the attitude on on some of
these women bro is ridiculous.
Their attitude is disgusting bro and
this guy was generally getting pissed
off at it.
So that's probably why people don't see
them as people,
you know, all all jokes aside. And I
don't know if you saw the stream, but yeah,
it seems even worse than the last time I
tried to be fair.
So I don't know what they expect people
to to to to
think of them.
Well, you think I'm a troll? UK asylum now?
Why am I a troll, bro?
But you can't bring them back to a room
and stuff. Even if you fed them and
watered them and stuff, you can't do
that, bro, because it's kidnapped.
Legally, it's kidnapped. So, you
couldn't do that. So, you need to find
another way to collect them. collection.
That's funny, bro. Is it?
No, I lost 100 pound on roulette yesterday.
I'm having a bet on Tuesday.
I'm going to get back to drinking soon.
I think I think I've had a long enough break.
MidFeb March. I'm back at it, bro. Back
on the drink.
I think I've had a long enough break now. So, yeah,
I'm not going to win it back, bro.
Unless I win it on football. I was
playing the 20p boost roulette. Yeah.
Yeah. I got [ __ ] by one team yesterday.
Selmsford [ __ ] me royally, bro.
That roulette is so addicting, bro.
It's addicting, isn't it? Yeah.
No, it's not addicting. It's just so
easy to go on it.
Yeah. At some point.
Yeah. Maybe two two and a half weeks.
Maybe a month.
Don't know yet.
Something to do in it. No photo.
I won a football bet last week.
2002 223 or 20 pound
five teams in it.
It's hard to win.
I don't know why I played roulette
yesterday, bro. I was just I just played boost roulette.
Not even a single winning spin. Five
spins. Miss, miss, miss. [ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] [ __ ] Lucky you.
Online roulette is so fixed, bro. Oh my god. Ain't it?
It's fixed, isn't it? Yeah. Uh,
This mustache is so annoying, bro. This mustache.
I need to get it trimmed, bro.
Anyways, I'm gone. Yeah,
in a minute. Online roulette is fixed. Slap maker
is fixed, man.
Yeah, it's fixed. Online roulette.
I'll do a bit on Tuesday.
Whatever is [ __ ] up today. That's good.
Yeah, I'm going to cook them later. Where's Greasy? Poor [ __ ]
Yeah, bro. Anyways, I'm going. Yeah. See you later.