Yo. Yo.
had some lush kebabs.
I cooked them in the end. I was going to
go live, but I couldn't be bothered them.
I don't know.
still doing this in 2026, man. Stalking
men on the internet that you don't know.
I can't believe you're still doing this in 2026.
I feel bad for these people, bro. I
really do feel bad for these um
these um life's losers.
That's what happens in the end, man. You
just kind of feel sorry for him, you know.
You do feel sorry for them. Therefore,
I find it [ __ ] stupid. Me.
Ugly old men on YouTube.
Ugly fat old men on YouTube that ain't
got no life trying to talk about other people.
That makes me laugh. You know what, man?
And it, you know what? It takes a lot to
make me laugh. I won't say I laugh at
anything, but that is actually that is
actually hilarious, bro.
>> What the [ __ ] Where
Yeah, I know how people can still be
doing this in 2026.
Well, there's me giving you [ __ ] the
[ __ ] benefit of the [ __ ] doubt.
When Laney said it was going to be the
same [ __ ] I was actually giving you the
benefit of the doubt. I was like, "Nah."
I was like, I was like, "Nah, surely in
2026 they'll get a life." But no,
same people. Same people doing the same [ __ ]
I want to call it same people doing the
same same people doing the same [ __ ] YouTube.
>> Don't forget I'm only on and off.
>> I'm only on and off. Yeah. So, >> do
it. these people.
Really, really, really, really sad.
I feel bad for him.
They should show these people, you know,
they show these people in um schools,
but not end up like these people when
you get older.
That's what people need to be taught in
school not to end up like these weasels.
He's all sad that they got a life
and and you know the funny thing is yeah
is that every person that they
oh [ __ ] every person that they talk
about is better than them better looking
than them. Got a better life than them.
Got more money than them.
Everyone that they talk about is
literally better than them. That's the
funniest thing about it.
They didn't like the word I used the
other day, man, when I called them
[ __ ] old wasters sat on YouTube every
day cuz it's the truth. The truth hurts.
They didn't like they didn't like that
word. They are literally wasters that
are sat on YouTube. They ain't got to
like it's the truth.
The proof hurts.
hating on younger people than them,
better looking than them, better than
them in every single way. They couldn't
say anything because they know I'm
right. They know I'm correct.
It's funny as [ __ ] is it?
But yeah, how they talk about how they
try to talk about other people,
that's how you know they've got
something wrong with them.
Like I said to Steven Alward,
all you've got to do is look at the way
these people look. You find your answers
very quickly. None of them are
good-looking. None of them are handsome.
They're all [ __ ] you know what. And
that explains part of the problem why
they do this every day.
It's basically it's basically a life
reject community where people have been
rejected from society. They don't fit
into society. So they so they come on here basically.
Peter knows how it is. Pet knows how it
Sing recording men every day. They don't
know. They're losers. And the definition
of the lo of losers. Yeah.
ain't got nothing going for themselves
and they try to preach to other people.
Hilarious, isn't it?
Funny, bro. Funny.
They try to pick on people that are
literally better looking than them, that
that are better than them in life, and
they try to project what they are onto you.
That's what they do.
It's the truth.
Yeah, that's the truth. I'm afraid
some kebabs. What did I have earlier?
Oh, yeah. I had some hot wings.
I drunk a lot of Coke today. I know I
shouldn't. I was just craving it like mad,
but it's all right. I brush my teeth
three times a day anyway, so
it's not a problem. Hey, man.
These people are still obsessed with the
way that I look and stuff. I see. That's
okay though, bro. These people don't
bother me because we know with these
people it's always self projecting, lad.
We always know with these people it's
self projecting. That's why we we can't
get mad at him. Bro, I just went on some
short and I was like, "Fuck." I was
like, "Bro, what the [ __ ] man? These 40
year olds that are worse looking than
me, older than me, and skinn than me is
talking about me
in 2026. Really, bro? I don't think so.
I really really don't think so, man.
What's wrong with these people?
That suck. What is really wrong with these people?
Here we go. Rise the white knight.
we go. White rice the white knight.
Yeah, D. I think it's strange these people, lad.
Oh, I know they're jealous, bro. I know
they're jealous. All you've got to All
you got to do, bro, is is look at the
way these people look that do this. I'm
not mentioning any names. You already
know the names. And I'm talking about
people that's even shown their face. You
tell me one of them people that are
better looking than me, bro. Not one of
them. You tell me one of these people
that have had more life experience than
me. Not one of them. Like I've said
before, there's people on here that's
got missing teeth
that show their face and talk about me. So
yeah. Oh, I made some kebabs. Greasy, by the way.
Yeah, I made some kebabs, lad.
Bro, a relationship doesn't mean
anything. Bro, what are you on about?
How are we jealous? You're the only
person. Bro, a relationship doesn't mean anything.
Rice, I've had more women than you and
and most people here put together. A
relationship doesn't mean anything.
And that's not even a skip, bro. That's
literally nothing. And even if someone
did have a relationship, you'd still talk [ __ ]
Nothing much. Steve and I, we're just
the same self projectors.
talking about the way I look even though
I'm better looking than them. I know
it's a weird one, lad.
Yeah. No one cares, bro, because you
look worse. Yeah. Yeah. But the thing
is, bro, you look worse and I'm not
scared to show my face like you people.
So, I don't really give a [ __ ] about
your opinion. Your opinion
doesn't uh I don't care.
I literally don't care, bro.
Your opinion is irrelevant. Other
people's opinions are irrelevant. I
don't care, bro.
Really, really, I don't care. So, yeah.
I literally don't give a [ __ ] lad.
And you've never had a date, so stop
self projectoring. We don't have self
projectors on this chat, lad. You've
never had a date, and you've never even
had a woman. So, see you later, self projector.
Anyways, I'm just um
You're in a depression. No, I'm not.
Again, more self-p projecting,
bro. You You actually thought Yeah, bro.
Like in 2026, these people would take
one day off of self projecting.
I actually thought in 2026, yeah, cuz
these people have got all of this money
and they're so good-looking and their
lives are so good that they would actually,
you would actually think that they would
they would take a day off for one day.
And of course they wouldn't sock. Most
of these people on here were virgins,
lad. Have you seen that many people beg
that uh autumn rose? Of course they
don't, bro. Of course they wouldn't.
Yeah, of course they wouldn't, bro. The
[ __ ] Most of these people are virgins on here.
>> Oh, did you see? Oh, hey bro. Did you
see uh LJ's live earlier? I was watching
it back here and he was trying to say
that I've been on here for 10 years and
I've wasted my life on it. A I haven't
been on here 10 years. I didn't even
know about Timmy 10 years ago, let alone
be on YouTube 10 years ago. B I've done
more in my life than he has whilst being
on YouTube. So, you know, kind of people
on YouTube could actually like be on
YouTube and kind of live a life, but not
the people that follow him and him.
They've literally got no life. So, I
mean, bro, not every single person that
goes on YouTube
has done nothing with their life. You
You have and and your followers, you
have and like Redstone, all them self
projectors, but not everyone, bro. Not not everyone.
Yeah, that's proper proper self
projecting that channel, bro. Proper self projecting. Yeah, that's
really no one cares.
And you know why I don't care?
Because I don't care about some fat
woman that uses filters on the internet
because I can go out and meet real women
unlike you people. See you later, self projector.
Anyways, yeah, Grezy, the kebabs was lost, bro.
Yeah, bye-bye. Keep repeating yourself
until 2027. You don't bother no one.
These people seriously don't bother me,
do the sock, they don't bother me, bro.
As soon as I had a long hard think to myself,
it's like, how how could these people bother you?
They're all fat. They're all old.
They're all ugly. They all ain't got a
life. They're all sat on YouTube 24/7.
How could they bother anyone?
It comes a time, bro, where you think
it's like, bro. Like, you you could
really make these people get you mad.
Not me, bro. Maybe other people.
Not me, lad. That's why they don't
bother me, bro.
That's why I'm as calm as a cucumber.
Do you like that little saying, Greg?
Calm as a cucumber. Yeah,
I haven't approached sober for months,
so to be honest with you. Uh, that's I
did an approach last Monday, but I was
drinking. I done two approaches, but it
wasn't a proper night out.
I'm collecting women. Um, now we found a
new hobby. I'm collecting them. My little collection.
Yeah. I was talking to this woman. Yeah.
She says, "Oh, you can come over and
then we can get married and have a child
and that." And then Greavves, I kept
talking about [ __ ] and then she blocked me.
I wonder if Ed's going to be
No, just like a little collection,
Grezy. But obviously, you can't kidnap
people cuz it's uh it's illegal. So
maybe you have to throw a house party
and then just collect them.
Yeah, you can't kidnap people, bro. But
don't know how you would do it. It's
just like a little collection. Yeah, she blocked me.
I wonder if Ed will be live today. Grievy,
I'm always waiting for his little live streams.
Yeah. We'll see if you'll be live today.
It's okay, Grezy. I'll just wait.
I'll just wait, lad.
Yeah, I'll wait, bro. Look at my beard,
Grez. You like it? Is it mad how I've
got this long beard and I can show my
face, but they can't?
These people can't show their face.
What does that tell you about them, bro?
I saw that all night mic on Wendell's
channel by the way. I was going to
comment on him on him saying, "Hey, you
little self-reflector, you still skin?"
I saw him on Wendell's channel off this
community, bro. All night, you know,
that all night um All Night Mike, bro. Yeah.
Dasok, have you have you seen Have you
seen that uh Have you seen that Jamie Thompson account?
Yeah, they're all simps, bro. Yeah.
[ __ ] nonslegs. Uh, simp who was it? Uh, Autumn.
Don't get these simps. I don't get these
white knights. I really, really don't
get them, bro. Women don't like them.
They've had less women than you. They
don't get women. Women don't like them,
but they still defend them. Madness.
Yeah. Yeah. I gambled yesterday. £100
and I lost. Well, £130. 30 on football
bets and £100 on the roulette. One team
let me down for £168.
Try again Tuesday.
I look ill. Thank you, man. That's nice.
Why don't you come and show your face? Mourism.
That's nice, bro. Why don't you come and
show us your face?
Diabetes? What the [ __ ]
Diabetes? I didn't know somebody could
look like they had diabetes.
Yeah. Why do you come in and show us
your face? I might take you more serious, lad. Uh
uh you bro, you're calling me a M when
I'm the best looking on this community.
It's silly now, bro. In 2026, it's very, very silly
to call someone a M that's better
looking than you.
But you keep telling yourself that, bro.
If it makes you feel better,
cuz you're just talking about yourself, lad.
I'm huge. Nope. I'm not even overweight
again. That's another self-p projection.
Oh, that's another thing that they're
doing. Uh, Dasso, they're trying to talk
about my weight when they're literally obese.
They are literally obese and I'm not
even fat. And I'm thinking, what the
[ __ ] It made me laugh, bro. They're
calling They're trying to say that I'm
what is it? Um,
porky and plump. And I'm thinking, bro,
I'm more in shape than they will ever
be. So, this is a new self-p projecting
thing that they've uh that they've uh
that they've come up with. They are
literally obese, the people in this
community, and they're telling me that
I'm porky. You keep tell yourself that,
mate. You keep tell yourself that.
See you later. Anyways, lad, go
self-reflect on another channel. Um,
yeah. I don't watch HS Tik Tocky.
You like LT in it. the sock. You like
LT? I haven't heard from LT.
No, I'll never talk to him again. Me
don't like bias people.
You know, I had to put him in his place as well. By [ __ ] Nah, bro.
Porky and plump, yet they're the ones
that are obese.
That's funny, is it, bro? They're the
ones that are obese and they're trying
to talk about me. These people really
need to fix themselves before trying to
talk about other people, bro. So
embarrassing, bro. So embarrassing.
I drunk a lot of coach today, Grezy. My bad.
I drunk a lot of Coke today, bro. I'm sorry, man.
Yeah, I was just craving it today, but yeah,
haven't been out today, bro.
Just a day of rest, you know, Greavvesy.
Just a day of rest. Yeah,
you need to watch the nephew streams. Uh, grey sh
I can't stop thinking of that.
You [ __ ] copycat. I was going to put
a community post up about it. Where is
he? Where they were talking about her
on the overclock is UK form.
Yeah, he broke his leg a while ago. Yeah.
It seems nothing has changed though. I
haven't approached properly for months
and it seems nothing has changed with their attitude.
Even his American friend was getting
sick of it. He says, "Oh, it's hard
here. They've all got attitude."
Yeah, bro. Even he was getting sick of
it. It's like, "Well, I haven't missed
much, have I?" Yeah.
I put it up on the community post.
That's where they all car. They all
copied each other.
Someone was like
and then the other one was talking about
I don't know why they used to say that.
He's [ __ ] stinking.
Well, we know why trend. We've been over
this many many times. They're trends
obviously in it. I saw something about
Justin Bieber today.
Oh, you've seen him in it, Stephen.
I saw Justin I saw something about
Justin Bieber today.
brought me back to 2011.
Do you remember that that uh trend that
sock the Justin Bieber trend in 2011 2012?
You remember that ain't it? Justin Bieber.
All these trends, bro. Copycat trends.
The one that's going at the moment is uh
Canada Goose. Canada Goose coat.
Everyone's wearing it.
See me, I wear stuff that no one else
wears. Vapor trainers, Ammani jeans,
sick silk. No one I'm wearing Spider-Man
t-shirts. I'm wearing Bot Simpson
t-shirts. No one's wearing what I'm what
I'm wearing cuz I'm not a little copycat. Not long.
Depends what you mean. Like grow it out
like that or grow it from like scratch. Not long.
My hair grows fast, too. Oh, that's
another thing. Apparently, I'm balding.
Yeah, right. More self-projecting.
Yeah, there's a lot of um a lot of copycat trends.
I don't know why they used to used to say that.
But no, Nons is lying though. Steven
Howard, bro. If you watch his stream,
he's trying to say that. No, no, he
didn't say that she was hot. He was
like, "Um, you can't deny she's
attractive and if you don't find her
attractive, you're gay." That's what he
said. And he did say that. He's he's
he's lying, bro. Just like when he was
trying to say to Laur, "Oh, oh, oh, oh,
that we don't I don't know Britney
trying to act like Britney didn't exist
exist." No, he was copying. Just own it.
You're a copycat. A [ __ ] stinky dirty
Just own what you are in it. you copying?
I've never had to copy someone else. I'm
not a loser.
I don't copy people, mate. I'm not a loser.
I'm not a [ __ ] loser, mate.
Bless Greavves Jenny's little northern accent.
Yeah, I'll be out again, Stephen Hour,
lad. I'll be out again
maybe two weeks.
I could have went out on I could have
went out yesterday. It would have been
really busy, but I said I weren't
drinking January, bro. I drunk two weeks
ago. That was because I was already out
and it wasn't a night out.
Haven't been on a night out since I
think it was early December.
[ __ ] long time ago. I just don't care
for it anymore, bro.
I will be out though, bro. Don't worry.
Get some content when I can be bothered.
when old Peter Betty can I mean like I
said I wanted to drink in March but
maybe midFebruary bro if I'm bored if
I'm bored enough in midFebruary then
I'll go out I told you I weren't going
on a night out in January it's boring
boring waste of time
waste it's just a waste of time I'm not
even going to say waste of money cuz
it's not about money
waste of time but then the only bad
thing is in January Stevens I gambled more
you gam more in it cuz obviously the
weather's [ __ ] and you think oh
so I still didn't manage to save as much
as I wanted to but it doesn't matter
anyways money comes and goes can't take
it with you when you die in it so
I see it lad yeah
I lost the power r yesterday. Yeah, I
still woke up in a bad mood over it.
Yeah, I woke up in a bad mood over it, bro.
I got some money coming anyways. So,
this beard is getting so annoying, bro.
I need to go to the [ __ ] barbers, but
I don't want to go barbers yet because
I'm not going out drinking yet. So,
I lost £100.
Roulette's [ __ ] fixed.
Unlucky for some. Roulette's [ __ ]
fixed as [ __ ]
I'm going to win on the football on
Tuesday. Don't want me that.
I need to try and get both teams to
score in the first half, bro. I'll get
it, though. I will get it.
I will get it. Don't you worry, lad.
I've had it before. I haven't bet I
haven't bet on it before, but I've got
it before. All I need to do is bet on
the right two teams. I will get it, bro.
Trust me. And when I do, it'll be worth it. Yeah, man.
Yeah. You can't win on roulette unlucky.
It's so fixed. You do five I I won on a
football last week. I put five teams 20
on five teams. I won £223.
You go on roulette, you can't win.
It's so fixed, bro. I tried yesterday
the boost roulette.
Ner having it at all,
you know. [ __ ] shite, bro. I can win
on a football and I can't win on the roulette.
Roulet's hard to win though, bro. Yeah,
I indigo I was on the overclock is UK
form and they were talking about Sher Cole.
Why were they doing that indigo?
They're saying she's they said
never once have I saw Sho and thought.
Never once has she made my dick hard either.
Not my cup of tea, lad.
No, not for me, lad. No.
I reckon they're going to go live around
10:00, I think. Ed,
maybe 10, 11.
They went out too late.
He doesn't let me put a bet on until the
day it plays. I'm going to do slow and um Enfield
that roulette. Steven Howard
[ __ ] in it.
Oh, it's a win.
playing mage stone.
Yeah, I've got an online account, so I
just do it online.
But they pay straight away. Once you
win, it goes the money goes in instantly.
The 223 went in instantly. Yeah.
That Joseph Fro has been so quiet.
They're not playing Tuesday.
What? When are they playing? Saturday.
We'll wait till Saturday then.
I need to put 500 pound on two teams,
bro. One day. I need to do it in it. Steven Howard.
Some, you know, sometimes when I've won
before, you know,
nah, no plans at all. I wish I just put
£500 on the two teams when I've put like
100 120, but
if it loses,
that's what I'd ever do, bro. If I ever
won I know my I know some guy, he won 17
grand in the casino, bro. £140. He won
17,000. If I won £17,000,
I would use two grand for the football
and just keep the 15.
If I won 17 grand, bro, I'd keep I would
I would flip that with a football, bro.
I'd put one grand on two teams and the
next Yeah. build it up. Yeah,
imagine doing that in the bookies.
Putting two grand on the football in the bookies.
Steven Howard, what the [ __ ] Jeez.
M it up, bro.
[ __ ] knows, mate.
I haven't approached sober for months.
Maybe I'll be too scared to do it now.
Nah, I don't think so.
No, I don't think so.
I ain't on it for months. No. No. Nah.
Why are you trying to call me ugly when
I'm literally miles better looking than
you and I've actually got teeth in my mouth?
You do realize in 2026 you're just embarrassing yourself.
You resemble a rat. You've got no teeth
and you have to go for disabled women.
You're a prime example of one of these
people where I'm saying that you need to
actually look at yourself. Your face
looks like it's melting. You've got no
teeth in your mouth. You look like a
rat. And you've got a disabled
girlfriend. Please refrain from talking
about someone that's better than you.
Thank you very much. You know,
you're another one.
I'm literally miles better looking than
you and I've never had to resort to any
disabled women in my life. That's not
even reacting. That's actually spitting
facts, bro. That's actually spitting
facts. Like you You are [ __ ] ugly as
[ __ ] How you How you think you can talk
about me with a face like yours? You're mad.
You're literally [ __ ] You're [ __ ] mad.
You're [ __ ] skint as well. So now you
can call anyone else skint when you're
with a [ __ ] cancel bedit. Didn't go
abroad until he was [ __ ] 30. Don't
[ __ ] talk about me. [ __ ] ugly
[ __ ] See you later. Anyways, bye-bye now.
Sorry about that, Stephen. How Dad,
these are the people that are trying to
what seems harder in the winter what to approach.
No, I can do it, bro. I just haven't
done it for months cuz I couldn't be
bothered. Well, I done it last I done it
last week, but I was drinking.
When was it? Last not last. When was it?
Last Monday. The Monday before that.
No, I'm going to the barber soon.
I don't know, man. I'm probably going to
go out in the next two weeks if I'm bored enough.
Uh, I'm going to go on holiday this year. Definitely.
And yeah, that's it.
Well, you find approaching is more
harder in the winter.
>> No, I just find as I got older, I just
can't be bothered with it cuz it's
always the same [ __ ]
It's always the same [ __ ] with them, is it?
So there's nothing to be enthusiastic about
cuz there's nothing to be enthusiastic
about cuz it's always the same [ __ ] But
I did do approaches last Monday when I was drinking
just to see if it would be any different in 2026.
But I don't really care, bro. I don't
care about the the dating [ __ ] anymore.
I don't care.
What do you think? Maybe I'll go out and
I'll be too scared to do it. So, now, Bob.
Nah, I don't think it's possible.
Been doing it too many years, bro. I
don't think so.
Done it for months. I don't think so. Yeah,
I already know that. That's why I don't
care about it anymore. I know. That's
why I don't care about it anymore.
Why do you think I don't give a [ __ ]
bro? And also, they're all the same as
well. So, you couldn't even take anyone
you met serious because obviously
they're all the same in it. So,
yeah. That's why I don't care, bro.
Yeah, that's exactly why I've had >> Yeah.
Yeah, this woman was like, "Oh, we
should get married in India." He wanted
to get married straight away, Grezy. Cuz
that's the way it works over there.
You know when you ask for some you you
know when you ask somebody to go on a
date with you. Here, uh
over there it's more like date
proposals. So you say, "Oh, let's get
mar uh marriage proposals."
So you're like, "Oh, let's get married."
And then they get married.
She said, "Oh, she wants to have a baby
and that and then she was sending me
reels of babies." Greasy,
but Peter Belly couldn't control his lusty bless.
I wonder if Nonser is going to get laid.
He's going to be [ __ ] 31 in [ __ ]
Oh, this month. And he's still a virgin.
I wonder if he's going to actually lose
it this year. Steven Howard.
Yeah, I told you I gambled, bro. I bet
on the football and roulette. I told you.
And there's more to life than women when
you get you had your fair share. And you
also get it after when you get older as
well. As you get older,
like 28 or old, I just literally don't
give a [ __ ] That's why I've been out. I
don't care for him, bro.
I told you, bro. I done three10 football
bets and I lost 100 pound on roulette. Yeah.
Yeah. One team let me down for 168.
Oh, I thought they were going to score.
The bastards, man.
Maybe he'll get laid this year, lad. Steven Howard.
I reckon he'll get he might get laid this year.
Oh, don't I shouldn't be saying this to
be honest, bro. We might get LT button
again. Oh, he's got a girlfriend. Don't say that. [ __ ] wanker.
Might have to be careful with what I'm
saying, isn't it, Bob?
We might want to get We might have
people butt in again and say, "But don't say that.
They start crying their eyes out cuz I'm
talking about their boyfriend.
So I might might want to be careful, lad.
Might want to be careful. Yeah.
Why did you see that though, Bob? As
soon as I as soon as I as soon [ __ ]
bro. As soon as I call him a virgin,
people people's crying. He got a girlfriend.
But then when he's calling me a virgin,
someone actually proved they've had
[ __ ] sex. No one says anything. And
cuz I pulled him up about it, he didn't
like it. Cuz I pulled him up on his
biasness. He didn't like it. Well, you
shouldn't be butting your nose in them.
If you haven't got anything to say to
one, don't say it to the other. I don't
give a [ __ ] if someone's got a
girlfriend. That's not proof that proof
that they've had sex. I don't give a [ __ ]
If a [ __ ] isn't proof and me being in
women's beds naked isn't proof, then a
girlfriend's not proof. Simple as that.
And he didn't and he didn't like it. So,
oh well, don't but in. No one asked you
to butt in.
[ __ ] sick of it being one rule for
one and one rule for another.
Steven Howard, we've had it with the
money game. We've had it with the police
game. I'm sick of it. I'm bloody sick of
the biasness and I had enough of it.
[ __ ] money, [ __ ] police, [ __ ]
Oh my [ __ ] god, bro.
Now I'm speaking to some woman in California. Greasy.
Maybe I can add her to the collection.
No, he [ __ ] doesn't. He was [ __ ]
defending the virgin.
No, he [ __ ] doesn't.
No, he doesn't. I was I was calling him
a ver I was calling [ __ ] last time he
was on here I was calling nonslegs a
virgin and he was he was [ __ ] he was defending him.
He doesn't [ __ ] lick my ring at all.
There's always been different rules for
Peter Belly, bro.
I only had a kebab, bro. Only had a kebab.
I drunk a lot of Coke today, but I did
drink it with a straw. So,
I know it's bad for your teeth, but like
I said, I brush my teeth three times a day, bro.
No, he's No, he's biased. No, he's he's biased, bro.
And to be fair, he's done it with a
couple of things,
right? I think I remember one time.
Yeah. Where this [ __ ] kept grassing on
me, grasping me, and I said, "Oh, I'm
going to I'm going to call the police
back." "Oh, don't do that because
because he's a grass." I said, "Well,
he's grasped on me." No problems. When
I've shown money, there's been another
rule. Oh, you can't show it again.
There's always biased rules, bro. One
one rule for one, one rule for another. Simple, lad.
And he needs to stop using that M thing
as well. If you watched Ed Matthews
yesterday, you you would have saw you
would have saw the you would have saw
um what these women were saying to these
guys. Bro, they get rude in England,
bro. All you got to do is meet somebody
with daddy issues. I don't give a [ __ ]
if some woman that I didn't approach
calls me a ma because she's got daddy
issues. That wasn't even the person that I approached.
So, you can't really par it really
because it wasn't even the person that I
approached. That's what they're like.
That's what they like in England, bro. Masculine.
They self-project. I don't give a [ __ ]
Do you think I give a [ __ ] that some
woman that I purposely didn't approach
called me a M? Because she's one herself.
Really, bro? Really? I mean, I
approached her friend and not her for a [ __ ] reason.
[ __ ] idiot, bro.
I don't do Yeah. So, you need to stop
You need to stop using that, bro, cuz
that's really boring, lad. really really boring.
You know, anyone that puts themsel out
there that's actually got a life, you know?
Well, Greavves is a little copycat. Yeah.
[ __ ] hate that [ __ ] Cheryl Cole
trend. Bob Bills. I'm sick of hearing
that name. I'm sick of seeing that name.
I [ __ ] can't stand that name, bro.
Just copying every time. copy and no
mind of their [ __ ] own.
Why the [ __ ] do they say all of this
[ __ ] Steven Howard, that she's
attractive and that? I don't think she's
attractive at all, bro. I don't know why
people say that. So why why so many
people say that, bro?
People used to go on about her and
stuff. What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but Stephen Al, why do people used
to always talk about her and [ __ ]
Yeah, RZ basically means approaching
women. It basically means chatting women
up. Riz. Yeah, that's a new a fairly new thing.
Wait, Greavvesy. So why why did you say
people used to call her fit and that?
Refresh our memory, Grezy.
I love Grezy. He's a He's a good friend of ours.
Do you know what accent? I can't stand
that [ __ ] hell accent. Greasy.
What do you What do you think the worst
accent is in England, bro? I think it's Birmingham, man.
That hull accent is disgusted. I have
something I watch something on Instagram.
It's some shop.
It's some hull. It's some shopping haul in it.
Yeah. Essex is pretty bad.
Essex is pretty bad. Yeah.
Yeah. Dudley as well. Yeah, Dudley is
the worst. Black Country. Black Country Scouse and
Holl is horrible. No, no. Stoke. Stoke
is bad as well. It's like Stafford mixed
with like Birmingham. It's disgusting,
bro. Stoke is bad. I'd say I'd say
Dudley. Dudley and and um Stoke, I think.
[ __ ] Have you ever heard that Stoke accent? Ah
yeah, Virgin boy used to say that he was
from London. I used to say, "You're not
no part of [ __ ] London. Stop trying
to beg it, you [ __ ] skin, virgin."
And he used to say, "No, I'm from
London." I was like, "You're not [ __ ]
London. You're nothing to do with
You are your [ __ ] dad."
[ __ ] saying that he was from London.
He [ __ ] ain't from no [ __ ] London.
No [ __ ] virgin like that is from
where I'm from.
Definitely definitely definitely not
Grezy. Definitely not, man.
I was born in Leight and Stone Grezy.
I'm a cockney Greavvesy. Well, I don't
know if I am or not.
Maybe I just missed it.
Maybe. Maybe I just missed it. But yeah,
you need to be born by uh bell
by the bow bell. By the bow bell in it. Yeah.
Do you remember that trend in it? Huge ass
when people kept saying Cheryl car was
attractive. [ __ ] copying you little
copycat. I'll tickle you. I'll tickle
I don't think it's the fact that they
said that she's attractive. I think it's
the fact that they would call you gay if
you never. Would you agree on that one, Grezy?
that they would actually call you gay if
you you never
I think that's the bit that made it the
the copycat statement.
I think so. Is it? Yeah. I think that's
what makes it the copycat statement. Yeah.
Queens is a funny troll, you know.
He's a funny troll. Yeah, bro. Little copycats.
Come on, Ed. Go live. I don't have any
popcorn though, Greasy. I got some
bought for me today, but I ate it all.
I ate it all. So, yeah. Um,
I got no Coke left now and I got no
sugar. So, I can't have the tea now,
Greasy. Cuz I ate all the sugar. Oh gosh.
I ate all the [ __ ] sugar, bro. Yeah,
I just stop, bro.
But like I said, I drink the Coke with a
straw in it, so it protects any um
what's it? Amal damage. I forget that.
It hurts. No, I can't just drink water,
lad. It's disgusting.
Well, it doesn't taste like anything,
but I mean, I couldn't just drink it, you know? Yeah. Yeah, that's it.
My approaches are sick.
You like my little cold approaches. He just
That was my little women collection. Greavvesy.
Someone said I'm a troll for that.
Someone said I'm a troll for that. What?
Collecting women? That's not a troll.
No, I'm not a troll, lad. Why did I collection? Yeah.
Yeah. I collect Lego.
Uh I like to collect women and stuff.
Like could you imagine that? You just
kidnapped a load of women. Yeah. And you
just held them hostage as a little
little connection. But obviously you
would feed them and stuff.
Well, yeah. I did tell them Grezy. They
said that basically I sound like a serial killer. Yeah.
They said, "What the fuck?"
And then you could just feed them and
stuff and just keep them in like a
little um room.
just collect some in it.
Yeah, I did say that, but I don't I
think they missed the point of what I'm
trying to say, you know,
just like a little collection
or try to date multiple people at a
time, Grezy. Maybe you could try to date
multiple people at a time
or something like that. like a little
collection going. What do you think, Grezy?
Cuz you I like collections. Everyone's
got their own little collections. You
got the DVD, obviously. I got the Lego
and like the women and stuff
and some toys. I collect toys too, Greedy. Yeah,
this woman was like I said, "Oh, we
should hold hands forever." And she's
like, "Oh, yeah. We could glue our
hands." I said, "There's something else
that I want to glue to you as well." And
I said, "I I I'll let you figure that one out.
I'll let I'll let you figure that one out.
She seemed confused by it
cuz you don't understand, Grezy, that
women was put on earth to basically
satisfy our needs. Do you not understand
that, Grezy? They're not people. They're
NPCs. Someone's like, "Oh, they're not
people." According to you, no, they're
not people. They're NPCs. They're not to
be took serious.
So, no, they're not people,
Grezy. They're not people at all.
They're they're just they just exist to
satisfy people's needs and then they
just move on to the next person.
Do you remember when I used to speak to
these women greasy and I said, "Oh, can
you get a sex change? It will be a bit better."
And I remember when women used to
message me about the house. says, "Oh
yeah, um I I'm interested in this w
room." When I was subleting the house, I
said, "Yeah, you can stay in the room,
but it's going to be double for you
because you're a woman and you're mean
and you go to restaurants with people
and you try to humiliate people."
You know this uh you know this you know
Ed Matthews friend Grezy? Yeah. The one
from America, he says that these women
do this stuff to humiliate you. He's
like he said Manchester is blue ball
central. He says that they they act all
nice here Greasy and then you try it
with them and they just humiliate you in
the end. Would you agree with that?
Yeah, I think he was talking a lot of
sense what he was saying cuz he was out
approaching in it.
Um and he was saying that yeah, it's
just to basically humiliate you.
He was saying America is way easier. And
I've had this conversation with with
Ant-Man multiple multiple multiple
times, but we've come to the conclusion
that like the West is the West.
So I I don't see how America could be easier.
I don't know, bro. I don't think so.
I mean, the West is the West. It's It's
full of idiots.
What do you think, Hugh asks? What's
easier dating in England or America? I
think it's probably the same though.
I'm guessing I don't think anywhere is
worseer than England, but I think
anywhere the West is the West, isn't it?
Yeah. Well, good for you, man.
I don't know.
I don't know, bro.
I just don't think I don't think this
grieves you. I just think if you was in
any other country trying for this amount of time,
you wouldn't be single. I don't know,
bro. But then he was saying that, oh, if
you was in America, you might feel the
same way about England. But I don't
know, bro. I just don't know. I've just
got this feeling that England is just
worse than anywhere else.
Cuz I've been with some Americans, even
in London, but I don't I don't know,
bro. I don't know.
It It's hard to It's hard to say, is it?
But they're all idiots in the West. Like
even when you watch Ed Matthews, Yeah.
you get these American guys saying, "Oh,
Ed," and then they start hugging him and
stuff. They are just idiots. They're
just influenced brainwashed idiots. Yeah.
I don't know, bro. What is harder? I don't know.
I just got this feeling if you was
anywhere else, Grezy, you would find
someone within 6 to 8 months.
I reckon in within 6 to 8 months,
you know, you'd find you would find
someone. I don't I don't know. Maybe I'm
wrong. I would never know until you
tried somewhere else.
Who knows, bro? Who knows?
All right, Greavvesy. You You do you
know the reason I I let Greavves on my
channel is because he makes me laugh.
Then he says there is some people that
make excuses for women. They don't care
about the situation, Grezy. They don't
care about what happened.
They're just only interested in who what
the gender is. Isn't that right, Grezy?
Isn't that right, Grezy? No, I haven't
got any um more Lego yet. I need to get
the Jo Josh set. Greavvesy.
They just defend women for being women.
That's funny, isn't it?
What? When they were saying that, oh,
they were just being nice and that.
>> Yeah. I don't know why they do it, bro.
Get the frustration. No, I don't I don't
I don't I don't get sexy frustrated
anymore. I don't care about that [ __ ]
No, I don't I don't get I don't get sexy
frustrated anymore. I don't get sexual
needs, bro. I can live without it. I
don't give a [ __ ]
Cuz you get to a certain point, you get
to a certain age, you know what women
are like. They're all the same. So, it
couldn't bother you. just the same way
as these people in here don't bother me
to be honest with you. I can live
without it. I don't care. I honestly
don't give a [ __ ]
Maybe if I'm out drinking again, I might
get horny, but I don't know, bro. But
who knows? No, I don't I don't need it, bro.
Yeah, I should have kept all the Izzies
in like a little dungeon in it, Greavvesy.
Oh, what? Like a like a little dungeon,
isn't it? I should have kept them in in
a little dungeon. Yeah,
like Al Stewart.
Do you remember Grezy? Al Stewart's um
Well, Al Stewart had a rape dungeon.
Do you remember the rape dungeon
that elf used to have?
Do you remember it? You saw the clip of
it in it.
No, I'll just have like a little dungeon
in it. And um
Well, how many isies are there? There's
quite a few, isn't there?
And obviously you have to give you have
to give them food three times three
times a day in it. Just pull it through
like the little letter box
and I'll bring I'll have like a little
camera and put a camera in there so
whilst I'm out I can see what they're
doing. Is it?
What do you think? I have a little
camera to see what they're doing whilst I'm out.
A little collection. Yeah,
that's funny. Is it?
Yeah. For Peter B. Crazy.
Someone was like, "Oh, women aren't
trophies to be won." I said, "Yes, they
[ __ ] are trophies."
Yes, they [ __ ] are, Greasy.
Like Yugo cards. You know how you
collect Yugo cards, Grezy?
Someone on Reddit said, "Oh, you should
you you should kidnap them and and make
them give you a [ __ ] and that and get
some more experiences."
He was trolling, isn't it? No, you can't
do that, bro.
Oh, I love it.
And what? And do you want me to do a
video showing the collection? Greasy.
What? You want me to do a video showing the connection? >> Yeah.
What What would What would you do,
Grezy? Call the old Bill.
What did you do? Killed your mail.
I was at some some people messaged me
back on um Instagram Greaves and I was like, "Oh."
Um and I said to them, "Oh, can I add
you to my collection?"
And then they stopped replying, "Grezy.
Do you know what I don't understand
about these people on Instagram, Stephen
Hour? They'll talk. They're like, "Oh,
London, but I live in Cambridge. What
about you?" And then you tell them where
you live, and then they just don't
respond again. What's the [ __ ] point
of responding in the first place if you
just got to disappear appear after the
second message? It doesn't make sense,
is it, Grezy?
What's the [ __ ] point?
doesn't make no sense.
You might as well just not even
responded in the first place.
Oh, bless you then.
You need a little collection.
So, what who would be in who would be in
the room then?
Oh, I'd want that Canadian one in there
as well. Do you remember that Canadian
one that posted about me saying that I
need help grievy? Her name was Brooke
her USA is he the 19year-old Aussie Izzy
or like a little collection
I'll picking it cuz some some I wouldn't
want you know some I wouldn't want there
to I wouldn't want them to be there. Um,
yeah. And you'll see all the you you'll
see all the you'll see all theies. >> Yep.
That's cute. Do you think that's cute? Greavvesy.
Is that cute? Grezy little collection.
No, they didn't see the content. Steven
Hardwood, they didn't see the content. Yep.
Do you remember with the with the
roulette being rigged? Greasy, they saw
the white man coming
in the bookies. Do you remember that
one? When I used to say that, uh,
Greasy, they saw the white man coming.
You found all that content lust, didn't
you? Like houses being broken into over
YouTube and that. Nah, I don't know how
you can laugh at that, bro. People
almost lost their life.
I don't know how you can laugh at that
crazy when people almost lost their lives.
You shouldn't laugh at that.
You shouldn't laugh at stuff like that,
man. People almost losing their life
over YouTube and you think that's funny.
You could literally be watching like a
GTA video on YouTube, Grezy. So, you're
watching DT on YouTube, right? And the
next thing you know, your windows have gone in
over the same website.
No, but what about me and the LT thing, Greasy?
You said what? One of the tenants could
have ended up dead or something. You
said, didn't you?
What do you reckon? One of the tenants
could have ended up dead or something.
That's what you said, is it? Yeah.
[ __ ] hell. My mom was worse than
that. My mom was worse than that rice one.
So, what you're saying, Grez, that if I
was in that day, then I would have been
woken up to a beating
over YouTube. Is that what you're basically saying?
Is that what you're basically saying, Greasy?
Is that what is that what you're basically saying?
That's [ __ ] crazy. Even when I was
watching that Ed Matthew stream, Steven
Howard. Yeah. When there's all them
people in the house. Can you imagine LT
went in the house when there's all of
them people having a little boogie
and someone opened the door?
>> I don't know why but that
that made me laugh. I agree with you.
That actually made me laugh, you know,
cuz you know like the nephews, he has
like a house in it and there's loads of
people there and they're just chilling
and that is it and they sleep there and
jump in front of the door.
That's like something over out of a
[ __ ] movie or something, isn't it? Yeah. That's bad.
No, it's not funny. It's not funny.
I think Laney's watching me again.
No, she's not.
No, I thought Laney was watching me.
That's not funny, though. When the
windows got smashed, greasy, that's not
funny, man. The first time Laney was
there, she was scared.
She didn't laugh at stuff like that.
That could give that could give an old
woman a heart attack. Give an old person
a heart attack, Grezy. And you're
laughing about it.
That's actually quite scary.
Do you know think that's actually quite
scary if you think about it?
Do you remember Mr. Be with that whole
LT thing breaking in the house and that?
One of them tenants could have lost
their life. And you think it's funny?
No, it's not funny, Mr. B.
Someone could have actually lost their life.
You know what I mean?
Mr. B, someone could have ended their
life. He's not madder than me though,
mate. He's not madder than me.
Trust me, he's not madder than me, bro.
Trust me, he's not madder than me. I'm a
crazy [ __ ] [ __ ] Don't forget. Yeah,
this is not this is not four or five
years ago anymore, bro.
I already told you when I lose from
gambling, I see demons in my head and
[ __ ] I've told you what I've done to
the bookies and that, bro. You don't you
don't you didn't believe me. Trust me,
bro. He's not madder than me.
This is This is This is This is lost
content for Greavesy, bro. Ain't it,
Grezy? This is last content for you.
Trust me, he's not madder than me, bro.
Trust me, he's not.
That's why I had to calm myself down,
bro. Cuz if I go on that channel, I'm
just I'm Because the thing is, Mr. B, if
I go on that channel, I'm just going to
end up meeting a guy, bro. That's why I
had to calm myself down the other day
because I would just end up starting
madness, bro, and finishing it. Trust
me, you don't know me, mate. You know,
there's c there's certain things I keep
off of here, bro, because of the you
know what and the informants and that, bro.
I told you what happened the other day
in the bookies. This [ __ ] woman was
running up her [ __ ] mouth. I went
back there, bro.
I went back there.
I went back there, bro. Yeah. I was
like, "No, no, no. [ __ ] that. I went
back there, mate, for round two."
There's nothing wrong with round two, bro. is there?
No, bro. That's what exactly the point
I'm trying to make. I I didn't go on the
channel for that exact reason. Yeah, bro.
That was mad at beefing, is it? Um, Grezy,
I was mad at beefing.
Do you want to see my new t-shirt on? JNA,
Mr. Bean, do you want to see my new t-shirt on?
I'm going to put it on.
Yeah. One second. I've actually had a shower, so one sec.
Actually, I'm just going to wear it
anyways. [ __ ] it. It's been washed.
It's been washed, lad.
Oh, go my little jar. Oh, [ __ ]
The guy would get defeated by somebody
wearing a [ __ ] He'd get defeated by
someone wearing a [ __ ] um Spider-Man t-shirt.
Oh, one second. It's been lost, by the way.
Excuse the beard and all that.
Yeah. Look, he had a baby. So, yeah, man.
You like it?
I think it looks pretty cool me,
but I don't understand how there's a
baby because there was never a baby in
any of the Spider-Mans. There was no
Spiderwoman. There was no nothing. So,
how the [ __ ] where is he? How did he
where did he come from? Because he was
never there was never a Spiderwoman. So,
there was never a baby.
T-shirt is lush. It's been washed. nicely. Oh, yeah.
>> Oh, you say it. >> Yeah.
You like the t-shirt, Steven? I like it.
It's pretty cool. Me.
Would you like to see me defeat LT in a
Spider-Man t-shirt, Stephen? Uh, Grezy
being defeated by someone in a Spider-Man t-shirt.
I like the t-shirt, me. I think it's pretty cool.
Yeah, all my other ones were just like
really faded and that. I think it's a
pretty cool t-shirt.
Well, you'd like to see that, Greavvesy.
What? Should I go to the Ed Matthews
house and call him to the Ed Matthews
house and see how far he gets there
with all them people in the people
chilling and then you hear like a knock
on the door
then you hear what a knock on the door. Yeah.
I'm speaking to this woman and she said,
"Oh, she doesn't care about age." And
no, no, no, no, no.
You feel like you hit the lottery when
you actually speak to them kind of
people grievy because where you're
always used to hearing some [ __ ] excuse.
What would be great? What would be
We're always used to hearing some bogus excuse. Squeezy.
What would be great? Well, the Ed Matthews house.
It's so hard to try to keep interest in
these women though. Um, Steven Howard,
because we only want them for one thing, don't we?
We only want them for one thing, don't we, Grezy? Yeah. Yeah, man.
Why do you find it funny house getting
broken into over YouTube, Greavvesy?
It's actually quite scary
to think that you can go to sleep and
wake up with someone attacking you.
That's actually quite scary. Why do you
think that's funny?
Why do you think that's funny when it's
quite scary? Do you like my little top, Steven Howard?
Yeah, but Gregy, could you imagine
someone actually getting killed in a
house over YouTube?
Like a crime scene like in the house over YouTube?
Yeah, but Greavves a crime scene over YouTube.
Is that funny to you?
Is that cre is that funny to you?
a crime scene over YouTube.
All right, Grezy, do you agree with
this? This guy's put a real up on
Instagram saying, "Don't get a
girlfriend until you have at least $10,000 saved." Nah.
No, I don't agree with that, bro.
I don't agree with that at all. Do you? No,
I'm not sure, lad.
Hurry up here a bit. What time is this
[ __ ] going live?
Sideman put a new video up today. Hide
and seek. Will you be watching it, Boozy?
Oh, bless you, Grezy.
Was you watching that live stream when I
got arrested in Newcastle? Grezy, you
was, weren't you?
I got arrested live on YouTube. [ __ ] bastards.
Years ago, bro. Years ago.
Three, four years ago. Nope. Wrong channel.
Yeah, the hotel lad.
No, I've been arrested literally on stream
in the hotel. I have been arrested on
stream about 3, four years ago.
Oh yeah, we need that Finnish Izzy as
well as our little connection. Griezy
Finnish USA one, the normal one, the Albanian one. Oh yeah.
Cute and it little connection.
Do you want my opinion? Dasok Daryl [ __ ]
They're all [ __ ]
That's what my opinion is.
Yeah, that's what my opinion is.
they used to say she's fit in it. Greasy.
All right, that's you know people used
to say Sher Walker was fit to copy
I'm not a Muslim, Greasy. How can I be a Muslim?
Why that's not why do people always used
to say that Shival was fit? I never ever saw it.
I don't know why people used to say that.
I know who that Je Collins is.
I know she isn't.
I know who she is, bro.
That's what Why do people used to say
that car was attractive?
They used to hype her up and [ __ ]
Maybe to fit in
to fit in. Maybe.
No, but people used to say if you didn't
find her attractive, you're gay.
And I never saw it. I always thought she
was [ __ ] stinking.
I never ever saw it. I got called gay.
We're not finding her attractive.
The [ __ ] How does that make someone gay?
Why am I gay, bro? What the [ __ ]
That burger was rather tasty, Grezy. I
might need to order another one. But
this time, I'll get the chicken one.
Yeah, but they he you know um that's you
know uh nons legs when I used to meet
him I used to have this conversation and
I I said I don't find shovel car
attractive and he said that I was gay
and I told him multiple times I wasn't I
just don't like her and he's like nope
gay gay called be gay.
The [ __ ] He's [ __ ] showing off.
Showing off, man.
Strange thing to say about someone, huh?
I think that's very weird.
What do you think,
Lord? To him.
He said that if you don't find her
attractive that you're gay. And then
when I went on the internet, other
people were saying it to other people as
well. Isn't that right, Greg? They said,
"Oh, if you don't find her attractive, you're gay."
I said, "I don't find her attractive at
all." Literally don't. He's like, "You
got to be gay." I said, "I'm not. I've
been with more women than you."
And he still [ __ ]
was saying about people being gay and
that. And then if you go online, you'll
see where people said it to other people.
Don't get it, bro. I don't get it.
What do you think, Dark? Must M must
have been the trend going around, is it?
And now we don't hear about Justin
Bieber, poor [ __ ] No one cares about
Justin Bieber anymore, but [ __ ] 2011,
everyone hyped him up. Everyone cared
about him. Is that right, Grezian? And
in 2012, but now no one gives a [ __ ]
about the poor [ __ ] You never hear
about him anymore.
No, cuz they moved on to someone else.
The bloody copycats. [ __ ] copycats.
You remember that one as well? The girls
used to all copy each other.
They all used to copy each other.
Yeah, they done it with Justin Bieber as
well. They done it with Justin Bieber.
They done it with One Direction. It's a
trend because when all of them people
auditioned before they were famous,
that's no one cared about them. No one
gave a [ __ ] about them.
No one cared about [ __ ] Am I Am I
lying, Gregy? Tell me I'm lying. And no
one cared about [ __ ] Harry Styles
when he was auditioning or when he was
at school. No one gives a [ __ ] No one
gave a [ __ ] about him. You think he was
getting as many girls as he was before
he was famous? No. No. Soon as he become
famous, mate, they all started copying each other.
Wherever sick [ __ ] [ __ ] you know
created that trend. Yeah,
you're not really anymore, bro.
You missed the roulette yesterday. I was
playing roulette, Grey. You missed it.
Yeah, you missed it.
I'm kind of hungry again, Grezy.
But I need to stop my little eating habits,
cuz I'll start looking like Big Daddy V
if I don't stop. only joking.
>> No, but seriously, um,
Grezy, you're so sick. You are trolling me.
So, Greavvesy was who who put me in care then?
So, Grezy, what who put me in a care system? H
Do you remember who put me in the curse system? Greavvesy. Greasy. Crazy. Yeah.
What? What did she do? Grezy. See?
Yeah, I got I got put into care. Greasy.
Yeah, I'm just under my little electric blanket.
Do you remember how many how long I was
spending trying to find a new mama? Greavvesy.
Did you used to like that grievy when I
used to go out every week trying to find
a new mama?
Trying to find a new mama.
Yeah. You remember them days, don't you,
Grezy? You should like the content. Yep.
Yeah, I I have so many additions to the connections.
I had USA Izzy, I had Sig.
Yeah, I connected so many women that year. Grimsy. Yeah.
loads of um
cuz at first I would just compare like
the experiences with the people that
I've met, but now I want more.
Now I want to actually collect them and
and and I want them to be in like a
little room with each other so they can
all look at each other and think about
their bad behaviors and what they've
done to Peter Belly Grezy
like like you know like a naughty step
and what they've done to little Peter
Belly and his little feelings over the
years. They can all look at each other
and and think about what they've done.
What do you think we've Z? Yep.
Why? What happened? What happened in the movie?
This woman was like, "Oh,
no." But I'd still feed them and stuff,
you know, and and and make sure they don't die.
But, you know, they just like a little collection.
Yeah. This woman was like, "You better
not be speaking to other women." the one
that wanted to marry me, Greavvesy. And
I already had my little collection on my
Instagram, Grezy, of people I was talking to.
Yeah. I said to this woman, "Oh, like
what would make you a good girlfriend?"
And then she told me all of these
things. I said, "Oh, that's cute. You
better be able to cook as well. Peter
Belly's belly doesn't feed itself.
You can make me some sandwiches if you can't cook
in the kitchen." What do you think, Reezy?
Yep. I like food cooked for me. Greasy.
I used I like Do you know when when
people cook you food? When the when the
tenants used to cook me food, bro. Oh,
[ __ ] hell, bro. You can't beat food
being cooked for you. No,
just people to add to my little collection.
I need to add some more Lego. I'll buy
some more Lego in a couple of days.
No, not at all. Have kids. Have kids
with people that are [ __ ] evil. [ __ ]
that. This cunt's having a laugh. Bob
Bills. He said have kids. What? Have
kids with evil people. No thanks.
You know, in this day and age where
there's [ __ ] Tik Tok and Facebook and
then have and then their mother's going
to be evil. [ __ ] that, Grezy. I'd rather
not. I've already got kids. My little my
little Lego. My little Lego Yoda.
What do you think of my As long as I've
got my little Lego Greasy, I'm happy.
my little Lego characters.
No. Why would I want to settle down with evil, bro? You're mad.
Do you like the Did you like the first
Lego set I bought, Grezy? I've got two
Star Wars characters. So far,
every time I play that roulette, I could
buy some more Lego.
I might order a set now, actually.
Grezy, I'm not sure.
Yeah, you saw my little women
collection, didn't you, Greavvesy? We
was collecting Izzies.
I like the Chinese one. She licked my butt.
Yeah. Jaw Jaw's the next one. Yeah. He's
got a red lightsaber. That one. Yeah.
Yeah. The connection of the grooves.
That's cute, isn't it?
How do you know about Jaw Jaw Greavesy?
He's cute, ain't he?
Imagine that, Grevy. A stream of me and
me and Chinese is he building Lego together.
Me and Chinese Izzy building Lego.
How cute is that?
Do you ever grieves you'll just latch on
to new boobies? Greavvesy,
that's how I used to get my vitamins,
isn't it, Grezy?
Yeah, I put on Reddit that I want to
collect women and stuff.
They said, "What the fuck?" Yeah.
O Steven Howard, you know that Red Star,
he's a proper gay boy, ain't it? Sat on
YouTube recording everything every day.
What a loser. What a little gay boy.
Imagine that. Steven Hour Jay, you wake
up every morning and you just and you
just sit on YouTube recording everything.
Imagine being that much of a loser.
I I I could never imagine it, lad. Never.
Could never imagine being that much of a loser, lad.
That's how you know you're down bad in life.
Now I'm feeling a bit hungry.
Yeah, I know. There's a lot of people
that want my ass.
They're not getting it.
Yeah, he's a loser, bro. He's a loser.
Oi, bro. Do you have Have you seen what
he looks like? That Jamie Thompson on
this uh thing, bro. I'll show you him.
Hi. Do you want to see it? There's
another photo, lad. Proper loser. Why Steven?
Why do you think they all get on with
each other, lad? Cuz they're all ugly. Nons legs.
They're all [ __ ] ugly.
Why do you think they all go for Peter
Belly? Cuz Peter Belly is better looking than them.
Isn't that right, Greavvesy?
I can show you a photo if you want, lad.
He is one ugly bastard.
And I'm pretty sure
he is [ __ ] disabled as well.
What? I'm sure this guy is in a wheelchair, bro.
What the [ __ ]
What the actual [ __ ] bro? Seriously,
madness. I'm pretty sure he's in a
[ __ ] wheelchair as well.
These are the kind of people
that are uh talking about me, bro.
What the [ __ ]
That's Jamie Thompson.
So he's ugly. Nons is ugly. Lj's ugly.
Do you not see the pattern, lad?
Bomb is ugly. Pat's ugly.
Do not see the pattern here. Terry's ugly.
Do you not see the pat in here,
Greavvesy? Cuz I I I can see it. I can
see the pattern with these [ __ ] What about you?
Back on Instagram. One second.
Yeah, that's Jamie Thompson.
these are the same kind of people that
are calling me Py.
He's in a wheelchair, is he?
He's in a [ __ ] wheelchair now.
These are the people that are talking
about young Peter Belly, matey. What a [ __ ] Yep. Probably, lad.
Yeah, he's [ __ ] Yeah, bro.
They don't look good. Any of these people, bro?
They don't even look normal.
Mad, is it? Right.
Why am I hungry, bro?
I'm a bit hungry, but there's nothing I
can really get.
You don't have any coke.
The coke tastes funny,
so I just won't have anything. Yeah.
What did you eat today, Grezy?
What the [ __ ] bro?
Oh, I'm surprised he actually shows his face
looking like that. To be fair,
I'm surprised he actually does show his
face. What about you, Steven Howard?
But what about the ugly virgin? He shows his face.
The skinned virgin shows his face. Yeah.
Imagine looking like that. Greavvesy.
What would you do if you looked like that?
What the [ __ ]
He actually looks like Peter Griffin, bro.
That [ __ ] actually looks like Peter Griffin.
That's Peter Griffin, bro.
Who do you reckon's more uglier, him or Virgin boy?
I don't know.
They're both pretty [ __ ] ugly, aren't
they? Probably both as ugly as each other. Sure. Yeah,
they're both [ __ ] ugly as [ __ ] Yeah, defin
I don't know how people could look like that, bro.
How can you stop caring about your
appearance though, bro? I mean, I brush
my teeth three times a day.
I wash my clothes every day. I mean, I I
don't sh I haven't The only reason I've
not shaved or gone to the barber is
because it's cold and I've not gone out
drinking. So, I mean,
how can you how can you how can you stop
caring about your appearance?
And if I was ever 1% fat like these
people, I'd be going to the [ __ ] gym. Yeah.
But then it's not about that. It's cuz
they they are just ugly. Anyways, people
like Nons and and and and and just
Jamie, they are just ugly. They're just
born ugly. It's not even about like that. Anyways,
they're just ugly as [ __ ] Even if they
shaved and and you know, they went gym,
they'd still be ugly. They're just ugly
[ __ ] Simple, naturally natural ugly [ __ ]
I don't know why he was laughing at my
beard earlier. LR11
laughing at my little fizz. Laughing at
my little face.
Why don't you show everyone your face?
I'm just lying in bed chilling. Going to
make myself a milkshake in a bit.
No, you laugh at me. Why don't you show
everyone your face?
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Yeah. Why don't you show us your face?
Cuz this is what one of the guys look
like on here that talk about the way
that I look.
This is him.
Yep. This is my biggest stalker on YouTube.
That's That's him. That's depression.
I'm not depressed, bro.
Depression. I'm not depressed.
There's a reason why I've not gone to
the barbers and I don't care if he's got a girlfriend.
I literally don't give a [ __ ] who's got
a girlfriend and who don't have a girlfriend.
I'm better looking. I've got more money
and I don't want a girlfriend. So, I
mean, I don't care. I'd rather look
normal and not [ __ ] like a [ __ ]
inhumane [ __ ] and have a girlfriend and
look normal and not have one, bro.
Nah, it's not debatable,
bro. Having a girlfriend isn't even a
skit. It's like telling someone that
they got no kids. It's lit. That is not
a skit. It's like telling someone
they've got no friends. That's not a
skit. A lot of these things that people
say on here, they're not even proper insults.
So, and I'm not depressed. There's a
reason why I've not gone to the barbers.
If I was depressed, I wouldn't be uh I
wouldn't be brushing my teeth three
times a day. I wouldn't be showering,
washing my clothes, changing my bed.
Bro, I'm not depressed.
I've got more of a life than you will
ever have, lad. You're the one sat on
YouTube 24/7, not me. You need to wish
you you you had a life before wishing
other people, lad.
You need to wish yourself to have a life.
life. You're the one on YouTube 24/7, not me.
Make that wish for yourself, bro. Not me, lad.
Yeah, bro. You need to wish yourself to
get a life, lad, before wishing anyone else.
Why am I so insecure,
bro? Who's the one that's not showing their face?
You are. So again, stop self projecting,
bro. If you're going to say stuff, man,
you need to make sure it's not about yourself.
That's the way things go. And everything
you say is just about yourself. So, yeah.
Yeah, bro. You're you're an idiot, lad.
That's that Jamie Thompson.
Yep, that's Jamie Thompson.
Uh, Nons's best friend.
That's what a lot of these people in
here look like. Mr. in. >> Yeah.
What do you think of the way he looks, Mr. Bean?
Nah, it's not Timmy, lad.
Nah, he looks worse than Timmy. Am I
gambling tonight? Nope.
No, he's worse than Timmy, bro.
I think he has got to be the most
ugliest person I've I've come across.
And he's very ugly, bro.
That's why he does this [ __ ] on YouTube. Obviously, bro.
I'd love to see someone on here. Yeah.
Actually look normal that does this. Mr. B,
there's not one person nonslegs ugly.
Jamie Thompson ugly. Lj ugly. Timmy
ugly. Bomb ugly. Pat ugly. I would love
one day for someone to look normal that
actually does this.
someone that actually looks normal, then
I'd be like, "Yeah, you know what?
They're kind of right." But that's never
going to happen because they're all
stinking, bro. You got someone that's 31
this month and they've got missing
teeth. They got missing front teeth.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, lad. Well, do you know
why I don't really talk about these
people much is because they're not even
worth talking about.
Because they're just losers. They're not
even worth talking about.
Got L J saying that I've been on here 10
years. I've not even been on here 10
years. And I've done and I've done more
than you in 28 years than you've done in
[ __ ] almost 50 almost 50 years, lad.
You're almost 50 and you have done
nothing with your life.
Really? What What have you done?
What have you done in 50 years?
He's almost 50. He said, "Yeah,
I haven't even known about this
community for 10 years. I first come
across Timmy when I was 18 and I come on
here when I was 21.
So, what the fuck?" And I've done stuff
on my years on YouTube. I've actually
done [ __ ] I've actually had a life. So,
what the [ __ ] is he talking about, bro?
He's talking about himself, bro. Wasted
my life. What the [ __ ]
bro? I don't even want to live to 50,
bro. I don't want to be 50.
What's the point of being an old wrinkly man?
I'll be going out again soon, drinking.
I don't know when, but imagine that Mr.
Be an old wrinkly man.
[ __ ] that, bro.
That's [ __ ] in it.
And then you die.
You're an old wrinkly man and then you die.
[ __ ] that [ __ ] bro.
I need to make this hot chocolate in a
bit. Hopefully, it's sweet enough,
Grezy, cuz I run out of sugar and the
shops are closed. Yeah.
Do you fear getting old, Grezy? I fear getting old.
I figure it out, bro.
Do I have diabetes? No.
Why would I I don't see the point in
living till 50, bro.
Once you're past like Yeah. 48 and that, it's over.
No is almost 50 and he's not been to
Asia. Imagine that, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Why would I? Sorry, I'm trying to
text someone at the same time. Yeah.
Right. Let me make this hot chocolate now.
better be sweet, bro. Oh,
it's not January anymore,
Gravesy. So, I guess I'm the February bear.
Is that funny? Easy.
A little way. Oh,
you know that G. know you wake up and
you got a full bladder and you have a nice wee.
You know when you wake up with a full bladder
and then you go wee wee?
It feels good on it.
It feels good now.
You remember when I used to go on them
dates with the women boos? You I never
and and I never
and I said I'm going to go to the toilet
and I never came back.
Yeah, I said I'm going to the toilet and
never come back.
That was cute. bless
making myself little hot Chocata.
I do hot chocolate.
Oh, I miss I miss B question. I kind of
You have the rest. He was on uh the
other month, wasn't he?
Funny [ __ ] though, was he?
Yeah, he was a funny [ __ ]
He said he was saying it to fit in.
You remember Greasy?
I asked I asked um Marquest why does he
say that about himself? He said a fair.
No, that virgin was just simply copying.
That's what he was doing. That skin
virgin was copying.
No mind of his [ __ ] own. Virgin copy. What?
Let me taste this, bro.
taste to [ __ ] Greasy.
Yeah, it's all right. Yeah, but there's no
might be able to get a little bit of
sugar in there.
Come on. Come on.
Sometimes it's there's a squeezer, isn't
it? the hot chocolates.
that [ __ ] [ __ ] up.
Nah. Why would I study game? It's got
nothing to do with game.
Why would I Why would I study game?
That's not going to change stuck up [ __ ]
Cuz the problem is them.
So why the [ __ ] would I be [ __ ]
studying game? You can't.
Oh, under the electric blanket I go.
>> I remember my electric blanket now. Oh gosh. Dude,
I need to go in a minute, bro.
that [ __ ] skin loses [ __ ] wild
[ __ ] neck in.
Yeah, I'm going anyways, lad. See you later.