Yo, man.
Just played a bit of rigged bonanza.
Same story there. Hey, bro.
[ __ ] man. I'm not even calling this
gambling anymore. I'm calling this fraud
from now on, bro. I'm not even calling
it gambling because if it was truly
truly gambling, you'd be winning some of
the time. I'm not even going to name it
gambling anymore. I'm calling it [ __ ]
fraud. There's no time. There's no
there's no way. Every single time you
can put money on, you can keep losing it
and keep blaming bad luck. No [ __ ]
way, bro. Only £50, bro. But it's not
the point. I was playing that slot for
like an hour, bro. A whole I was sat
there literally. He said, "Oh, you've
been playing 60 minutes. Same old story.
Same tease. Same teases. Finally got a
bonus. Paid nothing."
Bro, come on. What the [ __ ] is going on now,
you know? Rigged, rigged, rigged,
rigged, rigged, rigged, rigged.
That's all it ever is is [ __ ] rigged
as [ __ ] bro. It was only £50 as well. I
don't give a [ __ ] if it was only [ __ ]
I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
It's so fixed.
So so so fixed, bro.
The only reason I'm not proper proper
kicking off is cuz like I'm at thingies
house and people are sleeping and that,
bro. I'm trying to [ __ ] hold it in.
It's so annoying, bro.
It's so rigged. It's so annoying. I'm
not even calling it gambling anymore.
It's [ __ ] fraud. You can't play four,
five, six sessions and keep losing. No
way. And no way is anyone going to
justify it to me either, [ __ ] Simple. Yeah.
No base game wins, no nothing. Just
tease tease tease tease te's. And then
when I got a bonus, it just literally paid nothing.
Then I spent another 25 minutes trying
to get another bonus. I was doing like
40 60p spins. Nothing, bro. Nothing.
Nothing. Is there any form of gambling
that's not just completely [ __ ] rigged?
Like I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm curious. Is
there any kind of gambling you can
actually Well, it's not gambling. It's
fraud. I'm not calling it gambling
anymore because if it was gambling,
you'd actually be winning. So, is there
any kind of fraud that you can win on?
Is there any kind of fraud that you can
win on Mr. B? Because it ain't even
gambling anymore. I'm not calling it.
It was Bonanza.
Took an hour to get a bonus and then it
never paid nothing.
What the [ __ ] was even the point of that?
What is the point of this fraud? This
such clever fraud. It was only £50. I
was doing 40 lb 60p spins. Well, it's
not fun, bro. I feel like breaking
someone's [ __ ] jaw.
The only reason I'm not smashing this
whole house up is because I, you know,
my mom's house and there's people
sleeping and that. Otherwise, I would be
smashing [ __ ] up like I did in the old
house. It's [ __ ] irritating as [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] annoying as [ __ ] bro. It's so annoying.
So [ __ ] annoying, bro.
It's so [ __ ] annoying, bro. Serious.
Seriously, it is annoying
cuz it's blatantly cheating. You can't
gamble and gamble and gamble and never
win. It's It's not possible, bro. And
then you can only win on the football.
It's not possible. It's not possible.
Why are you not winning, bro?
Why the [ __ ] are you not winning?
What's the reason for you not winning?
I like the reason why you're not
winning. You know, simple as that. You
should be winning. If you are gambling,
you know, a couple of times, you should
be winning. Simple as that.
I'm getting [ __ ] I'm really getting
mood swings now, bro. This what I'm
saying, Mr. B.
I'm getting these really sick dirty mood
swings, bro. I'm worse than LT, bro. I'm
worse than that [ __ ] Yeah, you think
he's You think he's bad, bro. He's not
worse than me.
He's not worse than me, mate. Trust me,
he is not [ __ ] worse than me, mate.
He is not worse than me. I'm not saying
too much on here anyways because of
these uh little you know what informants. Yeah.
Well, it's not called gambling. It's
called money laundering.
It's not called gambling. It's called
money laundering. Because if it was
gambling, you'd actually be winning.
You'd actually be winning sometimes. No,
that's it's it's money laundering.
Yeah, that's what it is. It's money
laundering. It's not gambling. It's
money laundering. It's not gambling.
Now I'm starting to get them [ __ ]
demons in my [ __ ] head again, bro. I
swear to God, it's so [ __ ] annoying.
And they call this entertainment. What
part of any of this is entertainment? You know,
I'm getting really bad mood swings, bro.
really really bad mood swings.
I often to try and hold them in, bro. It's annoying. Yeah.
150 in two [ __ ] days.
180 in two days actually with the
football. What the [ __ ] bro?
No, I'm not doing another couple bets
on. [ __ ] off, bro. Suck my [ __ ] dick.
That's what you can do. Suck my [ __ ]
dick, you little stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] off, man.
Now I'm just thinking of the manager
now, bro. Now this is where these
thoughts start coming back now, bro.
These thoughts start coming back like the manager
um and them feeding their kids with my
money and that, bro. It starts coming
back again, bro. Starts coming really
really really back. It's really really
really really really bad. Really [ __ ] bad, bro.
Like super super bad. And it it's last
like 8 hours. It doesn't stop for like
eight hours, bro. They're bad bad bad mood swings.
All I can think about is the casino
manager laughing at me with these shitty dirty kids.
Bad, bro. Bad. Really bad. Yeah.
Really, really, really bad, bro.
Sick, dirty, stinky moose wins. I'm
telling you, bro.
Just lost [ __ ] 50 pound on [ __ ]
Bonanza, bro. What the [ __ ]
Can't say too much on here anyways
because of the grasses. But yeah, trust me.
H how do you continuously keep losing?
Can someone explain that to me? H
No, I just put £50 on Bonanza.
Can someone explain to me how you can keep losing? H
No, I just put 50 on.
Yeah, but you should be winning
sometime, shouldn't you?
Bro, I'm really getting bad mood swings,
bro. Like, severely bad mood swings. And
I have to calm it down because [ __ ] living here.
I want to wait for the [ __ ] casino to
the manager to finish, bro.
I was playing roulette, you [ __ ]
idiot, the other day. And that that even
that was rigged.
That's all I can think about, bro. is is
a casino uh the casino manager.
Trust me, that's all I can think of. You know,
you know what I mean?
I'll probably wake up in a bad mood, be
in a bad mood all day tomorrow as well.
That's how bad it affects me, bro.
That's how bad it affects me. I don't
give a [ __ ] if I've still got money. I
don't care. You are playing to win.
You're not playing to lose. That's how I
see it, bro. You know, these other
people seem to lose and they don't give
a [ __ ] [ __ ] that [ __ ] [ __ ] that. [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. Just 50.
It doesn't matter anyways. It was just
50, but it doesn't matter anyways, bro.
I don't care how much I never ever going
to say how much I lose in the future anyways. Cuz
people like you
seem to think that you need to lose all
your money. You seem to need You seem to
think that you need to be broke. No,
bro. That's not how it works.
Why would I buy beer when I don't go out anymore?
Well, no, because I gamble to try to win
more money with the 50. So, why would I
buy beer when I don't even drink?
Why would I buy beer when a I was trying
to win money and b I don't drink?
No. So, no. If I wanted to buy £50, if I
wanted to spend £50 on beer, I'd spend
£50 on beer right now. I spend £300 on
beer right now. That's not the point, you know?
It's not even stressful. It's just
fixed. And that's what it is. It's just So
now I'll be depressed now for like two
days. Bad is it bro? Really bad.
Really really bad. You know,
I don't understand how these people can
lose money and be okay with it.
I I don't understand how they seem to
can lose and be fine. It will ruin my
whole day. I don't understand how people
can be fine with being conned out of
money. I'd rather I'd rather the money
drop out of my wallet and I'd be okay with it.
Well, they are okay because when they
lose, they don't react the way I react.
You don't know how I react, bro. You
don't know the half of it. Yeah. I don't
put it on YouTube because obviously
these little grasses, bro. Trust me, no
one is as bad as me. Yeah, I've been in
betting shops. No one is as bad as me.
But trust me, they are okay compared to me, mate.
Cuz the other day if that person slowed
that car down, I would have dragged them
out of that car.
The other day, when was it? I think I
come out uh was it? Yeah. No. Yeah, it
was the day I went to that police thing.
It was last Friday. If they stopped that
car, I would have dragged them out of
that [ __ ] car.
Trust me. Trust me, I would have. Yeah.
I would have dragged them out of that
car, mate. And I would have saw Reggie,
you don't know what I'm like, bro. You
don't know. This is not four or five
years ago. Yeah. Simple as that. It's
not four or five years ago.
People seem to lose and they seem to be
all right with it. And if they're not
all right with it, they don't act the
way that I act. Simple as that.
Bad it, bro. Bad.
Timmy doesn't act like this when he
loses. We've seen Timmy lose, mate. It
got to the point if I if I ever lose in
the in the bookies, I'm spitting on the machine.
That machine, I'm spitting all over the
machine. And I've done it multiple
times. Now you tell me.
You tell me. Anyone else that does that, bro? Oh yeah. [ __ ] off.
[ __ ] off. How about that one? [ __ ] off.
But people like secular slot seems to be
all right with it.
Secular slot seems to be all right with losing
enough to make anyone depressed. And
they seem to think that because you've
got money no I don't give a [ __ ] if I've
got [ __ ] money. I don't give a [ __ ]
Simple as that. I don't care.
Does it matter if someone's got money?
Does it matter how much money someone loses? No. Yeah. Trust me,
I just don't like losing.
I just don't like losing money on that.
Simple. I don't like losing money on it.
I feel like I've been degraded. I don't
like it. I feel like I've been laughed
at and mocked. That's the way my That's
the way my brain goes. I've been mocked,
laughed at. Trust me, bro. My mind goes [ __ ]
Yes, they can. Yes, they can. Timmy's
does. Timmy's fine after gambling.
No, Timmy's fine after gambling.
Timmy doesn't go mad. Yeah. So, yeah.
He's not worse than me, mate. Well, he's
not worse than me.
No one's worse than me. And I've been
around a lot of people. They're not
worse than me. When I lose, I think of
them feeding their their their kids with
my money. Them laughing at me. Um,
everyone laughing at me. The whole
world's against me. Trust me, it's bad.
It's really, really bad. Trust me.
Mine's more anger than anything as well,
cuz it's [ __ ] annoying. I'd rather
drop 300 pound, bro. I'd rather lose
£300 than I would rather
I'd rather lose £300
on the street than than lose 40 on
gambling. That's how bad it is.
That's how bad it is. It's really that bad.
And I tell you another thing, it's not
even about losing money. I I went to a
place before, I put £50 in. I took the
50 back and it was giving me mood swings
for like 2 hours and I didn't even lose any money.
I don't know what it is, bro.
I just don't like I just don't like Yeah. Simple.
That's enough to put anyone into a
depression. It's enough to trigger
anyone to be mentally ill. You know,
I don't need to imagine a McDonald's.
I've got money. I don't need to imagine
money because when I'm putting money in a site
in my head, oh, I'm prepared to lose it
and I want to win. I I'm not going to
think that because I've got plenty more £50.
So why would I think of the £50 when I
could literally just buy £50 worth of
McDonald's? That doesn't make sense what you're saying.
It's not my last £50, bro. So I don't
know why you use examples like that.
So, I don't know why you're using
examples like that. It doesn't It
doesn't make sense.
It doesn't make any sense. But anyways,
it's not the point. Yeah.
So, I was going to go on roulette and
chase it, but obviously I'm not going to
be doing that. But yeah,
cuz if I did and I end up losing, I
would end up Yeah, we're not going to
get into it anyways cuz the grass is on
like Fatty Thompson. But yeah, just know
a lot of [ __ ] would be happening over YouTube.
So yeah, bro. Yeah,
I don't need a job. I've got enough
money. I don't need a job.
I don't need a job. I've got enough money, lad.
Thank you very much.
Just thought I play some slots.
Why you telling me to get a job, bro,
when I don't need a job? H No.
Yeah, he does. Yeah, Greasy doesn't know
anything though, does he?
Grievy doesn't know anything. So,
no, he's just going off by before like
two months ago. No,
that Joe F is too faced. I had to tell
him about himself and I had to tell LT
about himself as well. That's two people
I had to tell about himself.
Yeah, LT got mad at me, bro.
Oh, he's very touchy about his boyfriend.
Did he don't say anything about his
boyfriend on slayer because he gets on
the [ __ ] he jumps on the bandwagon.
No, he's not lucky on the machines, lad.
What he's posting is not real.
Trust me, bro. What he's posting is not real.
It's He's not lucky. No one wins on them
machines anymore. Not jealousy. It's
just facts. Nothing to be jealous of an
old man. I'm better looking than him.
I've got more money than him. I don't
need to be jealous of an old man. That's just facts. >> So,
you don't fool me. I said if you're
really winning that many times, go live
and gamble. He couldn't do it. Yeah. It's [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] lad.
All he's doing is putting money in and
taking it back out. It's so obvious,
bro. It's so hard to win money gambling
nowadays on anything, let alone them machines. So,
trust me, you don't have me fooled, lad.
You don't have me fooled. Yeah.
That wasn't his 13 grand. It was his
daddy's. He's never seen 13 grand in his
life. He's skint.
He's a skint loser. He's never had 13
grand in his life. That was his daddy's money,
which is why he can't show it now. Yeah,
>> that [ __ ] is [ __ ] skint as well as
ugly, bro. That's why he tries to call
me ugly and skint cuz he's talking about himself.
He is skint and he's also ugly as well.
He's a self projector lad. Oh [ __ ]
Yeah, I'll be depressed now for days, I think.
let me see. Yeah, that red star is a
proper loser, bro. Just sat there
recording everything every day. He's
another disabled loser.
Nah, I'll be in bed all day later
tomorrow. I think that's enough to make anyone depressed.
Wow, that's mad, lad.
Yeah, that that guy's a proper [ __ ]
bro. I think he's just like Jamie Thompson. Disabled.
Sat on YouTube recording everything
every day. Yeah, disabled loser, bro. Disabled loser.
Yeah, he's a proper loser, isn't he?
Yeah, proper proper lowife loser.
nothing going for himself.
Just like this fellow
ugly as [ __ ] I love I love it. I love
the people in the comments that try to
talk about the way that I look when I'm
literally better looking than them. I
love them comments, bro. They don't even
make me mad. They make me laugh, lad.
Yeah. Yeah. That's Jamie Thompson, bro.
That's what Red Star looks like. That's
why they're sat on YouTube every day
calling someone like me younger and
better looking than them the M because
I'm better looking than them. Yeah.
Stop asking stupid questions.
Yeah, I'm getting a mood swings again.
Greasy. I'm getting a nasty mood swings again. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm getting them dirty dirty mood swings.
UK asylum. Do you do you reckon that Red
Star is a loser? Proper proper loser, bro.
I don't know if people on here were just
disabled or they don't understand,
but he is a proper proper loser.
Only someone like Only someone would sit
only a loser, bro, would sit on YouTube
for years recording stuff hating people
that they don't know, bro. Only a proper
jealous bitter loser with nothing going
for themselves would do that. Facts, bro.
Only a bitter jealous loser with nothing
going for themselves or even a life
would do that, bro. Trust me. I'm never
wrong when I I'm never wrong when I talk
about these people, bro. Trust me.
It's because where they're ugly and they
ain't got a life of their own, they hate
being them. You see? So what they do is
they try to um
they don't like their own lives because
they're just fat ugly bongs. So they try to um
go for other people to forget about
their own [ __ ] lives. Red Star, the
Skint Virgin with no teeth. Uh there's
lots of them, bro. Lots of them.
Yeah. No, they ain't got nothing going
on. They're just fat ugly virgins,
you know? They're fat, ugly virgins with
nothing going for themselves. That's why
they're sat on it every day, bro.
And they still try to use kids as an
excuse as well. Oh, you said stuff about
kids, bro. This is 2026.
If these people actually had a life,
they literally would just go on with their life.
We said it, we've said it many times,
bro. We said it many times before.
We've said it many, many times before.
Look at these nasty mood swings, bro.
No, I don't like the attention. This is
why I'm not on it. I don't want these
[ __ ] ugly people following me, lad.
I don't want these [ __ ] fat ugly
people following me. Why the [ __ ] would
I want their attention?
If I knew where one of these people
lived, bro. Yeah, we'll leave that at
that. Why would I Why would I like
attention from fat, ugly, stalking low
lives? Make it make sense, bro. There's
times when I'm not on here for weeks,
weeks, and weeks and weeks. But it's not
about me anyways, bro. This isn't about
me, lad. Because it doesn't matter if I
go live. It doesn't matter if I don't go
live. It shows what these people are to
sit here and do this every day. It shows
what they are, bro. It doesn't matter
what I do. It shows what they are. If
someone has to if someone sits on
YouTube all they recording something
they ain't got nothing in their life.
And I'll say it in 2026 if someone sat
there on YouTube stalking someone in
2026 they have got no life. They are
jealous of you. It's as simple as that.
Doesn't matter what I do, bro.
Okay, think about like this, bro. Do I
sit there on YouTube every day recording stuff?
Let's let's let's lose let's use this
analogy, right? Do I sit there on
YouTube every day recording stuff? No, I
do not. I don't even go on people's
channels. Let's use that analogy. Yeah. H
So, at the end of the day, bro, it
doesn't really matter, is it?
You got no life. Simple.
They're fat losers. They got nothing in life. Yeah. Okay.
But there's people that come on here and
share them information. I don't go I
don't stalk them.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, bro. No, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. Bro, it t it takes two to
tango. Yeah, there's people on here that
share their life and go live. Do I stalk
them? No. Why? Because I'm better than
them. because I've got because I've got
a life on like them. That's the difference. Yeah,
that's the difference. You know why? Why
do I not react to these people? Why do
these people not bother me? But I'll
talk about them now. We're on a subject
is because I am better than them. They
are not better than me. So every single
time they obsess over me, every single
time these losers stalk me, it proves
that I'm right about them, they're not
right about me.
That's that's that lad, you know.
So, okay. So, why don't Okay. So, why
don't I do it then? How comes when
Seaside Mark comes on YouTube or when
someone else Why don't I sit there and
stalk people every day then?
So, why don't I stalk them? H Yeah. Simple.
I gave you No, I don't lurk him in many
chats. I'm not subscribed to no one. No,
I'm not. No, I'm [ __ ] not. No, I'm
definitely definitely definitely definitely not.
really really got a headache.
I'll be in a bad mood when I wake up
tomorrow as well.
Yeah, I was in a bad mood when I wake up
when I woke up today as well for like an hour.
Sausage, bro. You're self projecting, lad.
Nothing you say bothers us.
You're self-projecting. No one cares
about self-projecting comments. Like I
said, man, if you tuned in earlier,
we've seen what a lot of you people look like.
And you really are ugly and special
needs. So, bro, like it's not going to
bother me what you say cuz we know with
you, we we know the pattern with you
people. That's why I don't get mad. I
mean, look at the picture right here.
This is one of you people in the picture.
This is one of you's
that is literally one of you's in the
picture. One of your gang is in the
picture. So, do you think any of you's
should talk about someone like me? It
would never happen in a million years.
So, it doesn't bother me what what a low life says.
I mean, do you know what I find so
funny, Dak? Yeah. is is is like whenever
L J is live. Yeah. When I used to go on
this. Yeah, man. It Have you noticed is
the same people on there 24/7?
The same people that's got all this
money. The same people that gets that
has all these friends. Yeah. Right. On
YouTube 24/7. I love that, bro. That's
another thing I used to do, you know.
Yeah, bro. you. It's clear that you talk
about yourselves every day, bro. So, you
I don't know what reaction you're trying
to get, you know.
We've already gone over the people that
actually show their face and people
that's been doxed.
It's uh you none of you look look
normal. None of you are good-looking.
This guy in the picture is not good-looking. Look,
he looks like a he looks like Peter Griffin.
Maybe Peter Griffin's a bit more better
looking than him. Come on, bro. You know,
come on, man.
It's a sad sight. Sad sight to see, bro.
Sad sight to see.
Sad sight to see, lad.
So why is are you why are you on YouTube
24/7 anyways? Cuz I was off YouTube for
a couple of weeks, bro. So why are you
on YouTube 24/7 if you've got this perfect life?
Can I Can I ask that? Cuz you're not
multitasking. Don't even try and say
you're multitasking, bro. Because when I
was in the arcade last month and I was
trying to send money over to someone, I
couldn't even concentrate on two things.
So you tell me right what you are doing
on here. 24/7 if you've got this perfect life.
You know who you are. Come on.
Like I said, bro, have you have you seen
Have you seen Nons legs? That's sock.
Have you Have Have you seen Nles legs,
bro? Have you seen Have you seen this
guy in the picture?
I mean, LT says he's good-looking. LT
says a lot of stuff, but we've never
seen what the guy [ __ ] looks like, have we? So,
you know, see it that way. You know, see
thing, bro. I I brush my teeth three
times a day. That's sock. It never
happened where I don't brush my teeth again, bro. Never happened.
Bro, how you
hiding's perfect, lad?
I had a shower earlier.
I wonder how that guy in the picture
gets in the shower. H
Well, I have to keep my teeth clean, don't I?
I wonder how this [ __ ] gets in the shower.
Yeah, but you don't drink Coke like I do.
Yeah, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. Anyways, I'm going. Yeah. See you later.