D
[ __ ] game [ __ ] at night.
So I had to do a had to do another one.
Oh, here we go.
Hope them ain't been cancelled
cuz that'll be bloody [ __ ] [snorts] Oh man,
what's that all about?
>> [clears throat]
>> Why does that keep being Is that been p
Why does that keep doing that?
Now I need to remember which ones are
[ __ ] done now. Why does it keep doing that, bro?
Let me see. That is so weird, bro. I
don't That's so [ __ ] annoying, man.
I'm trying to do a [ __ ] bet and he
keeps [ __ ] voiding the [ __ ] thing.
Why does it keep doing that?
It's been postponed or
let me see.
So [ __ ] annoying, bro. It's done that
god knows how many times now.
Yeah, it's been postponed.
Most of them have been postponed, right?
Yes, because been disponed. The dirty
[ __ ] bastard. That's why. All right.
Now I'm going to cash out.
I have to cash this. I want one team,
bro. The [ __ ] man.
So, how much have we got
in this account?
Okay, £13. So,
[sighs and gasps]
this is so annoying, bro.
What's the point where most of them just
get postponed? I don't understand, bro.
What the [ __ ]
Right. What ones haven't been postponed?
Let's have a look.
Spin it. So, we got right [snorts] and Let's do
I'm going to do
I'm just going to lump the pound on it. Yeah.
Right. Yeah. It's cuz they keep getting
[ __ ] postponed. Are [ __ ] [ __ ] man. All right.
Okay. Now they've rectified it. [laughter]
They're showing the ones that haven't been postponed. Okay. So,
sorry about that, bro.
No, but I don't care. See you later. Okay. Um,
get a kick, lad.
I don't think Spennymore is going to I reckon. Okay, so
Not great odd, did it? Let's be fair.
Right. So, maybe put six pound on this.
Okay, that's still 126.
I reckon that. And then £6.15.
I know, man. It's [ __ ] me. It kept
canceling my [ __ ] bets. I'm having to redo him. Um,
yeah, I'm going to go with this one.
Okay, six pound on that one. And I got £7.6
returns 129. You have to do [ __ ] bets
like this because a lot of them has been postponed.
The correct score I had a good correct
score when it got postponed, man. [ __ ] Um. Okay. So,
all right. Okay.
[snorts and gasps]
Both teams are score. Um,
no, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, first half. Here we go.
[ __ ] bastards, bro.
I don't like it when they get postponed, man.
It sucks, isn't it?
I know. I don't I I didn't see the post.
I don't follow jealous people. I don't
go on jealous people's channels. If you
catch my drift, Dr. Echo,
I left that in 2025. It's 2026. [gasps] So, yeah. Okay.
Right. That's self. Yeah.
[ __ ] sake. Okay. So,
no, I don't want to do the same team.
Let's go back on North.
I reckon they will score in the first half.
Okay. So, [sighs and gasps]
£7 on that returns 119.
Let's do it, man.
There we go.
[ __ ] dirty [ __ ]
I ain't on. No,
I reckon that one's definitely going to
win. I'll put more on it if I if there's
like a perfect lineup, then I'll I'll
obviously put more on it in it. But the
lineups are [ __ ] It needs to be a
perfect lineup where they're playing at
home, you know. Yeah,
the biggest payout was 129.
[ __ ] postponed. Pponed. Pponed.
I got I'm going to order a curry soon. Oh, yeah.
But no, I don't I don't respond to um
jealous people anymore.
No, I don't I don't I don't play jealous people games
for the reason reasons why what I've
stated multiple multiple multiple times multiple times.
Simple, lad. I left it in 2025. This is
2026, not 2025.
So that's the way I see it. Um yeah,
both teams to score in the first half. Yeah. So,
yeah, there's still some good still some
good bets. £15 worth of bets. Yeah.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> I might I might start playing Runescape
again, you know. Yeah. >> [sighs]
>> See you later.
The [ __ ] did I come back on for, bro? Yeah,
Peter Benny has a lot of people jealous of him.
That's a good thing, bro, cuz you know
you're doing something right.
Oh, do you like it? Do you like it, Grezy? Yeah, bro.
£120 it cost me. It's actually still
Well, it was down from 160. It's
actually still 160 on the Lego site. Yeah.
I had to redo these bloody football
bets, Grezy, because a lot of the games got postponed.
[ __ ] sake. Gosh darn it.
Oh, you know that woman I was speaking
to on Instagram, she she didn't reply
for a little bit and now she's replied.
I said, "Oh, thank God for that. I was
going to call a SWAT team out. I was
getting worried about you. I don't know
if you got kidnapped or something. It's
not like you to to to suddenly uh to
suddenly not respond. But you know, at
work, they said, "Oh, I've just finished
work." I said, "Oh, okay. That's that's
okay then." You know,
you might were kidnapped or something.
That's why you're not responding. I was
getting [ __ ] worried.
Yeah, I was getting worried.
But everything's okay.
What are you eating today, Grezy? I'm
going to have a lush curry in a bit.
Yeah, when it opens. Oh, it's not even
long until it opens.
I am [ __ ] hungry, bro. But it doesn't open. Sure.
Yeah. In a bit.
So hungry, bro. [ __ ] hell.
Time to read them [ __ ] football bats
again. Oh, you still not that bad there
diet, are you, Gravesy? Bless you.
The characters are collecting
are are adding up nicely, aren't they,
Greavvesy? The characters. Yeah.
I've never known, bro. Do you know what
I was saying to my um mom earlier? Bro,
I've never known I actually said this
earlier to my mom, Grezy. I've never
known so many middle-aged people to be
obsessed with a 28-year-old.
I've never known it. I said to her,
like, I find it strange. Yeah. Like all
jokes aside, I was saying to her, I
don't go on anyone's [ __ ] anymore, but
I'm just saying like based on I said
like it's it's weird that like and and I
said to her as well like it's how long
they've actually been doing it for,
you know? They've been obsessed for
years now and you would have thought
they would have got bored. I said to
her, I found it like very strange.
We was talking about money and stuff. um
not money, but like um I was basically
just saying like what they've like done
over the years.
And I was just saying like I just can't
understand how like people would be so
jealous of someone that they don't even know.
Hateful. I said hateful as well. I
actually said, bro, I said hateful and jealous
um of someone that they don't even know.
Think about that, bro. Like say you've
spent Yeah. like a solid
I don't know, bro. Let's say, let's say
3 years. Yeah. You spent a solid 3 years
of your life hating people, trying to
get your money stopped. Like, you could
have literally done something with your
life in them 3 years.
What do you think, Grezy? Like,
I just find it odd to be honest, bro.
But may maybe it's just me how they can
be obsessed and jealous of of someone
that they don't even know.
I found it weird, bro. It just come up
in conversation, is it? So
that is [ __ ] weird, bro.
And then they say that they're not
disabled. This is what I mean with the
with the people in this community, bro.
They say they're not disabled, but their
actions show otherwise.
But that's one thing. Weird, bro.
Um, so anyways, but when are you getting
when are you getting a takeaway again
then? Friday, Saturday, Friday, Saturday.
I'm sure you have one once a week, huh?
I know. I used to, bro. When I used to
go to the gym. I'll be going to the gym
soon anyways, bro.
probably start uh
to be fair, I'll probably start Monday
to be fair, bro. Yeah,
it is. It is. It is weird. Hopefully
they don't get postponed, bro.
Very odd. Very very odd. Odd straightens.
Oh [ __ ] Look what's just come up. Bonanza. Yeah.
Play that [ __ ] Um, that's mad.
Proper proper mad, bro.
That is mad, lad.
Very, very, very, very mad.
They're so jealous. I've never known a
bunch of middle-aged people be jealous
of someone that they don't know.
You can't even You can't even get mad at
them, bro. I struggle to even get mad. I
couldn't even get mad if I wanted to, bro.
Cuz you just need to remember, like I
said, bro, many times, you need to
remember what these people look like.
You need to remember that these people
are on YouTube 24/7. So, they can't talk
about them. Trying to talk about anyone
else is just just embarrassing, bro. So,
I can't even get mad. I seriously seriously can't.
So yeah, very strange. Very strange. [snorts]
It's a life though. Um, Frankie Frankie.
I just saw Smokey Bee's comment. I don't
know why he's commenting, bro. He's not
blocked. I don't know why he's
commenting on [ __ ] He's not blocked.
He's being a bit of a s as well, but
he's not blocked. So, I don't know why
he just doesn't come on here.
Mad, bro. Mad. Mad people. Lad. Mad
To be honest with you, they should be
focusing on their own lives, these
people, to be honest. I mean, yeah.
Okay. you put up content, they can say,
"Oh, this is immature. That's immature."
But they really should be wondering
about their own lives. They shouldn't be
asked about anyone else's lives
cuz that's not what you're supposed to
do. You know, you're supposed to worry
about your own life.
You see comments where they say, "Oh,
like this person's got this money, that
person gets that money." And it's like,
"What the [ __ ] bro?"
you know, they're so obsessed with other
people's lives. It's very weird.
But obviously, you're not going to try
and figure it out, are you, bro? Because
they're [ __ ] disabled. So, you trying
to you trying to work out disabled
people, you're just going to [ __ ]
lose brain cells. That's why they're
disabled. Because it doesn't make sense. So, yeah.
Very odd. Very very odd. Mad.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
My bets winning today.
Almost that time, bro. Madness.
That is mad obsession, bro. M
I just do a bit of studying as you do. Yeah,
I do a little bit of studying here and there.
Why do you think I win a lot of the time?
Well, I've had to redo the bets cuz they
got uh anything got postponed. So, I've
had to redo him again. [snorts]
Yeah, just a bit of studying.
Yeah, over time.
Where is it?
Where are they? One second.
I'll tell you what they are.
There we go.
Yeah. So, I've got uh
Ken Ashton FC
and Mackersfield FC. Uh both teams to
score in the first half.
Then I got DOA and I got Charlie uh
Charlie, not Charlie, Charlie. Both um
both teams to score and them teams to win. Yeah.
Oh, just a bit of fun, eh? Yeah.
[snorts] Like I said, bro, I do a bit of studying.
on the lower leagues.
They might not both score.
I might lose.
If I lose both bets, I've lost £15.
There we go.
No, the highest the highest is um £129,
but I've only put £15 in. So,
we still good return in it. if one of
them wins and then the other one's 119.
So if they both win then it's over 200
pound. Like I said even if one of them
wins you've only put £15 in is it? So
that's a good return from that I guess. [snorts]
You can probably hear my [ __ ] stomach rumbling. That's hunger. Yeah, man. >> [panting]
>> Nope. I haven't been shopping. I'm going
to go shopping tomorrow.
What do you think of these people,
Dr. Echo? They're weird, aren't they?
See you later, lad.
You gave yourself away there. See you later. [snorts]
They're weird people in here. What do
you think, Dr. Eko?
It's very strange how they're obsessed
with other people's lives.
Very, very, very strange.
And by lives, I mean like um personal
life. I don't mean like content that you
put up. You understand what I'm saying?
It's I find them very very weird, bro.
They're very cringy.
I think they just need to get a life to be honest.
>> I feel like an idiot now to be honest, bro.
They just they just need to get a life, bro. Serious
[ __ ] wild, bro. I don't know how they
can be so hateful and jealous to someone
that they don't even know.
Proper proper madness, lad.
I just think it's jealousy to be honest
with you, bro. With with these people,
Dr. Eko, I just think with them it's jealousy.
you know, younger than them, better
looking, more money, you got family. I
just I just think it's jealousy, bro.
Obviously, you don't have to agree. I
don't I don't really care, bro. Like,
yeah, but you have Yeah, you you
obviously I have annoyed people, bro. Of
course, you've annoyed people, bro.
You're [ __ ] younger than these
people. You're better looking than these
people. Of course, that will annoy them
because, like I said, bro, I don't know
you. I don't know. I haven't seen you on
here for very long. But you got to
understand that the people on here are
actual actual wasters, bro. Like they
they've got nothing going for
themselves. They're past the sale by
date. They're very [ __ ] ugly. So, I
mean, of course that is going to annoy
people when you're better looking than
them. You've got a life. You can go out.
You know what I'm saying? Of course it annoys them.
Uh, nothing, bro. Nothing, man. I'm just
saying that uh it's just it's weird to
have loads of middle-aged people
obsessed with you every day. But
yeah, I just don't redone my football bets.
I think if one of them wins, I'm just
going to save it for Saturday and do
another one to be fair. Yeah, probably. Yeah.
Yeah. UK silent. These people are very
strange on it here on it, bro. Very strange.
No, I haven't started it yet. I don't
know when I'm going to start it.
Yeah, I know, bro. I know, bro. I know.
I heard that Joe F's done a post on me.
I'm not even going to read it. I don't
care. He if he's got anything to say, he
can come and say to my face when I'm in Nottingham.
It's as simple as that, man. Like, I I
don't care about these people, bro. I
know what they are.
When am I going to go Nottingham? I need
to set a date, bro, because I need to go
out drinking soon. So, I'll do a
community post in advance and I'll just
say if you've got anything to say, you
can come say it to my face. Simple as that.
Okay. Okay. One second. I'm going to
answer this one more time cuz I'm being
very nice to you. Yeah. Come on. One
second. Uh, who do I bet on? I I'll tell
you the teams in a in a minute. Um,
yeah, loads of copycats on there. Come
on, bro. You're playing with Lego doing
a kid's voice. No one is jealous.
What do you people look like again when
you get exposed?
You You know you people that show your face,
right? What do you look like that show
your face and and the people that get doxed?
Yeah. I rest my case. That's all I need
to say, bro. I I I don't need to say
anymore. Say no more, bro. Say no more.
How about that one? Look at that guy in
the picture. Look at this guy right in
the picture right here. This guy stalks
me every day. Look at him and look at me. Enough said.
I don't need to say anymore, bro. That's
that's the end of that. That's why no
one can get mad at it. But yeah, UK
asylum, there's loads of copycats.
Loads and loads of copycats.
See you later, lad.
Um, yeah, the teams. Um, one second,
bro. Sorry, man. I got distracted.
So, I got I had to um redo him, Dusty,
because the a lot of the games got
postponed. I done both teams to score in
the first half. Yeah, cuz um Ken Ashton
and Mackersfield FC both teams to score.
I'm ordering an Indian. Yeah. And then I
got DOA uh both teams to score and DOA
to win. And I got both teams to score
and Charlie to win. I've got a feeling
one of them is going to win. And if it
wins, I'm just going to carry the money
over till Saturday
and then probably just lump it all on a double.
Uh, one of them's £6.15
returns 129 and then the other one's £7
and it returns 119.
So, I mean, I've only put £15 in. So, if
only one of even if one of them wins,
it's still a good return
on Saturday. So, yeah.
What did you think of the community post
UK silent that I done two days ago?
Yeah. What did you think of it?
I didn't think there was games either.
When I looked earlier, it wasn't coming
up. And then when I went back on it,
now it's coming up. So, I thought, [ __ ]
it. I put 10 pound. I was like, "Oh, no.
I fancy a five on another one." So, yeah.
And I'll just stick on two team Saturday
if it uh wins. Yeah.
See you later. [snorts]
What do you mean you didn't rate at UK
Asylum? The community post. No, the
community post with the copycats.
Was it copying or not? UK asylum. Was it Would
you say that was copying or no? Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. What were they doing?
You remember what they were doing?
Like a certain person we know. E
like a certain person we know. Hey,
Greavvesy. Not mentioning any names. But um
yeah, say no more.
Yeah. No one no one wears what I wear.
Like I told you, bro, I wear vapor, a
body jeans, six six silk coat. No one
wears what I wear. I don't copy people.
You think I can't [ __ ] wear a [ __ ]
Canada goose coat? Of course I could. I don't copy.
I don't copy that. No [ __ ] way.
Yeah. I was speaking to this woman UK
asylum. I didn't hear from her all day
and I said, "Are you okay?" She said,
"Oh, I just finished working out and
we're talking again." I said, "Oh, I was
starting to get worried. I thought you
got kidnapped or something. I was about
to call a SWAT to I was I was about to
call the SWAT team."
Yeah, I was getting a bit worried, but
yeah, just finished work. We was voice
noting all day um yesterday. Grievy,
haven't told her about the collection yet, but yeah,
[snorts] you get me. Hey,
I was on the phone to my Dutch friend
for hours yesterday. Greezy, I might
start playing Runescape again.
I love I used to love Runescape. I ain't
played it for years. He still plays every day.
I don't give a [ __ ] if they're not in I
I don't I couldn't give a [ __ ] if they
are and they're not. Lad,
I'll be going to Nottingham soon
anyways, Mr. Bean. Just need to set a
date for it, lad. I'll be going soon anyways.
She sure is. Yep. I haven't told her
yet, obviously, cuz then I won't be able to collect.
Nah, just go for a drink and see what
that Jo's got to say to my face. Simple as that.
We'll see the We'll see how big he
really is, right?
Simple as that. You got a lot to say on
YouTube. I heard you've been posting
about me again. So, we'll see what
you've got to say face to face. Simple,
isn't it? And I want to go there
anyways. So, there's not going to be no
uh, you know, I control you and any of
that [ __ ] It's fine, man. Anything
you've got to say, you can say it to my face.
That's the best way, eh?
Yeah. She doesn't like double standards either,
>> Grezy. She doesn't like double standards
and stuff and she said that she defends
men and you know
and she's voice noting me and stuff UK
asylum and we're having chats but I'm
having to put on this act. I'm having to
put on this pretend act because I'm only
looking at them for my needs and stuff
and part of the collection
you know not them as genuine people. I
don't I don't care about them as people
only like a collection
or to get your need and to get your
needs satisfied. [ __ ] sake. Gosh.
I'll be going to Nottingham soon
and see what that Jo's got to say to my
face. Yeah. And there's not going to be
no fighting because it it wouldn't be a
fight. A cuz he's not going to turn up
and B it wouldn't be a fight, bro.
would not it wouldn't even be a fight.
Simple as that.
So yeah, and that's that. I'll be going
soon. So yeah,
I'm not going back and forth with
jealous people [snorts] on YouTube.
Yeah, I know. I don't react to them
anyways anymore. Private.
I left that in 2025 and now we're 2026.
So, we're on to like bigger and better things, lad.
Oh, just one of my stalkers, lad. Just
one of my stalkers.
No, it's not Timmy. It's one of my stalkers.
Yeah. Yeah, when I was talking to her, I
was looking at her pictures and her story, Reevesy,
and I was looking at her mouth and it I
was summoning up her mouth.
It's a bit small, but it should be all right.
Her mouth should be all right.
Should be should be big enough.
Nah, I'm only going to Nottingham
because I want to go Nottingham.
I'm only going to Nottingham because I
want to go Nottingham. Dad, I'm not
wasting my time, energy on these people, these losers.
I'm only going because I want to go and
this guy's been talking a lot of [ __ ] on
YouTube, so that's it. Yeah,
bro. Why do you think they don't get to
me? These people unlucky
because a lot of them look like this. A
lot of them are stinking. That's why
they do what they do every day, bro.
That's why they don't get me mad. That's
why they don't make me rage. Because I
know the truth behind these people, bro.
Lonely, no life, ugly. I don't give a
[ __ ] about them, bro.
And you know what I'm saying?
So that's why yeah look at the way they
look the people that are doing this.
I've said this I've been saying this a
lot recently where you just need to look
at the people that are doing this.
Ulier than you skinter
than you. Isn't that funny? in it.
See you later.
Yeah, man. You know what I was saying to
my mom earlier? Unlucky. Yeah. We was
talking about something. Yeah. And it
didn't come up. Well, I brought it up
and I said, "It's so mad how these how
the people on here can spend years
like being bitter and jealous towards
someone that they don't even know."
Does that not seem like weird? I'm
saying that the amount of [ __ ] they've
tried doing and what they've done. If
they spent them years into bettering
themselves, bro, who knows where they
could be right now.
It's so weird, isn't it, bro? If you
actually think about it,
madness, bro, is it? But then again,
they're disabled in it. though. You
trying to you trying to find you you
trying to like find sense
out of disabled people is your that's
your first mistake, bro.
It's madness. It is. It is mad as [ __ ]
that they've It's weird, bro.
Very very weird.
And it's And it is jealousy as well.
Unlucky. They they can swear to their
blue in the face that they're not
jealous, bro. But they are. They
generally are because again, these
people are uglier than me. They're
they've got less money than me. They've
got less of a life than me. They've got
less family than me. And it's not even
just about looks either. It's not even
just about that.
I sound better than them. I look better
than them. I am better than them, you
know? So, I'm not even just talking
about It's not even just looks. It's
It's different things as well, bro. you know.
So, yeah, that's why they're not worth
anyone's time, but just thought I'd let
you know what some of these people on
here look like.
And then, like I said, unlucky. I was I
was looking at these people. I was like,
"Bro, there's not one of the people,
there's not any of these people on here
that do this that look normal."
Like, they don't not one person on here
that does this looks normal. Is that not
telling you something?
Is that seriously seriously seriously
not telling you something?
Cuz it tells me something, bro. When
none of them look [ __ ] normal, none
of them look [ __ ] handsome,
none of them. That's what I started
thinking of, bro. Like, oh [ __ ] Yeah.
And you know what? Unlucky, I never ever
say that they've got no friends. Do you
want to know why?
Well, they don't have friends.
No, I'm not mates with Monty.
I know that, bro. Of, bro. You're
telling me someone that knows this, bro.
I never tell them, "Oh, you got no
friends." Because even if someone
generally had no friends, they could
still have a life. They could still do
stuff with their life.
I mean, so that when someone says that
you've got no friends, obviously they're projecting,
but I don't find it as having an ins I
don't find it as an insult. Same as
what's his face. Um when LT was trying
to say I've got no kids, I was like,
bro, you're using that as an insult.
Like some of these the [ __ ] they come
out with, they're not even insults, bro. So yeah,
if someone comes on here and they look
normal and they're doing this, I'll be
like, "Okay, yeah, you know, they ain't
got nothing to be jealous of." But, you
know, when you're looking at someone
like that in a picture, think about it,
bro. Just just just just
think about it, bro. If you act imagine
you actually look like that person in the picture,
like could you actually imagine looking
like that, bro?
Jesus [ __ ] Christ. Could you imagine
looking like that and going out like on
a night out? Think about it, bro.
And you [ __ ]
That is [ __ ] bro.
And you look like that in the [ __ ]
photo. Jesus Christ. you.
You don't see, bro. You don't even see
these people out in in in public.
You don't even You don't even see them
out in public, bro.
You don't see people like that out in public.
Yeah, I just spoke to this other woman on Instagram.
Still making excuses for women. Mad.
Some people never learn. Eh,
I don't care about that stuff anymore.
Anyways, I don't care. [snorts]
Yeah, we was just talking all day on Instagram yesterday
about stuff and that um
I haven't got any bad vibes from her yet,
any stuck up vibes or anything. So, we'll see.
She seems all right, bro.
Nope. I'm not here to do that, lad. I'm
not here to go on dates or or anything
or try to get someone for Valentine's.
I'm just here to collect.
Nope, no dates.
No dates, Grezy. Just collections. Yep.
Is that okay with you, Greavvesy boss?
Just a little collection. Yeah,
it's fun to have a little collection, isn't it?
Yeah, I was speaking to my friend from
Amsterdam for hours yesterday. Greavvesy,
remember when I went to Amsterdam,
Greavvesy? It was fun, wasn't it?
Yeah. He's got he's got a couple of he's
got a couple of kids.
And yeah, I wouldn't want kids.
So saying that someone's got we we speak
and that ain't it?
Nah kids, bro. No way.
Do you remember when I met my friend
from Amsterdam Grevy in London? The
lovely little picture.
But yeah, she doesn't ignore anything.
She's got a lot of tattoos and stuff,
but doesn't matter. As long as you got a mouth.
You got a mouth in it, Greasy.
Simple as that. So, yeah. Nope.
Do you remember Grezy hunting for a
candidate for baby Peter? Grezy
hunting for a candidate.
That's so cute.
Isn't that cute? Grezy.
That is [ __ ] cute as [ __ ]
I think it is me.
Why have I still got this freak?
You all right, Captain?
These people are still obsessed with me.
Dark. They're still obsessed with me.
They won't leave me alone.
They want my bottom.
These people want my ass in this
community. That's sock.
They want my ass, lad.
I'm going to order a curry in a mo.
Oh, I can't wait.
Nice bindaloo. E,
do you like my Lego video? That suck. Who's that?
I told you I weren't going to let you
down with a Lego Greavves.
They've got a Simpsons one as well.
I need to stop with this Lego now. But
there's still some characters I don't
have. Greavvesy. I need Chew Becca. I
need Obi-Wan. I need Luke Skywalker. I
need Darth Vader. And they're not cheap.
They're like 15 pound a piece.
Sometimes even 20 per figure.
I would be dumping her.
That's what I'd be doing. Dumping.
Yeah. I'd be dumping her.
I was on Reddit, Greavesy. They said
that I need they told me I needed to get
a life. What are you talking about?
I said about the vitamins and stuff and
they said you need therapy because maybe
you didn't get you didn't you didn't
breastfeed as an infant. I said what the [ __ ]
I was dead, bro. Some of the responses in it.
Some of the responses were class, bro.
Right. I need to order this food now. Oh no.
I think this phone's on its way out, lad. One second. [ __ ] [ __ ]
What about that, man? I think this phone
goes weird sometimes.
One [snorts] second.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. Yo
yo yo. Oh my god. Can you hear me? Yeah.
>> [snorts and clears throat] >> Okay.
Hey. Hey. [sighs and gasps]
No, it's order again.
It's not accepting orders. Why?
It should be open.
It should be open, mate. Mhm.
It pissed off.
Oh, [ __ ] off, Grezy.
That's [ __ ] Waxies. That does that.
The manager is a [ __ ] horrible [ __ ]
with his [ __ ] ginger beard.
You know, that's waxies. Yeah, it's a
it's a no virgin, no skint policy. So, I
couldn't even take Thingy if I wanted to
to to get laid because he doesn't allow virgins.
And mate, they can [ __ ] tell a virgin
when they [ __ ] see one, mate.
>> Skin, no skin virgins. I don't make the
rules, lad. I've tried. And no, no, he
he says no virgins and they can't be
skimmed cuz obviously the drinks are
quite expensive there. I'll be going to
Axis soon, Greavvesy. I might even go on
Saturday. Okay with you, boss. [snorts]
Okay with you, captain.
Yeah, I might go to Waxies on Saturday.
I don't know, bro, what I'm doing yet.
Oh, I changed the bet, Steven Howard,
man. I changed them.
Do you want to see them? I'll change
them, man, because they got uh teams got postponed.
What do you want to see, bro?
Oh yeah, man.
Well, obviously I'll get a trim, won't
I? What the [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm allowed in waxies cuz I'm not a virgin.
[snorts] I'm not a skin virgin. So,
don't let me in there, mate.
It's on my community post, lad.
One second. Give it a sec.
I reckon these ones have got a
Yeah. No, virgins. That's what he said.
I don't know what his problem is. So,
hold on. So, how the [ __ ] yeah, if
people are virgins, how are they going
to meet someone if they can't get into [ __ ] waxies? No,
no consideration, no nothing, you know,
for other people. He's horrible. He is.
He didn't let He didn't let me in once.
He was being awkward. But then, but that
weren't cuz I'm a [ __ ] virgin like a
certain person. And it's because um I
was wearing track bottoms.
So yeah, but not not not cuz I'm a
virgin or anything. Oh no, not not that,
mate. Because I've I've I've met a lot
of women in them in waxes, mate. A lot a
lot of women, mate.
But it wasn't cuz I'm a virgin cuz I'm
not a [ __ ] virgin. And I'm also not skin. So yeah,
trust me, he knows. I don't know how he
knows. He knows, mate. He just knows,
You know, he's a skin flint when he sees one.
Hey. [snorts] Hey, Billy Dundy.
Oh, you still there, Steven Allard?
Yeah. Did you like my bet? Do you like
my bets, lad?
Yeah, I heard that. Joe F's becoming
obsessed with me again. Steven Howard,
I'll be going to Nottingham soon. Steven
Howard. Yeah. So, you're going to see
you're going to see what this um you're
going to see what this Jo's all about, bro.
You'll be seeing what he's all about
soon, lad. Why is that still It should
be open. It says it opens at [ __ ] five, man.
Bless you then. You're going to be
seeing what he's all about soon. Steven Howard,
why is this India not open when it's
supposed to be, bro? What the [ __ ] Yeah.
Why do you like the thought of me
winning a fight against someone Greavesy?
winning a fight wearing a Spider-Man t-shirt.
You want me to wear the Spider, bro? But
it's not even going to be a fight, bro.
Because at the end of the day, the guy's
not going to show up. And if he does, it
would not be a fight. Trust me.
Trust me, it wouldn't be a fight. It
would not be a fight, mate.
You know, so
what be like should I start this thing
on YouTube where I win all of these
fights wearing the Spider-Man t-shirt? Greasy. [laughter]
No one can beat me with a Spider-Man
t-shirt. Yeah, t-shirt. Yeah,
I'm so hungry, bro.
But this is not open, this place. I'm
going to have to find another one.
God bless you then.
Yeah. UK asylum. They don't allow
virgins in this waxies.
No. No virgins. [ __ ] those.
I really need a curry. Bro, what?
I need Vindaloo, bro. Where? I can't
find a Roo on this one.
Yeah, I could have a me.
I don't have that problem
that certain people do. Grievy. Nah. Oh, bro. [ __ ]
I want to order from that Indian, but
it's not open. And it should be. I don't know why.
So hungry, man. Yep. >> [snorts]
>> collection and comparing.
Oh, is it open now?
Oh, I think it's open now. Grezy,
don't mind if I do. Captain,
I'm going the same order again. Chicken ticker.
Is that the one I went to?
I think it is. Yeah.
Let me ask Lane if she wants anything.
One second. I'm going to ask Laney.
Oh, I need some papadoms as I want to
actually buy them separate.
What is it with Laney never eating?
[ __ ] worries me, you know.
Yes, she doesn't want anything sundaom.
I want to get a couple of papadons. Uh
yeah, I might start the gym on Monday to be honest.
You know what? I might get a portion of samosas.
These are naan breads.
They have a tick on.
Never seen that before.
One second, lad.
Yeah, I'm just going to get some
cuz she says she doesn't want anything.
But [ __ ] you know she's like you know. Yep.
That's what's been ordered.
Oh, I can't wait, bro. I'm [ __ ] hungry.
I got some nice fried chicken yesterday.
But you know when you just fancy a curry?
>> Yeah. I got lane from me samosas.
My mom don't like hot food.
They've always let me in waxies, grievy,
except the time I was wearing tracksuit bottoms.
They reckon they just know that I'm not a virgin.
Same can't be said about a certain person.
What do you think, Vezy?
I think they can they can they can smell
the virginity on someone.
You know what I mean? They can they can smell it.
I don't know. But they can tell some
somehow, you know.
Oh, this is some woman's number I got
from Manchester. She's in in she's um
she was in London. I approached her.
I had a lot of I had a lot. Do you know
that a I collected so many, you know, um
3 years ago in April, Greavesy,
I had such a collection, man.
I need more.
had such um
such a collection. I got a number really.
Yeah, I got a number collection.
Yes. So, do you like to look at a bet, Steven Howard?
This woman's a grievy. Can I tell you
what this woman's saying on Instagram?
This is another woman, by the way. Um,
now this is another woman. So I sent her screenshots.
Greasy sent uh I sent nine photos. I
thought I sent 10. I sent nine. And she
obviously you get the gist of it. She
turned around and said, "Okay, so
granted, not being ready to date is
valid. I get that. That [snorts] one
girl that met someone literally two days
later was crazy." Really? [ __ ]
[ __ ] really? Is that Is that what
them screenshots said? What? What are
they doing, Grezy?
Most of these girls told you they
weren't interested. They were honest. I
beg to differ. A couple just ghosted
you. One of them just told you that she
wanted to get to know you first.
No. A bit more effing than that. Isn't
that right, Grezy? A bit a bit more
effing than that, mate. Bit more effing
than that. I don't think that's exactly
how that went down, mate.
Proves my point, bro.
Proves my point.
Anything to take away accountability.
Am I right, Greavvesy, or am I right?
That's not what them screenshots showed.
Why, bro? Why we Why does it do why I
don't understand, Grevy? Why do does it
have to be this big thing, this big song
and dance about something that's in
black and white? It's it's it it What is
the reason for this, Grezy? That there
has to be a song and dance about
something that is shown in front of someone's face.
Why don't they just take accountability
and say, "Oh, they [ __ ] led you on.
Who gives a fuck?" I don't I don't get
these people, bro. Greavvesy, can you
help me understand it? I don't
understand it, bro.
Instead of making up all of these
excuses and like [ __ ] They're so It's
so weird, bro. Givesy, it's weird, isn't it?
Why Why do you reckon she's making excuses, Grezy?
Why do you think she keeps making
excuses for them?
I hope it's not a gender thing, Grezy.
I'm not going to be happy if it's a
gender thing, lad.
Please tell me it's not a gender thing, Greavvesy.
Cuz I'm not going to be happy. [snorts] Griezy,
it's not a gender thing, is it?
Please tell me it's not, lad.
Yeah, it's strange, bro. It is strange.
They They make it It's so mad. They make
excuses for women even when they they're
shown black and white that they've led
your ass on. This is what me and the
other this other woman was talking about, lad.
um yesterday about the double standards
and stuff and she calls out women as
well. Yeah, it's strange. I mean, why
why won't they take any accountability?
Why won't they Sorry, not them. Why
won't they hold them accountable for anything?
Why Why is it so hard to just admit
you've led someone on Weasley? I don't I
don't understand it. We're not talking
about murder. We're not talking about [ __ ]
you know, beating up [ __ ] I don't
know, bro. Beating up kids. Why? Why
would they not hold them accountable for anything?
It's so weird, bro. Is it like some I
don't know. I want to understand these
people, but I can't understand them, bro.
They're showing black and white what
they're doing and then they're coming
out with excuses. Oh, they were just
being nice. Oh, they just told you that.
No, no, no. That's not what that h
that's not how that is, Grezy. Listen,
right? If someone wasn't leading you on.
Yeah. Let me tell you something, Grezy.
If someone wasn't leading you on, if
somebody gave you their number, they
would be telling you within them three,
agree with me or disagree with this.
Yeah, you can agree or disagree. You can
say whatever. If somebody generally was
not leading you on, they would set the
record straight within the third
message. Am I lying?
Like if you've that's my that's my guess
within two to three messages they would
set the record straight.
That's what you call honest. Them was
not them people was not honest. Not that
I give a [ __ ] anyways. It's not even
this year but I mean they are blatantly
playing games and blatantly leading you
the [ __ ] on. I don't understand what
what's so hard to to accept that. I
don't get it. Yeah. [sighs]
It's so weird, bro.
What do you think, Leaves here?
Yeah, but it's not about respect though.
Yeah, but it's not about respect. And
And that's another thing. Yeah. Agreed.
Yeah. I don't understand when they sit
there and they tell people to respect
women. I mean, they don't respect
themselves and they don't respect other
people. So, why would you respect them?
What the [ __ ] Like, that's the way I
That's where I see it, lads. Do they
respect you? Do they respect other
people? No, they don't. Why do you think
I make these Why do you think I say
these things about having them as a
collection in grievy? Why do you think I
say, "Oh, let me have them as a
collection." What else would you have
them for if you weren't collecting them
or or using them for your needs? What
what what would you be using them for?
They can't be trusted. They're not
normal people. They don't act normal. So
what what you have them on for? For
what? So you laugh at it and you make
jokes about it, but what you know,
they've shown what they're like. I mean,
I think the biggest I think the biggest
mistake is people people actually
thinking that they're that they're
normal. That was my for so many years.
Yeah. I used to think, oh, they were
normal and they were good people, but
they're they're not. So, yeah.
Anyways, onto this lush Indian man. All
of this lush Indian.
[ __ ] them. Anyways, bro.
No, you right. Steven Howard,
he's very touchy about his [ __ ]
boyfriend. [ __ ] Isn't he
Steven Howard? Don't call [ __ ] lunch
a [ __ ] virgin. He's very touchy about his boyfriend,
isn't he? Uh, isn't he, Steven Howard?
LT and Joe's very, very touchy about
their boyfriend. So you need to be
careful with what you're saying, lad.
They're very defensive, you know. Isn't
that right, Steven Howard? They're very,
very defensive about their boyfriend.
Oh, don't call him a [ __ ] virgin.
He's got a [ __ ] fat ugly girlfriend
and somehow that proves he had [ __ ] sex.
Yeah, [ __ ] hell. Very, very picky and
very touchy about their boyfriend. Be
careful what you're [ __ ] saying, you know?
going to be in big [ __ ] trouble here.
Do you like that little voice, Grezy?
They're very, very touchy.
You know, have you ever been touchy, annoyed, shortteered?
You like that little voice, Grez? I've
got loads of little voices I can do. Yeah, man. No.
Which one is that? Can you send me a link?
How much is that one?
This one was £120, bro. [ __ ] hell. [clears throat]
Expensive, isn't it?
I've seen a couple of sets to be honest,
Grey. I've seen a couple.
I need I still need Darth Vader. Grievy.
I need Darth Vader. I need Chew Becca.
I like Chewbeac. Have you seen it?
Chewer with his little crossbow. moves
with his little crossbow, lad
with his little crossbow.
He's cute with his little crossbow, is it? Uh,
I've got the cinema on the 27th Grezy to
watch the new Scream.
See, sometimes you you'll be sat at home
bored be like, "Oh, let me go cinema."
Oh, there's nothing in the cinema.
[laughter] You know what I'm saying?
until [clears throat] the 27th. There's no um
>> Yeah, I do as well, but there's been
nothing on for a long time. [snorts]
Okay, there's been nothing on for a long time, bro.
Like horror films, I mean. So,
I need to check um I need to check the ads
um the adverts when I go and and and see
Oh, [ __ ] What's that, bro?
Are you getting the Fold uh 8 when it
comes out in July, Grezy? Yeah, I'm
going to get the Samsung Galaxy Fold 8.
Hey, with you, [ __ ] [snorts]
Hey, what do you think of the bets,
Steven? They're looking good in it.
Hopefully I can win one of these bets
and then lump it on two games on Saturday.
Oh, bless you then.
Oh, I like that little saying. Pack up,
Greasy. The fridge is packed up. I can't
think of anything worse than a fridge
packing up in the summer.
Yeah. I'm going to show you the food
when it comes and I'm going to end the
live stream because I want to eat in peace. Yeah.
Yeah. It is good. All of the football
bets are done as good.
It's good, bro. It is good.
It is [ __ ] good. I said gosh. Oh gosh.
Nope. Mine's the best.
You don't think I'm a troll, do you,
Grezy? UK asylum was saying that he
thinks I'm a troll. Nah,
I'm not a troll, bro.
Why would I troll?
What would I gain by trolling? That's silly.
Yeah, I'm not a troll, lad.
This t-shirt smells really nice.
I need to nip to the barber soon though.
Yeah, I need to go to I need a trip to
the barber soon. Grezy,
I'm getting really hairy. Yeah, man.
Finishing my cup of [ __ ] [sighs]
I need a trip. No, I don't. I need a
[ __ ] good sleep.
Oh. Oh, a trip to the barbers. Oh, I get
it. Yeah, man. I thought you meant like
a trip to [ __ ] going out um to like
another city. Yeah, I do to be fair. But
there's no point in getting it just yet
cuz I'm not going out drinking.
So, and it is cold outside to be fair.
It's cold and I'm not going out drinking yet.
But I do need Yeah, I do need to go. [laughter]
we tripping over.
I was going to say the same about the
virgin, Steven Howard, but the virgin
can't grow a beard, can he?
No, the virgin can't grow one.
Never has been able to, mate.
How tall are you, Greavvesy?
I'm like I'm 5'9 or 510.
Wait, don't say I'm 5'10", bro. We're
going to get LT in the chat. He's got a
height uh he's got a height complex. The LT.
Yeah, he's got a height complex. So,
don't don't say you're [ __ ] 5'10",
mate. Even Even 5'9 is a [ __ ] You
know what I mean, man?
Yeah, don't worry, bro. LT LT watches.
He watches my every move.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
He's a strange [ __ ]
He's a strange [ __ ] lad.
Yeah, I've just gone on that Jo channel
cuz people's talking about it. Oh, bro,
look at what he does, man. He thumbs up
Nons's um comment. I told you that's his
boyfriend, bro. Bro, I told you that's his boyfriend.
Like I said, do you not know how to rule
people out, lad?
Do not know how to rule people out. It's
like, it's so easy, lad.
You should learn from the [ __ ] best, bro.
O, do you want do you go on uh Autumn's channel?
I go I see she posted something the other day.
[ __ ] alg. Look at all these simps.
A lot of simps on that channel.
Ew, a simp.
There's loads of simps on that channel.
Hip Smoke. Have you seen it?
I mean, I mean, think about it, bro.
That's the only thing they could ever
That's the closest they will ever get.
That's self projecting. See you later.
We don't have self projectors on my
channel. We left you in 2025 and now it's 2026.
All right. You know, that's the closest
they're ever going to get to losing
their virginity. These simps on this
community is begging um begging Autumn.
That's the closest they'll ever get to
losing their virginity. uh with a woman.
That's as close as they're ever going to
get. Pip Smoker,
that's also how you know A, they got no
life. They're not around women. A
they're [ __ ] uh uh sorry, B, they're
ugly cuz I mean, who cares about some
[ __ ] woman on the on YouTube using filters?
That's another way to rule these people
out. Do you not understand, Steven Howard?
These are ways to rule [ __ ] people
[ __ ] out. Son, do you not know?
Learn from the best, lad. Know these things. Mad.
Come on food.
No. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't know what their problem is with
me playing [ __ ] me um collecting Lego
or this community.
I mean, it's not just for kids.
It is for adults as well. Yeah,
LT's a creep. Jo's a creep. They're all
creeps cuz they defend a creep. Yeah,
I just bought Laney um some samosas.
Yeah, they are they're all creeps, lad.
See, they know I'm right as well. That's
why when I say about the virgin thing,
they can never answer because they know I'm right.
They know I'm right, lad. They know for
a fact I'm right.
And you never need to prove yourself to
any of these people on here. If they
want to project their skintess onto you,
they can do that, bro. because no matter
what you do or what you show them, um they're
always going to
they're always going to um talk [ __ ] sat there.
How many people do you reckon uh look
like that um Jamie Thompson?
How many people do you think look like
him on this community?
Nah, I'm not getting beans on toast
delivered, lad. I'm not skin like you. So, yeah.
I think a lot of him, lad. I think a lot of them
I think a lot of them are, bro.
I think some of them are in wheelchairs as well. Definitely.
That Red Star is definitely definitely
disabled. How you can sit on the
internet recording everything for years
on YouTube 24/7? You got to be disabled.
You have to be, bro. There's there's
there's no like there's no alternative.
Yeah, they are, bro. Defoer.
Mad, isn't it lad?
It's funny though. It is funny.
And they are honest even 24/7.
They are literally on YouTube 24/7.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
No, Greavves is not the best looking on
here. I am, bro.
And you know, another thing, they
couldn't answer me, Steven Howard. I
said, "Yeah, how comes all of you people
that do this are uglier than me?" And
they couldn't answer me, Steven Howard.
They literally couldn't answer me. Cuz why?
Because why? Because they know that I'm correct.
Stephen, how would they know that I'm correct?
I said, "Oh, let me ask you this
question. Why are you people uglier than me?"
And they can't they can't answer it.
Yeah, I I've got two bets.
Yeah, I like my bets. They're quite cool. [snorts] Yeah, bro.
I put my bets on my community post, Dusty. Yeah. Oops.
Oh my god. Hurry up, man. [ __ ] hungry. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah. Well, like I said, when I start
going out, bro, I won't be on here. I'll
be going out soon drinking anyways. I've
just been, you know, hibernating because
it's winter and that.
Did I get piped today? Nope.
And why are you asking them questions?
You don't need to know what I get, when
I get it, how I get it, how much I have.
Why? That's another thing. Why are you
so obsessed with other people's lives?
That's another thing. Why are you so
focused on what other people have? So weird.
So [ __ ] weird, bro.
That's another weird thing about this disabled community.
I've seen a couple people do that as
well. Oh, this person gets money, then
this person gets money, then you
literally don't know nothing.
Like, what the [ __ ] You're so obsessed
with other people that you don't know. It's weird.
I'll be off here soon anyways. I only
I'm only off and on here. Uh,
I've already done a lot of [ __ ] though, Greavesy.
I've already been to a lot of places and
done a lot of [ __ ] and had a lot of
experiences and that.
You haven't, Greavvesy. You haven't
really been anywhere, have you?
I said that you should go to Scotland,
but you're not interested, Grezy.
You're not bloody interested.
I I have plenty of life experience. Went
to plenty of restaurants, been to plenty of places,
done different things, been with plenty
of women. Peter Belly's got lots of life experience.
Is that right, Grezy?
I've got lots of life experience, bro.
No, Dusty. It's a good bet.
A lovely bet.
Oh, for [ __ ] sake, man.
Have you ever been to Amsterdam, Dusty?
You've never been, have you? [snorts]
Yeah, I've got a friend that lives
there. I was speaking to him for hours
yesterday and I spoke to him today as
well. I've actually met him when he's
come to London. We met on a game years ago. [clears throat] Yeah.
He's a cool guy, man. He's a cool guy. Yeah.
Well, I went for a certain reason and he
went just to copy me.
So, I mean, I don't smoke. No. But I do
the other thing, Dusty.
I do the other thing, don't I, lad?
Don't lie, mate. [ __ ] don't lie. [snorts]
And yeah, I went for that reason. And I
was excited to go uh to another country
and he just went to copy me.
Yeah, he went to copy me cuz he's a copycat.
[sighs and gasps]
He just copied me cuz he's a little copycat.
Is that right?
Because I was trying to explain this.
Oh, Dusty. I was trying to explain this
to LT, but he did. He didn't understand
it, right? Oh, I didn't know, but I
found out that there's 195 um countries.
Uh, I thought it was I always thought it
was 247. My bad. But anyways, think of
it like this, Dusty. Right. So, I've
gone to to a country, right? And there's
195 countries, let let alone the cities.
That's even lower chance odds.
And I go there, right? The first time
going there. And then a couple of years
later, some [ __ ] virgins there. Some
some skint virgin. Some skin bastard.
What? What's the What's the chances,
bro? What is really really the chances?
Same country and same city the first
time you've gone away. And you're
telling me that's not a [ __ ] copycat?
You're telling me that's not a bloody
copycat? The odds? What are the odds?
You know, you little copycat. You're a
Um, but yeah, I honestly I don't know why. Um,
people go. I mean, I I I smoked weed
when I was there and I used escorts.
People that don't do that, I don't know
why they would go. If they don't do one,
if they don't do one or the other, I
don't know why why they would go there
to be fair.
To be honest, I've never been back. Yeah.
I want to go [snorts] to Egypt and see
the camels and the pyramids,
grievy, but there's a lot of scammers
there and they hustle and harass you and
that. I've seen enough videos.
Yeah, I saw a video about it um the
other day. This guy was there and I saw
all night spas comment. Yeah.
Yeah. I banged two uh escorts when I was in Amsterdam.
I stayed in a hostel.
Dusty. I met some cool people. Trust me,
my trip was a lot better because I
actually went cuz I actually wanted to
go. I didn't copy another person. Do you
understand? Uh Dusty. I went to smoke
weed, use escorts. Yeah.
Oh, I do, Dusty. I do. I do. I mean, you
can buy the figures separately, but
there was a lot of complaints that
they're not genuine. There was a lot of
complaints that uh uh there was a lot of
complaints that um you know, uh there
was a lot of complaints that um
that they were used. But no, Dusty, you
know the thing is when I went to
Amsterdam, I was staying in a hostel and
people slag off hosts, but that you
actually meet people that are doing the
same thing as you. Trust me, I remember
it and I remember the people that I met
as well. It's worth it. Trust me, it is
worth staying in a hostel, you know,
even if it's for one night. Say you were
somewhere for like two weeks, just stay
in a hostel for two nights.
Trust me, man. It is. You meet people.
It's [ __ ] Obviously, like the thing is,
yeah, like the the the beds are [ __ ] and
that. It is [ __ ] Yeah. But like the
people that you you meet good people, man. Trust me,
you're making you you make friends with
people that are um you're making friends
with people that are doing the same
thing as you, bro. Like you already got
something in in common. You're solo
traveling and chances are they've been
to different countries as well. I
remember when I was I had this woman
staring at me, bro. She was staying in a
hostel as well. Trust me, a hostel's good, bro.
Like it is like even once in your life.
Trust me. And I'm not even just saying
that, bro. I swear to God.
Yeah, exactly. It depends what kind of
holiday it is and who you're going with
and that. Obviously, you know.
Yeah, it Yeah, it just depends, isn't
it? I would stay in a hostel again.
I went there by myself, but yeah, I went
cuz I actually wanted to go, Dusty. I
didn't go to copy another person.
You get me, Dusty?
I'm the only one in my family that's
been to Amsterdam.
Yeah. See you later. [snorts]
Still in progress. Come on. I'm [ __ ] hungry, man. Yeah.
But no, he just went to copy me.
Literally just a copycat.
Nothing but a copycat.
It's so obvious. It was copying.
It was just It was just too obvious,
Dusty. If it was like the fourth or
fifth trip and then you went there, then
you know, yeah, whatever. But no, that
is that is definitely uh that is definitely copying
copying the crowd,
copying the trend. Yeah.
Greavves been nowhere. Bless him.
Greavves has been absolutely nowhere. Poor [ __ ]
Yeah. Poor [ __ ]
Oh, is that my food?
I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. Wait.
Oh, please be my food.
Didn't even say It's here.
Well, I got you some samosas. I know you
said you didn't want anything, but I
just got you some sosis. Anyways, do you
think I should fancy them?
>> Oh, you don't like them? >> Yeah,
>> they're not good. >> No, more.
I got some stuff as well.
Mo, you know I'm quite a pig when it
comes to Indian food. M. No, it's just
the way I was made.
I'm going to enjoy this food one