Oh gosh, I finished that in no time, mama.
that was yummy. Oh mate,
that went right out the right hole. Gosh.
That was lovely. Oh gosh, [sighs] that
went down like a [ __ ] tree. [snorts] >> [snorts]
>> Oh, lovely.
Oh gosh. [clears throat]
Now I'm sleepy. You stay towards the football. [snorts] Oh gosh.
Sorry about that, lads.
Yeah, sorry about that.
Sorry, not sorry.
I started calling these people wasters.
Now they're using my [ __ ] words.
[ __ ] sad bastards. They [snorts]
can't even think of [ __ ] different bloody comebacks. Sados.
[ __ ] sados. I [ __ ] say
I won't be live for long anyways because
I need to call someone.
You know what?
All I see in this community
is hateful old age pensioners.
That's all I see.
Hateful, bitter old age pensioners.
That's all I bloody say. Nothing else. >> [sighs]
>> All on.
What are you doing? A
I got a lot of old age pensioners
obsessed with me.
It's a bit creepy.
It's a bit creepy. It's very creepy. Oh, [ __ ]
The joys of being better looking than
these people, eh?
It hurts [clears throat] them every day
that Peter Bell is better than them. >> [groaning]
>> Everyone's gone.
Where the [ __ ] are you, bastards?
Japanese people really need to get a
[ __ ] life, lad.
Really to get a [ __ ] life.
Where's the go? E
they can't even get people mad, bro. I
love one of these people to get me mad
like you're [ __ ]
to start punching walls and stuff, but
you can't, bro. Because you can't get
mad at these people because
because of what they look like and
how long they've been doing this for. And
just I find it impossible nowadays.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, man. I'll be live for another 10
minutes and I'm gone. Cuz some of us
have actually got a life to attend to. Wink wink.
But to be honest, I kind of feel famous, you know,
when I come on here. I feel famous. All
these middle-aged people obsessed with me.
I don't know. I kind of feel like um a superstar.
Well, it is it is it is cringe though at
the same time. It is weird.
It is it is very strange.
But I do feel like a superstar as well. >> So,
well, I hope when I'm in my 40s, I'm not
obsessed with a [ __ ] 28-year-old on YouTube.
That's all I can [ __ ] say, mate. I
don't know Anyway,
[sighs and gasps] Okay.
getting some Pink.
Anyways, I'm going see you later. Bye-bye now.