Yeah, man. Just woke up. Yeah.
When are you people going to actually
get a life, man?
Sorry, man. I have to ask the lad.
When are you actually going to get off
of YouTube and get a life? [sighs]
I don't think we'll ever know. No,
you just going to get off of YouTube and
get yourselves a little life.
Make a little life for yourselves.
Come on now, mate. You're running out of bloody time.
What are you going to get for you if you
get yourselves a little life?
It's okay though. I'll just wait.
We [snorts] wait.
Yeah, I'll wait until they get alive.
Yes, you then
straight on YouTube
soon as they wake up.
Yeah, these people need to get alive.
Seriously. Seriously need to get alive.
I didn't get a winning spin yesterday
out of five spins.
Makes you wonder, doesn't it?
Something hadock fishy going on in that
under that table. [snorts]
They say it's house edge, but nah, it's
not house edge. Can't be. It's got to be
something a little bit more than that.
I closed my account anyway. So, I'm not
doing no football bets, no nothing.
Oh, I have to do a football bet talking
about that so people stop asking about
the football bets. [sighs]
Yeah, I'm completely done.
>> Completely completely done with all of it.
>> Yeah. No point playing something that's fixed.
That's my That's my view on it. Cheating little bastards.
Something that seeks out a loser number.
Why would you want to play something
that habitly habitedly seeks out losing
numbers? That's [ __ ] madness.
at least seeks out [snorts] a losing
number. What's the fun of that? How can
I How can you even have enjoyment in
something that's fixed, you know? [laughter]
We want to [ __ ] [ __ ] that. Die virgin.
The loser. They love the loser number, don't they? Yeah,
they love the loser number.
They love the loser.
They make you go numbers that you ain't got.
madness, isn't it?
It's to get anyone down. I don't
understand how people would say that
people can gamble responsibly. I'd love
to know what they mean by that, bro. One
day, I would love to know,
you know, something that's [ __ ] fixed. [snorts] Yeah.
Managers, you know what? And I don't
regret it. I don't care. I literally
don't give a [ __ ] all them times where I
don't care. I literally don't care.
Simple as that. They deserve it, bro.
They literally deserve it. If they're
big enough to con people out of money
and rig machines and rig tables, then
[ __ ] him in it. They don't get to say
what people say. Simple as that. [snorts] Yeah. Yeah,
that one Oh,
what? You double.
Sorry. I have to click some of that.
Anyway, what's wrong with playing Lego anyways? [snorts]
It's such a big deal that playing Lego. [gasps] [ __ ] hell. Uh madness.
Wow. Bro, I'm on this guy's channel.
He's got a big mouth, don't he? We'll
see what he's got to say face to face
when I'm in Nottingham, bro.
I'd imagine he's got a lot to say for
somebody that's got such a big mouth or
in his case, not a big mouth cuz he's
scared of talking.
He's got a lot of [ __ ] to say on this
YouTube, doesn't he, bro?
Wow. Yeah, that's good, bro. I quit
gambling now anyways, bro. No, not even
I'm not even doing football bets anymore.
Yeah, I'm done with it, bro. Sorry, man.
You must have missed the live stream um
yesterday. I'm done with it, lad. I'm
completely done. 100% done.
Simple as that, bro. There's no point
playing something that's fixed. Simple.
There's literally no point. So, [snorts]
I'm completely done.
Wow, bro. Like I said, man.
Oh, just 60 on the roulette and £25 on
football bets. I covid-19 numbers and I
didn't get I didn't even get a winning
spin. It's so fixed
and I just closed the account down.
Not a winning spin out of five spins
when you covid-19 numbers. I don't think so. [snorts]
I woke up with mood swings today
thinking about it, bro. It's so [ __ ] annoying.
It's so [ __ ] bastard annoying. >> [snorts]
>> I don't give a [ __ ] if it's peanuts. I
don't care. I've quit gambling. I don't
give a [ __ ] if it's peanuts. It could
be5 pound. It could be£10. I I'm not
losing. Losing is not an option. I don't
care. Yeah. And it is peanuts. And guess
what? They still they still cheat.
They're still wigging people out of
money even when it is only £60. Get
[ __ ] Simple as that.
What the [ __ ] bro? Why is this Jo
talking about people's family when he
doesn't even know anyone in my family?
He doesn't know anything.
He is mentally [ __ ] and obsessed,
isn't he, bro? This This guy is mentally
obsessed. I'm telling you, bro. He's
another Jamie Thompson.
The looks, everything, bro. Probably in
a [ __ ] wheelchair, to be fair, lad.
What a sad loser.
So many losers on this community, bro.
It's un it's it's unbelievable. Like
proper down and out wasters.
They're trying Well, they're using my
words now, lad. No, there it's not I'm
not covering the wrong numbers. It's
literally going on any number that I
don't have on purpose. It's going on any
number that I don't have on purpose.
It's literally seeking out It's
habitedly seeking out numbers that I don't have,
which is why I [ __ ] close the account
down, bro. And I'm done with all of it.
Even the football. Simple as that, bro.
It's not about the wrong numbers. If I
if I any number I cover, they're just
going to make it go in other numbers.
It's as simple as that. And it's not up
for debate. And it's not up for
discussion. I'm done with it. Simple. Yeah.
It's money laundering now. At this
point, you're just money laundering.
It's not gambling.
It's literally money laundering because
it's not gambling because if it was
gambling, you'd win. Simple as that.
It's not even It's not even gambling,
bro. It's money laundering.
It's money laundering and fraud. It's
not even gambling. I don't even call it
gambling anymore since the gambling
industry is finished.
It's fraudled. If it was gambling, you'd
be winning some of the time. [snorts]
So, yeah, I'm done anyways with all of
it. So, yeah,
even the football.
It's shame, but that's the way it's got
to be, isn't it?
And I'm still getting the mood swings.
I'm still getting them, bro. I'm still getting them. Yeah.
So, what you think? Just because £85 is
peanuts that it's okay losing.
Is that how your mind thinks that just
because a certain amount is peanuts
that's fine? It's never fine, bro. It's
never fine. I could tell you mad stories
of of stuff.
Losing is not an option. It's as simple
as that. It doesn't matter how much it
is. I don't care how much it is and how
much I have left. I could lose 20 pound
and be a multi-billionaire.
I still it would still get me depressed.
I don't care. Simple as that. And that's
That's something these [ __ ] people
don't [ __ ] tell you.
Years ago. years ago.
I haven't won anything in ages because it's fixed.
What's the point of playing something
that's fixed? So, I'm calling it money
laundering now. I'm calling it fraud. I
don't like to call it gambling.
So, when in future, I want you to ask
me, did I do fraud? And no, I don't do
fraud. I don't do anything illegal.
Thank you very much. It's not gambling.
If it was gambling, you'd be winning sometimes.
the amount of times I've played roulette
in the past month. So, you literally
would be winning sometimes.
And not even that, it's not even just
that. You've done five spins, you've
covered 90 numbers, you would hit a
number. You would literally hit a
number. Doesn't matter what the number is.
Just like you would not hit five, six
times in a row, you wouldn't miss five,
six times in a in a row. That's the way
I see it. So, yeah. Simple
as that. It's enough to get anyone down.
Simple, bro. Is it? Yeah.
And I don't give a [ __ ] if it's only
£85. That's not That doesn't mean
anything. It doesn't matter how much it
is. I could literally not even lose
money and just playing. It would annoy me.
I could literally play and and get my
money back and it would still annoy me.
Nah, never been bullied by any of you people, man.
Nah, bro. You people bully yourselves.
Don't bully me, bro. You can't bully a
guy like me. Nah, man.
You people bully yourselves.
You're sadly sadly mistaken.
Nah, bro. But you people are still
bullying yourselves. I see. Yeah.
Like I said, bro, you're not going to
you're not going to get to me. So,
there's literally no point. You didn't
even get to me yesterday when I [ __ ]
mad. You could even get me mad when I was mad
because we know about you losers.
We know about what you look like. We
know about what you are. We know about your projection.
I could have got a beard and haircut
with the £85.
Okay. I mean, I could I could I mean, I
could I could gambled £10 right now and
I could have got McDonald's with a£10.
I could have gambled
£5 and and and and could have got
sweets. I could have gambled
uh £500 and I could have bought a TV. I
could have gambled £150 and I could have
bought a brand new trainers.
I'm just listing alternatives. Now your
your point is what exactly?
Okay. And your point is what? I've still
got money. I can still get a haircut and beard cut.
None of your business how much money
I've got left.
That's none of your business.
But I've got more than enough. And it's
none of your business.
I mean, I could lose another 100 pound
right now. And if I lose it, I could
have bought Lego with it. I don't
understand people that say that you're
just using other. [clears throat]
We gambled because we was trying to win
money. You understand? That's that's why
we gambled. [snorts]
[ __ ] hell, bro. That's so [ __ ]
when you say that. You know that.
It's none of your business. You need to
worry about your own life. Don't worry
about what other people have got. Worry
about your own life. What are you pe Why
are you people so obsessed with other people, man?
You know, you're so obsessed with other people's lives. Mad.
How much do you have left? Why don't you
tell everyone how much you have left? Yeah.
Yeah. I don't know why you do that
though. Anyways, I don't know why people
do that. When you lose money, they say,
"Oh, you could have done this with that.
I've got money, so I could still do what
I want to do." I don't know why you do that.
It's not our last money. We put it in
because we're trying to win money. I
don't know why you why you use that as
an example. It's It's so disabled when
people say that. Oh, you could have done
this. It's like It's like having It's
like having It's none of your business
what I've got.
It's like having £2,000, right? Or
£3,000 and losing £100. Then someone
said, "Oh, you could have bought a tracksuit."
Uh, okay. And you could have bought a
tracksuit with the £100 you lost. Um,
okay. Well, I mean, I can I can still
buy 19. You know what I'm saying?
That's none of your business what I have
if I've got cash or not. [snorts] That's
for me to know and you to never find out. Yeah.
Worry about yourself.
Yeah. Okay, bro. I'm skinn. Okay. Yeah,
bro. I'm completely completely skinned.
See, this is what I mean, bro. You're
You're sadly sadly sadly mistaken.
You're sadly mistaken. you. So you seem
to think that because someone's lost so
you you seem to think that people need
to lose all their money for it to affect
them. You're mistaken. You're very very
very very mistaken.
So you think that someone has to be skin
in order for it to affect them.
Really? You seem to think that someone
has to be skin. You're sadly sadly sadly sadly mistaken.
You really really don't know about
anything. You're just like that secular
slots. You seem to think that you need
to be low on money in order for it to
affect you. You're you don't know
anything, bro. You really really don't
know anything. Trust me, you don't. No.
Again, it's not about the money. So, I
don't know why you seem to think about
why you seem to think, oh, because
you've lost this amount of money or
you've lost that amount. It could be any
amount of money. You could have £5,000.
You can go to a casino right now. If I
lost £500, if I lost £100, I would just
go straight back home and go to bed.
It's as simple as that.
It is literally as simple as that. And
I've got examples where I've done it as
well where I had like six grand and I've
lost 100 pound and it ru out. You
really, really think someone needs to be
skinned in order for it to affect them.
Just playing it is annoying. Losing on
it is annoying. Not winning on it is
annoying. It's as simple as that.
Doesn't matter how much money it is. You
should know this [ __ ] by now.
Even if you gambled and you didn't even
lose money, it would still annoy me. It
would still annoy me if I if I just got
my money back.
Simple as that.
It's literally the biggest trigger for mental health.
It literally literally is a a trigger
for people's mental health.
That's literally what it is. It doesn't
matter how much money it is. It
literally does not matter. I don't care.
All I all I can think of is they the
managers are feeding their kids with my
money and [ __ ] That's I'd start getting
them thoughts again
because it's annoying and it doesn't
matter what the money is, where it's
from, or how much the money is. It's
annoying. I don't It could be [ __ ]
drug money, benefit money, working
money. I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't give a [ __ ] [ __ ]
whether I got it for free, whether I
worked for it. I don't give a [ __ ]
Simple, to be honest with you. Yeah,
it makes you feel degraded as well. Like
they degraded you. Like they've stripped
you and they've robbed you and they've humiliated you.
That's the thoughts I get, bro. Yeah,
that's the that's literally the thoughts I get.
You seem to think that it's okay just
because you get the money for You're
mad, bro. You really really You're
really really mad.
You really really don't have no idea
about anything, do you? Yeah. No.
I don't go to the bookies and every time
I Well, I don't I don't do it in the
bookies, but when I have gone to the
bookies recently, I've just spat all
over the machine. So, no,
I'm watching over my back to be fair,
but anytime I lose the bookies, it's
just a straight spit all over the
machine. Simple as that.
I done it about two um two weeks ago. A
big spit all over it. Dirty spit. The
woman was annoying me, calling me mate
mate mate mate mate. I went back for a
more mate. I weren't happy. So I thought
a big nasty disgusting spit all over your machine. Simple. Yeah.
I'm a spitter. I'm like a camel.
I'm a camel.
I don't give a [ __ ] Calling people out
of money is disgusting, but they still
do it. Rigging up machines is
disgusting, but they still do it. So,
who are they to play them all high ground?
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] They can wipe
it up. Simple.
Yeah. Rigging people out of money is
disgusting as well.
But they still do it. So who are they to
play the more high ground?
Who would they to play the more high ground? Huh?
Nah. My phone's worth too much money.
My wife is my phone is worth too much money, mate
to do that. No,
there's certain things I don't smash.
Like I used to smash my mugs when I used
to um lose in the old house, but I would
never smash my Belgian mug. Never.
Cuz that's my memory, isn't it? I'd
smash mugs like 20 pound mugs.
Nope. And I lost 60 on roulette.
And so we're not calling it bets. We're
going to start calling it fraud.
It's not bets. It's fraud.
Bets. You have a chance to win. Thank
you very much. It's fraud.
That's what it is.
[clears throat] Yep. Didn't even get a
win and spin indigo.
But hey, it's just gambling. You win
some, lose some.
Win some, lose some. Never win some.
Always lose it all. [ __ ] rigged.
Yeah, I was playing the lads roulette
and I just closed the account down. So,
there's going to be no football bets
now. There's going to be no nothing.
It's done now, bro. Done. Done. done sadly.
So they say uh that's what secular slots say.
That's what secular slot says. He says
as long as you've got all your bills
paid and it's only money you can afford
to lose, then it's all then it's all right.
I've never known something to trigger
mental health as fast as that in my
whole entire life.
I literally have not never known
anything in my whole life to trigger
mental health as much as that does.
It's literally it literally triggers mental health.
It's like you know when you drink Yeah.
and then and then like after a day or
two like you get depressed and stuff.
Nope. Only from gambling?
Nope. Only from gambling. Nothing else.
No. Without gambling? No.
But with gambling? Yes.
It's like if you drink a load of rum.
Yeah. You was on a bender and then
people get like comedowns and stuff.
Um, that's bit, but then you get like
the pressed and stuff and the drinking.
That's it. It was with gambling straight
away. Every time you play that roulette,
bro. It It does. It does. It does. It
[ __ ] your mental um [ __ ] your mental health up.
Trigger mental health. Mental health, bro.
and I start thinking of the people
that's [ __ ] me over and stuff like
that. I couldn't even explain it to you.
You wouldn't even understand.
So, I don't think it's a I don't think
it's a form of entertainment to be honest.
I don't think it's a form of entertainment. Nope.
Why would I come for eat? Bro, I'm not you people.
So, no, I don't come for eat. Why Why
you asking that, bro?
Why the [ __ ] would I come for eight?
What the [snorts] [ __ ]
I'm huge now. That's self projecting, bro.
Like I said, no self projectors in this
chat, man. You people are obese.
I'm not even overweight.
You're so obsessed with other people.
It's so weird.
You people are such weirdos, man.
Bro, you people are literally obese.
Like, you're actually like fatter than I
could ever be, bro.
Why is this is this do you know all of
this? Yeah. Let me let me try to like
sort of understand why you do this. Is
it to escape the facts of what you are
yourselves? Cuz like you know when you
sit on here and you call people um skin
and you call people that you don't know
you don't know anything about. You know
when you call people skin and you call
people ugly and then you start talking
about people's weight. Is it to Is it to
take the heat off the fact that you're
all of them things?
That you're like obese and you're fat
and you're ugly and you're skinn. I
don't need to prove you any I don't need
to prove anyone wrong.
You need to prove me wrong. Prove that
you're not a fat ugly bastard.
I don't need to prove some [ __ ] loser
on YouTube wrong. Are you [ __ ] mad,
bro? What the [ __ ] do you think this is?
No one needs to prove you losers wrong on anything.
Yeah. Why don't you come and come and
show what you look like, lad?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
All you people do on here is try to pick
on people that are better than you in
life. Better looking, better weight,
better money, better family, better
life. That's all you do, man. You you
you you try to pick on people that are
better than you. mad
when you're literally [ __ ] so obese
you probably can't even you probably
can't even walk madness.
Meanwhile, you're saying this, bro, but
you're act meanwhile you're saying this,
but you're actually obese.
You are actually obese [ __ ]
and you're talking about me, lad. When
you're literally obese.
What the actual [ __ ] bro?
Yeah, you probably are so fat you can't even walk.
And you're talking about me, bro. You're
talking about [ __ ] me.
[ __ ] self projecting to the max.
That Jamie that Jamie Thompson. Oh my
[ __ ] god, bro.
That is a face not even a mother could love.
Mad. That is [ __ ] disgusting.
I wobble out of the bookies.
Yeah, really, bro. You know, you're just
talking about yourself, is it?
Oh, [ __ ] sake.
Stupid [ __ ] [ __ ]
Bro, you do realize you're just talking
about yourself, is it?
You know, you're just talking about yourself. No,
you people are addicted, bro, to talking about yourselves.
It's quite worrying. Mad.
Okay. Why don't you show us what you
look like? Not here.
I just find it funny. Everyone that's
trying to call me fat is fatter than me.
Oh, well, I mean that it's I mean it's
not weird. It's like these people, they
call you ugly, they're uglier than you.
They call you fat, they're fatter than you.
That's telling me something, bro. that's
always telling me something.
The day one person on here that does
does this and actually looks normal.
I'll be like, "Okay,
everyone that does it is fat and ugly.
That's why I can't get mad at it.
They're fat, ugly people with no life
talking about me.
You literally can't even [ __ ] get mad.
I can't get mad, you know.
I'm going to put my camera on, bro. Look
at my beard, bro. Look at my beard.
I need to get shaved at some point, bro.
No, definitely definitely definitely not.
Bro, this is a medium t-shirt and it's
not even fitting properly. It's [ __ ]
a bit loose. I have to shrink it. Yeah,
bro. It's so mad that even like this,
I don't I'm not as ugly as you people.
And I haven't I haven't been to the I
need to go to the barbers.
Jesus Christ. I need to go to the
barbers and use a stool [ __ ] fat enemy, bro.
Mad mad mad self projection.
Yeah, it's mad, bro. You let me down,
you people. You really, really, really
let me the [ __ ] down, bro.
I [ __ ] gave you [ __ ] the benefit of
the doubt when Laney was saying that it
was going to be the same people. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. Bro, everyone knows that I'm
the best looking on here, bro. Everyone
knows that I'm I'm the best on here,
bro. Come on now. I don't have [ __ ]
middle-aged slobs obsessed with me for no reason.
Well, it's not luck with roulette.
Well, it's not it's not luck with
roulette, mate, cuz I done five spins
and I didn't even hit anything. And I
didn't hit any number, bro. Even the worst number.
I I don't know, bro. I know roulette's fixed. [gasps]
Obviously, football's not fixed, but
roulette is definitely fixed.
Obviously, football's not fixed, man.
[snorts] You can't say that, but
roulette is definitely fixed. It is. It
definitely definitely is fixed. Yeah. Yeah, man.
I look better than LT, though. I look
way better than LT. Nope.
You already know the answer to that.
You know I'm not going to be going out.
It's not comfortable. It's [ __ ]
annoying. Well, having this hair is
No, I'm not going out.
Nah, I'm not going out. [gasps]
Bro, instead of [ __ ] talking about
what I look like, let's see what you
look like. [ __ ] I'm going to put the
link up. Jesus Christ. Enough about
Peter Belly. Sick of you bloody
middle-aged [ __ ] slobs being obsessed
with the way that I look. Gosh darn it.
Let's see what you people bloody look like.
Let's see what you bloody people look.
Come on. It can't be hard to beat this, can it?
Can't be hard to beat this mug.
Let's see what you look like, mate.
But no, I'm not going out this week. I'm
not I don't know when I'm going to go
out again, bro. I keep saying I am, but
I don't think I will, bro. Nah,
I probably won't to be honest with you, bro.
I still think I need a long long long long time.
I told you 6 months, isn't it? I told
you 6 months and it's been almost three.
It needs to be 6 months minimum, I think.
So, all the experiences, I forget about
all the experiences. It needs to be
longer than that, bro.
Yeah, I reckon I reckon six to eight
months to be honest.
It needs to you need to forget about all
of the bad experiences.
One second, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. He's a weirdo, man. He's a weirdo.
The LT is a weirdo, bro.
He's a [ __ ] freak, bro.
I had to tell him about himself, man,
because he was defending his boyfriend.
Yeah, I told him about himself, bro, cuz
he was being biased in it.
Yeah, he was being a biased [ __ ] in it. So yeah. Yeah, bro.
Why don't you just go out and meet him,
freaking king? Are you scared of him?
I'm not scared of him, bro. I'm not
scared of no one, bro. I'm a big bastard.
In four years, bro, Peter belly's got bigger.
So, as soon as I get back to the gym,
I'm going to be more powerful.
Trust me, bro. Do you think that Prime
could ever do that now,
[snorts] bro? There's no way he would he
would out he would out he would outpower
me, bro. I'm quite powerful.
I've still got muscles as well.
Yeah, man. I'm not going to say anything
about that anyways. I'm not defending him, lad.
Yeah, I am huge, bro, in muscles, not fat.
No, I was just saying, Ben, that um
there's no way he could do that now,
bro. Peter Bell is a big [ __ ]
>> Yeah, man. I've still got my muscles
from when I went to the gym, man. Yeah, man.
How you doing, Ben 10? You're right.
It's nice to see you.
Yep. I've not long woke up
and I'm just chilling on my phone seeing
what's going on now. But yeah, I'm not
I'm not backing him anyways with the
Liverpool thing. [ __ ] him. He's a biased
bastard. So yeah, [ __ ] him.
He wants to start defending virgins and
ignore my evidence. [ __ ] him. [snorts]
Simple, lad. [ __ ] him, bro.
Yeah, I don't care. Simple as that.
No, I'm not showing you.
Ben, do you remember? Same people, same
story. See you next year.
Antman said that it's getting like he
said it's getting like England now. Um, Thailand. Ben.
Yeah, he's saying it's getting like England now
with the stuck up women and that. Well,
why don't you come and show us your face?
Oh, have you seen Oh, did you see that
Jamie Thompson guy Ben? He's saying that
they're becoming [ __ ] and that over
there as well.
He's saying that like he can still get
like 30 year olds and stuff, but he's
saying that it's getting um it's getting bad.
He said it will be finished in 10 years
Asia. He said, you know, like 10, 15 years ago.
Well, that's funny, bro, cuz all of the
things you're saying I can't show, I've already shown. Try again.
The [ __ ] bro? And guess what? You can't
even show your face. So, nah, I'm
beating you. No one's going to show you
people money or women anymore. We don't
need to prove ourselves to the losers.
We don't need to prove ourselves to losers.
[ __ ] off. You know, I'll be going to
Nottingham soon. Um, Ben,
yeah, I'll be sorting this Jo right out.
Let's see what he's got to say face to face.
Yeah, let's see what this cunt's got to
say face to face. Mate, I'll be wearing
my little Simpsons top whilst I go there. Yep.
Oh, Ben, did you see my Lego?
Did you see my Lego? Ben lost me an arm
and a leg. I've got no arms and legs left.
It's not funny. It's actually really serious. [snorts]
Oh, do I delete it?
I bought some Lego
I Ben, can I show you my little
collection of Lego?
Can I show you my little collection?
I've spent about £160 on this. [gasps]
Ben, can I show you?
All right. One sec. One second. It's downstairs.
Hey man, look. So, I've got Oh, it's
cost me a lot of money, by the way. I
didn't just buy the figures. I've
actually got I need to build another
man. There's another man as well. Look,
I got him.
Oh, you can't see. Let me switch my camera. Got him. Got Yoda.
I got Jar Binks.
He's my favorite. He sits down as well.
Do want to sit down. And look.
They're my little characters.
Yeah. And I'm going to start collecting
women soon, Ben, cuz I like collecting
stuff. So, I'm going to start collecting women soon.
Yeah, I'm going to start my little women collection again.
Just collecting them, you know,
like I collect my little um Yeah, I need
to build another man. Uh I've got one
more to build, but I could build with
it. I need I need some more though, Ben.
We're not finished. I need Chewbeca. Um,
I need Obi-Wan and I need
I need L uh Luke Skywalker
collecting women as well.
Oh, look. He stands up that one. Yeah,
my little characters.
Oh, also Ben,
where you gone? Oh, he's got good skin.
I got Crash.
I won him.
Yeah, I sleep next to him. His name's Crash.
Yep. I want him in the on the claw machine, Ben. [snorts]
Do you like my little Lego? What's your
favorite character? Um, Ben, out of the
ones that I've got, I like Jar.
I think he's a cool He's a cool one. He is.
Yeah. I like um I like Jar.
What's your favorite one, Ben?
Look how he just sits. So cute.
send messages for [ __ ] seven days.
What did I say? Gosh,
[snorts] Jar's hungry.
Jar, you ate some curry last night.
You're not having any more food. You're
going to get really fat. Hey, J.
You're so cute. Ja. >> [snorts] >> Yeah.
>> They are worth money. They're worth
about £15 each,
but obviously I'm just collecting them
at the minute. Yeah, they're worth and
they're genuine figures, too.
So, I might double up on them and sell
ones in 10 years and then still have the other ones.
Jar, you fell over. What happened?
I need to build the other one. There's another one.
So, I've got eight characters so far. >> [snorts] >> Yeah.
>> Little cavities. So cute. They're so sweet.
OH, I've put your legs wrong. Oh gosh. I
have to do it again. [snorts]
What are you doing, mister?
I put your legs on the wrong way. Gosh.
That way isn't it? What to say? Why do
your legs look like that? You see the case? >> [snorts]
>> Oh, do you like my little set, Mr. B?
Do you like them?
I've got one more to build. But look,
they've collected up quite fast, haven't they? Yeah.
Why [snorts] do these ones legs bend but Yodas don't?
He just stands.
H I'm not sure.
They'll be worth money in about 15 years.
These um these little characters. [sighs]
The Lego will be worth money in about
10, 15 years, lad.
But they're not for sale. They're mine.
should start going women hunting soon,
Mr. Bean. Add some to my collection.
[sighs and gasps]
A Lego women collection, Mr. B.
A sexual experiences collection.
I've got a sexual experience collection. Yep.
Collect them like you know like you you
know Star Wars and villains you know you
collect evil villains. That's what we're
when you collect women you're collecting
evil villains. My evil villain collection.
Yeah. That's what I'll be doing. Mr. being
my little villain collection. Yep.
I'm still fill up from that curry. Oh gosh.
What is my little thing?
Oh gosh. Well, I'll be back later.