Yeah.
To stop the thing from failing, you see.
Oh my god. [snorts] Yeah.
I'm back, lad.
Yeah, it's madness, isn't it? You know
what, bro? Like, I wish I could actually
laugh at it and actually like take the
piss out of it, but
you really can't, in it, bro. It's
actually It's actually mad, isn't it, bro?
I'm just wiping my trainers and jeans and [ __ ]
It's mad, is it? Like, you got to think,
bro, if it's like this now. Yeah. And
it's getting worse.
Like, what's it going to be in like 5
years time, lad?
Oh, I just come back drinking, lad.
All I hear, bro, it's getting worse,
bro. It is getting [ __ ] worse, man.
Honestly, bro, I need to like The thing
is, bro, we're talking You're talking
like Asia. Yeah, Kieran, Asia is not
even good anymore. Ant-Man messages me
every day. He says, "Oh, they're being
dickheads." So, it wasn't any surprise
to me, bro, to be honest with you. Like,
it wasn't any Oh, sorry. Almost said be
quiet. Um, sorry, bro.
Um, basically like cuz Antman like
messages me every day. Yeah.
Um, it wasn't any surprise to me, bro.
It's a sad situation, Kieran. Like, um,
uh, what was I saying, bro? Um
uh my other channel I couldn't go live.
Nah, bro. It was no mad story. I got a
mad story, lad. Mad story. It's bad,
Kieran, bro. It's really, really bad,
lad. All I can say is good luck to
anyone that wants to try in these
westernized countries anymore. Good luck
to you. My hat goes off to you, bro. Yeah.
You know, it's not even just that
anymore, though, is it Ken? Mate, come on.
Oh [ __ ] I need to get some food. I'm
hungry. I only had two sausage rolls.
Nah, John. I've just come back from a
night out, mate. First night out in many months.
No, you didn't. He's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
K, I just had a mad
Kieran, my other channel, bro. Um,
because basically the Streamyards is
connected to too many accounts and I
don't know the accounts.
I don't need my confidence back. I am
confident. I'm confident every day. I
done about 11 approaches sober queue and
about 11 sober.
My confidence never goes away, bro. What
you What the [ __ ] are you talking about, lad?
It never disappeared. Never has, never will.
Yeah, Kieran, bro. Um,
it was it was bad, bro. Um, so yeah, the
other channel, lad. Um, it's connected
to too many Streamyards and I can't get
onto the Streamyard accounts cuz I can't
remember them. So, that's why I can't go
live on that channel. Bro, I've done
some videos and waxes and that. You're
[ __ ] bro. You're [ __ ] hearing, bro.
Literally, bro, you're you're uh Did I
have a good night? Yeah, I met some good
people, but it is it is pretty bad. I'm
I'm left speechless, bro. Like, I'm
actually really really really left
speechless. I think it's because it's
been so long. Yeah. And you know, it's
gotten worse than that. I'm speechless.
I don't even know what to say anymore.
Like, there's nothing else anyone can
say. It was annoying me, Kieran. Let me
tell you, bro. It was annoying me. Yeah.
But, you know, but then I started
thinking to myself that like the thing
is, bro, yeah, that this is the norm
now. It's not normal, but it is normal,
if that makes sense. So, it's not
normal, but it is normal cuz it's 2026
and it's but it's it's kind of
depressing because obviously you're you
needing because you're obviously
thinking of the future. If if this is
like it now, what's it going to be like now, bro?
It's bad. You're not you, Bro, I haven't
been out for like 3 months, Kieran.
Truth is, I went out today, bro, cuz
someone was doing my [ __ ] head in um
some guy that I know and yeah, like I
thought, you know, I've been out for a
while. got my train. But yeah, it's good
luck to anyone trying in this country.
You're going to need it.
So I was doing them sober as well, K. I
was doing them sober. I done the first
one at the train station. That is
[ __ ] madness, bro. You are [ __ ]
Simple, lad. Don't know what to say.
Don't know what to say anymore, bro.
You know the game is dead.
And the thing is, no, no, but the thing
is, Kier, I done a lot sober, lad. I
done about 12 of them sober, bro. And I
felt like I I didn't even feel like I
had done it for [ __ ] 3 months. I had
done it for 3 months. I didn't even feel
like I had done it for 3 months. I still
felt exactly the same confident. But yeah,
good luck to anyone. Um, and then
don't get me, let me let me let me get
started on the [ __ ] escort thing in a
minute. I'll tell you about the escort
thing in a minute. Um, yeah.
I'll get you on to the escort thing in a minute, bro.
I do that. You can always come back when
I drink, bro. [ __ ] man.
The escal thing was mad, bro. I But like
I said, I didn't I didn't think I
expected it cuz of Ant-Man, what Antman
was telling me about Asia. So, [ __ ]
Yeah, it's not good, bro.
warmed it up. [ __ ] that.
I just felt like going out today to be
honest with you, bro. Um, some guy was
doing my head in so
it's sad. If you didn't meet anyone
years ago, Kieran, you're basically screwed, lad.
If you're straight anyways. Yeah, man.
Look, got the Spider-Man t-shirt on,
bro. Repping it. Repping that [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, it was bad to be honest with you,
bro. It was bad. And he never even
stopped there to be honest. [snorts] Um
Yeah. No, Kieran [ __ ] um went to this
B, bro. Listen. Yeah.
>> I went to this um
to this [ __ ] This is a routine for
me, bro. I don't if this is a routine
for you, but every time I go out, which
I don't go out anymore. It's been
months, but I do go out, bro. I get
numbers. I got five numbers, I think.
Yeah, I got five numbers. Um I always
stop off and go to the thingy. Um and
I'm telling you, this person must have
been about 36, bro. Must have been about
36, 38. And they're saying, "Oh, yeah.
Yeah, we can we can we can have sex. We
like, "Oh, we can have sex." Yeah. But
um yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] I don't
give a [ __ ] And this is a
38-year-old [ __ ] escort. It's getting
worse, bro. Everywhere's getting worse.
Asia escorts everywhere. It's It's
impossible now, bro. Literally, you
can't even get a [ __ ] date. Do you
know how, bro? Do you know how hard it
was? Yeah. You know how hard it was?
Yeah. To even get these numbers today, [laughter]
bro. You don't know how many people I
had to approach.
Um, so basically what happened was and
then and then the other one and she
said, "Oh, and then the other one was
trying to say, "Oh, then do this." I
said, "No, no, no, no. We're not going
to do that." Yeah. The security guard
tried opening the door. I said, "Close
the door now." Yeah. cuz I'm going to I
I will leave when I'm ready. Close the
door. I'll say what I want and I will
leave when I'm [ __ ] ready. Yeah.
Staty pants, bro. And that's why, bro, I
don't go out, lad. I don't really drink.
I don't I don't do this [ __ ] anymore,
bro. Cuz it's just too Nah, it's not me,
>> Yeah, it will never change, lad. What do
you expect? It will never change.
So, that's that.
It's depressing really, bro. But
yeah, I'm going to get some food.
Jump in the line. What was that?
Oh, I got that one. That one is [ __ ]
But yeah, um, all I can say is good good
luck to you, Kieran.
Good luck to you, lad.
It can't be open. It open.
Don't know. Five or five, guys.
It's sad. Really, K bro? I would love to
laugh at it, but
it's like it's
not even something to really laugh at,
is it? Oh,
nah. Close. I thought it was closed.
So, this is what you're getting now,
bro. And a lot of these people I was
speaking to, Kieran, they were very
entitled. Um, obviously they didn't
insult me, but they're very, very, very,
very entitled. Good luck to you. That's
all I can say, ladies. Good luck to you.
Um you're not to anyone that wants to
continuously try in these westernized countries.
And the thing is Kieran, you do realize
it is getting worse as well. Um it is
getting it is is worse now um than it
ever was. Like you got more chance of
I'd say safely
winning the lottery.
I'm going to get some nuggets. I think Yeah.
Yeah. But the thing is, bro, like it's
it is normal, but it's not normal.
That's what I'm saying. Yeah. Yeah. I
got some nuggets. Yeah. It is normal,
but it's not normal.
If that makes sense. It is, but it
isn't. Like I watched this I watched
this Ed Matthews and this guy was
getting the same thing that he friend
and that and it was starting to annoy me
as well. I think it's normal to annoy
people, bro. I think it is normal to
annoy people. I don't think there's
people that just don't become annoyed at
it. Um, it is really annoying, bro.
It is really, really annoying, bro. And
I and I normally laugh at everything.
See what these fine numbers say.
No, we're not talking about Yeah. I
mean, he's friend, bro. It like,
nah, you ain't got no chance. And then
when you've got like 40y old [ __ ]
escorts thinking they're better than
you, Kieran, it's [ __ ] It's literally
What's the world coming to, bro? What
[ __ ] What day what day and age is this, lad?
I was talking to this woman. Yeah, she's
from Boston in it. Approached us over by
the Burger King in Leicester Square
talking and that talking, oh, I live in
East London. Oh, I live near the city.
No, no, no. asked for a number. Oh, I
got a boyfriend. [ __ ] off. It's so
annoying, bro. But I did get someone's
number actually from Boston today.
It's just not a laughing matter because
you've got to actually think of like the
future and stuff. If this is like this
now, you know, what's it going to be
like? You know, it's only going to
continuously get worse. And like I said,
Kieran, the attitude on some of these
women, bro, it's you can't even explain it, lad.
Yeah. Send her my way. If not, she's
washed. 40 years old.
Who's 40, bro? The [ __ ] Who's 40?
I went to Waxies, lad. I'm going to put
that video up for Dusty.
Yeah, I'm going to put it up.
Oh, yeah. She is 40.
I mean, you can have her if you want. If
you don't like [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's not funny though, bro. It's It's
quite sad to be honest.
I was telling my friend in Amsterdam
this as well, to be honest. It's
actually quite sad. And I said, "Open
the door." I said, "No." I said, "Close
the door and I will I will I I open the
door." I said, "Close the door and I'll
open it when I'm ready." Yeah. It's just
toxic. People don't And these things can
actually escalate. You don't understand
Kan that these things can actually escalate
like and it can happen a few times, bro.
It's like you're [ __ ] in London, bro. [ __ ] sake.
It's not funny. It's madness.
Now, why you don't go out anymore, lad?
I was doing him sober, bro. I was doing
him sober, drunk. I just don't have the
energy anymore for this [ __ ] lad.
Anyways, I put this waxy video up.
[snorts] No, but the thing is, bro, the
thing is, Kieran, like two years ago,
bro, it was actually like pos the thing
is Kieran, bro, like obviously I've got
my I've got myself to blame as well, to
be honest with you, you know, and I can
tell you this, bro, cuz I've been in the
game a very long time. Yeah. Like two
like 3 four years ago. There's people
that you you could have still been with
now. Okay, we get that. But what I'm
saying is now trying to start off now
you're [ __ ] Basically, you really are
[ __ ] Trust me. Like it's not all this
Asia is bad. Asia is Asia is literally
60% finished. So if Asia is almost 60%
finished, bro, what do you think this is?
You know, it's it's
Yeah. If Asia is almost 60% finished,
then this is finished indefinitely. So
that's that, bro.
>> [clears throat]
>> You know, I I can't imagine getting
lucky now in this day and age, bro. I
really really can't. Back in the day,
you could Back in the day, you could
have been with someone, but now you
can't, bro. Sadly, it's bad.
Uh, so yeah, that's how we're at here in
that day. I met a couple of people from
West London today. Obviously, I was in
central London, so
naturally you would
I don't know what you could do, Kieran.
Like, I mean, I think the only way is
like if depends like what whatever you
want. I mean, if you want sex, the only
thing you got to do, the only thing you
could do, bro, is probably join the
point probably join the porn industry.
And I'm not even chatting [ __ ] when I'm
saying that, bro. I mean, but obviously,
I don't know what people want, bro. But,
you know, if you want a relationship,
bro, you got no chance, bro. You really
are really [ __ ]
Now, don't don't forget, bro, I've been
doing this for a very, very long time. I
know the game, bro. And it used to be
about about it used to be about one in
seven about one and eight. Now
you I don't know what it is, bro. Impossible. So yeah, no. No. >> [snorts]
>> I thought I'd be scared to do it sober,
but I I wasn't, bro. I wasn't.
Yeah. And it's even getting harder to
get actual numbers now, Kieran, because
before you'd get the numbers and
obviously they just [ __ ] you over, but
now you you'll find it's even harder to get that.
So, you'll find it's even harder to get numbers.
And if it's harder to get numbers, then
it's going to be harder to get dates.
And if it's harder to get dates, it's
going to be harder to meet someone.
So, you understand what I'm saying, bro?
So, yeah, bro.
So, then it's going to be harder to
actually get someone to meet. Then it's
going to be harder to actually You just
got no chance. Simple, bro.
But Reddit tells you there is a chance
to scare him.
No, I don't need tips from him, bro.
I've been approaching before him, bro.
I've been approaching before that [ __ ] mug.
He's only 23, you know, bro. I've been
approaching before him.
Um, it was all right, bro. Yeah, had a
nice roast No.
Yeah, it was good, bro. I had a good
Christmas, man. Some good presents as
well. Yeah, bro.
Need to go to bed soon. I'm so tired.
as in waxies. I love it, bro.
Yeah. And Matthews. Yeah.
But even he's friend in America said
it's harder here than it is America. But
I don't know, bro. I met a lot of
Americans today and they're just all the
same, bro. It doesn't matter where where
they are now. Like even Kieran even even
even Antman was saying like in the west
like in in Asia the younger ones are
[ __ ] you can only get like 30 odd year olds
but obviously you can't get that here.
So it's it's getting like it here bro
you're it's going to everywhere's going
to be finished in 10 years.
A festival is going to be easy. Why is
it going to be easy in the festival?
What I mean, we're in England
and women are are the same. So why why
is it going to be it's never easy
anywhere, bro? Uh he's 30. Um 33 32 33.
Yeah, I did meet somebody today from
West London and that like they gave me a
hug and that. They seemed all right. We
was talking for a while, but who knows, [snorts] bro.
I [snorts] was speaking to this person
on Instagram, Kieran, all day and that
and they seemed all right, but they've
just kind of ghosted me.
Yeah, but the point he's trying to get
at Kieran is um the point he's trying to
get at is like do the young boys are suck up. So
yeah, it's madness, lad. madness.
Yeah. Yeah. I know you drink at home
now, don't you, Kieran? I know. I
noticed that. You drink at home, don't you?
You drink at home, don't you, lad?
Then they don't they don't David they
use age as an excuse.
Doesn't matter what they are bro here
you couldn't I'd say here you couldn't
even get with a 60y old.
Nah even even the only people that I
speak to bro that are actually like kind
of normal they're they're miles away
bro. There's one in America and [ __ ]
they're they're miles away, bro.
Yeah, he hanging as well. I'm waiting
for this [ __ ] um McDonald's.
Yeah, bro. I'm waiting for this macked
and I'm going to go to bed. I'm tired, bro.
Yeah, I'll go live tomorrow, bro.
So, what do you reckon the solution is,
Kieran? It's finished, isn't it?
Everywhere's finished now, bro. Well,
Asia's just hanging on. But yeah,
don't put yourself through it, lad. If
you want to go, if you want to work, if
you want to, you know, I was confident
as well, but I didn't lose my
confidence. I [ __ ] done it. sober
[ __ ] I didn't give a [ __ ] bro. I
done it like, you know,
but yeah, England's the same old England.
>> Yeah, man. Never change that. Never change. Y.
Yeah, but it's everywhere, Kieran.
But it's everywhere, Kieran. It's not
just London, is it, lad?
Think about it, bro. It's London. It's
Manchester. It's everywhere.
It's not just London, bro.
It's everywhere, bro. Yeah.
Why do I need to get my confidence back,
Bob? I'm confident all the time.
What do you mean by that? You don't just lose it.
Well, I got four or five numbers anyways. So,
I've never been reading for a night out.
Funny enough, I've got a friend in
Reading and I've been meaning to go and
see him, but I just haven't done it.
Yeah. Yeah, true. No, everywhere is
everywhere is the same now, bro.
Everywhere is the same now, bro. I was
speaking to this person, bro, for ages.
She said she's a Christian and we was
having good combo and that.
She seemed all right, but we'll see tomorrow.
I had been ready for a night out,
but I got a friend that lives there.
They sound like farmers in it, Kieran.
Yeah, I've seen it. It's a grower, isn't it?
It's a growler, lad.
Yeah, it's a grower.
Reddit tells people to approach people. Kieran
Oh, it's 4 minutes away. My McDonald. Yeah. One sec.
3 minutes away. I'm mad.
So, what are you going to do anyways,
Kieran? Now, moving forward.
The only thing is, Kieran, you actually
do meet some characters when you go out drinking, lad.
I met some funny people, bro. But
it's the women that ruin it, isn't it?
You meet some characters, bro. You know,
you make connections and [ __ ]
That mean that's me now for probably two months, lad.
That's me now for [ __ ] two months.
No, no, no,
How can it be 3 minutes?
You fle. That's nice, bro.
I did get a couple of numbers. So yeah,
I don't know about 10 sober Bob bills.
Draining it is. It's not even scary.
It's actually draining
if you know what that means.
It's draining, lad.
Yeah, I go out now for ages, bro.
Well, if we
Well, if one of these numbers want to
meet me. Was it busy? It was quite busy
to be fair,
considering it's [ __ ] It was a Thursday. Yeah,
was quite busy, man.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, I went in my tracksuit
with Spider-Man t-shirt underneath it.
My [ __ ] McDonald's is here.
Come on, sir. I am [ __ ]
Imagine delivering that in that rain, mate.
No, not really.
>> They're miserable olds.
Hello, man. You good?
>> How are you? >> One.
I just got some nuggets.
That's pretty much the only thing that
was open. So, Huh? >> No.
>> Didn't say nothing. [clears throat] >> Yeah.
>> I told you no one was going to turn up.
They get [ __ ] seriously hurt. Peter
belly eats nuggets. What does Peter belly eat?
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Yeah.
>> A [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, they're sick, aren't >> they?
Yeah, they are pretty thick. >> Yeah.
Nothing more than what your [ __ ]
sister said, though. [clears throat]
I'm talking to someone now. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Don't
>> do I p in [ __ ] in [ __ ] England.
Yeah. No chance, man.
Got Paul in England. You're right, lad.
Got more time to pick him.
More chance of pink flying, lad.
But that guy didn't show up. Show up
today, did he?
[ __ ] had enough. I have enough.
It's very scary though if this is what
the f that this is what it is you know
in this country but it's actually really scary
really really scary but
I find it scary Damn. [snorts] Bad. Really bad.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, that light.
This is why the brakes are needed. You
see, John, you know, you understand that
there's breaks for a reason.
That's why you need to take breaks from
stuff, you know.
Not good, bro. It's not good. Anyways,
I'm going I'll be back tomorrow anyway.
I'll be back tomorrow, lad.