Oh, [ __ ] hell.
>> I'm actually going to keep this up to be
Yeah, I'm still going to hit it.
Oh, still lovely and warm.
This is the life, mate.
Being on a [ __ ] electric blanket.
What the [ __ ] more could you ask for, mate?
In all fairness now. Hello. Hello. Face. One second.
How many numbers did I get? I think I got five.
I can't even remember, bro. I got five.
I think it was
not going to be messaging them. Not nothing.
No messages. No, nothing.
I'm not messaging them.
No, not really. I just stuck to beer.
Well, I did have one shot. Well, it was
something else. It's not like a a shot.
I don't know what it was. Not really.
That's why I stick to beer. You see?
Yeah. I got five numbers, but I won't be
messaging any of them. That's just a collection
on my little phone,
you know. Just collecting.
Yeah, I'm a bit tired, but I'm not hung
over. I don't think so.
No, that guy didn't show up yesterday,
did he? [ __ ] idiot. I knew it, bro. I
knew. I knew. I knew the guy was a
fraud, man. When they start talking
about Wii and Mer and all of this [ __ ]
they're just keyboard warriors. It's so
easy to tell.
It's so easy to tell, bro.
Like no one's that's meeting is really
saying that stuff. No,
I knew it though. Ain't it, bro? I
actually called it in it.
I'm going to know whe to go to Redden
tomorrow, you know. I kind of don't want
to drink again.
for a while.
I don't know.
Oh yeah, that was the other one.
Yeah, I get confused, man.
I don't know.
A nice little collection of numbers.
Lovely. My phone book.
[ __ ] took ages, bro. Took [ __ ] ages.
I feel sorry for any man that wants to
seriously date in this country. Good
luck to you. That's all I can say, lads.
That's all I can say.
That's all I can actually say to you.
Good luck to you.
You're going to need it, matey.
No, no, no, no.
Yeah, man. Just chilling now
on top of this electric blanket.
It's nice, man. It's nice. Nice and warm.
I could fall asleep, you know, in this tracksuit.
I'll sleep well today knowing I've got
some more numbers for my little collection.
I like the little pictures and stuff. You know,
I spoke to someone yesterday, man. They
actually seemed all right and stuff, but
I don't trust people.
Do you know what's so weird is that
Yeah. Like I would actually say, yeah,
through all of these pe all of the
people that I meet, bro, women are
actually worse than men. Like as as as a
whole. Yeah. If you was to actually say
as a whole, women are actually worse than men,
even though like no one's innocent and
[ __ ] and they do stuff as well, but I
mean like they're actually worse
as a whole. And I'm not I'm not the only
person that says that. You know, loads
of people say it.
All these [ __ ]
I don't know, man. >> Yeah.
It's a madness, bro. Mad.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
I was mixing beers and stuff. You can
mix beer. That's the good thing. You can
mix beer. You just can't mix spirits.
If you just stick to beer,
you don't get any um you don't get any
anxiety. If you have rum or whiskey and
you stick to one,
um, then you're just lagging a bit for
like two days. And then if you have
[ __ ] shots, it almost kills you. So
they go in categories, you see.
You stay away from them shots, mate. [ __ ] hell.
I didn't have any baby Guinness to be fair.
You don't know. Nah,
you know, I just was someone was pissing
me off yesterday, so I thought, "Fuck
it. I'll just go out."
I mean, you can mix spirits. Yeah. But
you're going to get a really bad
hangover. And you you mix them and you
get a bad hangover. That's why you don't
mix them. That's why it's not advised to
Unless you want a stinking dirty
hangover. I'd rather just stick to beer.
I didn't drink any anything but beer yesterday.
Well, I did have one drink with someone.
They they offered me. I said, "Okay."
But why would you want to mix spirits
when you're just going to have a bad
hangover the next day?
I'll never forget that hangover two weeks ago.
I thought I was going to die, bro.
No, I'm not even joking. I was being
sick and I had a headache at the same
time and I couldn't even eat the food
that I bought. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, they say that. Yeah. But
yeah, it was raining yesterday as well.
I don't know why I didn't have any Guinnesses.
baby goodnesses. Sorry.
I think I was just so pissed off on the
um sober approaches and that
very draining. Very draining.
That's what it is.
This bloody country is getting worse.
It's getting bloody worse, lad. This country
is really bad now, man.
[ __ ] got escorts that are trying to
dictate to you. Really madness.
Mad mad mad mad times, bro. Mad times.
But I still don't regret going out
anyways cuz it was just something to do.
Oh, that's some thingy. [ __ ] hell.
I didn't get one.
Oh, I loved your little self-p
projecting comment yesterday about
nervous. Never nervous me, mate. Never
Yeah, nervous about what? This guy
didn't even show up. Never nervous.
But I knew he wasn't going to show up
because of what he was saying. It's just so obvious.
It's so obvious. Anyone that's saying
like, "Oh, you're this, you're that,
you're a M." They're not showing up nowhere.
It's as simple as that. I knew this.
And we got this [ __ ] to do on Sunday as well. Another one.
No, I've got one on Sunday. Yeah.
Which a it's not going to be a fight
because he's not going to show up. And
even if he does show up, I got my
Spider-Man t-shirt in the washing
machine. Ready for it?
I had a shower.
Yeah. Too nervous. No, I'm not nervous
like you people that don't leave your house.
Nah, I don't get nervous like you little
self projectors that don't even leave your house.
No, that's you people, bro. You ain't
even got a life.
Imagine that, bro. Not even having a life.
It's chronicle. Chronicle.
I heard you like was on YouTube all day
yesterday as well. My mom told me.
I was out so I didn't I didn't go on it
after I ended the live stream, but heard
you was on YouTube again. Yeah. It's funny.
It's funny, bro.
Yeah. Anyways, I knew that [ __ ] weren't
going to show up. It was too obvious.
Way too obvious. Yeah.
Where's [ __ ] grievy gone? I can't
message anyone on Instagram for [ __ ] 5 days.
So, I can't even tell people like what
happened last night and that.
But yeah, it has gotten worse though.
Definitely gotten worse.
Dr. echo from the last time I got from
the last time I went out.
Every time you go out, it gets worseer.
I said to Ant-Man now, so like if you
can only get 30 year olds in in as in
Asia, what's going to happen when Asia
is completely finished
in 10 years time? Then here's going to
be this. He's already here's already done. So, [ __ ] knows.
But like I said, I wasn't surprised at
the um escort thing.
I wasn't surprised at all.
Yeah, I wasn't surprised at all, man.
Nothing surprises me with with um this country anymore no.
You need to get yourself to Thailand lads. Yeah.
And even if you do actually find someone
that's actually like genuine in that,
they will actually be in a relationship
as well. So it's like the odds are just
so stacked against you that like
it's just madness.
I saw this video the other day, man.
I did have this chat with this person. So,
I don't know, bro. Weird, isn't it?
It's weird in there.
It's weird in there. I might Do you know
what? I might get myself, you know, I
might get myself a little bagel.
Oh, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
I want to get a bagel, man.
But I'm never getting a bagel ever again
from I'm never getting a salt beef bagel
ever again. Nah, that put me off. All right,
turkey bacon. Nope. Disgusting.
That's a bagel. Grilled chicken.
Yeah, I'm going to get myself a bagel.
Hello, Greavvesy. I got five numbers to
add to the little collection.
Now ask me if I'm going to message them.
No lettuce. No mayo. Add cheese.
No. Oh, yeah. I just want cheese.
Yeah, I've got I got five numbers, but I
haven't them Greavvesy cuz I just like
looking at the just looking at it on my
phone. I don't want a message. I just
want a collection. You see?
Well, the fight night was yesterday, but
the guy didn't turn up. I was live for a
little bit. You missed it. And he and he
wasn't, and he didn't show up.
I was wearing the Spider-Man t-shirt
under the tracksuit.
No. Let us know, mayor.
Yeah, I need to get I got to get a bagel.
I'm having a Chinese later.
Oh, definitely. Yeah, I need I need
something for now, though. I'm hungry.
Oh, uh, well, this Smokeoky B is on
Sunday and Joe F is whenever I announce
I'm going to Nottingham.
No, I wasn't calling them out. We
planned to meet yesterday. Do you not remember?
Yeah. And it's not it's not going to be
a fight with any of them.
Trust me, bro.
It's not going to be a fight.
Oh, Laney just messaged me saying I want
a bagel as well.
Stop watching me, Laney.
I just f I fancy a I'm going to a
chicken bagel, bro. [ __ ] hell, Laney.
Yeah, Laney wants a a salmon one.
Yeah, I got some new numbers. Grezy,
this woman was like, "Oh, like you're
going to have to um you know, go to
university and and complete a degree."
And she said that you have to go to
church. I said, "I'll go to church. I've
never been to church before."
She's like, "Oh, like can we go to
church?" And that I said, "Yeah,
right. Where is this bagel, bro? If
there is there even this bagel.
Where's this salmon bagel gone? Oh, nope. Nope. Mine.
There's no salmon bagel. Why is there no
salmon in bagels?
This one looks nice. Butterm Buttermilk
fried chicken maple. No, cuz it's turkey
bacon. No, I don't. No thanks.
Nope. Mine grew in my collection.
Why don't they have
Why don't they have um
the salmon one? That's it.
Yeah, Greavves. I went to waxies, lad. Yeah.
Why don't they have um
salmon? Why don't they not have it?
No, you don't need to pay for mine. I've
got my own [ __ ] money.
Jesus Christ. I don't want you to pay.
I've got my own money.
Thank you very much. [ __ ]
Yeah. I went down to waxies, lad. Yeah,
the attitude's getting worse. Hey. Hey,
listen, Greavvesy. Yeah. You know, women
as a whole is worse than men. You do
realize that? like they as a whole are
worse than men. And you'll know this
because when you go out and you meet
people, you you you you'll see they are
actually worse than men. Like that I can
safely say as a whole they're worse than men.
So the fact that that's that's true,
bro, and people still defend them and
don't defend men. Um you know, they are
worse than men, bro. Trust me.
women. Men don't think they're the [ __ ]
Men don't have bad attitudes. And that's
not being gay. That's speaking facts,
bro. Before you try and say that
someone's gay, you know.
I was going to do the Caroline Reaper
burger challenge again for you, Greavvesy.
Before drinking, I done I got I done two
s I got two sausage rolls. I only ate
two sausage rolls from Greg's
cuz I couldn't get into the other pub
that was shut. Uh, they closed the thing
down, you see. So, I just got two sausage rolls from Gregs.
The money. I'm sending you the money back.
What do you want me to do it? Uh, Grevy
the Carolina Reaper Burger challenge again.
Yeah, go on then,
mate. I've had that Carolina Reaper
burger is hotter than anything you'll ever have. Trust me.
It almost It almost killed me, bro.
You remember Grezy?
Did you know I was going to get some more numbers? Um, Grezy,
right, I'm going to order this bagel
now. You must have knew it was going to
happen. Is it?
Yep. I just like collecting. What can I
say? Hey, Grezy.
This person seemed all right in that. I
think they said they were 23 and that we
was talking. But yeah, I've tried ring stop once.
But a lot of these people yesterday,
Greaves, he had like bad attitude.
I mean, what do you expect? You got
Ant-Man was telling me about Thailand
and stuff, how he can only get 30 odd
year olds. So, it's no surprise that
England is that bad. Do you know what
I'm saying? So, you know,
all I was pissing myself laughing
yesterday, Greavves, I think of some of
the comments that you make. My I was I
was getting my haircut. I was getting my haircut and
I was thinking when you said that it's a
copycat community, bro. I had to hold my
laughing so bad. I did lay it out once
and I just kind of like just pretended
like there was something wrong with my
lip or something.
I had to really really hold it in, bro.
I was like, "Oh no, I'm stuck now."
Cuz you said you said it's a copycat community.
So what is it? Is it only Is it only Is
it only this community that copies Grey?
It's only this one that copies, isn't it?
So is it's only this community that copies.
I don't know why that just made me laugh.
Oh, that's another thing, Grezy, is that
even if you do come across someone
grievy, yeah, say you generally do um
come across someone that is is is
normal, they will be taken cuz somebody
would have got there before you. Just to
tell you how much the odds and stats. I
was talking to someone yesterday, bro. Um
and then they they showed me a picture
of them with the person that they're
with. So even if you was to come across someone,
they would be taken. And so that's also
what you also got to think about.
The odds are very, very, very, very
stacked against you cuz you've got to
deal with people that's got unrealistic
standards, stuck up people. Some people
might be lesbians.
Um, and then you know, you obviously got
people that are in relationships. So
what chance do you realistically have?
>> It's not normal, but it is normal, if
that makes sense.
It's 2026. It's the norm. So,
I tried to be mature about it, bro. I
tried to be mature about it, but it is
hard at times, you know?
It's hard to do it. It's hard to like
when you're sober and that and then
[ __ ] you have to deal with the
[ __ ] Grezy, you know. But yeah,
that's why I don't do content anymore,
Greasy, because everyone just copies.
What's the point of me doing anything or
showing anything on this community
anymore when someone just copies? Like
you saw the other day, Smokey B joined,
then L joined, then Prime was joining, you know,
they would just copy each other, you know.
Oh, Grezy, this is so nice, man. Wear my
little tracksuit under the electric
blanket. I'm going to fall asleep soon.
I reckon I'm going to fall asleep soon.
I'm tired, bro.
I'll [ __ ] fall asleep in this
tracksuit after the bagel.
I'm [ __ ] bro. Don't have time. Just tired.
Hungry. Do you remember when I took King
to get bagels, Grezy? He loved them.
Do you remember? They gave him free [ __ ] meat.
They gave him free meat. Do you
remember? Bless him. He loved the little
salt beef bagels.
Yeah. Bless him.
Grezy. Oh, now now someone else is going
to get a [ __ ] bagel, aren't they? Greasy.
Now someone else is going to get a
bagel. Do you know what I might get
later when I'm out? Like some digestives. Digestive biscuits.
Yeah, man. Some digestive biscuits.
But no, it is a seriously though, it is
a copycat community cuz LJ's copied my
pork um my curries and stuff and and the
boxes and stuff.
See, they don't they don't have a mind
of their own.
That's why they copy
in it. That's why they copy, lad.
Oh, the only thing this person did say
to me was they said that they I was
talking to her and she's like, "Oh, I
like hot I love hot food and that, but
the only thing they don't like is
cheese." I said, "You don't like cheese?
How the [ __ ] can you not like cheese?
Cheese is cheese is lovely, Grezy."
And I said, "Oh, see you later,
Greavvesy." And I shook their hand. They
said, "Oh, you don't want a hug?" I
said, "Oh, I would love a hug. Actually,
I got a hug yesterday." Grievy,
how cute is that? A little hug.
I've never shook someone's hand before
and they said to me, "Oh, don't you want
to um you're going to hug?"
I always thought that that was like just
too much to hug,
you know? So, yeah. You know what I'm
saying? Is it?
So maybe, just maybe, but I can't I
can't message them though because obviously
I can't message them obviously. Can I
agree with Z?
Cuz it's just it's they're not to
message, they're to be collected. So yeah.
Well, obviously, but not somebody that
I've spoke to for 10 minutes.
Oh, that's so cute. A little hug in it, Grezy. [ __ ] knows.
I don't know when I'll be out again.
Greasy, lad. Truth be told, I was out
yesterday cuz someone was pissing me off.
So, I just thought, "Fuck it, bro. I
need to refresh my mind or something,
bro, cuz this is [ __ ]
Yeah, they said they were Christian.
So, I take it uh you you wouldn't be
able to get with a vegetarian then,
would you, Grezy? Nah.
What you going to do? go for a meal and
[ __ ] they have [ __ ] the vegetarian
option. That is such a buzzkill.
Vegetarians are I mean in terms of like
if you if you're going to actually like
date someone that's such a buzz kill.
Not that they are one, but if if you're
how how is someone that loves meat?
Well, no, because someone said before
that if you hug someone, it's too much
like when you when you just first met
them. So I when you've just been
speaking to them for 10 minutes. So I
thought, you know, that's um
that's what it is. So
[ __ ] those lad.
It was hard trying to get these numbers
yesterday though. Grezy, I love to see
you [ __ ] do it.
It's draining as well. very draining.
I'm surprised you didn't go on the live, Greasy.
You should have went on my live. I was live yesterday. Miss you.
Yeah, you bless you then if you was asleep.
Get down to Waxies, lad.
Uh the manager was being a [ __ ] again. I
told him about like there's somebody
that I met like seven times and
basically he's a big [ __ ] virgin. Um
so can he come into your establishment
and maybe try to meet someone? No.
Weren't having it.
We weren't having it, bro.
Yeah. No virgins.
And the thing is, you know, if any of
these people on YouTube got me banned
from somewhere, it's pointless because
the managements change all the time. So,
I was able to go back to that place
where I had that problem with the B.
Well, except from like O'Neal's, they
never change. But most places the managements change.
You know what I'm saying? We change
where there's so many people. it
changes. So, it's just waste of time if
anyone was to get you banned from anywhere really.
What's Carolina Reaper Burger is the
hottest thing ever. And you'd wonder why
they would even do that.
That is so silly. Think about it, Grezy.
When they get you banned from places or
try to That's so weird, lad.
Yeah. On here. Yeah, that B is
definitely a virgin. That voice of
reason is definitely definitely a
virgin. I proved it, bro. Look how much
he begs this um all in Rose and they
they suck up to this [ __ ] fat woman
using filters. I don't need to do that.
I can just go out and and get some
numbers to and add to my collection.
And if I do get someone's number, I'm
not messaging them because it's just for the collection.
You get me? Yeah, that V was a
definitely a virgin.
Non is a virgin.
There's loads. There's quite a few
virgins on here.
So what did you say when you see that I
won't be I don't just want one person.
What do you say? I don't just want one person.
Yeah, I can get loads of numbers. I I
the first approach I done yesterday was
at the train station.
sober. Straight sober, bro.
So, I I still have it in me, you know,
for so long I'd be nervous, but nah,
it's like riding a bike.
It's in your DNA, Greavvesy.
It's in my DNA.
Oh yeah, Greavesy. How can you be How
can you be happy with one one person?
How can you be happy with just one
person? Think about it, Grezy. There's
so many people, so many shapes, so many sizes,
different um breasticles.
Why would you just stick with one when
you can have a whole load?
I get none. I've had more women than
you've had hot dinners, lad.
I've had more women in three years than
you've had in hot than you've had hot dinners. Nope.
I've had more women. I'd love to see
you. I would love Do you know what,
Greavves? Yeah. Do you know what's so
mad? Yeah. Even if people want to do
this, I would pay good money, bro, to
see one of these people approach a woman
on the street,
it could never happen, bro. They they
would not have the balls, bro. Even to
do it drunk. They wouldn't even have the
com They wouldn't even be able to do it,
bro. You're 38, brother. Just because
you're 38, that doesn't mean you've got
more life experience than me, bro, in
every single thing. Like Like I like
that video I done on JF the other day.
I'm 10 years younger than him and I've
gambled more than he has. That is a
fact. I have I literally have gambled
more than he has. Different positions in
life. People are in different positions,
bro. Just cuz you're 10 years older than me.
There's There's people There's There's
people that are 38y old virgins.
The [ __ ] So what? Just because you're 38.
Like, bro, if he was 80 years of age,
it'd be more believable.
If it was 70, bro, you're 38. What's 10 years?
What? What is 10 years, bro? Come on,
mate. Come on. You haven't had more
women than me, bro. Trust me. I used to
go out three times a week. You really,
really haven't had more women than me.
You're not a chance in hell, lad.
Why? Why are you talking about
countries? Stick to the subject, bro.
We're talking about women. You need to
learn to stick to the subject.
You think because you think because
you're 38 that means someone's had more
women than someone. I've had way more
women than you, bro.
If these people could could speak to
women in person, Grievy, I don't know
about this guy. I don't know who he is,
but Greavves, if a lot of these people
could speak to women in person, right?
Yeah. No, I never said about you. I said
to Joe, I was using it as an example.
You know, if any of these Liz Grevy, you
know, if any of these women could speak
to any of these people could speak to
women, you know, they wouldn't beg women
on on YouTube. If you do realize that we
lit, they literally would not like Do
you understand that? That also gives them away
because obviously they know that they're
fat. They know that they're [ __ ]
ugly and they can't speak to people. So
that's why think about it. That's how
you know as well. Hey listen, listen
listen. Hey, bro. That's how you know
that they're not better than you. These
people that are calling you, bro, that's
how you know they're not better than
you. Cuz if they were better than you, Yeah.
why are they begging women on the
internet? If they're better, they're
better than you, bro. Why are they
singing women on YouTube? Ask Ask ask
yourself that question.
Think about it for a second, bro. If
they could speak to women in person and
they weren't fat and ugly and [ __ ] they
wouldn't they wouldn't care about some
women on YouTube.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I' I'd [ __ ]
myself. I don't think so.
Yeah. My bagel's coming in
6 minutes. Oh.
Yeah, my bagel's coming in 6 minutes, lad. Yeah.
I'm hungry, bro. It's all that beer. Greasy.
I'm pretty sure somebody I approached
yesterday was a [ __ ] escort.
I'm not sure
but I know I did get numbers but again I'm not
decision then bro
am I not right in what I'm saying though
about the women [ __ ] grezy
think of it yeah this just use this
video as an example yeah he calls people
porky he calls people this he calls
people that yeah isn't he the one
begging women on YouTube and I'm not and
I'm just not. So that tells you two
things, bro. A, he doesn't have a life
and he doesn't meet women in real life
because he hasn't got a life. And B,
he's an ugly bastard.
You're boring. See you later.
What? Me and you, Greasy.
No, but it's true what I'm saying
though, is it? Come on. When when people
are doing that on YouTube, bro.
Yeah. You'll never see me begging a
woman on YouTube, bro. Ever. Ever.
Meeting a woman on YouTube.
No [ __ ] way, bro. That's only for
people. And it also proves their skin as
well. So yeah, everything that they say
is just theirelves.
Why are good-looking people with a life
begging women on YouTube? Ask yourself that question. I know. Yeah,
I did turn up. I was live.
So, you might want to you might want to
go back because I was live and he didn't
turn up. So yeah, stop talking [ __ ]
You [ __ ] idiot. You got the wrong
person, mate. I definitely turned up and
I went live and he didn't show up
just like I knew he wouldn't.
Yeah, I was in the pub right next to the
park waiting for him to go live in the
park. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And where was
he? Nowhere as usual. Just like Smokey B
is going to be nowhere on Sunday. Cuz
I'm going to do this.
One of Peter Belly's punches. Greavvesy.
That's the end.
That's the end. Greavvesy.
Oh, you're going to laugh at this,
Grezy. You know when I went to the
barbers yesterday? Guess how long I was
on the chair for?
He said that he was going to come on
here. So, see you later.
Anyways, guess how long I was on a
barber chair for, Grezy? Two hours.
They had to wax my nose twice cuz I was
so hairy. And it took ages because I had
so much hair, Greavesy. But I'm all
groomed now, so it's all good, you know.
[ __ ] hurt as well, man. I got my eyebrows threaded.
Oh, he's probably gone to the shop. Yeah. [ __ ] boy.
Was it before these G
I don't swing that way.
I don't swing that way, lads.
I like Reddit, Grezy. It's got the
little cute avatars.
Have you gone shop, Greg, or you still there? That's funny.
as I this [ __ ]
Right. It's coming out. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, my bagel's coming, man.
Human human. Yeah, my bagels here. One sec. Be back.
There you go.
with this white.
That was not Mhm.
>> It's hot as well.
That makes no sense.
How can something smell hot?
>> I have cheese with mine. Is that weird?
>> You're a very cheesy person there.
>> But you don't have to with it, do you? Norally.
I like these ones, but I don't have them everywhere.
No, put it in the bun. >> Oh, >> yeah. It
Oh my god. Can you bring some tissue or something? It's nice. >> Huh?
>> I like this. I like the ones where I
took I like the ones where I took King.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Mom, we'll go to We'll go there to that
bagel shop. Yeah. One day and you'll get
a proper salt beef bagel. Imag
your order. Is that your order? The door.
That's who it is. Huh? Mom.
Yeah, the Carolina Reaper burger. Yeah,
it almost killed me.
But you know, Virgin boy, he can only
have a pulmer.
Is that a virgin?
I got a lot of people on this community
who been stuck that want my ass.
I don't swing that way, bro.
I had that [ __ ] fatty Peter Griffin
he made in me again.
You don't understand. I'm not
interested. I don't want them.
I'm out the closet.
It's very nice to
just leave it. Oh. Um, yeah. Take that
one down. Put it back in the fridge
then. Yeah. Got a McDonald's Coke as well.
It's nice though.
You got to beat the bagel, you know. Thank you.
I'll see you later now. Yeah. Oh,
listen. Um, we'll eat together like a
copycat in it.
Let's eat together like big fat copycats. Cats
agreed. Why did you say it again?
Why thing you said that if you don't um
find um thing attractive that you're
gay? What was the reason again? Sorry,
I've got memory loss, lad.
I've really I've got memory loss.
Oh, I'm having a lovely Basil UK asylum. Basel
and um a McDonald's Coke.
Hope that's not [ __ ]
I got that fatty Jamie emailing me
again. UK asylum.
Leave me alone. I don't want you. You
fat ugly bastard.
Come out the closet.
They want my ass though.
Nope. Oh, by the way, Gy, early hours of
the morning, I had McDonald's. I had 20 nuggets.
I tell you I tell you a place you like
grievy is joby.
Have you heard of joby? It's basically a
fried chicken place but there's no grease.
Um they have one in Liverpool obviously
they have them in one in London. They
have them in London. I don't know if
they have it where you are.
Are we eating together? Gre like copycats.
But we actually eating like two a pair of copycats.
So why did Figgy say that you can't deny she's attractive?
You can't deny she's attractive.
You can't deny it.
Why can't I deny it? Lovely.
I'm not messaging any of these women. Nope. Nope.
Why can't I deny she's attractive?
Nonsense said that I can't deny it. Why
can't I deny it? I've got a very
specific type, Ruzy.
Why can't I deny it? H
I I I miss Bquest
Music. I was thinking about Bquest
yesterday. Remember Barkquest?
I asked him why did uh thingy why was
thingy saying that stuff and he said to fit in
said that he says it to fit in
does he say to fit in them
cuz we you know some like women yeah
like I said to you before
no one ever says that if you don't find
them attractive you're gay like you
remember That Italian woman that I went
on a date with, she was quite cute. She
was better than her, but no one said,
and I put her up in my picture, but no
one said, "If you don't find her
attractive, you're gay." And she was
better. So why is that crazy, huh?
And she was miles better, I'd say.
I've never heard I didn't say anyone say
that about her.
Why? You never answer my questions. We'll sh Yeah.
Are you happy that I went out and and
collected some more with the music?
And I got a little hug as well. Really good.
I got a little hug.
The bagel was delicious. M.
There's a lot of closeted gay people in
this community. Um, Greasy, did you like
that little video done to Joe F. It got
a couple of thumbs up.
Yeah, they are gay, bro. If you got a
channel dedicated to another man, you're
a batty man, bro.
You're a [ __ ] It's It's straight up,
bro. Straight up, lad.
You wouldn't even act this way towards a
female, let alone another man. Any
plans today, Captain? I've got plans.
I'm staying in bed.
I'm going to try these later.
Griezy loves Peter B.
You love Peter B. Greasy, you just come
in here and take the piss out of me.
What if I start trolling you? Would you like it?
You know what I wrote on Reddit?
I said that women shouldn't be paid for working.
They should get half the They should get
half the wage that um that men get. What
do you think, Grezy?
I not get paid at all. Griezy,
how do you think? How How do you feel
about that? Griezy.
Griezy, do you actually think I'm a troll?
Cuz this UK asylum said that I'm a troll.
I don't think so, bro. Why would I troll?
What the [ __ ] do I get out of trolling, bro? Uh
What do I get out of trolling? Honestly, nothing, man.
Nope. Nope. Women should get less
squeezy. Nope. Nope.
Cuz obviously they put they put men
through [ __ ] and like [ __ ] and that. So
they should get less for that. Nope.
They should get paid less. No.
You should get paid less.
Or being bad people. Yeah.
Yeah. There was two women I met
yesterday and they were from uh they
were from Boston. Greavvesy. Of course
they would be from [ __ ] of course
they would be from [ __ ] Boston.
What do you think of waxies? Did it look good, Grezy?
There was some women there, Greavvesy.
Don't worry. I did get some.
Even though it looks like a It looked
like a sausage fest. There was There was
women there. It was quite busy for
Thursday. I think there was a game on or something.
Think about think about that, Grezy.
Everyone's going for a nice drink or to
catch up with their mates or to watch a
game and I'm just going for my little collection. Grezy. Yep.
How cute is that? No other reason.
So what if someone says, "Oh, they want
to date me and stuff." Grezy,
what what how will I what will I say to them?
I could just like try to get with
multiple people. Grezy,
that'd be cute. Grezy, isn't it?
You know what would be really cool?
Yeah. If you had a baby with two
different people in in the space at the same time.
Imagine that, Grezy.
Like, you know, at the same time. How
cool would that be, Grezy?
So, you you you get someone pregnant
around them at the same time.
So, you have two people carrying your
baby. Grieves. How cool would that be
if you could if you could if you could have that?
No. No. No. No. No. The other women
don't know. The other woman doesn't know
the other woman.
You know, the other woman doesn't know
the other woman, so they wouldn't know about it.
Do you understand?
So, there is two people that don't know
each other and they don't even know of each other.
It's just people that you've you've you
know, you've had sex with. How cool
would that be, Grezy? You know,
and then what if they had triplets,
Grezy? Both of them. And then there's
six Peter Bellies in the world in a
space of nine months, Grezy.
Do you reckon? Do you reckon the world
would be a better place with six Peter Peter Bellies?
Imagine that. Six Peter Bellies, Grezy,
isn't that cool?
You know, isn't that cool? Greasy
could do some baby updates, some family
updates, Grezy on YouTube.
What do you think?
That'd be lovely.
Do you get me, bro?
I said to you before, can I go and try
and get someone pregnant for the sake of
it? Greasy. And you said that's not okay with you.
Greavves. You said that's not okay with
you, is it?
I said, "Is that okay with you, boss?"
She said, "No, not okay with me, boss."
So, so wait, is that possible, Gregy?
You could actually get three or four
people like pregnant in the space of a
week if obviously you got like you got
the chance to have sex and stuff. Grezy,
do you reckon that what you reckon you
could that could actually happen
like all at the same time?
Not all at the same time, but like
within a period of like a week or two.
Do you think that would be a good idea, Grezy?
Isn't that cool?
I think that'd be really cool. Grooy,
all risk to the care system. No, they
can't just put your child They can't
just put your child in care, Grezy.
They can't just do that. Uh,
no. They can't they can't just take my baby
baby Peter Grizzly. Yeah.
Do you actually think I trolled O Gy? Honestly,
do you remember when I said to Triple H?
Chair, you should go for a drink with
Anon Deck in Newcastle. Be realistic, P.
I was being realistic.
Be be realistic, P.
Do you remember that? Oh,
do you know when I I used to hate doing
McDonald's deliveries when I'd done Uber
Grezy, the Cokes would the Coke would always spill. Yeah.
The Coke would always spill. Yeah.
I wonder when was the last time these
people on YouTube got a hug from a woman. Greavvesy.
I was looking at the person for about 10
minutes, Greavvesy, before approaching.
And I was like, I don't want the other
person who I approached to see
that I've approached.
And I was like, h that could potentially
be my mama. Grezy,
my collection of mummies. Boozy. Grezy.
So if this person says they'll meet me
again, I'm going to be happy with one person, right?
It's okay, boss. Oh, graves. Yeah.
Yeah, but I'm going to stay with them, right?
Yeah, I'll stay with her, right?
Nope. Nope. I don't get with people.
I just collect people greasy.
There's a big difference.
Who do you who who do you find more funnier?
Who do you find more funnier? Uh, Grezy,
me or Mark? Sees Mark.
No, I love Reddit.
No, I love Reddit, bro.
Yeah, but Mark's a troll though, Greasy.
I'm not. He's an actual troll.
I never understood why people used to
hate him for being on benefits because
at the end of the day, bro, yeah, they
didn't have to watch him. And another
thing is if he's not [ __ ] over the
system, someone else is doing it.
What's your thoughts on that?
Well, it does it it does make sense, Squeezy.
So what? Just so what? All so you think
that Oh, just because you meet one
person that's that's okay
for all of this [ __ ] they've gave you
over the years. Nope. Nope. I'm collecting. Yep.
When I got my
Who the [ __ ] is that?
Yeah, but I don't want to stay with one.
I want to be I would want to be with multiple
cuz I'm special. Greasy.
Why? Yeah, but I can be in a
relationship with with multiple
different people, Greasy.
with multiple different people.
Okay. But then, okay. So, what if you if
you meet someone that's really nice and
stuff, but um you know, they don't have
you know, they don't have big boobs,
then how are you going to get your vitamins,
right? Okay. So, then how you going to
get your vitamins then
since you have to stay with one person?
Do you not understand?
How the [ __ ] you going to get your vitamins then?
and calcium and stuff maybe. Yeah,
like curries and bananas and stuff
like bananas and curries and stuff like
that. and stakes.
But then what if you meet another woman
that's got bigger ones and they said,
"Oh, so say you've been in a
relationship. or or he was in a
relationship for 3 years and then another
and then another uh um
then another um women come along with
bigger ones and said, "Oh, you can get with me."
Then what greasy?
You can't just break up with someone
that you've been with for [ __ ] three
years, can you? You know,
prawn is available. Curries. Yeah. Yeah.
I get my vitamins from curries in the winter.
Yep. Curries, ribs, bagels.
I need to take my wash out. Greasy.
Oh, you have peppies all the time. You disabled [ __ ]
That's all you ever have. You [ __ ] disabled bastard.
Uh, I got I think I got four or five
added to the collection. Yep.
You really are disabled. You are ponty
lad. You really are disabled.
There's a lot of disabled people in this community. busy. Yeah,
we're all copycats as well, aren't we?
Nah, Jo's not disabled. He's just he's
just a closeted gay.
You know, these people Indigo like Jamie
Thompson and stuff, they're just they're
just closeted gays.
Unhappy gays. That's what they are.
They hate the fact that they're gay
and they take it out on me.
Oh my god, I spilled a bit of hope
there. Let me wipe it. It's gone. Yeah.
Yeah. They're gay, bro. That's why you
couldn't reply back to me. If you've got
a channel dedicated to another man, you're homosexual.
Simple as that, bro. They are gay. Gay boys.
They're not even doing it to a woman.
Think about it, Grezy. They're not even
doing it to a woman.
Uh, zero. How many women have you seen V with Yeah.
But then they they tried to call me
someone that's better than them. Yeah.
They're the ones that beg Autumn Rose,
but I'm the I'm the M and I'm the one
that's disabled apparently.
That's even worse, lad. Yeah.
It's weird, is it, man? I had that fatty
fatty Jamie messaging me again.
The only one that's special is you.
Special you. poverty
you everything is you pathetic you
like bro educate you don't have no
education so you couldn't educate me
even if you tried bro you are gay bro
you're literally a [ __ ] homosexual
channel is dedicated to me bro you
nonslegs and Jamie yeah you need to book a room
you need to literally book a room Bro,
you need to you all need to come out as
gay. Yeah. And then just just just book
a room, bro. And just just have it out
with each other cuz you're you're you're
definitely a closet gay.
You're definitely a definitely
definitely a closeted homo.
You really are homosexual.
Just be happy, bro. If you want if
you're gay, just be be a happy gay.
Are you happy gay? You know,
you're proper proper gay, bro.
Just like your other boyfriends.
Yeah, bro. Just just just Yeah,
literally, bro. Cuz you you're something
else. I wouldn't even do this to, bro.
No man obsessed with a woman would even
do this to a woman, bro. What they do on
here. And you don't do it for reaction.
You are actually obsessed. There's a big
difference. There's people that do stuff
for reaction. Yeah. But you are actually
obsessed. And by that I mean And by that
I mean I could leave for 2 years and
you'd still be doing it. You would still
be doing it every day thinking that I'm
watching. You're gay, bro.
And you know I'm right. That's why you
can't say anything back cuz you know I'm correct.
I mean people used to go on Timmy's and
just say stuff for reaction. I mean
that's a bit different. You are actually obsessed.
There's You are obsessed with another
man, bro. Come out.
Yeah. I don't swing that way, bro. And
if I did swing that way, you're not my
type, Joe. Don Slegs is not my type.
Jamie Thompson isn't my type.
You all laugh at me, bro. You've got a
channel dedicated to obsessing over me.
Bro, bro, bro, you've got a channel
obsessed with another man. Come out the
closet. Any laughs that you think you
have out of me, I have tenfold laughs at you back.
Pathetic middle-ag wasters. Bro, you
think I don't get laughs out of you. You
are wasters. That's and you know what
I'm saying about you is the truth.
That's why you're saying stuff. How can
a bunch of middle-ag rejects laugh at anyone, bro?
Look at you. Look at L J. Look at Nlegs.
You're all wasters. You're embarrassments, lads. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Bro, you've got a channel
obsessed with another man. You're a
gaylord, bro. Seriously, come out. You
You seriously need to come out the closet.
Bro, I laugh at you as well. I laugh at
you. I laugh at LJ. I laugh at how
you're so obsessed with me.
How I live in your head. It's so
laughable. How I can live in other men's
heads. I love it. I laugh at it, bro. I
love it, lad. How people can be so
jealous of someone they don't know.
It's mad. It's mad.
It's really, really, really mad, lad.
That's really mad, bro.
You I laugh at you. I laugh at your
boyfriends. I laugh at you more than you
could ever laugh at me. Look at you,
bro. Look at you showing your body, bro.
Thinking that you're fit, bro. One
punch. I would knock you flying.
I would literally knock the [ __ ] out of
you, bro. Yeah. It's It's not even a
joke. You've got a strong punch, bro. I
would knock the [ __ ] out of you with one
punch, bro. But that that's all it would
take. You stupid little northern sausage.
I got a strong punch. Do you hear
yourself, bro? Do you really really hear
yourself? You do you hear yourself?
I got a strong punch, bro. Really?
Really? Go suck your boyfriend's dick.
You, Jamie Thompson, and launch legs,
bro. You need to suck their dick. Come
out the closet with them, bro. You'll be
happier. You'll be much happier if you
come out the closet.
You know, you'll be a much happier
person. You can't laugh at someone
that's better than you, bro. It just
doesn't work. Sorry. It just doesn't Seriously. Seriously.
Uh I'm I must remember you say people
call you virgin must be be them a virgin
themselves. No, no, no, no, no. You are
actually a [ __ ] I'm not saying that
to troll you. I'm not saying that to
take the piss. You and your boyfriends
are class A [ __ ]
And I'm not saying that to be nasty. You
are gay. You are a [ __ ] And I'm not
saying that to try and take the piss or
to just say it, bro. You are gay. The
day I've got a a channel dedicated to
other men is the day I kill myself, bro.
Is the day I literally I I literally get myself sectioned.
Like, you are gay, bro. You're a [ __ ]
Are you You actually are, bro. The
evidence is there. Yeah, whatever, bro.
Yeah, whatever. Joe, you didn't even
Well, I'll be going to Nottingham soon anyways,
bro. Us? What do you mean us? You're a
bunch of losers. You know when you say
we, Joe? Yeah. You're the life's losers.
Does that not sink in? You say to me,
"Yeah, that stuff don't sink in with me,
bro." When you say we, you're all
losers. You're rejects to society. Your
opinion doesn't mean anything. You're so
rejected that society don't even accept
you. No one cares about losers that
don't leave their house, that simp over
women, skin people. You're so irrelevant
that your opinion doesn't even matter.
You're a bunch of losers. So continue
thinking that you laugh at people. You
laugh at yourselves. Deep down, you know
it, bro. Simple. You're just a bunch of
gay, jealous ass losers. Laugh at what
you want. No one cares about a bunch of
losers that mean nothing,
you know, about saying that you've got a
strong punch. I would knock the [ __ ] out
of you. The absolute [ __ ] out of you
with one punch. I'm much bigger than you
will ever be, bro. Yeah, bro. Last, bro.
Bro, bro, bro, hold on. Hold on. Hold
on. When did I last talk to When did I
last talk to Charlie?
When did I last talk to Charlie? I'm not
the one saying, "Oh, oh, he's got a
girlfriend. Don't say that about him."
Bro, you're sucking dick every day. I
don't talk to Charlie. You suck
nonsense's dick every day over someone
he hasn't even proven he's had sex with.
I don't talk to Charlie. I'm not gay
like you. I don't have a channel on men.
I'm not gay like you. You, Jamie
Thompson, and [ __ ] nodds. You're a
bunch of gay boys. Don't project your
gayness onto me. Don't start talking
about Charlie because you're gay. Don't
start changing the subject now. You and
your [ __ ] boyfriend, you suck his
dick every day. Oh, don't say that about
him. He's got this girlfriend. You
[ __ ] little [ __ ] Shut the [ __ ] up,
you stupid little [ __ ] Go suck your
boyfriend's dick. Oh, I've got a strong
punch. A strong punch, you little weak
northerner. Yeah. Really? Really? Is
that why you didn't even show up to the
place that you were supposed to show up as?
Go and [ __ ] suck your boyfriend's
dick. Go cry some more that I called him
a virgin, bro. Literally, go and cry
some more. I'm calling him a virgin
again. Go and cry some more. I spoke
about your boyfriend. Go and suck his
dick and make him feel better. And
whilst you're at it, go and suck Jamie
Thompson's dick as well, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] You [ __ ] sad poverty [ __ ]
fake pension. Fake wins [ __ ]
Why do you think that my video got three
thumbs up? Because it's right. What I'm
saying about you,
you sad, weakling little bastard. Yeah,
because you what I'm saying about you is the truth.
Yeah, man. Let's go on.
Let's go on Joseph Farrar's channel.
Indigo. One second, lad. Let's just have
a little gander.
cuz he must have some good content, right?
Let's have a little look cuz I'm not subscribed anymore. PJ
PJ PJ. It's PJ PJ. Okay, that's enough.
Yeah. Okay. Your channel is basically
dedicated to me, bro. Come out the
closet. You'll be a much happier person.
You literally will be a happier person.
And I'm not reading that paragraph that
you wrote on me. So, you wasted your
time. Come out the closet.
It was the best advice I could have
[ __ ] gave you, man.
Do you think you're going to get a woman
this year? Do you Do you reckon you'll
get a woman this year? I don't know, bro. Yep.
Last point. You've never had a
girlfriend. You're self projected.
Listen, bro. Listen. You can say all of
this stuff to my face. Yeah. Listen.
Listen. You are the [ __ ] bro. Come
on, bro. Come on the panel and talk. Why
don't you come on the panel and talk,
bro? You're so much of a [ __ ] You
can't even talk, lad.
Bro, you are a [ __ ] like your
boyfriend, can't you? Isn't Isn't your
boy Isn't your boyfriend LJ dyslexic?
You want to talk about spastics, bro?
Isn't your boyfriend dyslexic? You
[ __ ] gay boy. I've got a strong punch.
I've got a strong punch. Oh, bro. That
imagine saying to someone, "I got a
strong punch, bro. I would I could knock
you out with just an elbow.
I can knock you out with just an elbow.
You [ __ ] gain all over the o. Go cry
some more, bro. I'm calling I'm calling
your boyfriend a virgin again. Go and
cry some more. Cry some more about this
girlfriend. Go and cry some more. Go and
suck his dick some more.
He's got a girlfriend. He's got a
girlfriend. I don't believe it. Go cry
some more, you little dick sucker
[ __ ] And guess what, bro? You're
never ever going to do anything. And
when I'm done on Sunday, when I'm done
on Sunday, I'm going to Nottingham and
I'm going to show that you're not about
nothing. And I'm going to tell everyone
when I'm going as well, bro.
And I will and and and we'll see who
who's the one that's will talk. And I'm
going to talk about your boyfriend so
you can cry some more about this
girlfriend. Oh, don't say that about,
man. You [ __ ] little [ __ ]
Seriously, come out as gay.
Seriously, he he needs to come out as
gay with stuff, bro. I'm telling him
yet. I'm not even trolling him when I'm
saying this. He generally needs to come
out as a [ __ ] Not even not even, bro,
a a straight man with an obsession
with a woman that they're in love with
could be this obsessed as they're
obsessed with me. He needs to literally
come out as gay. Why have you not come
out as gay yet?
Like, if you I mean, I see on Reddit.
Yeah. People are always asking, "How do
I come out? How do I come out?" I don't
know what happens in the end, but yeah,
you need to come out, bro. You're a
angry homosexual just like your two boyfriends
that we know of. You're you're angry homosexuals.
Like, you lit You literally are.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
No, he has to stalk you. Ah, he's been
he's been stalking me for longer than 4 years.
No, he's been I mean he's been stalking
me longer than four years.
Oh, I've got other plans. Yeah, I've got
I've got Bro, I've Bro, obviously I've
got other plans.
Obviously, I've got other plans. Why?
What? What do you think? I'm just going
to go all the way some to somewhere for YouTube, bro.
For them to say, "Oh, I control you."
Oh, bro, I'm not stupid, bro. I wasn't
born yesterday. Of course, I'm not going
to go all that way for him. Some jealous
little fat gay loser.
No, no, no, no, no. People are saying,
"How did they come out?" You should go
on it, Joe. You need to come out as gay,
bro. You'll be a happier person,
bro. It's because they're gay. Do you
not understand, Unlucky? They're homosexuals.
They hate the fact that they're gay.
Like, even even try to talk about his
boyfriend, bro. You call non legs a boy
a virgin. He starts crying about his
boyfriend. That's what I'm saying, bro.
You need a room, bro. Do you want me to
book you a room in Blackpool? I'll do it
right now. You, Gay Thompson, Nodle
Legs, you could all suck each other's
dick and and get it out the way, bro.
You're the one with the channel talking
about me every day, bro. No one spent I
ain't got other men on my phone. I don't
have other men on my phone, matey. You
do, and your boyfriends do. Not me, lad.
Not me. You're the one that's got
[ __ ] sh You your Well, actually, no.
It's the No, actually, it's the four
It's No, it's the four gay boys, isn't
it, Joe? You, Red Star, Jamie. Yeah,
it's the four gay boys. Do you know what
we're going to call you now? One of the
four gay boys. That's what you are now. Yeah.
You're a gay boy. Four gay boys.
That's why you talk about gay so much,
cuz you are gay. You're a [ __ ] I knew
it, bro. That's why I got three thumbs
up because I'm right about your [ __ ]
ass. Yeah, it's the truth. It's the truth, lad.
It's It's the truth. It's the truth, man.
Go and cry, bro. I'm calling your
boyfriend a virgin or you're not going
to cry some more. Go cry some more and
defend him, bro. Oh, he's got a
girlfriend. Don't say that about him.
Are you not sucking his dick today? Are
you not Are you not being gay today? Or
are you gonna take one day off of being
gay? Is that your is that your is that
your day off of being a gay boy? Is it
Is it Friday is it is it literally Fridays, lad?
So Friday is when you're not being a gay
boy. You sure you're not going to defend
your boyfriend and cry some more about
this girl that can't consent to sex?
You sure you're not going to defend your boyfriend? [ __ ] [ __ ]
You [ __ ] [ __ ] lad. Yeah. Madness.
No, but seriously, come out of the
closet. It will do you a lot of good. Yeah, man. Sad bastard. Yeah.
Bro, do you know what? He's such a short
ass as well, Wister. I would literally
knock the [ __ ] out of him with one
punch. It's that bad, bro. It's
literally literally that bad, you know.
He's He's a He's a little short ass.
[ __ ] hell, man. You You're a sad sad
bastard. Really are.
You're a sad sad [ __ ] Yeah, man.
Mad, mad, mad, mad, mad. You would have
thought Yeah, I could understand,
Wister, if it was women that they were stalking.
I could understand if they were like
obsessed with women,
but they were obsessed with other men,
bro. What the [ __ ] Yeah, you're gay,
bro. You You're really really really gay.
It's okay to be gay, bro.
Nothing wrong with being gay.
Yeah, there's nothing wrong with being gay. Yeah.
It's okay to be gay, lad. It's okay.
I said that you were closeted gay.
There's people with kids that are gay.
There's people that have been married
that are gay.
You're gay, lad.
You're really, really, really, really gay.
I'm wearing Tommy Hilfiger boxer shorts
and you're wearing X boxer shorts,
but apparently I'm the one that's that's
that's living in poverty.
You do love to talk about yourself,
don't you, man? You do love to talk
about yourself a lot.
You do love to talk about yourself.
Yeah, man. It's okay to be gay. Nothing
wrong with being gay.
Yeah, because he's a [ __ ] Unlucky.
Because he's a gay boy.
Because he's gay. Just like Non's legs.
Just like Red Star. Just like Jamie.
They're gay boys. They they are actually gay.
There's nothing wrong with being gay.
The bartender yesterday was gay, but he
seems very happy with his life. Good on
him. He's He's happy being gay. That's
what you need to be, Joe. You need to be
happy being gay.
Yeah, you need to be happy being gay, lad.
He's not the only one. He's not the only one, Wister.
Imagine someone like Nonss and Jo
speaking to women in person. Could you
imagine them doing a cold approach?
They'd be like, "Uh uh."
No, they wouldn't say they wouldn't say
anything. Their anxiety would never
allow it. Their anxiety would never ever
Sorry, Joe. I don't swing that way.
I'm not interested in you. I'm not
interested in your other boyfriends. You
just don't do it for me. You just don't
do it for me, mate. You really, really don't.
before you did clearly because you're on
YouTube talking about me every single
day. So where do you have the time to
[ __ ] this misses when you're on YouTube
24/7 talking about me and talking to me?
So when was the last time you did it?
Um, no actually it was about 3 months ago.
Which was before you clearly cuz you're
on YouTube every day obsessed with me
like your boyfriends. Yeah.
You need to get a life, bro. You
seriously need to get a life.
You need to get a life, lad.
Uh, I didn't pay him anything.
You're a midriff.
Yeah, he's a [ __ ] bro.
I would never ever [ __ ] bang what
you're with. And I would never bang what
Launch Legs is with.
Nah, you couldn't even You couldn't even
pay me to do that.
You really are a [ __ ] idiot.
So, are you going to come to Nottingham
then when I announce it a week
beforehand or what?
Well, it is illegal. That's why he's
never done her. So, are you actually
going to meet me then? Yeah.
Oh, man. Do you know why I respond to
you, Joe? Do you know Do you know why
it's actually addicting to respond to
these people? Because where you're so
stupid, it actually makes me feel good.
That's actually why I respond because
you're so you're so stupid
that it's just addicting.
It's like it's almost an an addiction
like to to respond to stupid people like
you know what I'm saying. Yeah.
Let's see my face again.
That's my face. I can show my face.
Yeah, man. That's my face. Yeah. Better
looking than you and your boyfriend's.
That's my face. And I ain't got no
double chins. But you you can't show
your face. That's the last thing you
need to do now. You've shown your body.
So why don't you show your face?
Yeah. So that's that's the last thing
you need to do now. You need to show
your face. You could never do that, bro. Never. Yeah.
Yeah, man. Why don't you show everyone
what you look like?
Yeah. I don't give a [ __ ] bro. You
can't show your faces. You're not going
to get at me, bro, for the way that I
look. So pointless.
Even Even trying that one, lad.
You don't show your faces for a reason.
So, you're not going to get a medi lad?
That's a question I would love answering one day.
I bet this [ __ ] looks like rice.
Yeah, I went to the barbers yesterday. I
wasn't I was on the chair for two hours.
I was very hairy with stuff.
It took him ages, bro.
No, I just want to I'm just curious what
you look like.
That's not gay. I mean I mean what's
more gay? asking someone to show their
face to prove they're not ugly or
someone that's got a YouTube channel
dedicated to another man.
What What do you think, Wister?
Would you would you say that someone
that's got a channel dedicated to
another man is more gayer than someone
asking just to show your face?
I'd say I'd say you're probably more gay
to be honest.
I'd say you're probably more gay.
I'd say you're just maybe a little bit more gay. Yeah.
Do you know what's so mad is I've
probably got more of a sex life than you
and your boyfriend. Then I'm single.
That's how tragic it is. Go figure. I
probably got more of a sex life than you
and I'm single.
That's actually how how sad it is to be honest.
Never heard of that chocolate bar. Never.
Happy Mother's Day though.
Mother's Day is not May. It's March,
isn't it? Grievy.
This person in America said, "Happy
Mother's Day in May." Might be America.
And it might be May in America, but I
know it's March here.
Yeah, they've definitely got a That's
weird. I'm sure it's March's Mother's Day. Grievy,
but they're saying it's May over there.
Oh, yeah. I think I have heard of that whisper.
speaking to this person in California. Griezy,
I'm not going to get into the chats.
They're quite uh you know what is that
okay with you, Grezy?
But they live in California.
That's the only problem, Grezy.
But I mean, it'd be good content, in it,
isn't it, Greavvesy?
Go to California, get a [ __ ] and come back.
as you do, Grezy.
And and come back.
No more uh fake gambling wins. I miss
them. Well, I'm not sub to you anyways,
but I noticed you don't put your fake
gambling wins up anymore, Joe.
You must be skin and you can't pump the machines anymore.
You put money in the machines and then
you take them and then you take it out
acting like you've won. It's so obvious.
It's so obvious what you do.
Bless you then.
Bless you in life. H.
Last point. You've never had a
girlfriend? Yes, I have had a girlfriend.
Nice try, nonslegs lover.
Nice try, nonslegs lover. Sound jealous.
I won a football bet last week.
So jealous. Yeah, that's the only thing
you can say. Like I said, go live in the
bookies and show us you win.
Show us you winning. Yeah, man.
You should show us you winning live in
the bookies. Why not?
I'm not jealous if someone wins.
See, so that's the only thing you say
when people know that you're bullshitting.
That's the only thing you can say is
that they're jealous. Yeah.
Nice, isn't it?
I need to buy some more stuff.
Oh, I could fall asleep, you know. I'm
just bl in this in in this blanket, you know.
I only I only wiped them, didn't I? So,
oh man, eyes are so [ __ ] tired.
Yeah, I will in a minute.
You know, Mother's Day it is March, isn't it?
>> But in America, they celebrate in May. >> Yeah.
They're Yankee Doodles.
>> That's where Spider-Man comes from, Mom. Huh?
That's where Spider-Man comes from.
I got the cinema on the 27th, don't I?
Yeah, the new one. Ma,
even though they are just going to be
similar, it's something to I will go and
watch that. You know what I mean? Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, man. Yeah, it heats the um
cover up, doesn't it?
The electric blankie.
Yeah. Crash Bandicoot said he had a good sleep.
He's cute in it. Oh, mate.
I am [ __ ]
You wanted a little salmon and bagel. Bless you.
>> Yeah. I don't know why they didn't have
it. might run out of it. Yeah. >> Yeah.
I'll never get a salt beef one from
anywhere ever again after that. Never.
I think it's actually put me off it
forever, you know. Yeah, that was
disgusting. Whatever that was, mom. Huh? It's weird.
No, no, no, no.
I was watching a GTA video.
I'm good at washing m
cuz some people have hygiene, don't
they? Unlike some.
They got missing teeth, bro.
How the [ __ ] do you have missing front
[ __ ] teeth? Dirty bastards.
One of the [ __ ] virgins.
But they're sat on YouTube 24/7, is it?
>> And I' and I'm not on here as much as
they are. I'm I I actually have a life.
Yeah. We're talking about you, Joseph.
Me and Laney's talking about the characters Grezy.
Yeah, I'm single and I have more of a
life than them and I want less than them.
Makes you wonder, don't it? Yeah,
it's the same people every day.
So, you know, when you say this is a
copycat community, who's copied me then,
Greasy? So, which people have copied me?
I'm kind of tempted to message that
church person that I met,
but then it ruins the collection, isn't it?
So, who has copied me then?
No, I don't want to message them. I just
want to collect, you know.
Yeah. So, who's copied me then? Grezy,
you must can you name like two people
that's copied me?
Yeah. And who else was he has is he the
only one that's copied me or was there someone else?
Yeah, it's a copycat community.
Yeah, it is a copycat community to be
fair. And my holidays get copied as
well, don't they, Greavvesy?
My my uh my my holidays get copied, right?
Okay. Okay, Indigo. So why did nonsex go to Amsterdam?
copycat in it. What's the chances,
Greavesy? There's 195 countries and
loads of different cities, right?
And you just ended up in the same one I
went to the first time you went away.
Doesn't that seem dodgy to you, Greasy?
Does that seem ultra dodge?
That's really dodgy, bro. Probably.
But well, I didn't see one. I only went
to Well, yeah. But
yeah, what's she going to What's she
going to say, bro? I mean, a lot.
No, I didn't.
I didn't get one. No,
long story, but no, I didn't.
No, they were being entitled [ __ ]
Yeah, it was really bad, bro.
Nah, it's just I don't think Greavvesy knows either
cuz Grevy fell asleep.
They're even entitled as well. Grezy
this they don't make they don't make
sense here cuz Grezy the thing is yeah
they provide a service Grezy for
customers. Yeah that so they're
providing a service which is supposed to
be simple but they make it the most
awkward difficult thing and they've got
stinking attitude. It doesn't it doesn't
make any sense.
And then they try to dictate to you when
they're offering a service. How how can
you offer a service and then start
dictating to people? It doesn't make sense, bro.
It's just weird. But anyways, it's just
all negative, bro. I don't I don't
really want to talk about it to be honest.
Double copycat. Yeah.
And and the curries as well.
Oh, I can't be bothered to get into it, bro.
And Grezy, don't remember. Don't forget.
Yeah, he done a curry challenge. Then I
done a curry challenge. No, he we we No,
I done a Grim Reaper. I done a Coline
Um, Grey, I I I done a Caroline Reaper
challenge and then LJ done a curry
challenge. Then I done another curry curry challenge.
Is that copying
What? It's uh it's copying is it? Yeah. Indigo.
So why did Nleg say um
Shel Cole was good-looking?
It's a copycat. Really?
Why did she say that she's good-looking?
Didn't she say that she's Didn't he say
that she's good-look?
Basically, I went to this Esco house and
she said that she doesn't give a [ __ ]
without a condom and [ __ ] And then she
had attitude and then the other one had
attitude. And I'm thinking like, are you
providing a service or are you dictating
to people? Doesn't they just doesn't
make sense. I knew that was going to be
a thing eventually though.
And the thing is they were older than me as well.
One was like in their 30s, just so
entitled. I had to tell them about themselves. Grezy.
I literally had to tell them about
themsel, bro. And I did. And I'm
thinking, "Oh my god, bro. If this guy
didn't piss me off yesterday, I wouldn't
have even went out."
And she was being like really entitled.
And the other one was like, "Oh, I don't
I don't put it in my mouth without a
condom." And I said, And then the
security guard, he he opened the door
for me. Yeah. Greavvesy. And I said,
"No, no, no. Close the door now. Close
the door and I will leave when I'm
leaving. When I'm finished." Yeah. And
then he closed the door. He didn't even
try and say anything because obviously
there's always security there. Yeah. I
said, "Close the door and I will open it
when I'm ready to leave." Yeah. And I
just Yeah. I just shouted a load of
[ __ ] bro. And they they And I just left
basically. Yeah. But do you see what I
mean, Grezy? It's mad because that and
and one of them one of them look like in
their 30s, bro.
I know Chinese is he would never act like that.
The entitlement and with with these uh yeah
the entitlement bro is mad
with these um with these women bro.
You could tell by their attitude
yesterday when I was approaching as
well, bro. The attitude, like their body language.
Yeah. So, how is someone older than me
out their prime trying to dictate to me?
Just doesn't make sense, bro. But I
expected it because I mean, Thailand's
almost finished, so I mean I I expected
it, bro. To be honest with you.
I expected it.
Yeah. I said you I said don't open the
door. I'll do it when I'm ready. She was
shouting down the stairs saying um
saying about oh I don't do something in
my mouth. Bye. I said bye. I said I will
leave when I want to buy. And this
wasn't even the one I was asking. I was
like bro you you're not going to provide
say say that you provide a service and
then start dictating to people. That
doesn't even make any sense. Like you're
supposed to be offering a service and
then you're saying how you don't do
stuff without [ __ ] What the [ __ ] bro?
You know, it's mad. It's just It just
doesn't make sense this country, bro.
Yeah. Shut up, Joe. You're a little gay
keyboard warrior. You're irrelevant.
You little gay boy. No one cares about
you. Go suck your boyfriend's dick.
He won't charge you. He won't charge
you, lad. He won't charge you.
But no, bro. I like I said, I only went
out yesterday cuz this guy was annoying
me, bro. There was a reason why I went
out yesterday anyways. So,
yeah, she had a real bad attitude, bro.
But I'm thinking you're providing a
service. So, yeah. When you if you go to
escorts now, you're going to get bad experiences
seven out of 10 times.
You'll meet one, you will meet one like
that is not like that and but they're
very hard to come by nowadays. Trust me,
bro. And it's gotten worse over the
years because of the entitlement with
them. Um, they really got really bad
attitude. They they are worse than men
as a whole. They women are worse than
men as a whole. It doesn't matter if
there is good ones. Even if there is
good ones as a whole, women are worse than men.
Women are worse than men. Trust me, bro.
In in many many ways they are.
Think of think of it like this, bro.
You'll go to a pub, right? And you would
never get attitude from a man. You'll
never get a man thinking that they're
better than you. Never. Never. Never. It
would never happen. And not in a gay
way, in a normal way. You would never
have a man thinking that they're better
than you. Trust me.
So it's weird, bro. Never.
It doesn't even matter if there is good
women or not, bro. As a whole, they are
worse than men. Trust me. So yeah.
Yeah. And Yeah. And and the other one
that was given attitude didn't even see
me. And I didn't even see them. They
were shouting from like the toilet.
So, and the thing is the thing is Grezy. Yeah.
It's not like you're asking someone to
lick your ass, right? And recall them
licking your ass. Like, has anyone ever
watched porn before? Like, if you watch
porn, you would see that it's very, very
normal for people to start with [ __ ]
or get [ __ ] I mean, it happens
what, 9.9 times out of 10. You're not
asking them to lick [ __ ] from your ass
and you to recall them. you are. That is
literally a normal sex act. If they're
providing a service, right? Yeah. Then
isn't isn't that like part of the service?
I mean, they are, bro, but
that's being very very awkward.
I mean, and the attitude as well. And
it's not it's not about the boundaries,
bro. There's ways of saying stuff, bro.
You don't understand that. There's ways
of saying stuff. Yeah. And Yeah. They
don't I mean they don't have sex they
don't have sex without a condom, bro.
None of them will have sex without a
condom because of that reason.
I mean they don't have sex none of them
will have sex without condom. They never
have. I mean no one asked them to do
that bro. No. No. But the thing is Grezy
no none of them will ever have sex with
you without a condom. None of them will.
That's always been that way. No one's
ever said anything about that. But the
thing is Grezy um
you don't understand bro. Like there's a
way of saying stuff like there was what
and I don't even think they realize that
they're doing it. I was speaking to
someone yesterday that was sat on the
table with their friend, oh if you don't
mind I want to continue with like
talking to my friend. But it's the way
they said it. Like the attitude on them,
bro, is bad.
Like the attitude is there's a way of
saying things and they and I think they
don't where they're so naturally rude
they don't even realize they're doing it.
A lot of them are um yeah, they're
really entitled, bro.
Really, really, really bad. So, yeah.
I don't I didn't want to do it without
one, bro. Did you listen to the story?
No one wants to have sex without a
condom. We was talking about [ __ ]
We was talking about We was talking,
Bro, you don't get what I'm trying to
say, bro. We're not talking about sex
without a condom. We're talking about [ __ ]
Yeah. They're saying about how they
won't like have a have a [ __ ] about
condom when that's they usually always
do that. And also it's the way they're
saying it. All they've got to say,
Grezy, if they truly truly had
boundaries, all they've got to say is,
"Oh, I I I don't do that. Sorry." It's
the way they're talking and the way
they're saying it. You know, that's a
big thing. Do you not understand?
You know, it's like that person that was
talking to their friend, all they've got
to say is, "Oh, like not to be rude or
anything, but can I just like continue
my life?" And that's fine. It's the way
they say these things, bro.
Yeah. This is what I'm saying. That's Yeah, man.
Most of them are entitled, bro. They
really And the fact that people that uh
people that provide services for people
are acting that way just doesn't even make sense.
That's a normal s that's a normal act.
And then to say bye, it's like no, there
is no you don't tell me by. I'll leave
when I'm ready to leave. Um,
so yeah, I don't go out for that reason
anymore, bro. You know,
you tell me, Greavesy. Yeah. One man.
Well, if I'm disturbing them when when
you approach them, then there's a way of
saying Well, there's a way of saying
something. Or just keep walking. I mean,
there's ways around saying things, you
idiot. You know, if someone's
approaching me, I'm just walking away.
or I'm being nice and I'm getting out of
there. Simple as that.
You not see how there's a way of saying
things, you [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah,
they are proper proper entitled. They
are worse than men. I have I met a
couple of men um yesterday, bro, whilst
I was drinking and they do not have the
attitude that these women have. They
definitely definitely don't. Even though
they are [ __ ] a lot of them are
[ __ ] Uh they you you notice it is
literally women that are worse than men.
You don't get men thinking that they're
better than you, bro.
And you do not get men thinking that
they're better than you. Trust me, it's
a madness, bro. It's a [ __ ] madness.
And you know what's so scary is that
it's actually normal. Do you know that?
What's so scary is this is normal now.
This is actually normal,
you know. That's that's that's the scary
thing about that's the scary thing about it, you know,
and I try my best not to like escalate
things, bro. I'm getting out there
before like someone's insulting me or
something, bro. You know, so yeah,
it's bad. So that's how things usually
escalate was because of their attitude,
their [ __ ] disgusting attitude. But
then you got people defending them. This
is what I don't understand. You get
these white knights that defend them
when they are worse than [ __ ] men.
You know, they're [ __ ] literally
from the start. Like it's madness.
It is. It is mental, bro.
Bad. Bad. Bad.
You would have thought they would have
been defending men more than they're defending women.
But the thing is, Joe, people the thing
is Joe, people like your boyfriend, one
of your boyfriends, um, he thinks by
defending women and singing women, women
are going to like him and he's going to
be able to get with somebody that's not
disabled when it's never going to
happen. That's generally how these simps
think. That's how these white knights
think. They generally think by defending
women they could be 30, 40, 50,
they could still be virgins, you know,
and they would still defend women.
They're mad. They're nuts. They're
literally literally literally literally
nuts how their mind actually works. It, you know,
they will defend them even though
they're worse than men or the same as
men and women don't like them, but they
still defend them.
What the [ __ ] lad? When they're not
even in the [ __ ] right, bro. It's weird, bro.
But as a whole, like the people
yesterday, it was all right yesterday.
You know, there weren't many [ __ ]
out. The only [ __ ] were a few of
the women as usual, but you know, no one
trying to butt in people's business or anything. So, yeah. Yeah.
[ __ ] that for a game of soldiers.
Well, they don't get what they want.
They don't get women.
Well, they don't get women. They defend
women and women don't like them. But
they still defend them.
Look at on legs dating a disabled that
don't [ __ ] him. Not been with nowhere
near as many women as I have. So, if
anything, wouldn't I be the simp?
Uh, no, bro. I changed. I just changed
into my jeans.
Uh, in the ball I was in at first. Yeah.
But when I went to go to another one,
no, I just changed into my jeans. I had
them in my bag. So, no,
but the other bar was and the other pubs
and that, but yeah, there was just one,
but it was all right. I had them in my bag anyways. So, yeah.
Mad, bro. Mad.
In 10 years, it's going to be completely
impossible in Thailand as well.
Good luck to you. That's all I can say. Yeah.
It's bad, is it, bro?
It's bad, but it's normal. Yeah.
You watch any porn though, you watch any
porn, you see people get [ __ ] you
see people get sex, you know.
But that never used to be like that. You
go to that place, they would they would
give [ __ ] They would, you know,
they would do that [ __ ]
Like I said, it's only getting worse and
it's only going to continue to get worse.
this society is only going to continue
to get worse. Um,
it's not going to get any better. So,
you know, even in other countries, so yeah. Yeah, bro.
But then you'll come across like one
escort that's actually really nice.
You might come across one that's
actually like really nice, no problems,
but they're they're hard to find, you know?
And I noticed even ones that had their
numbers, they started becoming [ __ ]
as well, like via text. They started
becoming like proper [ __ ]
Um, there was well, I say some, I meant
I mean one. Um, they they were being a
[ __ ] like a couple of months ago,
even though they had met me like four
times. It's over, bro. Simple as that.
It's finished. It's washed. It's over, bro.
Yeah, I know. It's the way they act. I
had one say to me, um,
by I'm thinking, uh, you don't need to
be rude. And they swore by. I said, you
don't think that's being rude? So, it's
actually that concerning that they don't
even realize they're actually being
rude. They don't even realize it. That's
the most scary thing about it.
I mean, you can be rude if someone's
cold approaching. Yeah. But it just
proves the point about women then. It
just proves my point about women. Yeah. Being entitled.
They're more entitled than anything.
Um I'd say the word is more entitled.
But yeah, you go to that place like a
year ago, you'd never have these
problems. And if you was really lucky,
you'd get um Yeah.
But yeah, you can be rude out cold
approaching, but then it just proves it
just proves what I'm saying to be true.
I come across a couple of rude people yesterday
as in like entitlement and attitude, not
like what they said.
But yeah, they were
there's one before Indigo. Yeah, I was
with one before. Yeah. and they weren't
expensive and they said, "Oh, is
everything okay? Are you happy with
everything?" That's a service, bro.
That's a service that is supposed to be
provided to a customer. And there was
another one. And obviously the Chinese
one as well. So you you can well I don't
know about anymore but you know if you
was some of the time you you'd come
across them and they would treat a
customer how a customer is supposed to be treated
not start being entitled and start dictating.
Um that's just doesn't make any sense
at all. So
yeah, I told him about himself and I
told the security guard, "Close the door
cuz I'll leave when I'm [ __ ] ready."
And he didn't even say nothing. What
could he say?
It's mad though, is it, bro? It's not
even anything to be proud of, bro. It's
[ __ ] It's pathetic.
I I I actually was on the bus back and I
was like I was gobsmacked, bro. I I
didn't even know I could I didn't even
know what to say.
I don't even know what to I don't even
know what to say anymore, bro.
It's quite scary, isn't it? This is what
the world's come to.
Buying drinks, huh? What are you talking about, bro?
I don't know, bro.
I don't know. Do you know when I when I
you know when I cold when I cold
approach bro and they act like this?
Yeah. I just think to myself like after
the fourth or fifth one, I'm thinking
they can't complain about men. They
can't complain about dating being hard for them.
They they literally can't even ever say
dating is hard for them.
when Peter Belly's in town. They
literally cannot even say that. How can
they generally generally generally say that?
They can't even They can't even It's not
even comparable men and women's um
struggles on dating.
They don't have a right to call anything hard
when they're given chances and they're
not taking them. It's stupid, bro. It's
like me getting chances and not taking
them and saying that dating's hard. How
does that make sense? doesn't make sense.
There was one I was speaking to, bro,
from America. And it's like, and you're
just thinking to yourself that it's just
their loss. And it's a shame really
because they it is a shame because they
will complain about men and how men are
this and how men are that, but when they
come across someone that's normal,
they're not interested. So, it's
literally just their loss
just like it would be my loss to be
honest. You know,
it is strange. It is It is very very very strange
to be fair.
I had one I appro I approached one.
Yeah. And this one actually did have a
boyfriend and I said her friend said to
me, "Oh, you know, you're so sweet and
that, you know, for coming over and that." So,
but that person actually did have a
boyfriend cuz they showed me them. But,
so you can see that, you know, they can
complain about men all they want and
they can say dating is hard for them all
they want. But the fact of the matter is
they have been approached by someone
that's normal, right? And they're not
giving anyone a chance. So, they're not
in any right to complain about men. And
where I've approached so many people,
even sober, they they can't even say
dating's hard for women. I'm sorry.
They can't even say it's hard for them.
I'm I'm really really sorry. But they can't.
So that's that. But that one actually
did have a boyfriend cuz they showed
like they actually did. Bro,
there was one from America I was talking
to outside of Burger King.
You know, Lester Square, the Burger
King, if anyone's from London. And I was
talking to them for like 5 minutes and
then they just come up with some
[ __ ] excuse. And then it's like,
there you go, bro. you know, you're lost again. So,
it's weird, isn't it? It is weird. Strange,
but it's the norm, unfortunately.
So, it is the norm. Yeah,
I would have thought people would have
been inclined more to um
unless you're like fat and ugly and
[ __ ] bored, then I could then I could
understand it. But we're just not going
to get into this again, bro. Cuz it's just
the more you think about it, the more
how [ __ ] up it really is, bro. The
more like, you know what I'm saying?
You know what I'm saying?
The more you think about it, the more
that you get into it and then the more
you just realize it is just really [ __ ] up.
Yep. She was from America, bro. I swear
to God, I was talking to this person for
about 5 minutes and they live near me
and I'm thinking, "Wow, that's an
opportunity they've lost. That's their
loss." Simple as that.
You know, it's it is just so [ __ ] up, bro.
This so Yeah, it was next to the pizza
and I'm thinking, "What the [ __ ]
Don't they want to meet normal people?
Don't they w to like I don't understand it. So yeah, it's weird.
I don't like it, bro. When I was walking
in I don't like it when I was looking in
Leicester Square. When I was walking in
Leicester Square, they've all got that
look in their eye, bro. That westernized dirty look.
like that NPC look in their eye, bro. If
you look at my eyes, Yeah. they're just
like normal. If you look at my eyes,
bro, they're just normal.
You understand? They're just like normal.
Like dark eyes, but you see their eyes,
they literally look like NPCs.
You can actually see it in their eyes
how westernized they are. It's all that
Tik Tok. Maybe if I stop if I start
going on TikTok, my eyes will start
looking like theirs.
I'm not even taking a piss. I mean it,
bro. Their [ __ ] eyes, bro, are like,
what the [ __ ] They've all got that same
look in their eye.
But it's like a dirty westernized look, bro.
The eyes never lie.
Indigo. The eyes never lie, lad. Oh well.
And yeah, so Indigo, you even if you was
to find someone
um this is what we were saying earlier.
Even if you was to find someone, right?
Say you actually found someone that was normal. Yeah.
If you actually found someone that was normal, right, um
they would be taken. So even by the off
chance you found someone, say you found
someone, yeah, like one in a million,
they would have already been they would
already been took by someone. They would
already they would have already been in a relationship.
So yeah, it's worse odds than gambling really.
Not that I'm ever going to go back to
gambling, but you know, it's just the
odds are way. You just have no chance. Simple.
Just no chance, bro. So yeah,
it is strange why they wouldn't um want
to give someone um Yeah.
I don't waste my time with these
[ __ ] It was, you know, I went out
for a reason.
I I haven't been out for months. So
maybe I'll go out again in another two
months. [ __ ] knows.
I don't know, bro.
Know what I'm doing.
You loser. Bye-bye, mate.
My head's beating.
I'm coming off in a minute. I'll be back
later. Kieran said he'll be back.
Yeah, I gave up anyways, bro. I just
went out because there was a reason why
I went out, bro. I already gave up ages ago, bro.
And it seems like things are just dog
[ __ ] even more now in 2026. Yeah.
Oh, I just had some stress with
something. I'm not going to get into it.
Keep my [ __ ] head in. So I was like,
I'm just going to go out, mate.
It's good, you know. That's when it is
good, you know, sometimes drinking every
two months when got [ __ ] going on and
that and you just can't be bothered.
Just refresh the mind, you know,
otherwise you'll go insane.
But it wasn't just it wasn't just just
trying to uh get [ __ ] bro.
No, they're not worth
[ __ ] one of the day, bro.
And I feel like whenever if I get my
haircut, bro, I feel to go out. I don't
want to waste it, you know.
I don't want to waste the haircut and
the beard and
you know how it is. Huh?
What do you mean?
How good does that feel? Yeah. When you
need to go when you need to urinate and
then you finally urinate. You know, I
love that feeling. You know,
you know when you need to wee
and then you go wee. Oh, and you get
back into bed.
Bro, I'm probably going to go back to
sleep to be fair, bro. I'm tired, man. Oh, [ __ ]
Oh, [ __ ] me. Oh, man. Oh god.
I need to wait a little bit before I go
and sleep, I think. Ly.
Yeah. Anyways, I'm out of it. Yeah. And
I'll be back live later. Gan said he's
going to be on. So, yeah, man. I'm going
to sleep. I tried to go to sleep. Well,
in a bit cuz just ate and I don't I
don't want to wake up with heartburn. Horrible that.