Yeah.
Wonder if Kieran's um going to come on
like he said he was.
Yeah, I was on uh
chat uh what's it called?
I was on chat GBT.
You know, I think
it's good. You know, I agree with you. I
was on that chat GBT.
Do you want to know the verdict? Nah.
I said is did people used to say um Joe
Cole was attractive um
um to copy each other? Do you want to
know what it said?
But this is pretty accurate. Read it if you want.
He said, "Yeah, for some people
absolutely yes. Copying others was a
real part of it. When someone becomes
that universally praised, a chunk of
people don't stop to check their own
taste. They just mirror what everyone
else is saying because it signals
belonging in brackets. I get it. I'm
normal. I'm on the same page. It sounds
fiction." in brackets disagreeing felt
weird or contrion
is partly socially learned. Hearing I
quote, "She's stunning a thousand times
nudges your brain to agree." So for
those people saying Cheryl Cole was
attractive wasn't a deeply examined
opinion. It was more like repeating a
meme before we called them memes. That
said, copying doesn't mean no, nobody uh
nobody generally meant it. It just means
consents got in got inflated. Some
people loved her look instinctively.
Others kind of observed the opinion. Uh
no self-reflectives on this channel, lad. Um, yeah.
I said, here's another one.
Said, did people used to say Sh was
good-looking to fit in? Yeah, some
people definitely did say to fit in.
No self- affected on this channel.
So, it was to fit in then.
It was to fit in. Greasy.
Yeah, it's good. Uh, chat GBT is good.
I'm asking a couple of things.
Some people meant it, some people just
said it to fit in.
All right, so I messaged I couldn't help
myself. Greavvesy. And um basically uh I
I messaged the numbers. One actually replied. Yeah.
I couldn't help myself. Where is it?
And if you like her, despite the copying
culture, copying culture,
or or still like her now, that's your
own taste. Not borrowed.
Yeah, it's pretty accurate, isn't it?
Copying culture. I like that one.
This is a copycat community. That's why. Yeah.
Coffee and culture. I like that. Yeah.
I like that, Grezy. So, anyways, you
know, do you want to know what this
woman asked me, Grezy? She was like,
"Oh, when did you last um uh approach
women?" I said, "Oh, months ago
at line." And she asked me what my body
count was. And I just told her free.
Yeah, agrees. Yeah. I told her pack of lies.
It's the one that was talking about church.
You can see the westernity in their eyes.
They're NPCs, lad.
Yeah, you can you can see it. You can
see the westernity in their eyes.
Yeah. I said free. I couldn't help myself. Crazy. Maybe
maybe later I will.
Are they all the same? Pretty much.
Ed's not been live. Greavves.
You want me to um
Well, it's none of her business. You
shouldn't be asking me my body count.
She's all right in that. I've been
talking to her all day, Greasy, but you
shouldn't be asking people their body
count. That's none of your business, you know. Yep. Yeah,
because it's none of your because it's
none of her business.
I've actually been with six people
without escorts, but I just said three in it. Nope.
Well, it is. I've been with six people.
So, it is
uh and it would have been to her as well. So,
I prefer lion lad.
I want to ask the AI something. Wait
one minute. Shut up.
Copy and go.
What is typing?
No, I'm not a freak like you, Indigo.
Uh, too high.
Yeah. Do you know what's so funny? She
said to me, because if like cuz I have
to ask because if somebody's body count was 25,
um, you know, that's a nogo. It's funny
she mentioned the number 25, isn't it? you know.
Oh, no. You're not defending your
boyfriend today. Oh, very touchy about
your boyfriend being called a virgin.
You might want to do a cry me a [ __ ]
river song. Go cry some more. Go cry
some more about your boyfriend. DON'T
CALL HIM THAT. DON'T call him that. Is
going to love this. Yes, she did. And it
was free as well.
I said free.
People does don't need to know, bro. You know,
people don't need to know.
All right. One second.
I love asking AI things.
Well, obviously she does because she's
had sex three times, you [ __ ] [ __ ] So, yeah. Yeah.
I I asked I asked AI, right? Yeah, whatever.
Just cuz you can't cold approach women,
Joe, you don't have the balls.
Yeah, exactly. So, she probably died. Yeah.
Well, obviously I didn't tell her that,
did I? Why am I going to tell her that?
Certain people don't need to
Chinese brass. What are you talking
about? Chinese brass.
What the [ __ ] are you going on about?
Joe, at least at least I don't have to
resort to disabled like you and your
boyfriend that you touchy about. I can
actually meet normal women unlike your
boyfriend. And you can't even you can't
even deny that.
Hey, hobby eyed Joe with a 200lb phone.
You can't even deny it.
You can't even deny it. I've never had
to resort to disable like you and your
boyfriend. And everyone will agree with
that. You and your boyfriend that you're
touching about being called a virgin.
Hobby Joe with a 200lb phone. I can make
it rhyme cuz you're living in poverty
with your 200lb phone and your [ __ ]
skin. Your [ __ ] skin. 200 phone. Your
Poverty eye Joe with the 200 phone.
You know what I'm saying? Poverty eye
Joe with a 200lb phone. Why you not
crying over your boyfriend being called
a virgin? Are you done? Are you done
with doing that now? Are you done with
You done sucking dick for one day? Have
you finally come out, lad?
Finally come out, mate.
No. Poverty eye Joe. Poverty Joe with a
200 pound phone.
Get it right. Suck my [ __ ] dick. You
Oh, actually, no. I don't want you to
suck my dick. I'm not gay like you. I'm
not gay like you and your boyfriend. Not
legs. You and your boyfriend. You all
touching about each other. You need to
book that hotel room. You pair of gay
boys. Get it out your system.
Get it out your system. And you know
what? Yeah. If you actually do have a
partner, I do you know what it as much
as No, no. To be fair, as much as we
call you Nonlex's girlfriend, disabled,
right? And that I actually feel sorry
like you're actually gay and and you're
with you're with your MS and you're gay.
He's with these Mrs. and he's gay. Two
gay boys with a woman. Have you told
your partners you're gay?
Have you told your partners that you're
a [ __ ] They want they they'd love to know.
to make pictures.
Have you Have you told your partners
that you like dick and you're stalking a
man on YouTube every day? Tell them how
much you like dick.
They love to know, mate. They love to know.
They love to [ __ ] know.
Oh, you're very touchy about your
boyfriend, aren't you? Crying about call
him a virgin. You're very touchy, aren't
you? Sorry, I won't say anything anymore, mate.
>> No, you are an actual [ __ ] though.
Seriously, I'm not even joking. You
really are a [ __ ]
No, you actually are a [ __ ] You're
not the only one, though. Yeah.
Do you like um do you like AI's responses?
Uh that's not a key point.
And see you later.
Key point. What a nerd.
You people need to actually get a life, man. Honestly. Yeah.
You actually need to get a life.
I don't want you, Joe. I'm I'm not going
to give you my ass. So, leave me alone.
You and your boyfriend,
bro. That's why you used to use that
word a lot. Gay. Cuz you're gay yourself.
No, I don't. Bro, I don't to strip
Morgan. That's your boyfriend, though.
That's your boyfriend.
That's your boyfriend, bro. That was
[ __ ] stalking USA, Izzy, and [ __ ]
trying to get information. Not me.
That's your [ __ ] boyfriend who you
cry about when I call him a virgin. You
cry so hard like a little [ __ ] Oh,
don't call him that. I find it hard to
believe. You're very touchy about your
boyfriend. Very, very, very touchy about
a virgin being called a virgin. Very touchy.
very very very touchy about your
boyfriend. That's why I try not to
mention him nowadays cuz you get very
touchy and I almost feel bad and I feel
a bit sick.
So you got you you going to turn up to
Nottingham or not?
Are you going to turn up tonight again?
Will I go?
No, Joe. No. No.
Definitely. Definitely not. I love how
AI said that. They did say to fit in.
Greasy. That's mad, isn't it?
Oh, that's actually crazy, isn't it?
Copy copying culture.
Nah, I don't I don't stalk men online
like you, you gay bastard. No, we're not
all like you, hobby eye Joe, with a 200lb phone.
Nah, we're not all like you, you gay bastard.
You gay [ __ ]
Yeah, man. I'd love to see you in
Nottingham anyways when I give you a
week in advance, man. Show me about this
punch. Yeah, man. Show me it. Show me
it. I'd love to see it. I've got a I've
got a strong punch.
I've got a strong punch, mate. I [ __ ]
flaw you before you even put your hand
anywhere near me. You [ __ ] weak
bastard. I've got a strong punch and I'm
fast, bro. I'm bigger than you and I I
can tell you right now I'm foster than you.
Uh I was live, mate, and you was nowhere
to be seen. Yeah, stop embarrassing
yourself, mate. I was live and you
weren't there, you little [ __ ] And
this is exactly what you people do. This
is exactly what you people do, bro. I
was in I was in a pub rounder. Yeah.
Where was you? You didn't even come on
YouTube. You didn't even come on the
live stream. Where was you, you little [ __ ]
Where was you?
Where was you, man?
Brother, you wasn't even on the live.
Me, Steven Howard, UK asylum was on the
live waiting for you, you little [ __ ]
You wasn't even on the live when I was
live. You [ __ ] idiot. Shut up, gay
boy. Don't come on here now acting like
you was the one that that was on here
when you wasn't.
You little gay boy. And you're going to
do exactly what this [ __ ] weak [ __ ]
is going to do.
Brother, I was live. I was live. Where
was you? Where was you at 6:00
yesterday? Where was you at 6:00
yesterday? Cuz you wasn't on YouTube.
Shut up. Have a timeout for talking
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] You can have a
timeout. Come back in 5 minutes. [ __ ] [ __ ]
You're not about that life. You
Literally not about that life. You tell
someone you're going to meet them.
Someone goes live
and you're not on YouTube. Get a grip,
you sad bastard.
So boring, is it, bro? So boring.
So so so boring.
Yeah, man. And where's this Kieran anyways?
I knew I had something to tell him. Yeah.
Yeah. I went I was at Waxies yesterday,
Dusty. It was It was It was fun. Very very fun.
Made some new connections. It's great, you know.
Good old waxies once in a while.
Yeah, he did agree to meeting me. Yeah,
it was 6:00. You was asleep. I was live
uh until I think it was quart 6 and he
wasn't on here when he was supposed to.
Yeah, he did. Yeah,
he did agree to meet me. Yeah.
No, no, he did agree. Yeah. No, he did
Well, if he doesn't agree to meet me,
then he's a [ __ ] Simple. Well, if he
doesn't if this Joe doesn't agree to
meet me, and don't forget, he's closer
to Nottingham than I am. Then he's just
a [ __ ] And that's the end of that. He
is a [ __ ] If I can travel 150 mi away,
you can travel 70 mi away. Simple as
that. Why is Why have we always got to
go to these people for them to then come
up with excuses like the bomb, like
Trevor Dawson? I'm not doing it. I'm not
doing it because I'm not going purely
for someone on YouTube. It's as simple
as that. So, if you don't turn up, you
don't turn up. Simple.
There's a reason why I'm saying
Nottingham Greavvesy. There's There's a
reason for it. There's an actual valid
reason for it, as you know. So,
I'm not wasting my time and my money
going all the way to these people anymore.
like I did [ __ ] for god knows how
many years. So yeah,
nah. No way. Not a chance
for jealous ass ugly people on YouTube.
No thanks. Nottingham's an option though
because I'm going there anyways. So
which is why I said obviously smokey be
that's London is it? So I mean I I'll
just go there and then just have a drink,
you know. But yeah, there's no way I'm
going to leads when I already know
exactly what's going to happen. It was
the same [ __ ] with Trevor Dawson,
same [ __ ] with Bomb,
same [ __ ] with [ __ ] Arsenal Mark.
It's the same [ __ ] with them.
So, what's it called, Grezy? Is it a copying culture?
Stop trying to bring LT up, bro. You're
not going to get what you want. You're
wasting your time, bro.
You're literally wasting your time.
Don't even try to [ __ ] sto. It's not
going to work. Yeah.
Yeah. Speaking to this person all day. Um, Greavvesy.
Quite good, is it, bro?
No, I haven't haven't been at it to be
fair. Haven't tried. No.
Yeah. Just stating. Okay. Okay. And who
have you met on here? Who have you had smoke for?
Who have you Who have you had smoke for
in this community? No one. Just shut the [ __ ] up.
Literally just shut the [ __ ] up. Yeah.
It's funny as [ __ ] is it?
Yeah. All good, man. AI is funny as [ __ ]
Yeah. I'm just happy collecting the figures. Yeah.
AI is funny, bro.
It really is funny. copying culture
don't seem that way on it. Don't it grooves?
They said that they used to say she was
fit so people wouldn't call them weird.
Reeves because they didn't want to be
called weird. You see
that's what AI said.
Not much, bro.
Not much. I didn't spend much yesterday.
I asked the manager could think he come
but it's still no virgins.
He's very strict about this no virgin
policy greasy. I don't know why. Just no skin virgins.
Simple as that. So sorry mate I tried.
It was [ __ ] chocker, was it? Waxies
dusty. It was [ __ ] choa block. Yeah,
we It was choa block, wasn't it? You
know what I mean? It's cha block. Bless
you. Oh, bless.
Oh, bless y'all. Oh, man.
Where the [ __ ] is this Karen, man?
Still off the I'm still off the
gambling, John. Not going back to it.
Yeah, I'm off it, bro. I'm not going
back to it either. [ __ ] that. Yeah,
I'm done with it, Dusty.
Greavves is going to miss that. Ain't
it? Greavves used to like me gambling.
used to like the reactions and the
madness, didn't you, Grievy?
Also, people used to copy my football
bets, didn't they, Grezy?
The little copycats. Little copycats.
One second. You've done
the rough with What will happen if I do
the same bet as you, Dusty?
Could I do the same bet as you? Exactly
the same bet.
Obviously, I have to run it by Greasy first.
H, that seems like a good bet. I might
do the same one.
Yeah, I have. I'm talking to someone.
We've been talking all day.
No, I didn't spend much yesterday. It
wasn't a waste of money. I wanted to go out anyways.
No, it wasn't a waste of money. I didn't
even spend much.
Yeah, but I'd have to run it by [ __ ] uh
I need to run it by Grezy first.
Can I um do Dusty's bet?
Can I do Dusty's bet? Greavves.
Yeah, I know he's trolling me, but it's
funny as [ __ ]
Of course, I know he's trolling me, but
it's just funny, isn't it?
I'm only joking, bro. I'm not doing any
gambling. I was taking a piss.
And you do realize I'm trolling all of
you people as well in a way.
Think about it, bro.
Think about it. But I'm a smart troll, aren't I?
I'm not trolling with everything, but I
am I'm I'm also trolling the audience
like what Seaside Like what Seaside Mark
used to do.
No, not not what you think. UK asylum.
Nah, I'm being serious about collecting
women and that.
The only reason why I'm not trying to
[ __ ] this number up I've got is because
this is someone that I've actually
approached, bro. And it's so hard to
[ __ ] get a number that replies back
nowadays. So, I'm not going to
I'm not going to do it just yet, you know?
Oh, Dusty, I went on AI and I asked about uh
uh Chev Car, man. It was funny as [ __ ]
Yeah, I went on AI chat GBT.
You should have, bro, you should have
heard what it said. It's funny.
It's a good site that
I love that you know. All right, Dusty.
I was getting my haircut yesterday and I
was thinking of some of the things Greavvesy said.
It was making me laugh,
you know. So embarrassing
when he said there's a copycat community.
I don't know why, but this makes me laugh.
I think I think it's the community bit. Yeah.
Do you want to do you want to um know
what AI said, Dusty?
Oh, no. Just some guy I uh
used to meet. He was um saying that she
was attractive to f
Yeah, I've got an AI on it, bro. Oh [ __ ] Yeah. Look,
look what this said. Listen. Listen,
Dusty, right? This is another a
different Wait, bro.
The people used to say Chev Cole was
good-looking to fit in. Yeah, some
people definitely did say it to fit in.
This is AI, by the way. When Chevro call
hit peak fame, calling her good-looking
became a kind of social default. It
wasn't always carefully a carefully
thought out opinion. For a lot of
people, it was a way to blend in with
the crowd. An easy low-risk opinion
everyone agreed on. Something you
repeated because everyone else was
saying it. Those are like they're the bullet points.
No, waxes is good, man.
I met an American yesterday, Dusty. She
was from Boston. Her little words was cute. Greavvesy.
I said that's not English what you're
speaking you silly goose. I met her in waxies. Greavvesy.
I met her in Maxis
on a couple of approaches.
Uh, it's good, but it's just it is a bit
too uh busy there. But yeah,
it was busy for Thursday on in February
to be fair.
Her and her little words greasy.
I when she couldn't hear me, she was
like, she was like, uh, what is it? Oh,
bless you. You in your little American ways,
Grezy. Is that cute?
Yeah. But do you know the thing is
that's good about Thursday, Dusty?
There's less [ __ ] Like you
actually meet more like genuine like
people. Like I'm saying generally, bro,
because Saturday is just full of
[ __ ] It's too busy and full of
When you go Thursday, it's just right. You know,
I still am captain. It's just full of
[ __ ] Whereas Thursdays is good,
man. I didn't come across any [ __ ]
Well, the women were [ __ ] some of
them. But, you know, I didn't really
come across many. It was It was all
right, bro. They all seemed all right. So, yeah.
Oh, I had a Chinese G we
had savoy chicken fried rice and some
barbecue spare ribs.
Oh, Grezy. Um, uh, Dusty put a football
bet up that he's doing for tomorrow, and
I was thinking of doing the same one as him.
I don't know what your opinion is on
that, but obviously I have to let you
know things, you know, I can't let you
not know about things because obviously
you're part of this channel, is it? Uh,
don't know what your opinion on that is.
I'm going to do the same bit as him. Yeah.
So, even AI is saying that people used
to do it to fit in. Greavvesy.
A way to blend in with the crowd.
Creepsy. That's what it says. I'm not
lying. A way to blend in with the crowd.
An easy lowrisk opinion. Everyone agreed
on something you repeated because
everyone else was saying it.
Oh, Jesus Christ. This is too funny, bro.
Yeah. So, I'm allowed to um copy Dusty's bet tomorrow, Grezy.
What? Ed hasn't been live for a little
while, has he? copycat community. Yeah.
Yo, I only like the the Northern League
and the South League.
I agree with you. Do you actually think
I'm a troll? I'm not a troll, bro. I
don't know why UK calls me a troll. I'm
not a troll. What do I do that makes me a troll?
What the [ __ ] do I do that makes me a
troll, bro? Come on.
Never tr my life, lad.
Yeah. What's wrong with play? Yeah.
What's wrong with playing with with
Lego? So what? Because I play with Lego,
that means I'm trolling.
Nah, not me, Greavvesy. I'm innocent. Bless you.
I used to like you, Grezy, when you
called me a big fat stinking copycat.
I used to like that, Greavvesy. But what
I don't understand, Greavves, is why
don't you troll anyone else? Why is it only me?
Why is it only me you go for?
You got LJ, you got Virgin Boy,
you got Timmy.
Don't know why you only go for me.
Yeah, but what about [ __ ] Virgin Boy and [ __ ] um LJ?
Yeah, I agree with you. I think I
remember you used to say Kerry and Rice.
You went on Monty's and said Kerry and
and Rice, isn't it?
Yeah, I was just about to say that. How
about Seaside? Yeah.
Yeah, you can. Of course you can get a
reaction from them. Of course you can.
If you was if you was trolling them, of
course they'll react to you.
So if I do a football bet right
tomorrow, Reeves and I put it on my
community post, what will happen
if I think of my own one and just put it
on, you know, the community post.
What's going to happen, Grezy?
I'll do a nice little football mat put
on my community post.
What do you think will happen?
What do you think, Dusty, if I do my own
football bet tomorrow and I do a community post?
Oh, that's yeah, that's exactly it,
John. But he has come up with Yeah, that
is true. But he has actually come up
with funny stuff, John.
You know, it's a copycat community.
He come out with that.
So yeah, but is anyone going to copy it?
This is what I mean, bro. That AI made
me piss myself, bro. I didn't think AI
was going to say that.
A way to blend in with the crowd. Dusty
cuz it's funny seeing him say it with
his little Stitch picture.
Oh [ __ ] hell, man. Greasy's a
greasy is a clever troll. Yeah.
And what if agreed with you and what if
I go to what if I go to what if I go on
holiday to Egypt?
What will happen in the next 3 months?
No self-reflections on my channel. Um,
they're just Ling Mongs. But what if I
go to Egypt
on like a little holiday
and I come and I come back in 3 months
and go on people's and go on people's channel. Crazy them.
No, it's not even funny to be honest,
bro. It isn't even funny.
That's very [ __ ] weird, bro.
No, it got to a point, John, where like
I couldn't even like I had to keep my holidays private
cuz if I went somewhere, someone else
would go there, John. Yeah, bro. It
actually got bad. No trolling.
Actually started copying places I was going.
[ __ ] weird, bro. Weird as [ __ ]
So weird. Dusty
going somewhere just because someone
else went there. What the [ __ ] Yeah,
that's why I kind of like keep that [ __ ]
private now. [ __ ] in a couple of days
you'll be seeing someone in waxes. Grezy.
Yeah, there was this one there was this
one guy uh I went to Amsterdam, right, John?
And literally um the first place he went
was Amsterdam. Not straight away because
obviously he couldn't afford it because
he's skinn. Um but like as soon as he
could think about it, bro, what's the
chance that someone else's first holiday
is [ __ ] Amsterdam? There's 195
countries and think of how many cities
there there is.
No, I'm not out tomorrow. Well, I'm
going to try and get this person to meet
me, but nah. If not, then no. Uh-uh.
No. I I drunk yesterday for a reason. I
went out for a reason yesterday. I was
[ __ ] pissed off. It's not a regular
thing, but yeah.
Why would I go there?
Why the [ __ ] would I go there, bro?
I've been to lad.
Yeah, it's that one that was obsessed
with me, John.
He's obsessed with me. Yeah, it was one of them.
Yeah, that wrong in um media. Yeah, I
think I just think that they're closeted gays, John.
You got Jo, you got him, you got Jamie
Thompson. I think they're just closeted gays.
No, I'm not drinking tomorrow, bro.
Don't really like drinking that much. Yeah.
It does seem strange, doesn't it, John?
And the only reason he can't get into
vaccines is because there's a no virgin policy.
So, virgins are not allowed to go in
there for some reason. I don't know why, but
they don't allow virgins.
I'm not obsessed with that [ __ ] I just
message her. She replied back straight away.
This is looking good, bro.
There's no [ __ ] ups.
with that virgin. Dusty, I don't I don't
have a channel dedicated to [ __ ] any
of these people, do I, John?
I don't have a [ __ ] channel dedicated to them.
[ __ ] obsessed with that little version.
No, lad. I'm not obsessed with them.
They're obsessed with me, bro. I don't
have a channel dedicated to them. I
don't do community post to them. I don't
do videos to them. They're the ones
They're the ones that obsessed with me, bro. Yeah.
I think they're closeted gays, John.
Doesn't matter if I react or I don't
react. What's What What does that What
does that mean, bro? You could leave
YouTube and they'd still do it every
day. So, does it does it really matter?
Whether you react or you didn't react.
I mean, they never stop. They will never
ever stop anyway. So, why does what
what's that matter?
Like I said, John, I think even if you
left Ju for 2 years, I don't think they
would stop, bro. The only time they'd
stop is if they were dead or in prison.
No, it doesn't bother me. I'm just
saying what they are. They're gay.
People are allowed an opinion, bro.
People are allowed an opinion. And the
fact that they've got a channel
dedicated to me shows that I bother them.
If they're if they're doing community
posts and doing videos on me every day,
doesn't that show you that they're a
little bit more bothered by me than I am them?
But yeah, no, John, unless they unless they die
or they go to prison. I feel like that's
the only way they'd stop, bro. They
would never ever stop. Ever.
Never ever ever stop. Cuz like I said,
where they're so obsessed, they will
literally think that you're reading and
they actually think certain accounts on
me as well.
Obsessed people never stop, bro. Trust me.
Obsessed autistic people never stop.
No, I don't care.
No, I don't really care. Yeah,
I told you, bro. I can stop gambling at
any point, John.
Told you, lad.
See you later.
No. autistic self projectors on my channel.
Bro, you do realize you're wasting your
time even trying that because it's not
going to work. The management changes
all the time.
So, it's not going to happen.
Sad bastard, bro. That's another thing
they do, and I do this on purpose. Uh
that's another thing they do, John. If
you show that you go to a place share
like say for example you go to a
um like a pub. Yeah. They will try to
find out the pub and try to get you
banned because they're sat at home. No
life, no money, nothing going for
themselves. That's what they do growing here. Absolute wasters.
So they'll call up the place and say,
"Oh, this person and oh that person and
oh this person." But the managements
change all the time.
Like literally all the time it changes.
So they're literally wasting their time
even doing that.
I think it's sad as [ __ ] me. Greavesy.
They done it with side mark as well,
didn't they? I think it's sad.
That is some sad coward [ __ ] That is,
bro. And in London, the management
changes all the time.
Yeah, they do it on kick.
we're still talking to this church. Um person greasy. Yeah.
Is that what you mean? Like
kick stream is getting it greasy.
That's what you mean, is it? Kick streamers.
Yeah, they get a lot of [ __ ]
They get a lot of [ __ ]
I heard that HS is a nons.
Apparently he's a pedo. Like he's he's
on a register. Is that true?
HS Tik Tocky.
I know he's been to prison, but yeah.
Have you heard about that?
I heard he's on the register.
H you know who he is then is it Greavesy. Yeah. 15.
>> Yeah. Do you remember when they got
swat? Do you remember when they were
getting that Ed Matthews swatted? Greasy,
did you see? You've seen it happen, in it.
You've seen it happen, haven't you?
I think yeah, I think a lot of people do
to be honest.
I see this thing where he went up to
this woman and said, "I want to taste you.
You want to taste? He said, he said, "I
want to taste you." And she started like
[ __ ] um blushing.
Funny as [ __ ] bro.
I don't watch HS, but I know who he is.
It's so funny. You saw that Indian thing though, Greasy.
It got heated, didn't it?
But she start that woman started it
though, Greasy. She actually started it.
Remember, she actually started it
because she said, "Oh, I date I don't
date Southerners." And he was like, "I
don't date [ __ ] northerners.
Then he was, "Oh, I don't do Indians."
But come on now, who actually started it
in all fairness. So,
think about it, bro.
And the indie guy was like, "That's clearly racist,
Grezy." He said, "Just leave us alone.
That's clearly racist.
That's so weird you saw that.
What did it pop up on um Instagram for you, Greavvesy?
Yeah. Did it make you laugh?
I said to her, "You don't like horror
movies?" She said, "I would if I was in
the mood, but never in the mood to be
scared." I want to say, "Oh, bless you."
I haven't said that yet
to her, but I might say, "Oh, bless you."
I might just say, "Oh, bless."
That's an all right thing to say and it
really are blessed. Right.
See you later, self projector.
I agree with you. Um, a new copycat
statement is going to be made tomorrow
around 11:00 a.m.
A new one's been generated. Greasy.
A new copycat statement.
Yeah, around 11:00.
So, what if there's been no copycat
statement made for ages? What will
people do, Greavvesy,
if it's if it's been like on this
community, if it's been like a year and
there's there's not been a new one made?
What do you think will happen then? Nah,
they'll just wait.
They'll they'll wait. Yes. until a new
copycat statement has been made.
That's what will happen. No, they'll
just wait. They'll keep refreshing.
See you later.
They'll just keep refreshing um the YouTube page,
Grezy, until one's been made. Is that right, Grezy?
So, wait. If they found another
community, then what would they do, Greavvesy?
Just chilling. Steven Howard,
we've got a new Izzy to the collection.
Yeah, we found a new one
that we're talking to. Steven Howard.
So now find a new community and then what?
I love it, bro. What t-shirt by Grezy? Quezy, Dad.
So, what will they do? Find a new
community in Denmark.
Yeah, Greavves, you answer the question.
Okay. Greasy. And what will happen? And
what will happen if I go to Egypt? Then what? Greasy. Yeah. Heat.
Copycat statement. Grezy,
you still there? Steven Howard.
Yeah. You know the O'Neal's Water Street, Dusty?
I walked past it yesterday. Same front
door bounces, same management. That's
the only place where it never changes, Dusty.
The only place where it never changes. Yeah.
Look at Greasy waiting. He's going to
stay up, aren't you, Grezy? You're going
to stay up all night until 11:00 in the morning,
aren't you? for the next copycat
statement. I know you better than you
know yourself, Creepsy. It's a copycat
culture community. I know what you're
gonna do. Yeah,
you got to copy. Yeah. Oh gosh.
Yeah, your alarm is set. So, what
grooves you're calling nonslegs a a big
stinking copycat then?
So, he's also a copycat then with the
Amsterdam thing, right?
Well, you're brave saying that, Greavesy. One second.
What will happen if I go out drinking
tomorrow? Steven Howard.
Oh, the t-shirt. I've just checked my email.
No, I don't like that t-shirt. Hopeless.
Why do you love Stitch so much? Greasy.
How am I a troll? UK asylum. Can you
please explain to me how am I how am I a troll?
Why am I troll UK silent? No,
I collect Lego UK asylum.
I was joking, bro. I'm not a troll.
I'm not a troll at all.
What's going to happen UK sign him if I
put football bet up to up tomorrow my community First,
what happened up in you guys?
That LJ is such a loser. Steven Howard,
anyone that rings up places.
Anyone that rings up places to try to
get people banned, they're losers.
They're [ __ ] losers, bro. No.
What would you do, Grezy, if I got I got
back into the gym?
Then what? Grevy.
All right. Do you remember that account,
Grezy? Poor [ __ ]
Graves, you remember it?
Oh, [ __ ] I wonder where I wonder
where he is in life now.
It's so mad. It could be literally
anyone. It could be an old man. Imagine
who it actually is. Greavesy. Could you
imagine? Cuz it's got to be someone. Poor [ __ ]
I might go to Legoland. I might go to Legoland Greezy
and do a video. Yeah.
What you want me to to say? What you
want me to go to? Um Disneyland, we
would be lush. All
right, Kieran, did you see what LT was doing?
LT was being biased. You saw it all,
didn't you, Kieran? He was doing the
girlfriend thing again.
He was when I was calling him a virgin.
Yeah. LT com on my live stream saying,
"Oh, um, he was saying, "Oh, well, yeah,
he's got a girlfriend and that." And
they said, "Oh, you don't say anything
when I show me get my dick sucked and
that." Yeah, you little dick sucker.
I was emailing him and that. He was
being biased like what Joe F does. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Did you see it? I done a video on it,
bro. Like a [ __ ] like two weeks ago.
Yeah, he he's biased as well. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, I think a lot of these people in
here, bro, are [ __ ] uh undercover gays, lad.
A closeted gays.
Yeah. You've been off here for a couple
of months, ain't you?
Yeah. This is the copycat community, Kieran.
Yeah. I've stopped gardening again,
Kieran. Man, it was getting bad.
So what you're saying is do they so
every single person on here was guilty
of being a copycat? Grezy.
So what you're saying is everyone copies
one way or another. Like everyone Yeah.
What are you up to today, Kieran?
How do you know, Kevin? I am. Yeah, Um,
yeah, Dusty, go to Thailand before before before
that's finished as well.
Yeah, that's my advice.
Oh yeah, agrees. So what if I go to Orlando Florida
and I put it on YouTube? Then what?
Then what will happen?
But you won't be able to doing that the
week after cuz he's [ __ ] skinned. But
maybe maybe 10 years later. Yeah.
Uh, did he just post it? Where? Oh,
this guy is so obsessed. For people who
might not be aware, he's pip was on the
third. He gets pip every four weeks on Tuesday,
but he doesn't know anything. One sec.
Why is he talking about when people get
their money when he literally doesn't know anything?
He shots a virgin in it, Kieran. in he Oh [ __ ]
Am I busy texting?
Am I busy texting? W there.
Why is he talking about when people get
their money when he doesn't know
anything? The skin little virgin.
Why Kieran at Joe F is another Lavry Mong.
He's another Ly Mong.
No, I'm not friendly with him, bro. He's
a non-legs lover. I'm not friendly with him, bro.
I'm not friendly with that [ __ ] He's a
two-faced little non-legs lover. Little bastard. Yeah.
I'm not friendly with that [ __ ] idiot.
Well, that's Well, okay, Dusty.
So, why is he not saying Okay, then if
that's the case, then why is he not
saying anything to him when he's calling
me a virgin?
Cuz I've proved I've had sex.
Yeah, it's the same argument, Kieran.
We've spoke about this before. No, I
don't like him cuz he's biased and he
talks [ __ ] behind people's back. So yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. And when he calls me a virgin,
Kieran Joe doesn't say anything about it.
One sec. Yeah, but when he calls me a
virgin, um, no one says anything, Kieran.
Joe just lets it play like an Elvis Presley record.
So why am I going to like a biased person?
I say to them, Karen, if a if a if if a
[ __ ] isn't sex, then a girlfriend
isn't sex. And ever since I've said
that, bro, they haven't been able to say
anything. If a porno isn't sex, then a
girlfriend isn't sex. It's as simple as
that. And what can I say?
>> One second. All right.
How do you turn auto correct on um
Samson Greavves? Okay. Nice. Earth. He
You live near Windsor, Karen. Yeah. No.
Greavves is a troll, lad. Grez is a troll.
What the real question is, Kieran, is
how can someone be a virgin that's shown
them having a [ __ ] and being in
women's beds naked? That's the real question,
not how can someone be a virgin that's
got a disabled girlfriend that can't consent.
I think that's the real question, lad.
Isn't that right, Kieran? That's the real question.
Yeah, I'm surprised that LT was being
biased, Kieran. Uh, I said to him,
"Yeah, I haven't seen you comment on any
of Virgin Boy's post calling me a
virgin." Then he started having a go at me, lad.
I said, "If you truly believe that
someone's not a virgin because they've
got a girlfriend, why haven't you said
anything about him calling me a virgin
millions of times?
He didn't like He didn't like the truth, lad.
Nah, he's not blocked.
He isn't blocked. He isn't blocked.
And is is Joe blocked? Joe's not
blocked, Kieran. Joe's not blocked.
We know Joe's not blocked. And we know
other people are are not blocked.
Showing a [ __ ] Showing a girlfriend
doesn't mean you've had sex.
Well, then showing a girlfriend doesn't
mean you've had sex. It's as simple as
that, isn't it, Kieran?
So, showing a [ __ ] and showing being
in women's beds naked and having them
admit to sleeping with you is not proof,
but somehow a disabled girlfriend is
that he hasn't even kissed on camera.
Care to elaborate?
So, so what is it then? You just stopped
at a [ __ ]
I mean, it's it's more proof than a girlfriend.
Um, and I think Kieran would agree with
me on that one.
Mad K is it lad?
Yeah, I know I'm wasting my time.
They're biased. And that's exactly
that's what I'm saying. Kieran, I don't
waste my time. They're biased. And LT is
biased. And Kieran, another thing. Yeah.
Kieran, another thing is he's been
biased with a couple of different things
as well. Money, police, they're all
biased. Even LT is biased.
But what I what made me laugh here with
with LT Kieran yet is he would
continuously complain about biased people. Right.
Yeah. He'd he would continuously
complain about people saying, "Oh, um
you know, uh people didn't believe I
went there and people believe I didn't
go there and whatever."
And then he's doing it himself. So, I
mean, he can't really complain.
Do you get me? Um, Kieran.
So, no, they are all biased, bro. They
are all biased, lad.
They are all biased.
It's weird, isn't it, though? It's
weird, Kieran, that they're like a nons,
isn't it? Cuz the thing is, Kieran, you
know, if you if I left for two years,
they would never stop. They would never
ever ever stop. You do realize that?
Like they would never stop, lad.
>> Yeah. I'm not, bro. I'm talking to her
right now. Yeah.
What's his name?
Yeah, I had a mad escort story
yesterday. Kieran, you probably figured,
didn't you? I only went out because some
guy was pissing me off and I had some
stress, so I was like, "Oh, I have to go
out and drink and shit." Sometimes it's
good, but I'm not I'm not going out tomorrow, bro.
You know, I look out
and LT is not blocked by non leg is not
blocked by non legs.
And I'm pretty sure you would have heard
it at least once before he was blocked. So yeah.
Well, she's not a Muslim, so I don't need to. No,
she keeps thinking that I'll cheat. Greavvesy.
Not keen thinking, but she just said
like she's had people she's had people
cheat on her, so she thinks that I'll
cheat. No, I'll never cheat.
I only stick talking to one person.
No, I'll only just stick to talking to
one person. Isn't that right, Grezy?
Yeah. Yeah. He's b Yeah, it doesn't
matter if he was troll or not. He's
biased. It's as simple as that.
And that Jo, lad,
that [ __ ] Jo,
bro. Kieran, he's the worst. Nope.
Mine, Greavvesy. All mine. Nope.
She's part of my collection. [ __ ] off.
You go out in cold approach if you want
to talk to someone.
Nope. Come on.
No, he is up Sean's. He's up his ass,
bro. He is up his ass. One sec. Hold on.
And someone call him