Sorry, bro. Someone was calling me.
Sorry guys, someone called me.
I'm too invested now, lad. Sorry, bro.
[ __ ] sake. Yeah, someone call me. Yeah. Heat.
Yeah. Sorry, bro. Someone [ __ ] called me. No.
What about me, Grezy? What about when I
was led on? Led on and used. Greasy.
Was that all right, Grey? When I was
love bombed and led on.
No, she's mine. All mine.
She said that she loves hugs.
Nope. You never find her. Nope.
I love hugs, too.
I love hugs. I love kisses.
Why do you want to know who she is? Creepsy. H. Nope.
I I'm not going to mess her about.
She might mess me about. [ __ ] losers.
Come on, Kieran.
How did you know I was texting them? Greasy,
you knew straight away in it. Where's Ken?
Do you actually think I would cheat on someone? Grezy
You should trust me a bit more. You can't you know
Yeah, it does.
Of course it does.
So, what do you want me to pass? Do you
want me to give her to you, Greavvesy?
You want me to give her to you?
And what will you do?
She will never Google me, mate. because
by that time she doesn't know my name.
No one's ever Googled me, bro, cuz they
don't know my name.
And they and and most people don't
Google people anyways. So
Sorry, man. Someone called me. So most
people most people don't Well, some people do,
but I've never had anyone Google me.
Never had any woman Google me ever that I've met.
Oh, what happened, Dusty? Is they will
find out once you've already met them
like a hundred times and by that time, Grezy,
they know you well enough. Do you understand, Grezy?
Say if someone found out that you said
mad stuff online before meeting you,
they're not going to meet you. Let's say
you've met someone a hundred times and
then they found out
they're more likely going to stay. Do
you get it?
You get what I mean, Grezy?
Makes sense? No.
What are you going to talk What? Yeah,
but you just want to talk to her about sex, Quezy.
You're just going to talk to her about sex.
And if she was all right, would you
would you would you go on a date with
her, Grezy? If she said, "Oh, let's go
on a date."
If she said, "After two months of
talking, let's go on a date."
God bless you then.
Yeah, I love hugs as well. Grezy, she
loves hugs. I love hugs.
But there was one time I was hugging
someone and kissing someone. Grieves and
I felt something in my toddy.
I felt something in my toger.
I don't know what happened. Oh gosh.
Yeah, you've been looking for someone
for a while now, Greavvesy.
Yeah, I would troll them and that, but I
wouldn't do it because I've actually had
to go out and approach. 23.
She's 23. Greavves. Is that too young
for me? 23? Nah. Nah,
don't think so.
Who was the other one?
Yeah, she's 23, lad.
Oh, self protecting. See you later.
Yeah. 23. Yeah.
I bet you'd sleep with an 18year-old,
wouldn't you, we
said, uh, you come across as genuine and
stuff. She said, "Oh, thank you. So do
I might say to her, "But what if you
what what I might I might message her
and say to her, but I'm scared you're
going to go and give other guys [ __ ]
behind my back."
Weezy, will that [ __ ] the whole thing up?
If I said that like we
scared that you're going to give people
[ __ ] in the toilets whilst we're on a date.
Nah. [ __ ] that, bro.
No. No. No. No. No. [ __ ] that. No way. Yeah,
maybe you could have a Christian baby.
So what will happen Greavesy if I go
live in waxies
and I start like pulling women and
kissing women what would the virgin do?
How would the virgin react if I start
getting numbers and hugs and kisses?
Would the greeneyed monster come out?
Greavves the virgin
would virgin come out.
I might do a stream like that, you know,
like a proper proper stream somewhere
where they don't know where I am.
Is that all right with you, Greavvesy boss?
And then the next day someone else will
be doing it.
So when I do a copycat statement,
Greavesy, people have got 24 hours to to copy it.
Oh, it's not valid anymore.
Yeah, she said I come across as genuine
as well, Grey. She said I come across as
nice and stuff.
Is that you? Where is he? Come on. Yeah.
Remember when I was with that 19year-old
Greavvesy? I stayed with her, didn't I?
I stayed with that 19year-old and I
Grezy. I never spoke or got with any
other women. Did I grieve? Nope.
I might have to know about USA. Is he?
So whilst we're talking, all I'm
thinking about is someone to to satisfy
my needs. Greavesy,
isn't that right, Grevy?
Yeah, she did do that though, didn't
she, Grezy? Do you remember when I used
to tell the dates I went on about her? Easy.
I got a [ __ ] in Nottingham before.
Straight after that, I was talking about her Yeah. There's Timmy.
Oh, he's another copycat. Griezy.
he's another one of poppies.
Is that right, Breezy?
Where got my haircut? When I've got my
haircut before Timmy's done a video,
remember straight after
Yes, she say that she had a nick that
cheated on her brie. there.
I didn't tell her about the escorts I've been with.
What if she don't know if I told her
about them? Greedy. Peace. Yep.
She pulled the connection we
Oh, come back here and
that's how this about USA. Is he dusty?
No, I haven't told her about any of my
bad experiences. She told me about her
ex, but I didn't tell her about any of my experiences.
I feel like people don't want to hear it in it. So
I used to tell dates about bad
experiences I had grievy.
Then I never heard back from them the
next day. Grezy,
I used to tell them
and then then I never ever heard from
them again. Grezy.
I haven't showed my Lego set yet. Griezy.
Oh my gosh. Look at it.
You think I should tell her that I collect Lego? Hello.
Hello. Who's this? Hello?
Are you all right?
I'm going to kick you now.
See you later.
I want Kieran back. hearing.
So I tell this woman about my Lego
found my YouTube.
I thought she found my Ship.
Now I want more.
Come on Ken.
Who's that virgin?
A little part-time job. Oh gosh.
What do you think, Steven Howard? Should
I tell her about USA? Is he? Hello.
>> Hello. Is this PJ? >> No.
>> Yes. You sound like you've done your
bollocks in my head. >> Really?
>> Yes. You've been on YouTube a while a
lot lately. Timmy, would you agree that
this is a copycat community?
>> I would agree that you need to sort your
life out. [ __ ] what Shauny thinks. I
talk my wheel voice now, PJ. I'm sick of
talking to you seriously because you
don't listen. People have tried to look
out for you. People have tried to care
about you regardless your behavior on
social media and you don't listen, PJ.
And you want what it is PJ White,
there's only so many times people are
going to tell you cuz it's like watching
paint dry, PJ. You know what it is,
Timmy? I'm sick of these [ __ ] I'm
sick of that virgin.
>> Yeah, but why don't you ignore him, PJ?
I've got [ __ ] trolls on my back. I
get V. I got [ __ ] Winchester. I get
all them. Do you see me reacting, PJ? No.
>> PJ, right? The end of the day, the
reason why people download your videos
for three hours a day and they've got
there's loads of channels on you because
you are the gift that keeps on giving.
You constantly constantly react. M.
>> So if I stop reacting, they'd go away.
>> Yes. It might take 6 months, PJ. It
might take 12 months, but they
eventually goes away. Why would you go
on about the same [ __ ] if the person
>> Stephen Steven Albert, do you reckon if
I ignore them, they'd go away? I don't
think so, bro.
>> Oh, PJ. Okay, PJ,
listen. Listen to me for once in your [ __ ] life.
>> What do you think, Steven Howard? Nah,
>> PJ, even if they don't go away, right? I
could be off YouTube for 10 years,
right? Winchester will go on about me
for 10 years getting the same old seven
viewers a day watching himself writing
to himself the same old [ __ ] PJ because
he's not getting a reaction because I'm
not responding to
>> Well maybe I'll maybe I'll maybe I can
call the police
>> but but I don't understand why you
[ __ ] do PJ because this is obviously
affecting me mentally.
>> Have you seen that account Timmy? Have
you seen that account? Um Jamie Thompson.
>> Yeah I think he's quite funny.
>> He's a [ __ ] Have you seen Have you seen
Have you seen what he looks like? Have
>> Yeah, PJ. It doesn't matter what he
looks like. The reason why he's winding
you up and listen to me for once in your [ __ ] life.
>> I'm winding him up. It's It's cuz you
constantly react to
>> No, but I'm winding him up as well.
>> You're winding No one at PJ. Can you
>> If I was If I wasn't winding them up,
Steven Howard, okay, if I wasn't winding
them up, they wouldn't have a channel.
They wouldn't have a channel about me
every day, would they? Steen and knock
him out clean. And don't be
>> If I Listen, listen. If I if I didn't
wind them up, then why do you have
channel being obsessed with me every
day? I must be winding them up. I must
be getting in their head somehow. Ste,
I've been trying to beat them for 10
years. You're just constantly going to
act like a child. No one's going to want
to know you. Your channel's going to
downgrade. They're going to get bored of
the same [ __ ] People get bored of the
same [ __ ] drama. The I mean, how old
are you per PJ? You're 30 years old and
you've got the mental you've got the
mental age of a [ __ ] 5-year-old PJ.
thing is PJ, right? You think I'm
criticizing you. I'm no lefty. I'm not
going to tell you what you want to hear.
I'm going to tell you what you need to
hear so you finally start [ __ ]
growing up. Right, PJ? Why do you let
words honest? I mean, I've done it for
10 years. PJ, talk to someone who's got
>> I can't I can't listen to him, bro. I'm
sorry, bro. He's He's talking [ __ ] man.
I can't I can't listen to him, man. Sorry, Stephen.
He's talking absolute bike, lad.
He's talking absolute [ __ ] lad.
What he's saying doesn't make any sense.
Steven Howard, sorry. I got to kick him,
bro. Because A, Steven, I don't react to
them. And B, bro, why? What is he even
talking about, bro? People reacting,
people not reacting.
Even if you listen, Steven Howard, you
you could ignore them, bro, for 15
years, right? Literally, you could not
come on YouTube for 15 years, right? And
then as soon as you soon as you go back
on it, as soon as you could literally
come off for 15 years, go on all of the
channels and they'd still be doing what
they're doing every day for in them 15 years, bro.
Because they do it because they're
mentally obsessed. They don't do it for
reaction. This is what I'm trying to
explain to the idiot. He doesn't get it, bro.
He doesn't do it. They don't do it for all reaction.
How do I not react? No, that's an
opinion. That's not an opin That's an
That's an opinion. I'm sure I'm sure
I've ignored some of these people for 6
months before Steven Howard.
So whether you react, whether you don't
react, they're never going to stop.
They're deranged, obsessed, jealous people.
They'll never ever leave you alone. The
closest you'll have to leaving you them
leaving you alone is if you left. And
even then, they would still try to do stuff.
They're mentally mentally obsessed.
There's a difference.
Me trying to get a reaction out of
someone is like it's like,
you know, trolling Monty on on a
hangout. Yeah. Or trolling someone to
try to get a reaction, a little reaction. Right. Um,
not what these people do. Do you understand, lad?
He's an idiot.
You absolute idiot.
My friend in Amsome said if you ignore
them for two years they'd go away. I
don't think they would, bro. I don't
think they would.
I think Lord I think the people on Lord
Jay's would go away. Steven Howard,
maybe L would go away. Maybe
some accounts, but the main ones will
never go, bro. They'll never leave you alone.
The jealousy, the obsession, they will
never ever leave you alone, bro. And
there's no point trying to explain this
to Timmy, bro, because he's a [ __ ]
idiot, bro. He doesn't He doesn't get
this. He doesn't He doesn't understand it, bro. You know,
it's like, but they went they went on
about the GV for ages. Steven Howard,
yeah, you know, the gov. They went on
about the gov for ages and then when he
went off YouTube, they stopped like
after like maybe a year. But the thing
is with him, he didn't have channels
obsessed with him the way that people
are obsessed with me. There's a big
difference. Do you get it?
These people are closeted homosexuals.
So yeah, it's um they'll never ever stop.
You can leave YouTube, you can be on
they'll never ever stop, bro. Just like
that. Jo will never stop. Yeah.
UK asylum. Yeah, Timmy's saying that if
I ignore them, they'll go away. UK asylum.
Yeah, Timmy's basically saying that if I
don't react to these people, they'll
they'll they'll leave me alone after a year.
Would you agree with that?
Would you agree with that, lad?
What? Even if I ignore them? Yeah. Okay.
So, what if I left YouTube? UK asylum.
What do you mean absolutely greasy?
Nothing. They've done nothing to trigger
me over um
They've done no one. None of these
people trigger me. They're just self projectors. Nah.
Nah. Like I said, maybe L J and people
on L J's channel will,
but people like Nons legs and Red Star
and No, no, no, they won't because they
actually try to [ __ ] with you off
YouTube. The thing is with these people,
Stephen, how they actually try to stalk
you off of YouTube as well.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. Them them three, four people will
never, but the other people will. Yeah,
maybe after a year, but not not the deep
deep obsessed people.
Well, no, they're not. They're just
going to they will just continuously
mention you and try to find you on other platforms.
like um no what they'll do is they'll
stalk you on other platforms and try and
find you on other platforms and they'll
still post about you, you know,
cuz I want to go live and I want to talk
to people. I don't give a [ __ ] if it
fuels them. It's nothing that they've
not said before. They're just repeating
little gay boys
because I don't give a [ __ ] about them,
lad. That's why I'll come on here as
much as I want and I don't care about
the little gay lords. The closet
homosexuals. Closeted homosexuals is not
my problem, bro.
That's their that's them, bro. So, I
don't give a [ __ ]
The They're closeted homosexuals. So,
why am I going to let closeted
homosexuals stop me going live?
You know, that's the way I see it. Yeah,
they're [ __ ] gay as [ __ ] bro. But
no, them four people, even after two
years, no, they would never stop, bro.
They would never stop.
I think what they would do, Stephen, I
would. Yeah, I think they would start
trying to stalk you in real life.
I think they would [ __ ] I think they
would try to [ __ ] with you in other ways. Yeah.
Yep. They've got no one, bro. And
they're closeted homosexuals, too.
Steven Howard, add that on top, lad.
Yeah, I'm still talking, bro.
She's sending me kisses as well. We
Who's falling into the trap? 23. Yeah, Peter. >> Yeah.
Lovely, isn't it, Greasy?
They don't know who they met yet, do they, Griezy?
They don't know who they've met yet.
Okay with you, boss.
Wooy. Is that okay with you, boss? Yeah.
I just want a baby pet. Grezy,
I've been love problems before. We
get yourself down to waxes, love.
No, but that I I like that little
American I was talking to a maxis.
She was like her little her little American dialect.
That little American dialect.
This is a copyc
I can't leave YouTube. I love Greavvesy
too much. I honestly think Yeah. If
Greavvesy didn't come on here, I don't
think I'd go live.
I love I love Greavvesy, man.
Oh, bless him then.
If I ever get married, Greavvesy, I want
you to be my my my best man at my
wedding. Is that okay, Greavves? You can
be the best man my wedding, Greavvesy.
Uh, this is a copycat community.
Is that right, Grezy?
You can come to the wedding
and if I ever have a baby, you can you
can be his uncle.
Do you remember the AI?
Oi. Um, Greavvesy, you didn't know about
the AI, did you? Basically, I wrote
something on chat, uh, DBT.
Do you want to know what it says? I've
already read it to you, Greasy B to Steven Howard.
It wouldn't be the same me going live
and not seeing that little Stitch
picture, Greasy, of yours. Poor [ __ ]
Oh, do you want to know what what it
says? Steen Howard.
So, I wrote on um chat GBT, right?
And I wrote, "Did people used to say
Shevel Cole was good-looking to fit in?"
And this is what it said. It said,
"Yeah, some people definitely did say it
to fit in." I can't even read this
without laughing. When Cheryl Cole hit
peak fame, Gordon Good looking became a
kind of social default. It wasn't always
a carefully thought out opinion for a
lot of people. It was a way to blend in
with the crowd.
An easy lowrisk opinion. Everyone agreed
on something you repeated because
everyone else was saying it.
Every time I read it though, it just it
just makes me [ __ ] laugh because mom,
I wasn't expecting that to say that.
I didn't expect it.
I didn't expect it. I didn't expect it.
A way a way to blend in with the crowd.
Oh my god. Well, that's going to catch
me when I'm on the bus. It's mad.
Way to way to blend in.
I asked B question. Yeah. Why did Neneg
say car was attractive? Do you remember
Greavves? And he said he said it to fit in.
Of course it does. But that's mad that
Why is it coming up like that on AI?
Think of it, Grey. Why is that coming up like that?
That's mad, bro. So, it is actually good
this AI thing.
But and there was also this one, Steven
Howard. I asked a similar view right
and they said yeah for some people
absolutely yes copying others was a real
part of it
when someone becomes that universally
praised a chunk of people don't stop to
check their own taste they just mirror
what everyone else is saying because it
s it signals belonging um in brackets I
get it I'm normal I'm on the same page.
It avoids friction.
Um quote um in brackets disagreeing felt
weird or contrarane. Um attraction is
partly socially learned here and I quote
she studied a thousand times nudges your
brain to agree.
That is [ __ ] funny as [ __ ] bro. I
might put this on my community post. So
for those people saying Shuko was
attractive wasn't a deeply examined
opinion. It was more like repeating a
meme before he called them memes because
they weren't me. They weren't memes back then.
That said um that said copying doesn't
mean nobody. Wait, let me read that
again. That said copying
that said copying doesn't mean no one
nobody generally meant it. It just means the conscious
got inflated inflated. Some people love
her and others kind of
absorb the opinion of her.
Oh bro, I can't even read that with a straight face.
Let me ask another one. One second.
What was that? One second.
Just chilling, bro. Yeah.
Is it possible for someone have a girlfriend
and be a virgin?
Um, yeah. I'm speaking to someone.
I got five numbers and yeah, true
replied I'm speaking. But it's getting
worse though, truth talker. It's getting
a lot worse.
The women's attitude and the entitlement
and that it's getting a lot worse.
Oh, okay. So, yep.
Here we go.
Yep. Absolutely possible
and way more common than people think.
People assume girlfriend equals sex, but
real relationships don't work on a
single script um on a single script.
Someone might have a girlfriend and
still be a virgin because they're young
and just not there yet. They're pretty
young. Um they or their partner are
waiting by choice, personal values,
religion, or just comfort. The
relationship is new. The asexual low li
uh libido are still figuring things out.
Okay. Uh they are long distance or
logistical barriers. One or both have
anxiety, trauma or health issues.
So it's saying here
that is possible for someone to be a
virgin that's got a girlfriend. Now let's see is
is it possible for someone who's proved
Okay. So, it says if we're using the
basic literal definition of virginity,
someone who has never had sex, then no,
if it's generally proven that they've
had sex, they wouldn't be a virgin by definition.
That's what it says. So
why do people
This is I like this, you know. This is cool.
No, he hasn't. We don't know if he's had
sex, bro. There's no proof. A girlfriend
is not proof,
bro. And we we don't know that, bro. We
can't say for sure, lad. He could have
no dick. He could have erectile dysfunction,
you know, that might be his carer, not
his girlfriend. We don't know if he's
had sex, bro. But we know that I've had
sex cuz I've proven it.
But no, no, no. We don't know that he's had sex.
We don't know that for definite, lad. To
be fair, unless someone's actually
proven it like I have.
So this is what it says. I I I I put why
do people used to say you're gay if you
don't find Sher Co attractive?
And it says ah this is classic social
signaling and peer pressure in action.
And it's less about Sher Car
specifically and more about how people
how people please taste and identify.
Here's why it happened. One, conflating
attraction with identity. For many
people, saying if you don't find X
attractive, you must be gay was a
shorthand for you're doing something
socially unexpected. It wasn't literal.
It was a lazy tease a way to pressure
comfort comfort confirmity.
Um, group think group think and social
confirm can't even pronounce that word.
Sher was heavily hyped up as a natural
beauty icon in the UK. Saying you didn't
think she was attractive, marked as you,
I quote, different. teasing you as gay
was a socially safe way for peers to
call you out without directly insulting
you in brackets. Ironically, it's also
homophobic, but that was often overlooked.
Bottom line, it wasn't really about
Cheryl Cole. was about using a
highprofile celebrity as a social litmus
test for confirmity, masculinity
or heterosexual norms.
So basically saying it was to fit in.
Oh, bro. Oh, I swear to God. This is
what it says.
You're not going to believe what this
says, bro. Hey, bro. You're not going to
believe what this says. Did
did did people like did people like
Harry Styles to fit in?
Yes, definitely. In many cases, just
like with Jew,
a lot of the admiration for Harry Styles
wasn't purely personal attraction.
Social pressure and cultural influence
played a hu played a huge role.
bandwagon effect group think
how many styles was everywhere music TV
magazine social media saying unlike
Harry Styles was a was a was a socially
safe way to align with peers especially
in teen or young adult circles if
everyone else loved them it was easier
to nod along nod along than admit indifference cultural
signaling. I told you. Yeah. Cultural
liking Harry. S like Harry could signal
that you were I quote in the know or
part of pop culture. Teenagers
especially use celebrity fandoms to show
belonging. Media amplification.
Media constantly framed him as charming,
stylish, and attractive. Even if
somebody wasn't strongly drawn to him, personally repeated
exposure makes it feel natural to say
you like him.
I didn't see avoiding ridicule in school
or online group. Saying you don't like a
popular celebrity can lead to teasing.
Some people say they liked him just to
avoid the feeling of left out. Oh my
god, I'm dead. Oh wait, wait. Let's read
that bit again. Read. Wait, let's read
that bit again. Some people say they
liked him just to avoid feeling left out.
It's here. It's in black and white.
Many people truly liked him. But in
every large fan base, there was always
some who who are one second. One second.
Many people truly liked him. But in
every way large fan but in every large
fan base there were always some who are
performing like him as much as they
actually do. Especially when socially
acceptance is at stake. Wait what?
Wait wait wait wait.
previously it said especially when
social acceptance is at stake whatever
I can't I can't this is killing me this
is this is killing me is [ __ ] killing
me I'm lying
I told you it was it was a trend back Bottom line,
bottom line, liking Harry Styles uh
brackets or Sher Cole or any pop star
was a mix of genuine attraction and social confirm.
The more fishbone praised the celebrity,
the more peer influence shaped public opinions.
If you want like a breakdown, how much
of celebrity love is usually
performative versus genuine using some psychology
psych psychology and research? It's
actually fascinating. Do you want me to?
It's not let I want to press Yeah, but
it's not letting me.
Social acceptance is at stakey.
Is that Yeah, it's not letting me.
Oh, do you just type yes? If you want, I
can break down love. It's not letting
me. Do I just press yes or
social acceptance is at stake? Well, I
just press yeah. Okay. Okay. So
perfect. Let's dig into it. I'll break
it down carefully. When we talk about
how much celebrity love is, I quote,
genuine versus performative.
Psychologists and sociologists
often focus on social influence, identity
signaling, and media effects. Here's the
breakdown. Could you imagine Monty reading this?
Rezy one genuine attraction. Um dash
fandom. Some people generally like a
celebrity because of physical
attraction. They find a celebrity's
appearance appealing. Personality.
Personality or charisma. Celebrities
often seem relatable, funny or kind
through interviews, music or TV. Artist
talent, music, acting or creative skill
can trigger admiration. Emotional
connections. People may associate a
celebrity with nostalgia. Personal
growth or meaningful media moments.
These are true personal feelings
independent of peer pressure.
Right? Are you ready for this? Excuse me. Two perform
performative fandom social confirmity.
Some people I quote like a celebrity
mainly to fit in or avoid judgment. This
happens because of peer pressure
especially among teens and young adults
and not young adults. Not liking a
popular figure can build social
can feel socially risky. Group identity
band can signal belonging. For example,
I love Harry Styles. I'm part of this
friend group or cultural moment bad
ragged effects. People often adopt the
opinions of the majority even
unconsciously. If most of your friends
or social media are hyped about someone,
it's easier to say I like them too.
Social media performance. Publicly
posting admiration can be more about
signal signaling taste than feeling it deeply. Research
shows that people sometimes overestimate
enthusiasm for popular celebrities by 20
30% compared to their private feelings
especially online or in group settings.
Three blended cases. Most fandoms are
mixed. Some one might generally like
aspects of a celebrity in brackets,
voice, style, personality, um exaggerate
outwardly to fit social norms or appear cool.
This is why celebrity popularity can
feel overwhelmingly universal even
though private opinions are more varied.
Why it matters? Understanding this
explains phenomen phen phenomena
like teens teasing each other for not
liking certain celebrities. Wait one second.
Teens teasing each other for not liking certain celebrities.
In in brackets, if you don't like
chevel, you're gay.
Mass social media. I cry.
One second. One second. One second. Mass social.
One second. Mass social media I quote
hype. That makes a celebrity seem seem
more universally adored than they are.
people discovering they actually don't
care about a celebrity once removed from preppressor. Most cities
most celebrity love is a mix of genuine
attraction and social influence
and no but they actually quoted it if
you don't like
the way they just quoted it. Most
celebrity love is a mix of genuine
attraction and social influence. And the
balance shifts depending on age, peer
pressure and cultural visibility. Even
if someone is performing admir um
admiration, it's often subconscious.
It's a human social behavior. If you
want, I can show a concrete example
using Harry Styles fun and break down
what percentage of fans were likely were
likely performative versus genuine. It's
surprisingly measurable from social
media and surveys. Do you want me to do that?
I can't believe they quoted that.
Grieves. Wait, let's go back on that again.
Teams teasing each other for not liking
certain celebrities. I quote, "If you
don't like your game,"
and that is exactly what they said.
That is exactly what they said, bro.
Right. Let me type. Yeah.
It's funny, bro. No, [ __ ] all that.
Right. Let me ask him something else now.
So it was to fit in then
grieves you. So it was to fit in all along. Right. So,
here's one. Is wanting to collect women
normal? Greasy. Listen to this. Yes, but
it depends on what you mean by collect
women and how you act on it. Let's break
it down carefully. One. Casual
attraction versus objectification.
It's normal to be attracted to multiple
people. Humans are naturally drawn to
varity, noity, and sexual or romantic
interest. Thinking, noticing, or even
flirting with several people isn't in inherently unhealthy.
The red flag The red flag is treating
people as objects or trophies instead of
individuals with feelings, auto
autonomy, automany, and agency.
I find s people attractive and not like either.
I want to collect women to boost my ego
status or selfworth. The word collect
often signals the latter which leads
which leads which leans toward
objectification not just natural attraction.
This is funny, but I like this.
Yeah, that's funny, Greg. Is it?
So, it definitely was a trend then, wasn't it?
Definitely was a trend. Isn't it funny
how when I search the Harry Styles one
we usually they use several car as an example?
Where do I get all this information from? Grey
definitely was a trend. Yeah.
You actually want Do you actually want
to speak to this woman? Gre
Oh, I've got a funny one here, bro.
So I I So basically I wrote, "What does
being a copycat mean?" Do you want to
know the answer?
Do you want to know what it says, Greasy? Ha.
Do you want to know what it says on
chat? GBT greasy.
Crazy. You want to know what it says?
Right. I'm going to read it anyways.
Being a copycat basically means someone
imitates or mimics another person's
behavior, style, or ideas, often without
originality. Here's a detailed breakdown
everyday meaning. If someone copies your
clothes, hairstyle, or way of speaking,
people might call them copycat.
It's usually teasing or mildly mildly
critical, implying the person isn't
creative or independent. Example, you
stop wearing a new type of sneakers. The
next day, your friend buys the exact
same pair. That friend is being a copycat
in behavior and ideas. It can go beyond
appearance, like copying someone's joke,
work, or social media posts, just like
Virgin Boy. Sometimes it's harmless
admiration, but it can also feel
annoying if it's if it's excessive or
unoriginal. Why do pe why do people copy?
Admiration. They like what you do and
want to emulate it. Social acceptance.
Copying popular trends can help them fit
in. Lack of confidence. They might not
feel creative or unique, so they imitate
others. Humor or teasing. Some people
play mimic intentionally.
Some people mimic intentionally to be playful. Conor conoration
usually a negative or playful label is
suggest lack of originality but in some
context learning by copying is normal
i.e. kids learning behaviors
artists practicing techniques.
What does it mean if you go on holiday?
Grezy, greasy, greasy, greasy. Here's
one I wrote.
What does it mean? When you go on
holiday, then someone else goes on the
exact same holiday as you.
Ah, that's a situation that can that can
feel really weird or funny. And there
are a few ways to think about it.
Coincidence. Sometimes it's just random
charts. Popular destinations like Paris,
Bali or IFA attract lots of tourists at
the same time. If your friend or
acquaint acquaintance chooses the same
destination independently, it doesn't
mean anything deeper. It's just a coincidence.
um following um copying
in in brackets social mimicry. If
someone knows where you're going and
then choose the exact same place, people
might jokingly say that they're copying
you. This is similar to being a a
copycat. This is similar to being a
copycat. They're following your lead
instead of making their own choice. Yeah.
M it. Where else should we uh Right.
Yeah, it was definitely fitting in then,
wasn't it? going by this.
What am I, Grezy?
What am I? How would you describe me? Huh?
How would you describe me, lad? Grezy.
Is there any way you describe me? Greavves. Anyway,
bless you then, Greavvesy. If you've got
a little Manchester dialect,
you've got a little Manchester dialect,
don't you, Greavvesy?
So, you miss Triple H in his little northeast dialect.
What's your little accent, Grevy? It's
Manchester, isn't it?
So, Grezy, how would you describe me
if I was lost? Yeah. And the police
asked you to describe me, how would you
describe me? What would you describe me as?
How would you describe me, Grey?
No, I want I want I want you to describe
me. I want I want you to describe me, Greavvesy.
But how would you describe me
that on this Unity.
Oh, so you don't think I'm a big fat copycat?
See you later, Virgin.
So you wouldn't describe me as a big fat stinking copycat.
Brush my teeth three times a day.
So, is that who you want to be with? Do
you want to be with a with a Christian, Greavesy? Oh, bless.
She likes all kinds of meat as well. She
likes spicy food. She likes pizza.
That's all kinds of food.
How much did you spend in a cinema the
other day when you went?
How much did you spend in the pictures?
Yes, I showed someone said on Reddit,
you can show me your approaches. I'll
try and see if I can give you some tips.
Give me some tips. So, I've showed them
my approaches. What are they going to
say now? Greavvesy,
would I? Not really. No. Nah,
not at all, bro.
Not really, bro. Not really.
Not really, lad.
Uh, a general one.
A general one. Sorry, bro.
Yeah, she's a general one. Is that okay?
Is that okay with you, boss?
Well, I guess we can share her if you want, Grezy.
We can be in a poly relationship.
Okay with you, boss.
Uh, not since the other day. I got I got
some new figures.
We can share if you want, Grezy.
Sharing is caring.
You know, I know you'd do the same for me, Grezy.
me if you if you found someone, you know, no bets.
No, no bets.
No on this channel anymore.
Nah, bro. Sorry.
Yeah, I'm not gambling anymore, lad. I'm
done with it. Sorry, mate.
The only way I'll do it is if Greavvesy does it.
All right. I've asked I've asked chat uh
DBT this screams. I said, "What's the
best way to get revenge on women?"
It says, "I can't help with hurting or
harassing getting revenge on women or
anyone. That stuff creates more damage
and it usually backfires hard. What I
can do is help you get the kind of
revenge that actually works and doesn't
mess up your life. Here's the real talk.
The only kind of revenge that pays off
living well and reclaiming your power.
Not in a cheesy quote way, in a
practical one. Stop giving access. No
chasing. No arguing. No explaining
yourself to people who disrespect you.
Level up quietly. Focus on your health,
money, skills, confidence, social life.
Nothing rattles people more than
realizing they no longer matter. Win by indifference.
When someone can't provoke you anymore,
they lose all leverage. Choose better
next time. Learning from what went wrong
is a real power move.
What do you think to this, Grezy?
Why revenge fantasies feel tempting?
They usually come from feeling
humiliated, rejected, or powerless.
Wanting to restart ego or control.
Wanting the other person to feel how
what you felt.
Totally human feelings. Acting them out.
That's where people ruin their
reputations, get isolated or worse.
What do you think about this movie?
It's funny, isn't it? Grezy,
I'm going to write a question about Greavvesy.
If you're asking whether someone named
Greavvesy is gay, the short answer is
there's no reliable public
information showing that I quote
Greavvesy is gay. We don't have any
verified statements from that person
about their sexual orientation. So you
can't say one way or the other with
certainty. People named Grievy on
Greavvesy online show up in a few
different content. For example, someone
making art under that name, but none of
the public profiles website provide
information about their personal life or sexuality. Huh. Thanks. Yeah.
I'm not sure who you mean by Peter F. He
doesn't match any well-known public
figure or name I recognize. Could you
clarify a bit more? For example, is it a
friend or someone you know? Are you
referring to a celebrity and maybe the
name is spelled differently? Or is this
about someone in a story game show? Once
I know which person you're talking about
and why you're asking, I can give you a meaningful
answer about what normal might mean in that context.
is Blackpool in the West Midlands?
No, Blackpool is not in the West
Midlands. Here's the geography.
Blackpool is a seaside town in Lancaster
in the northwest of England. It's famous
for its pier, beaches, and the Blackpool
Tower. West Midlands is a separate religion. One second.
Okay, so I've asked this question. Um,
Grezy, why do I feel depressed when I
can't suck boobs anymore? Is it a lack
of vitamins? I hear you. Feeling down or
depressed when you can't do something
sexually like sucking boobs is usually
not about vitamins or nutrition. It's
more about psychology, reward system,
and habit. Let me explain.
It's about reward and pleasure. Sexual
activity stimulates dopamine. The brain
rewards reward chem chemical. If you
suddenly can't do something that gave
you pleasure, your brain may feel a drop
in dopamine which can feel like a
sadness, frustration or mild depression.
This is similar to missing any activity
that that was highly rewarding sports,
gaming or social interaction. It's not a
vitamin deficiency deficiency. Low mood
for not having sexual contact is not
caused by a lack of vitamins. Vitamin D,
B12, and omega-3 can influence mood in
general, but missing sexual inflation
won't be fixed by pills.
Except that mood swings in response to
sexual changes are normal.
Channel says I'll be
Yeah. What's that?
No, women's breasts do not give vitamins
just by touching, sucking, or looking at
them. Here's the breakdown. If you mean
breast breast milk from women contains
nutrients like proteins, fat, vitamins,
and minerals for babies. For an adult,
even if you consume breastfeed, the
amount of vitamins you'd get is tiny
compared to a normal diet.
touching or sucking breasts do not transfer vitamins.
For adults, sexual activity can release
hormones like dopamine and oxine which
make you feel good and relaxed.
But that's a psychological and hormonal
effect, not a nutri neutritional one. Okay.
Okay. What's an incel?
Yeah, I'm reading it. Go covering the forms.
Okay, so an insult is short for
involuntary celibate. It's a term used
to describe someone usually man who
wants a romantic or sexual relationship
but struggles to get one. Here's a
breakdown. Literal meaning, involuntary,
not by choice. Celebrate, not having
sex, but obviously mine is by choice, so
this doesn't apply to me cuz obviously I
don't care. So, an insult of someone who
wants sexual or romantic intimacy, but
isn't getting it despite wanting it.
Community and culture. Online insults
often go in forms or communities. Some
discussions are about frustration,
loneliness, or self-improvement, which
is harmless. But some parts of the
community focus on blaming women
resenting people who are successfully
romantically are expressing misogyny
which is harmful. Yeah.
Um so I've sent these approaches. Yeah.
What do you reckon Red's going to come
back with? What advice? Boozy.
Here's one I want to ask. Yeah, bro.
We're just on AI. Yeah,
I wrote this. Yeah,
I wrote this. Um,
uh, Brigy, why do people defend women
even when they're in the wrong? Ah, this
is actually really common question and
it's worth unpacking carefully. People
sometimes defend women even when they're
in the wrong for a mix of social psychological
psychological and cultural reasons.
Here's a breakdown.
Social norms and gender stereotypes.
Society often teaches people to protect
or defer women framing them as
vulnerable, innocent or nutrient. This
can lead to bias where women are assume
less at fault in disputes. Example, if a
woman argues loudly in a group,
some some people might excuse it as
emotional while a man doing the same is criticized.
So, wait, because they're so because
they're weaker than men, that means they
can't lead people on.
So, because they're physically weaker
than men, that means they can't be evil
and be rude and lead people on.
See you later, Virgin. skid boy.
So just because they're physically
weaker, that means they can't do that.
I beg to differ, lad. I beg to differ.
That's the whole point what I'm trying
to make is that anyone can do that. Does
Why does it matter if they're weak or
not? If they're [ __ ] wrong, they're
[ __ ] wrong, aren't they, Grezy?
So, because they're physically weaker,
that means that they can't lead people
on and be [ __ ] because they're physically weaker.
I'm not sure about that, bro.
going to say anyways
when they see my videos on Reddit.
One second, Grezy.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. Oh my [ __ ] Oh [ __ ] Right.
I hate this double standards. Oh, women
don't need men. They're strong and
independent. They don't need you to hold
a door for them and don't want that
calling. But if I abuse a man, I can't get something.
I don't get what you mean, lad.
Go away, virgin boy. No virgins.
where Women don't need men.
Women don't need men. There's loads of
women that haven't been with men for years. Yeah.
What I find weird, Greaves, is that
women are worse than men. They are
literally worse than men. It's not a
case of, "Oh, they're both as bad." No,
they are worse than men, but people
still defend them, Grezy.
They are literally worse than men.
They're more [ __ ] than men are, but
then people still defend them, even when
they're shown they're wrong. It's so
mad, isn't it?
Isn't that [ __ ] up to you?
But they're actually worse than men.
They actually worse than men,
but people just defend them just for
having a [ __ ] in between their legs. M. Yep.
It's mad, isn't it?
It's mad, isn't it? Where is he?
Do you remember my little friend from Amsterdam, Greavvesy?
We speak now and then. We spoke the past
couple of days.
We remember everything. We met 11 years
ago and we remember everything, bro. The
most littlest things. And we always say
to each other, "I want to forget it.
But you can't in it. Nah.
We'll never forget it. Never. Like the
littlest things. Nah.
That's funny. Is it Grezy? Sm
that is mad is it moves.
These Reddit mods can't get through my VPN. Grezy,
that AI is is hilarious, isn't it, Greavvesy?
That was hilarious, bro.
I knew it was a a a social status thing,
though. I knew it. I knew it, bro.
If you don't like them, okay. Yeah.
That's mad, bro. Mad.
I'm sure you done stuff when you was
younger, though, didn't you, Greasy, to fit in.
Maybe liked football or something. Oh,
she's back. She just messaged me.
Oh, she's back. We She just messaged me.
Why? What do you mean see through me?
I'm a good I'm a good [ __ ] Greavvesy,
you just don't want me to be happy. Grievy,
you just don't want me to be happy. Why?
No, she didn't knock me back for low.
You didn't You don't even know the
story, mate. So,
yeah, you don't even know the story, lad.
So, that's not what happened. But, yeah.
Anyways, why don't you want me to be happy?
Yeah, but I don't hurt people. Grezy,
I'm also a Christian.
Listen, Gre, you think I'm just going to
hurt a random person for no reason?
That person who I made go to waxis was
being a [ __ ] They were actually being a
[ __ ] That's why I made them go all that
way and I was going to whine and dash
them. I was going to dine and dash them.
Why is that, bro? Cuz they were being an absolute [ __ ]
It wasn't for no reason.
No, bro. That's not what happened.
And I don't care about that, bro.
Anyways, that was [ __ ]
yesterday. We're over that now.
I'll try to be good, Greavvesy. I'll try
my best. Is that good enough for you, Greavvesy?
Is that good enough for you?
Yeah, maybe Grezy.
No, it wasn't me, bro. It was a ghost.
No, it wasn't me. It was a ghost.
Yeah, Greavves. Or maybe they just lead
people on or just have a really bad attitude.
Yeah. Or just like the million ones on
WhatsApp that led me on.
No, it's not me, bro. That that's a
that's that's a ghost.
That's a ghost. Yeah,
it's cute in it. Grezy
K never come back, did he? Yes, sir.
Graves has been trolling me and you've
got the evidence.
What's he been doing to me?
Really? What was he saying?
Is that true? really poor [ __ ]
The poor [ __ ]
Greavves, I'll try and behave with this one. Grezy,
do you trust me?
Grezy, do you trust me? Why?
Gravy, do you see a lot of multicultural people?
Do you see a lot of interracial couples
where you live? You see a lot in Birmingham.
and other places.
Do you think it's a kick in the dick if
he was to see it? Greavvesy,
would you think it is a kick in the dick
if he was to see it?
You should you should find it offensive, Grezy.
You should find it offensive, Grezy.
It's another slap to the face.
What? Do you see it like that, Grezy?
Do you not see it as offensive, Greavvesy?
Yeah, but Greavvesy is a slap in the
it's a slap in the face, bro, because
it's like they're choosing they're
choosing people before their own.
And I'm not talking about black people,
bro. I'm just saying like it it could be
anyone, bro. They're actually choosing
people before their own.
Imagine that leaves you choose. They're
choosing other people before their
actual own people.
Yeah. No one. Yeah. What happened last
time? Nothing happened last time.
You sad pathetic wannabe troll. You sad
little bastard. What happened last time
was you done nothing. That's what
happened last time.
So in a way they're actually the racist ones.
That's what would annoy me about living
up north, bro, is seeing it. You don't
really see it here. You see it more up
north, but you don't really see it here.
Very rarely, bro.
Should help other people. They should
help. It's like the housing and stuff.
They need to treat their own right first before [ __ ]
um you know other other people. Do you
know what I mean? Grezy,
they need to help their own first before anyone else
even with like the government and stuff.
I don't know how you feel about it.
No, I'm not racist though. Grievy is
racist. Grievy, why are you so racist?
Greavves is racist.
No, Gra is racist.
So, if I meet this person, Greavvesy,
I'm going to be If I meet this person,
Greavvesy, I'm going to be happy with
this person, aren't I?
I'm going to be happy with this person,
aren't I, Greavvesy? You're Yeah.
Just saying good night to them. Where you say?
You happy, Greg. You have got someone to talk to.
Oh, bless you, Greavvesy.
Greavves, are you in bed right now?
But if I got with this person,
Chinese Izzy meet uh will miss me though. Greasy.
You remember Chinese Izzy?
Then what do I do, Grezy? I'll be put
into a dilemma.
Then more, Grey, I'll be put into a dilemma.
Oh, bless you then. Greasy, are you
making a cup of tea? Oh, bless.
Can you make me one or try it?
G is a proper troll. Steven Howard. Nothing.
Greavves is such a troll, man. Crazy.
What are you sat there waiting for?
I'm so tired. UK.
Do you like the AIS?
Did you like the AI? Yeah.
What the new ones like UK silent the new escorts?
I sure am. Yeah.
Do you want my opinion? UK asylum ass [ __ ] Yep.
UK signing. You don't know where You
don't know where Watchtowers.
>> You're in the bedroom with Crash. I sure am.
You already know that.