Oh man. N.
What a sad bastard loser.
What's so funny, bro? I didn't even get
the notification and I didn't get the
notification. I went back on it.
Jesus Christ, bro. Come out the closet already.
Come out the closet already, lad. Jesus Christ.
Yeah, man. I actually saw Timmy's um
community post, bro. And that [ __ ]
Money M was talking [ __ ] I was going to
respond back, but they're just not even
They're not even worth anyone's
breath, bro. Or time. So, I didn't.
They're literally just There's no point
in arguing with disabled people, lad.
But yeah, I did see that. Yeah.
Well, obviously, bro, it's a copycat
community. What do you expect? They're
not worth it, bro. Just like this Joe
F's not worth it. Like I said, he's been
talking [ __ ] on my [ __ ] community
post as well.
I completely owned him, bro. Like I
said, I'll be in Nottingham soon
anyways, bro. So, you can say all of
this [ __ ] to my face, can't you? And
show me how strong your punch is.
[ __ ] idiot, man.
There be a lot of people copying my bet,
bro. A lot of people
that because it's a copycat community, you see
it's a copycat community. What do you expect,
guys? was a proper proper [ __ ] man.
Kieran didn't come back last night, did he?
Yeah, he didn't come back. I was going
to tell him about this Jo guy. He's a
proper nonlover, bro.
Yeah, man. He didn't come back.
It was funny, bro. You know what? Where
they're so stupid, bro, it's addicting.
like their stupidity is so amusing and
it makes you feel like it makes you feel
so intelligent, bro. You know what I mean?
Yeah, I owned him on the last comment,
bro. What can you say to that? What a
[ __ ] bro. Come out the closet.
You'll be a much better person.
Yeah, bro. I'm definitely definitely
definitely not. And another thing is
managements change all the time.
So I mean you do realize how busy a
place gets and how management's changed.
So that's just a waste of time you doing
you know that's literally just like a
waste of time you even doing that.
That's literally a waste of time because
a it's busy and and b the management's
changed so I'm not buying from there.
When I go out again I'll show you I'm
not buying from there.
So anyways, see you later, [ __ ]
We're not having any spastics on here. So yeah,
[ __ ] sad. I'm coming off this
community soon. Anyways, bro, I had to
think to myself once the weather starts
getting better, should be all right in a
couple of weeks. I'll be off. Anyways,
when I'm done with this [ __ ] tomorrow
and I'm going,
I'm done with these jealous retards, bro. So
yeah, I'm going to start making it routine anyways.
I'll be off here, lad. Completely.
Completely off here.
So, that's it.
Not for a while, though. I'm not done yet, bro.
Where the [ __ ] is K, man?
Do genuine people know my email? Bro, I
don't I don't date fat, ugly women like
you. I've had more women than you've had
hot dinners. I don't target fat, ugly
women like you, you and your boyfriend.
And I don't collect men's numbers. I
collect women's numbers. Something that
you and your boyfriend can't do cuz
you're so ugly. And you got no
confidence. I'm not like you and your
boyfriend targeting disabled girls. Fat,
ugly, because you can't get anything normal.
I am talking to someone though. And
she's not fat and ugly like you and your
boyfriends. Ooh, you and your boyfriend
are so alike. Have you booked that hotel
room yet? Your gay boy. Your little gay
boy. Bro, listen. I am going to I'm
coming to Nottingham soon, bro. Make
sure you show me this one punch. Yeah,
that's very, very strong. Make sure you
show me this strong punch.
I will knock the [ __ ] out of you in half
and a punch, bro. Half half a punch.
Make sure you show me this punch, you
little gay boy. Yeah, I'm going to knock
you on the ground. Show everyone your
ugly face. This is the ugly that's come
on YouTube every day talking [ __ ] and
[ __ ] mention your boyfriend in it so
we can see his boyfriend knock up on the
[ __ ] floor. You know what I'm saying, lad?
You [ __ ] little gay boy. And get your
facts right before writing stuff. I've
never ever met a woman from Oxford.
I will [ __ ] knock the [ __ ] out of you
and anyone can [ __ ] put any amount of
money on it. You skinny little northern
[ __ ] fat ugly misses. Fake pension,
fake win, poverty ridden little [ __ ]
It's all going to come out in the end as
well. I will knock I will Do you know
what I'll do? I'll just knock your teeth
down your throat. That's what I'll do.
I'm bigger than you. I'm stronger than
you. I'm bigger than you and I'm
stronger than you, bro. I will knock the
[ __ ] out of you. It's not It's not even
a joke. You think some povertyridden or
nons lover is is is going to even be
able to throw a punch at me, bro?
Really? Really? You really think that's
going to You really think that's what
it's going to go down, bro? I could just
elbow you in your jaw and that would be
it. You [ __ ] dirty little closeted
gay boy. And I'll say it to your face as
well. You're a dirty, stinky closeted
gay boy. Like, you're not even going to
get a punch, bro. How are you going to
get a punch on me? I'm bigger than you.
How's that? How's that going to happen?
You know, you [ __ ] dirty little
Yorkshire [ __ ] uh chuckle vision
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] Chuckle brothers. Yeah.
Uh bro, no one's going to be running
away from you, bro. Do you know what? Do
you know what? Do you know what? I've
also got a history of showing up to
places and talking. Something that you
can't do, bro. Come on. I've also got a
history of talking and showing up.
Something that you can't do, you gay
boy. Closeted little gay boy.
something you can't do. You closeted
coward poverty mongode with the 200 pound phone.
Yeah, bro. Bring your boyfriend as well,
bro. Bring your boyfriend as well. Knock
you both out. Simple.
Come on, man. Come on. Easy. Easy, bro. [ __ ] easy.
Yeah, bro. Keep showing your fake
pension and your fake wins. You're
[ __ ] And bro, listen. All of the
women I've had have always been better
than you and your boyfriend. I don't
target fat and disabled like you and
your boyfriend. Cuz I'm not ugly like
you and your boyfriend. I'm not socially
awkward like you and your boyfriend. I'm
not a closeted gay like you and your boyfriend.
You [ __ ] absolute [ __ ]
So you'll get a week's notice anyways,
lad. Yeah. So make sure you show up. I
want I want to see this punch. Everyone
wants to see it. Everyone wants to see
this strong punch.
Yeah, bro. Everyone wants to see this.
Just make sure you turn up. Yeah.
There we go.
That's all I need to say now. Anyways, yeah. Simple, bro.
Make sure you show up, lad.
I can't wait, lad. You got a lot to say
on YouTube. So, yeah. You you'll have a
lot to say to my face. Don't think so. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, man. I got to go out today, bro. I
got a web [ __ ] in it.
Uh Timmy, thanks for copying my bet, man.
Thanks for copying it. You're a copycat.
You little copycat.
You're a little copycat, Timmy.
You a little copycat.
You little copycat.
And for your information, Joe, I put um
on AI, is it possible to be a virgin if
you've got a girlfriend? And the answer is yes.
The answer is yes.
If and when I'm in places where you are,
you won't know who I am till you feel
Shuts up. You're not about it, bro. I
read that first bit. Shut up, bro.
You're a waffler.
You're a waffler. You're not going to do
nothing, mate. Stop trying to sugarcoat
[ __ ] Stop giving the same excuses as
[ __ ] that Prime used to give. I'm
going to tell you where I'm going to be,
and it's up for you to go there. If you
don't go there, then you're a [ __ ]
Simple as that.
You're just a weak little man. You know
what? Yeah. If you're actually if you
was actually fat, yeah, you'd actually
have more of a chance. You would have
actually had more of a chance.
No, I'm not putting the link up for you,
Timmy, bro. You give me You give me a headache.
[ __ ] off, man.
Yeah, you give me a [ __ ] headache.
Yeah, someone will catch me one day,
bro. Listen, like I said, I'm going to
let you know where where I am when I am.
Yeah, I done a football bet. Yeah, man.
And I only put £10 on it, which to me is
not even really gambling, is it?
Yeah. Yeah, I put £10 on it.
Nah, I can't listen to you, Timmy, bro.
You give me a headache, man.
Really? Really give me a headache. I
can't I can't be annoyed listening to you, man. Sorry. Sorry, Captain.
Yeah, you're in London. Yeah. Okay, bro.
Yeah, man. I I know what you're about,
Joe, man. It's It's so easy. It's so
easy to to to know what you people are doing.
[ __ ] hell, man. Just come out the
closet already. Don't know what you're
waiting for. What you're waiting for,
bro. Why don't you just come out the closet?
[ __ ] my head hurting, man.
I didn't know I met a woman from Oxford.
You learn something new every day.
Never in my life have I met a woman from
Oxford. I think you got brain damage, lad.
I think you got brain damage. Yeah, definitely.
And I didn't know Triple H lived in
Spennymore. You learn something new every day.
Sad little bastard. You gave yourself
away though like too easy, Joe. Man, you
gave yourself away too easy. As soon as
you started defending your boyfriend the
way you was defending him, it just gave you away.
It literally gave you away, bro. You
need to be smarter next time if you're
trying to like be discreet. It's too
obvious. The way you was sucking your
boyfriend's dick every time you got
called what he is, it was it was too
obvious. You know, it was way too
You're not very smart at all, are you?
And I've asked AI
and AI says that it is possible to be a
virgin with a girlfriend. That's what AI says.
Yeah. Do you remember AI yesterday? UK
asylum. Oh, it was giving me [ __ ]
jokes, bro. It was giving me jokes.
It was actually giving me jokes, bro.
Do you remember what we were saying?
Pips smoker to blend in with the crowd.
Oh, to to just agree to not be seen as weird.
Oh, it did make me laugh. That did make
me laugh, mate. Yeah,
that was funny, bro.
Yeah, that did make me laugh. That's funny.
That is funny, bro.
Do you remember it? UK Asylum.
But when the weather will when the
weather gets a bit better and it stops
raining, I'm going start be going out a
lot. So, I won't have time for this [ __ ]
to be honest.
One second. One second.
Let me go back on it. It says, "A way to
blend in with the crowd. An easy
low-risk opinion everyone agreed on.
Something you repeated because everyone
else was saying it.
Who does that remind you of?"
Yeah. And also it mentioned uh about
being insecure which is what I said UK asylum
you know you know like um it's also in
like when people are insecure about
their sexuality and stuff you know when
you're you know you're still a teenager
and you know people are teasing you that
was just a way to get out of it
you know by saying you like that Listen.
Nah, bro. I used to go to that gym.
Oh, look. Look. It said UK side of it
said, "And if you liked her despite the
copying culture or still like her now,
that's your own taste, not borrowed." Yeah. copying culture little copycats.
Now explain to me UK asylum. How am I a
troll? So what? I don't go out drinking
and approaching people.
I do. I approach people. So why am I
trolling? But what what am I doing? That's trolling.
I'm just an old person trying to live my [ __ ] life.
Why would I troll, bro? What? How am I trolling?
Yeah, but how am I how am I provoking them?
How am I provoking them?
Well, like when I used to go on dates
and stuff knowing that it would piss off
a certain virgin, UK asylum,
knowing that his anxiety could never
allow him to do it. You mean that kind of thing?
You mean that kind of thing, mate?
Pisses a certain virgin off,
doesn't it, mate?
Yeah. UK silent, bro. You You never
Do you remember UK um Asylum when I when
I approached uh
USA? When I approached USA is non legs
was making community posts.
He was going [ __ ] mad, wasn't he?
His little brain couldn't hack it cuz
I'm not a virgin like him. And his
anxiety could never
his anxiety could never, lad. It could never.
Um, well, considering
he's got a YouTube channel dedicated to me,
uh, I would say that he's the one that's
obsessed with me. I'm not obsessed with
that virgin. He's the one that goes on
about me. You must not be aware of his
channel, Dr. Eko.
I'm not obsessed with that ugly bastard.
I just don't know why somebody would
want to copy another person. I'm not
obsessed with that [ __ ] ugly copycat
rat bastard. The [ __ ] bro?
No, no, no. I think you must be unaware
of that uh channel or you must be delusional
cuz that [ __ ] is obsessed with me lad. Yeah,
definitely definitely definitely
obsessed with me.
Nothing Stephen Football bet lad
bro I'm I'm not obsessed with him. I'm
just I just can't get my head around the
whole thing of it.
Why somebody would copy another person
just to fit in?
It's the whole thing I I I can't get
over, you know.
Yeah, I don't know football bet Steven
Howard. You might want to go on my community post.
Only £10. I can't justify anymore, bro.
And this it's basically not gambling, is
it really?£10 £10 football bet. Could
you really class that as gambling? Not really.
I could have put a lot more on it, but
nah. [ __ ] all that, bro.
Like I even done a football bet today to
be honest. I said I weren't doing them
again. So, but £10.
Come on, man. Yeah. Yeah,
but yeah, I will be off here soon,
Stephen Howard. 100%. But I've still got
a few I got to meet that [ __ ] tomorrow.
I'm having a roast dinner tomorrow.
Steven Howard got some nice steak today.
Yeah, I got a bit of food shopping in him.
Yeah, I will be coming off here living
my life as soon as the um it's on my main channel.
Um, yeah, like I said,
would go out today, but no, I don't want
to. [ __ ] that, bro.
Maybe I'd consider it if I wasn't
speaking to someone.
Maybe, but I'm speaking to someone in it. So,
I done more than enough to satisfy my
curiosity. So, that's that, bro.
But there was no way I was going to get
my haircut and not go out. Nah. No way.
That's a waste of my my book. Nah.
It's a waste. Yeah.
Oh, Steven Howard, what you going to copy?
You little copycat.
Yeah. I don't really like gambling, bro,
and the [ __ ] it causes and that. So
that's why I just put £10 on it.
It's not money, bro. I have [ __ ] I've
got money. It's not about that. But it's
just like nah. Nah, bro.
You're a proper copycat, lad.
You little copycat.
Yeah, the the weather's [ __ ] today,
Stephen Howard. So, I'm just staying in, lad. Yeah. Um
15 to one. 155. Yeah.
Yeah. 10 returns 151.
I still not I'm still not going out even
if it wins, bro. It's not about money. I just
not about that at all, bro.
Just making sure, you know, Steven Howard
don't want the genuine people to think
the wrong things now, do we? Yeah, man.
Joe F is one of the brothers.
Stephen Howard, me, you, Greavvesy, and
Kieran and Jo. Joe F's one of the brothers, lad.
What's your opinion on that?
See you later.
No spastics on this channel, man. Jesus
Christ. You not get the hint. [ __ ] hell.
You know these people, Steven Howard,
are very very stupid, you know, trying
to get me banned from places because,
you know, the the thing is Yeah. The
thing is Steven is a the places are
packed so they're never even going to
recognize if you go in. It's not like
O'Neal's and B the man the managements
change all the time. You know that place
I had a problem with the bouncer. I was
there literally yesterday bro uh
Thursday when I went out Thursday. It
changes all the time. It's like
completely a waste of time even trying
to get someone banned from somewhere.
because the managements change literally
all the time,
different faces. It's it's a complete
waste of time.
It's so disabled. And you know, when
they do it, Stephen Howard, it proves
that they've got no life as well. It
proves that it kills them when you're
out drinking and they're sat on YouTube,
no life. That's another thing. And
that's not even me getting mad, bro. I'm
just saying like that's my opinion. And
also like the management's changed. The
only places it doesn't change, bro, is is um
is um his own hills. For some reason, it
never changes in there. So, they got me
there. But even a casino, I haven't
tried getting into casino for ages, but
you'd still be able to get into casinos
quickly. It's pointless. It's stupid,
bro, cuz the management changes.
But where they've got no life
experience, Stephen Howard, they don't realize this.
They don't they think, "Oh, it's the
same people. It's only a few people
going in there." They don't realize,
bro, like you were just blending with
the crowd. If you went there today, you
were just blending with the crowd.
They're very, very, very stupid, bro.
Very, very, very stupid.
Yeah. No, I know, bro. I know. I know.
But I'm just saying anyways. Bro, why do
you think I pull it up there, bro?
Because I didn't care. You think I
didn't know what they were going to do?
Sad, fat, ugly people that don't leave
the house. Think about it, Stephen
Howard. Look at that V, bro. Let me Let
me tell you something. This is not a
reaction. This is facts. This is telling
me that this is telling you the truth.
Yeah. Look at him, bro. Yeah. Some fat
ugly loser. Can't talk to a woman in
real life. We've already seen what he
does. Yeah. With that autumn. He sits at
home stimping over women on YouTube cuz
he's a [ __ ] virgin. So, bro, of
course he's going to get jealous when
someone like me, better looking than
him, better better confidence than him,
got more of a life than him, can
actually go and do what he can never do.
Bro, you got to think, bro, that these
people are sat at home all day. Wasters.
That's why that's why the word That's
why the word wasters hit a nerve, bro.
And I said what they were. Then they
started trying to copy me with it cuz
they are wasters, bro. Waster virgins.
Can't make friends. can't talk to women.
They're wasters, lad.
You know what I'm saying?
Oh, and this ghost of ducks is another
two-faced one as well.
I've seen you talking [ __ ] on Lauria um
the other day.
So, yeah, I'm off here anyway. Steven
Howard from um
when does the weather start getting
better? I'm going to start going out
like probably Yeah, March, I think. Bro,
I still got a couple things to do on
here. I'm just waiting for the weather
to get better and then I'll hardly be on here.
I might be live like once in a while,
bro. Like if if I get if whatever. But,
bro, I'll be doing stuff. So,
I saw you saying something called Lord
J's man. Oh, that's what it was. Oh,
yeah. V was like, "Oh, yeah. Press one
if you want me to um call Waxies." And
you was pressing one.
That's what it was. Yeah. Yeah, I
remember that. Bro, you know that's
stupid because the staff and managements
change all the time.
It literally changes like all the time.
So, it's just so silly to even do that.
Except from O'Neals. They never change
for some reason. I don't know why.
Well, like a new channel, Stephen Hour
would just There's no point, bro, cuz I
won't be uploading much.
So, there's no point.
Really? So why are you now at work then?
Okay. Okay. Let's have it one second.
Stephen Howard and Indigo. One second.
Firstly, uh I have had a job. Uh and
second of all, you don't have a job
yourself. So in it it maybe before
telling other people they don't have a
job, you might want to get yourself a
job first. And yes, I have had a job and
I can I I will work when I need to work. Yeah.
You don't have a job. You are not at
work now. It's Saturday. You're supposed
to be at work. Yeah. You don't need to
worry about if someone's got a job or
don't have a You don't have a job. Yeah.
And why am I a danger to women? What?
Because I don't lick women's asses. Come
on, bro. If you're going to say stuff,
back it up. You're allowed your opinion.
You're my my One second. Your whole
family are benefit scounges. One second.
One second. One second. Hold on. Hold
on. Bro, you don't even know anything
about anyone. You don't know anything
about anyone's family. What the [ __ ] are
you talking about, you stupid little
[ __ ] Firstly, my mom's retired. Yeah.
Yeah. Secondly, she's worked her whole
life. Yeah. My sister works. Yeah. And
I've worked. So, what the [ __ ] are you
talking about, you stupid little [ __ ]
My mom's worked her whole [ __ ] life.
Yeah. She brought up three kids and
she's worked her whole life, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] Yeah. How is my mom pounced off
the pounc off the system? Stop talking
about people that you don't know, bro.
Yeah. Stop talking about people you
don't know. And all of this singing and
this white nighting, it's not going to
make women like you. Oh, you're a danger
to women. Oh, you're a danger to women,
bro. It's not going to make women want
you. You're still going to be alone.
You're still going to be a virgin.
You're still going to be jobless. Hack
it in. Stop talking about people's
family. Like, you don't know anything
about anyone's family. You don't know
whether they've worked. You don't know
whether they've not worked. Why are you
not at work? Why are you not at work?
I'll answer your question if you want,
but you answer me firstly. Why are you
not at work? And you're on YouTube every
day. Answer it and then I'll answer you. Simple.
Elaine has worked. I have worked. And my
sister does work. And you do not work.
And you never have worked.
Just another self projector.
This is why I'm coming off of here,
Steven. Because of these retards, lads,
you know. Well, apparently my mom's never worked.
So, apparently, so
everyone in my family's worked.
Literally every person in my family has worked.
Literally has worked. every single
person in my family.
So, you must be self projecting, lad.
Bro, no one's more more losers, bro.
You're the one that's on here every day
on LJ's channel. You are a loser. You're
a big loser sat on YouTube with no job
telling other people to get a job. You
are the loser. You must be a loser to be
on L's. You must be a loser. Anyone that
comes from that channel are born losers.
They're rejects to society. Anyone that
goes on that channel are the biggest
losers ever, lad. You are a big loser.
Anyone that goes on Lav's channel, all
right, Steven, tell them. Yeah, anyone
on that channel is a major loser, a
reject to society. No job, no money,
nothing going for themselves. It's the
truth. You don't like the truth, but it
is the truth. Anyone that goes on that
channel is a [ __ ] loser. Is a reject
to society. You people have got no life.
You don't go out. You don't socialize.
You're just sitting on YouTube being wasters.
That's what you are, bro. Like, what the
[ __ ] And then you're telling people
their families never work. You don't
know anyone's family, what they've done,
what they haven't done. What the [ __ ]
Madness. Absolute madness.
Yeah. Yeah. Whatever, bro. You're the
one. Yeah. Okay, brother. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay, bro. Well, at least at least I
don't simp women on YouTube like you,
bro. I'm better looking than you will
ever be. I've had more women. I've got
more money. Someone like you will never
ever be able to talk about me, bro. The
only clap bods are you ugly losers. You
ain't even got a life. And I'm not even
going to say you ain't got friends. I'm
not even cuz that's not an insult to
tell someone they ain't got no friends.
You [ __ ] ugly people ain't even got a
[ __ ] life to stand on. You embarrass
yourself on YouTube every day. No
[ __ ] You don't have no interaction
with anyone outside YouTube. You're born
losers. You need to you need to
literally invest in a mirror, lad.
You really need to invest in a mirror.
You fat ugly people really need to
invest in a mirror. Next time you get
your little benefit money, bro, look in
that mirror and have a hard look in it, bro.
You [ __ ] stupid little [ __ ]
And this is what I'm This is exactly
what I'm talking about. Steven Howard.
You know what I'm saying? This is
exactly what I'm talking about.
Exactly what I'm talking about. You know,
bro, why do you think Kieran doesn't
come on here anymore much? That was the
first time in what, like four months, bro.
People are bored of it, lad. People are
bored of these fat, ugly, waster losers.
They're bored of them now, bro.
He hasn't been on for four months except
from, you know, yesterday and the other
day because they're b everyone's bored
of it now, bro. Everyone's really,
really bored of it.
If the weather wasn't [ __ ] I'd be out
today, bro. Well, I have been out today
already, but I'd be out drinking.
You know what I'm saying? They're just
ugly, hateful little rejected people.
Do you not think? Yeah. Do you not
think? Yeah. Steven Hour, that kills
them that I can go out, I can collect
women's numbers, I can chat. Do you not
think that [ __ ] kills these fat ugly losers? Bro,
do you not think it kill? Do you not
know that? That even something as simple
as that kills them, bro. Their anxiety
would never ever ever ever allow it.
Never allow it. They can't even leave
the house, bro. They're just [ __ ]
wasters, bro. Yeah, I have done a bit,
man. It's on my community post
if you want to copy it. Drinking on your
Well, do you know what, bro? Let me tell
you something, bro. Let me tell you
something, right? Let's use your
analogy. I'd rather go out today
drinking by myself than be a loser like
you on L's talking about people every
day that you don't know. I'd rather go
out drinking by myself
than be like you losers.
See you later. That's self projecting.
That's it's all Listen, bro. You've got
more chance yet of winning the lottery,
Stephen Howard, than any of these people
saying something that doesn't apply to
themselves. Everything that they say, it
just applies to themselves. They're yet
to say something, bro, that doesn't
apply to themselves. Bro, I would rather
I literally would rather go drinking by
myself talking to women than be on large
js being a loser like these people. Bro,
I know anyone would would be able to do
it, bro. I would I know anybody would
pick what I'm picking. Bro, would you
rather be on Laura J's a lonely loser
talking about people that you don't know
or go out drinking and socializing? I
know what one I'd pick. I know exactly
I know what one I'd pick, bro.
You know what I'm saying?
How about How about you suck my [ __ ]
dick to answer your question? Suck my
[ __ ] dick, you little [ __ ] Yeah,
how about you suck your mom and you suck your dick.
You suck and suck my dick. Sorry. Suck
your dick. Suck my dick and [ __ ] your mom.
And you know where I live and you're not
going to do anything about it. Don't
even think you're going to [ __ ] ask
me questions, you [ __ ] little [ __ ]
Yeah, go back to [ __ ] LJ's channel,
you [ __ ] mug. [ __ ] funny.
Sorry about that, Steven.
It's madness, bro. A lot of a lot of
what it is, bro, bro, on here. Yeah.
A lot of what it is with these people on
here is is is jealousy with these
people. Yeah. Think about it, bro. What
do these people do every day? They wake
up on YouTube, no life, no life, no
money, no family, sat on YouTube 24/7,
lad. And you know what I'm saying? You
know, well, I mean, I can I can pop on
to someone's channel now and again and
and and and and see and I can tell you
right now I'm not sub to him. It's
called clicking on it manually.
It's like I mean it's you can click on
someone's channel manually. Think about
it, bro. They're just [ __ ] old
wasters, losers. None of them have got a
life, bro. Yeah. Steven Howard,
trust me, bro.
Bro, you're not No, you're not balding.
One second, Stephen Hard. This guy Bro,
this guy literally is right about what he's saying.
He says, "At least we aren't balding."
No, you're not balding. You was You
became bored 20 years ago.
So, you're not You're not bored. You're already bored.
Sorry, bro. That was too easy. See you later.
And this is what I'm saying with these
people, bro. It's just always going to
be projection with them. That's what I'm
saying, Stephen Howard, man. Like, I'm
I'm off here soon, bro.
And I'll be live like once in a while.
Whatever. You got my email anyways. So,
that's that, lad. Yeah. Yeah, man.
And what a lot of these people are
steaming hours is they're two-faced as well.
I mean LT is not really too faced
because he's not honored enough to be
doing it like so I mean but you know
like I'm I'm talking about like people
like Joe F and whatever. You'll catch
them talking [ __ ] on Lord Mong's
channel. I'll go on it like once every
couple of days and and you'll see bro
all of these people are fat. All of
these people are [ __ ] ugly. You've
seen them bro. All of these people ain't
got no life. No, they've got nothing
going for themselves.
Like, and then they want to preach to
others about who's worked and who's not
worked. How can they sit there and tell
you your family's not work when they
don't even know your [ __ ] family?
Have you ever heard of someone being
retired? You [ __ ] idiot.
Know what I'm saying? And they don't
have a job themselves. They're sat on
YouTube every day being wasters.
Wasteful people got nothing going for themselves.
You know what I'm saying? Um,
Steven Howard, no job. They got no job,
but they tell other people to get a job.
What the [ __ ]
Do you know what, bro? It this Do you
know what another thing is, Stephen? How
this community is so embarrassing.
It really, really, really, really is
embarrassing. You know, I've never I've
never told anyone
right about like this in real life, bro.
I never have. Never have.
To be fair, bro,
it's so embarrassing, bro. It really,
really, really is the most embarrassing
community, bro, I think you'll ever stumble across.
There's no like there's no point of the
actual thing, bro. Think about it. Yeah.
No one puts gambling videos up. All it
is is a bunch of middle-aged losers that
self-reflect their own life onto other
people. That's literally the whole of
the community, lad.
this ugly jealous people with no life
being obsessed. There's literally no
point of it.
You know, you see some of them kick
streamers, bro. And what them kick
streamers are doing. Yeah. And then you
look at this community. What the [ __ ]
It's mad, bro. Mad.
It's actually Well, I come on here to
speak to Steven Howard. I come on here
to talk to Grezy.
It's so weird, bro.
You got [ __ ] people that are 23 on kick
doing mad [ __ ] bro. Making all kinds of
[ __ ] mad money and then you come and
then you come with this community. Think
about it, bro.
There don't really seem to be a point of
this community, is there?
How you can you could you know there
it's fair enough for you saying I've
never worked even though I have worked.
I've done I've done plenty of jobs. But
then you're telling people their family hasn't worked.
What the [ __ ]
Everyone in my family has worked.
Everyone. Literally everyone has.
Madness, bro. Self projection to the maximum.
Proper proper self projection with these
people in it.
They used to do it with Mark as well.
Nah. Yeah. You're saying that it's past
time and entertainment, but bro, you're
on here 24/7.
I mean, but you are on here 24/7. So,
how can it be a pastime when you're
literally sat on here 24/7 and it's what
you do on here as well, and that's
another thing. It's also what you do on
here. It's how long you're on here for,
and it's actually what you do on here.
The obsession and the hating. It's so
weird. That is so weird. Like, do you
actually think that's normal, man? It's
[ __ ] gay as [ __ ]
What a lot of the people do on here, man.
That's what I'm going to be doing. Yeah.
And there's only a couple of people on
here. That's all right. To be fair.
Well, I can tell you it doesn't matter
if you work or not. Yeah. Because 95% of
the people on LJ's channel don't work.
You know what I'm saying? 95% of people
on um LJ's channel don't work.
Even if you do work, congratulations.
95% of them don't.
You know what I'm saying? They used to
do this. I couldn't understand the hate
for Mark. You know, I could never
understand the hate for Seaside Mark
with the whole benefit thing. I could
never I could never understand it. I
could really really really never
understand it, you know. Never never
could. I don't know about you, Steven
Howard, but I never could. Honestly,
it's so It's [ __ ] mad.
I could never because a think about it.
Yeah. They they they chose to keep
watching Seaside Mark. And B, if he
wasn't [ __ ] over the benefit system,
someone else would would be doing it. If
he wasn't doing it, someone else would
be doing it and people continuously do it.
And not to be racist or anything because
I'm not racist, but it's it's nice to
actually see an English person [ __ ] the
system over than someone else as as
usual to be fair. So I I never I never
understood that that the whole seaside
mark thing with the whole Marie and that
I don't know much about that. But I'm
talking about just the benefit thing.
I don't know much about that. But I know
like that just never made no sense
because there are people that
continuously [ __ ] the system over. It's
happening and it will always happen. So I mean
poor [ __ ] poor [ __ ] you know.
I hate When did I say I hate the
English? Did you not just listen to what
I just said? I said it's nice that if
someone is [ __ ] over the system, it's
a it's a English person. It's a British citizen. Poor [ __ ]
And think about it. Do you really think
Yeah. Steven? Yeah. Do you remember like
Suicide Mark? Yeah. about 8 years ago
when he was wearing them Ralph Lauren
shirts and ret and ret and you know even
if he got all these money legitimately
bro they'd still find a way to hate and
and and try to [ __ ] him over. I'm sure
of it. I'm sure of it, bro.
I'm sure there'd still be jealous people.
I'm sure there would still be I'm pretty
sure there would be
maybe if he maybe I don't know say he
got like inherited money or he won money
or I don't [ __ ] know he had a pension
or some legit way where he was no way
[ __ ] the system over. I I think he'd
still get hate. I generally think he would,
you know. Well, seaside. Well, what
Jenna? Well, seaside Mark used to have a
life, didn't he? Used to wear nice
clothes. Used to go out and do stuff.
You know what? And a lot of the people
in here don't even leave their [ __ ] house. So,
you know what I'm saying? A lot of the
people there don't leave their house
who sat in all day.
These people could never go out and
speak to women. They could never go out
and meet new people. I know that for a
[ __ ] fact. And it's not even a big thing either.
Yeah. I don't know much about that, bro.
But I know about the benefit thing, bro.
Like, cuz that's what's what they
started with the benefit thing. Oh, he's
on benefits and ret and no no. You know
what I'm saying?
So, what would you do? Okay. So, what
would you do? Okay. So, what would you
do, right? If Okay, let's just use this
analogy, right? So, what would you do if
I worked for one month? Yeah.
And then I won and I won second and I won,000
and I chose to not work ever again. What
what what would your opinion be?
and I and I got no money. I was just
living off the 50 grand. What then? What
would you say?
Would you still hate?
Would Would you still hate or what?
Because I don't know, bro.
I don't know, man. That's what I was
just thinking. I was thinking exactly
the same thing before you said it.
It's cuz they're they're biased, bro.
For some reason, they like him.
Well, what would you do? What would you
So, you you wouldn't have a problem with that?
Okay. So, you So, you wouldn't have a
problem with that?
It doesn't matter if it would last long
or not. I'm just saying what would you
do, you know? Yeah,
but it's weird because you tell people
to work and even if they did work, you
would try to make them lose their job.
So, I don't really understand that one
to be honest with you.
You would literally try to make people
lose their job if they worked. So,
it's very weird. There's I feel like
there's a lot of hate and bitterness and
jealousy on this community, but it's
with it's within with these people.
Steven Howard, it's within.
It's like um
it comes from within
a lot of these people.
No, I wouldn't.
I like that. How hard can it be, man? He
has actually come on my door. I like I
like that guy, bro.
He doesn't bother anyone. He doesn't try
to troll anyone. I know who he is, bro.
I know who he is.
He's a He's a Nah, bro. No, no, no. Bro,
stop talking [ __ ] Stop talking
[ __ ] about what you've said and
done, bro. Even it, bro. Tik Tockers get
hate. Streamers get trolled the [ __ ] out
of. And they ain't done nothing. They
ain't done nothing. They get swatted.
They get policed. There was This guy
almost got shot in America.
And they never said anything about kids.
They ain't done anything bad.
So why do they get a load of [ __ ] They
these t these streamers get mad hate,
bro. The same way as I do.
You know what I'm saying?
They get mad hate, bro. They get mad
[ __ ] done to them and they ain't done nothing.
They ain't done nothing at all. Just
they simply just don't like them. So yeah,
they get a lot of [ __ ] I'm not scared
of LT, Joe. How could I be scared of LT
when I messaged him calling him a biased
[ __ ] and done a video on him? Bro, no
one's scared like you.
But I love how you avoided what I just
said. These these kick streamers get
more [ __ ] than I get. They ain't spoke
about kids. They ain't done anything but just be
just a bit arrogant.
Trust me, they get a lot more hate than
me, mate. You're always going to get
hateful, jealous people on this community.
You're always going to get that.
You're always always going to get that.
I just don't know how people find the
time for it. It's [ __ ] mad. I could
not Yeah. It doesn't matter what someone
does or what someone says. I couldn't
dedicate my life to stalking someone
every day. That is mad to me.
There isn't a reason
that that Ed Matthews gets a lot of [ __ ]
and there isn't anything he's done. I
don't think there is anything he's done bad.
I don't think so. I think people just
don't like him because he's a [ __ ]
But he hasn't done anything
as in like he hasn't done or said any
mad stuff. He's got no convictions
against him or anything. So, and people
really [ __ ] with them, bro.
Really bad, bro. Like, they call the
police everywhere they go and
everything. So, nah.
Yeah, but that's not He's a [ __ ] as
in he's arrogant.
So, what? So because someone's arrogant
and a bit of a [ __ ]
that means you can get them swatted. So
you're always going to find reasons to
not like people. Being a [ __ ] is not
a big enough excuse. I mean, I come
across [ __ ] all the time. Does that
mean I should go and knock him out?
Because I because they're [ __ ]
Well, I didn't get come across any
[ __ ] on Thursday.
Yeah, but not everyone's going to like
everyone. That's the point I'm trying to
make is not everyone's going to like everyone. So,
Some people like him, some people don't
like him. So, not everyone's going to
Not everyone's Not everyone's going to
like him. Some people like him, some
people don't like him.
Do you get what I'm saying? So,
but I assume people do it to him as well
cuz they're also jealous. Stephen Howard. Yeah.
Yeah. But then you like non legs, Joe.
Of course I'm unlikable. Yo, bro. I'm
younger. I'm better looking than you.
That's why you That's where it comes
from. It comes it comes from jealousy
with you people. And I and I swear by
it's jealousy with these people. I swear
I will swear to I'm blue in the face
that it's jealousy with these people.
And I can back it up as well. And I can
back up what I mean as well.
Yeah. So then why don't you Okay. So why
don't you comment on some of his [ __ ]
that he says that you don't agree with?
Not about me.
Not about me. Just in general. Why don't
you say, "Oh, I don't I think you're
this. I think you're that." Of course,
you have similar views on me. You're
both obsessed with me.
You're actually You're actually both
obsessed with me. So,
yeah, you're both obsessed.
I could never be obsessed with I
couldn't even be [ __ ] obsessed with a
woman nowadays, let alone a [ __ ]
other man. You got some time on your
hands, you two, man. You really got some
time on your hands.
I couldn't even be this obsessed with a
[ __ ] woman, bro. There was someone I
was speaking to all day yesterday,
Stephen Hour, and I haven't even
messaged them today. I haven't even
messaged them back. Can't be [ __ ] And
then there's Joe F casually with his
[ __ ] boyfriend stalking a man all
day. It's mad
as as you do. It's [ __ ] wild, bro.
It's [ __ ] absolutely wild.
I haven't even messaged them back. I was
talking to them all day yesterday. Yeah.
I can't I because I couldn't I couldn't care less.
I'll never stop biting my nails, bro.
Cuz I couldn't care less.
I genuinely couldn't care less. I'm not
going to [ __ ] them over though. If they
if they actually want to meet, I'm not
going to [ __ ] them over. I [ __ ] that
other one over at Waxies cuz she was
being a little [ __ ] There was a reason for it.
But I'm not going to I'm not just going
to [ __ ] someone over. You know what I'm
saying? For the sake of it. They were
that they was an absolute [ __ ] They
were being an absolute [ __ ]
Try to be passive aggressive and that
and think they were better than me. [ __ ]
you. You know, so yeah, that's why I done that.
Yeah, it's on my community post.
Okay, I can't. Well, maybe you should
tell your boyfriend that you can only
get disabled, fat, ugly women, Joe.
Maybe you should tell your boyfriend
that he can't get anyone um that isn't vulnerable.
that he can't get anything other than
vulnerable since you don't like him. You
should ask him that. I'm surprised you
haven't. Oh, yeah. I only done £10 on it
though, which I don't even class that as gambling.
I put £10 on the football bet.
So to me, that's not gambling. So I only
put£10 on it, bro.
Yeah, basically. Yeah.
Yeah. I I met two women, Joe, um on
Thursday and they were from Boston. Oh no.
The only two Americans that I met that
were from Boston. What's What's with all
with all of that, Joe?
What was that all about, Joe?
Yeah, you are. You are sad.
I got a steak foot today, Grezy.
I bought a couple of days food shop. Yep.
Oh, that's not nice to say that. Uncle
Andy, you don't need to be jealous.
Nah, not T-Bone. I didn't go to the butchers.
I got a nice sirloine steak. Ooh,
that's going to be yummy. Why not?
So why can't why can't Joe F be um
one of the brothers, Stephen?
What do you mean my track record?
Nope. Nope. I'm not meeting Ojo. Nope.
Just a collection.
Do you not understand? I'm I'm only collecting.
No, I don't I don't meet evil people.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
Why Steven Joe's one of the brothers, bro?
Why isn't he one of the brothers?
O Grezy, I can't get over that AI yesterday, bro.
Oh my god.
I can't get over that.
Would you say it's pretty accurate then?
you say it's pretty accurate?
If you liked her despite the copying culture
or still like her now, that's your own
taste, not borrowed.
Big up AI. copying.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, man. I love I love
this chat. EBT. Yeah,
I think so too, Grezy.
I asked my mom about you, Grevy. I said,
"What do you think of Greavvesy?" She
said, "Oh, you seem a nice enough chap."
And then I said to Laney, "Nah, I think
he's trolling me. Yeah,
Laney doesn't know that you're trolling me."
Copy. All right. Um, did you see my
community post, Grezy?
What did I put up on my community posty?
What did I put up?
Well, considering it hasn't started yet, maybe no.
No, the bet hasn't he hasn't started
yet. The game's
I saw a cat today um Steven Howard
outside someone's [ __ ] door.
What do you reckon it was doing?
Grezy. Yeah, you get a new one every couple days.
O yeah. No, generally, man. Yeah, every
couple of days. Grezy.
Yeah, I saw a cat outside someone's
front door today. Greavvesy, it was
looking at me. What do you think it was doing?
Yeah, it was just outside someone's
[ __ ] front door.
Yeah, maybe I'll message that person.
You said you want to talk to them, don't you, Greavves? copycat saving. Oh,
I'm not sure. It was probably that
that's probably Steven Howard under that account. No.
Do you remember AI Greavesy? They said a
lot of people spoke about Cheryl Cole
because they were insecure.
Greavvesy. Yeah, Timmy does copy people
though. Greavvesy, he does. Do you not
remember when I got a haircut like a
couple of years ago and then he got a haircut?
Yeah, he does. Yeah, Timmy does copy people.
And what is Timmy in this community?
Yeah, a copycat community. No, he does copy people.
So, what is Timmy then, Greavvesy?
What's the verdict?
Have you got the verdict yet?
No, that silver golf thing made me laugh, bro.
Who's your money on um Gregy if this
Joseph Ra shows up in Nottingham?
Who's your money on?
Peter Bell is a big [ __ ] nowadays,
bro. All them ribs that I eat, Greavves, the ribs,
you know, the curries and stuff.
I'm a monster now. Weezy,
I'm a monster. That's why Joe F knows he
will never he will never meet me.
He says that he's not meeting me in
Nottingham. He says that he will see me
when he sees me, which basically means
he's he's he's shhat it. Basically, he
shat his pants.
You like one of Peter Belly's punches.
Trust me, Greavvesy.
Okay, Grey, you still didn't answer me.
So, what is Timmy then?
I remember when I started playing live
roulette again a little bit after Timmy
was playing live roulette.
He was also playing live roulette. We
so what's the verdict we see?
So how can you describe Timmy Aldridge?
I would, but I I'm too busy collecting
women in Lego Grezy.
So you know. Yeah.
Do you know why I'm not trolling this
person? Greasy. It's so hard to actually
like approach someone and get a number
and then get them reply back and stuff
like you'd be very stupid to you cuz
you're just trolling yourself. It's all
right on Instagram or you know dating
apps and stuff but you've actually had
to go out there and put the effort in,
bro. That's you're just trolling
yourself. You can do it once you've met
them a couple of times.
You can start being silly. Do you know
what I mean Greavvesy? No,
I'll tell her once I've met her a couple
times, meet me a couple times, I just
say that, "Yeah, you're I kind of I've
kind of got a collection."
And how many And how many
how many years
did Timmy get for it?
Did he did he do prison time or did he
get a file or what?
This is a copycat community. Yeah.
And what did he do as soon as he got out? Wow.
What did he do as soon as he got back out?
What a [ __ ]
Grievy, do I do I ask you questions
knowing that um knowing the answer already? Greasy.
I ask you when I know the answer
already. That's what that accountant
used to do. I used to ask them questions
and then I used to answer it when I used
to say like um
why did my mama leave me?
She said, I said, "Why didn't she tell
me she was my mama Grezy?" And he
replied saying, "She wanted to keep it a
secret, Peter Belly.
She wanted to keep it a secret."
And I said, "Well, what about the other
woman I had one night like Stan with?"
She said, "That woman, that woman was
never your mama."
To me, Grezy
was never your mama.
Do you remember that one, Greasy, when
when that that same person used to come
in and take the mick out of me?
He said there's nothing Peter Belly can
do to change these [ __ ] sit with
these [ __ ] women. Do you remember?
Maybe if I do some approaching videos
and put it back on my main channel,
he'll come back in it. Like you said,
Greavvesy, he's picking his moment, in it. Yes.
I love that [ __ ] chat. GBT, bro.
I'm going to ask it some more things.
I'm going to ask you some What's that?
Okay. So, I've asked um chat GBT, "Women
hate me because I'm not black." Hey,
that sounds really painful to feel, and
I'm sorry you're carrying that around.
Feeling rejected or visible can mess
with your head. I want to be careful
here, though, because women hate me
because I'm not black is a really heavy
conclusion. And it's also it's almost
and it's almost not it's almost
certainly not the full story. When
you've had a streak of bad experiences,
your brain looks for one clean
explanation. so it hurts less. But that
explanation can end up being way harsher
than it actually is. A few things that
might help reframe this. Women aren't a
single group with one preference.
Different people want different things
when attraction doesn't have them.
I'm just reading this.
Yes, people said Sher Walker was fit
largely because they generally found her
attractive but copycat bam web
absolutely played played a part two.
Both things were true at the same time.
How it worked back then. and Greavesy.
Early on, a lot of people did
independently think she was fit. Once
tabloids, TV shows, lads, mags, and
factor kept repeating it, calling her
fit became socially reinforced, saying,
"Yeah, she go turned into a default low
effort opinion." Especially in the UK,
you'd hear it even from people who
probably hadn't thought deeply about it.
It doesn't mean everyone secretly
disagreed. It just mean some people
generally fancied her. Some people
thought she was fine but overrated. Some
people echoed it because it was the accepted take. One second.
I'm on chat. DBT. One second.
This is what it says. Um, greasy masculinity
policing. Saying if you don't
if you don't fancy her, you're gay was
less about her and more about placing
straight male identity. It was a cheap
way to enforce confirmity, shut down
disagreement, embarrass someone into
going along with the group. Uh,
so it wasn't in security thing, was it?
Then um greasy. Copycats.
[ __ ] little copycats. You are right.
I'll be back later. Yeah.
See you in a