[snorts] Yo, [clears throat]
I feel really, really, really, really
sorry for these people, man. I really
feel bad for them.
Bullied all their life, closeted gays.
You got to feel sorry for these people,
man. You really have got to feel sorry
for these autistic people. Really,
they come online trying to bully people,
but they just bully themselves.
I feel really bad for these bully
victims, man. I really feel really
really bad for them.
They really really have been bullied
their whole life.
It shows like how much they come on
YouTube and they hate and stuff. It's
sad, isn't it?
Really, really sad.
There's me thinking in 2026 they would
have got a life.
No, they haven't got no life.
Yeah, I only I only done I only done a
10 pound bet.
This account was like, "Oh yeah, how you
lost. You can't stop losing, bro. I lost £10."
These people really are bully victims.
Proper proper tryh hard bully victims,
bro. Like for real. They really really
are. I know, bro. I lost 10 pound. Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I know, bro. What am I going to
do? I lost 10 pound.
They're such repeating disabled losers.
I'm coming off this community anyways,
bro. So, after today, I'm not going to
be live for a little bit. I'm talking to
this person as well, so I don't really
need to be on here anymore. So, yeah,
bro. That's that.
Can't cuddle to cope with what, bro? Huh?
What? Self projecting, repeating ugly
people. Why would I need to cross? Why
would I need to cuddle crush for that? The [ __ ]
I went on J L earlier and it was the
same bully victim people. They've
literally got no life, Dusty. They have
literally got nothing going for
themselves. Just YouTube. YouTube is all
these disabled people know.
Mad, bro. It's literally all these bully
victims know is YouTube.
Sad, isn't it, bro?
YouTube every day.
I was just looking at I was like, "Fuck,
bro. These people are older than me.
Sad sad disabled bastards.
Yeah. Anyways, after this live stream, I
won't be on for a long time. Very long
They're proper autistic. They also stalk
people's bets as well, Greavvesy.
They're such losers. That's how you know
in this community they're obsessed losers. Cuz
like some of them will do a bet. Yeah.
Other people will do a bet, right? And
then they they they stalk your bets.
That's how you know they're just life bully victims.
There's not even a point of even being
on here anymore.
You know what I'm saying? And I get
accused of being a [ __ ] troll. No way, bro.
Well, it's probably cuz they're too
skinned to do their own bet. [ __ ] retards.
I'm surprised I'm not [ __ ] completely
brain damaged to be fair.
You go it, bro. It's just the same boring people.
It's just the same boring ass repeating
people. Uh, have you have you gone on
it? We're live streaming that.
It's just the same old boring repeating
old farts. They're boring as [ __ ]
Should they be out with their mates
today since they've got all of this
money and all these friends and everyone
else is this and everyone else is that?
Think about it. Yeah.
I've got no life on here, bro, at all. Crazy.
They really got no life for you. [gasps]
Yeah, you don't have a life at all. Trust me.
Someone on thing is wrote, "Oh,
Mon and Jo is obsessed with each other."
Firstly, um I'm not obsessed with this
[ __ ] He's the one that posts about me.
And secondly, what is it with all of
these ugly people calling someone better
looking than them a month?
Again, a mirror is a good investment for
a lot of these people.
They're calling people that are
literally better than them in life. How
does that even make sense? [ __ ] retards.
Yeah. The [ __ ] bro?
They're little disabled comments. Yeah, mom. Disabled,
ugly, fat people. They got a life. [clears throat]
They got a life. I had a lovely steak for dinner.
But yeah, I won't be on it from
tomorrow. No reason now. Literally no
reason. I'm going to start going out and
talking to this person. Yeah,
this is a disabled community.
[snorts] Nah, bro. It was only only lost£10. Nah.
>> [clears throat]
>> No, bro.
You know, you know, Captain,
and it's not even that anyways. I'm
going to start I'm going to uh start
going out of your week again soon
anyways when the weather gets a bit better. So, um
yeah. So ei e e e e e e e e e e e e e e
e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e
e e e e e either way. Yeah.
Now Grey, can you do me a favor?
If I'm uh when I'm off of here for a
little bit cuz I need to do stuff. I
need you to do me a favor. I need you to um
record basically everything a lot of the
time and I need you to email me in maybe two weeks.
So obviously I can come back with the
evidence that these people have got no
life and they're on YouTube,
you know, and obviously I want to ask a
lot of questions as to why you're on
YouTube every day if they've got this
fantastic life. So you're going to need
to um yeah record a lot of stuff.
You're used to recording stuff. I need
you to email me in two weeks. So
whenever I come back like a month, whatever. Um, yeah.
I want to see if these people still be on YouTube
or did they get a life music?
So, what if I go to a restaurant
tomorrow, um, Greavvesy,
and I record it and put on YouTube, then what? >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, I already ate I cut myself steak and mushrooms.
It was [clears throat] lush. Yeah, bro.
Oh, bless you then. Chicken and chips from where?
Yeah, [clears throat] I'm not having a
takeaway now for a couple of days.
Is that all right with you, Greasy Boss?
[snorts] You know the thing is, Grezy,
the longer you go without them, the more
you crave them.
You got me.
Oh, bless you. Then
what is it? Fried chicken.
[snorts] Fried chicken. Nice. Nice.
Like I said, I've already ate
I fancy a milkshake though, you know,
like a McDonald's one, but I I'll just
make myself a cup of tea.
I'm having a roast dinner tomorrow. Greasy.
Beef and gam. Smoke's coming.
[clears throat] Yeah.
Yeah, man. I have a take away in a
couple of days. Yeah.
Do you like this community then? Greavves.
Yeah, I lost 10 pound today. Hey,
grieves you. This person on Reddit said,
"Oh, okay. You seem like you you don't
seem like you were too pushy. I would
advise against voice text. Personally,
unsure about the general female
populist, but I prefer stream comfortable someone."
She didn't say anything about them
agreeing to meet and they're not doing greasy.
What's your opinion on that?
She didn't really say much. I sent her
10 screenshots. Um Grey
didn't mention anything about the
leading on the ghosting.
Strange. Anyways, let me make myself a
cup of [ __ ] Oh,
wonder why that is. Greasy. Why she
didn't say anything?
Just completely dismissed it.
I only gambled£10 today, bro. I I've
quit gambling when you can't really
[ __ ] count, you know, betting£10 as
gambling, man. Come on.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, [ __ ] that.
The industry's finished.
You can't dismiss £10. Well, I [ __ ] can.
I can [ __ ] dismiss £10.
are UK asylum. Can you answer me since
[ __ ] Greavves is in? I showed this
person my um
text on Reddit. She's like, "Oh, okay.
You don't seem like you were too pushy.
I would advise against using voice text
personally and show about general." Why
didn't she say anything about the
leading on Greasy?
He's obviously read the the combos. Strange.
It's just ignorant, isn't it?
Why would you Why would she dismiss that, Greasy?
You want to give your opinion on it?
You know what? I'm actually going to
make myself a hot chocolate.
>> [clears throat]
>> Why do you think you pay silent?
Why do you think she dismissed it?
She read the messages and stuff. She
wasn't rude or anything, but she didn't really
latch on to like just saying they were
going to meet. They never
being ignorant, is they?
I wonder why.
I can hope that ain't a gender thing. [ __ ] mad.
I like everyone to be seen as equal. You
know, I'm that kind of person.
I'm that kind of person, you know.
So, what are you going to do? Um, when
I'm off here, Greavves, you're just
going to wait until I come back.
Yeah. The eyes never lie. Grieves me.
That's what Ant-Man said to me. The eyes
never lie. The eyes never lie.
Are you So you going to wait until I
come back then?
Will you just wait? I guess.
That's quite nice.
The hot chocolate.
So, you just got to wait, I guess. Oh, lovely.
In bed with a nice malta hot chocolatey.
What more could you want?
What [ __ ] more could you want?
How was your fish?
It's nice. Would you have a hot chocolate? >> No.
Oh, it's nice.
A five guys milkshake today. Greasy.
Yeah, I was speaking to her earlier. Greasy.
Yeah, she seems like fun. [clears throat]
She seems like fun.
>> [clears throat]
>> The other numbers didn't reply back,
which kind of makes me sad. I was hoping
the American was going to reply back.
Her little words and her little voice
was cute. Greavesy, I met her at Waxies.
Grey, I met her at Waxies.
I might do a little waxy stream for you
when I go again. Greavvesy.
>> [clears throat]
>> How about that, Gregy?
[clears throat] Yeah, I should just I
should have just done two [ __ ] teams,
but the thing is if you do, you got a
lot of money on it, and I didn't fancy
lumping money on two teams. So,
You get what I mean? Greasy.
So why do nons legs go to waxies then? Indie guy
UK asyl him. [snorts]
I don't think I've had it. I know what
it is, though. It's that noodle place.
It's a noodle place, isn't it?
It's a It's a noodle place now.
Think I might have had it once.
might have had it once years ago.
Oh, what if I go tomorrow to walk to
walk greasy? What would you call me?
If I go tomorrow, [laughter]
did you actually set your alarm then?
Yeah, for 11. I think I was four or five
minutes late. Sorry,
couldn't get signaly. Sorry about that. But yeah,
you know what's so mad, Grezy, is the
thing that I was saying about um Chevro
Cole and that that AI thing confirmed
everything I was saying was true. So I
was right all along, wasn't I, Grezy,
about the insecurity to blend in with the crowd,
fit in with the crowd. I said, "Yeah, it
was basically everything I said was
right, wasn't it? Tell me, Greavves, I
wasn't right about that. Yeah,
I was pretty much spot on, wasn't I?
I just had a feeling.
I just had this feeling, Grezy.
You know, it's all about the name, not
about the person, it's the name.
I was 100% spot on with that. Yep. Oh, crash. He's here.
He's my little mate.
Yeah, I lost £10.
Why is she be posting about me?
Yeah, we lost.
You didn't put £50 on that bet. Stop talking [ __ ]
You didn't put 50 on that bet.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Bet you then [snorts]
Can I eat the chicken with you, Greasy? Wait,
how many pieces of chicken are you getting?
How many pieces?
How many pieces are you getting? G again.
No, I'm just asking you a question.
Chicken and chips.
Let me look at the chicken. I I know a
nice chicken and chip shop.
How many pieces?
I normally have four pieces.
What? And ship share.
You know what? I might be I might be a
big fat dirty stinking copycat today
considering I'm off YouTube for a while after today.
Oh well. I don't like mayo though.
I don't like mayo, you know.
So you're getting free free and and and chips, right?
Free pieces and chips.
Right. I'm ordering it.
I ordered it.
There we go. Job done bum. Job done.
Probably you should say that I found a
nice chicken shop I ordered from the other day. Any opinion
and your opinion Gra chicken
right wait until it comes.
Well, about an hour and a half ago, you
had a steak. Steak and mushrooms.
But I need I need I need my um I need my
vitamins, don't I? I got this big fight
tomorrow. Don't I
got a big fight tomorrow. So,
Nope. I don't want it. Did you?
She said, "I think they were leading you on.
Can't wait till my chicken comes. Grey,
what am I being today? Grey, what am I being? >> [laughter]
>> And then when I And then when I have a
takeaway, you can copy my one. God, you
can copy my one. Little copycat.
A dirty stinky copycat. [laughter]
take away because um you're getting a takeaway.
Did you know that, Grezy?
There's no other reason other than
you're getting one. Did you know that?
No, I'm getting it from a chicken a nice
chicken shop. It's not KFC though. [snorts] Yep.
Like you said, Gre, it's a copycat
community, is it?
So, how was I right then, Greavves, you
answer me this? Yeah, since I copied
your order. Yeah, and I'm serious. How
was I How did I know about the Sher Cole
thing? Cuz AI said that I'm completely right.
It seemed like I got it spot on.
No, it won't be cold.
no, not chicken and chips. It's not
Burger King or McDonald's, bro. Not
everything comes cold.
So, how did I know then, Greasy? It was
a It was a copycat culture. Yeah.
So is that where nons legs got it from then Greavvesy?
So is that where he got it from? Ah, see.
Did you like the example they gave
Boozy? Um, an example. You're gay if you
don't like your girl. They said it so
they said it so [ __ ] like blunt. You
know what I mean? Grezy. They said it so bluntly.
What's it copying culture
thinking? Don't be
Yeah, I remember them days.
So, what do you think about this person
I'm speaking to, Grievy?
You reckon we'll we'll get on well?
So why why am I
so why wouldn't I be a matchy?
Why wouldn't I be a match? Why not?
Yeah, but I'm wanting to meet someone. Seriously, grievy.
I'm willing to, you know, want to be with someone. All right. No.
Oh, but she knows I'm atheist. Greasy.
She knows I'm atheist. I didn't lie
about my like my religion or that.
You get me, Grezy.
I didn't lie about any of that stuff.
And she's not Catholic either. So I
didn't lie. I didn't say, "Oh, I said
that I'm not Muslim. I'm not a Christian." Or
she didn't seem
like how I say like it's it's hard to explain. Yeah,
but there's only one thing I'm thinking of, Reeves,
and I'm not going to that might be a
problem. I'm sure you can work that one out. Yeah,
haven't heard from that one off
Instagram for a couple of days. Greasy.
It seems like she'll still give me a chance. Greavvesy,
I just think she wants to meet someone
that doesn't mess her around or cheat on her.
You get me, Greavvesy.
Yeah, cheating is bad. I don't know why people cheat.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
I mean, we're we're I mean, we're normal
people. It's the lovely mongs that aren't normal.
It's the lavry [ __ ] Mongs that aren't normal.
I finished that steak in about 5
minutes. I had uh steak and mushrooms
and I completed it in about 5 minutes.
Finished it in about 5 minutes.
What's your opinion on that, Grezy?
Not even joking.
I held it.
No, I don't have it rare.
I have it well on medium. All
right. Do you want to know what this
person said to me on Reddit? grievy. She said
she said that's weird, my dude.
I said I said I want validation and control. Grezy,
what's your opinion on that? Z. Nope.
>> [clears throat]
>> Come on. food. Nope.
Hey, Steven Hour. Do you know um Virgin
Boy by and Red Star? They've got a
Facebook chat just about me.
Wow. They need to come out the closet, bro. Proper stalkers
by Steven Howard lad.
I don't know what the pieces are, but
they picked up when it comes.
What? Yeah, they're definitely
definitely gay, bro.
They're taking they're taking stalking
to the next level, bro.
They're definitely definitely gay boys,
bro. They're definitely gay.
>> I'm telling you, bro. 100%, bro. Him,
that Red Star, and Joe, they're gay,
bro. I promise you, they're [ __ ]
I 100% promise you they're class A
[ __ ] bro. I wasn't even using it as
an insult, bro. I was being for real.
No, they're proper proper gay boys, bro.
Proper proper gay boys.
Come out, bro. It's 2026. [ __ ] hell,
man. You know, it's not that on It's not even that
Stephen, bro, just make a new account. Yeah,
because I'm coming off here for a bit
anyways, bro, cuz I need to sort this
thing out. But I mean, coming back Yeah.
Madness, isn't it, lad?
They are gay, bro. Definitely gay.
They're definitely definitely gay, bro.
They're 100% a [ __ ]
For someone to spend all their life on
the internet stalking another man,
they're definitely a [ __ ] Reaction,
no reaction, they're gay, bro.
They are actually gay, lad. Yeah. proper.
They're proper gay [ __ ]
>> Yeah, it's come out the closet already,
man. [ __ ] hell. Yeah, man.
Why is Joe F not a brother? Steven Howard,
he gave himself away too easy, man.
Too too easy. Cuz he's a thick bastard.
He gave himself away too easy, lad.
Kieran's a brother, but he's not on here
much. That's the thing. [snorts]
Yeah, they are definitely gay, bro. Definitely gay.
Definitely are gay.
Of course he is, bro. As soon as he
started saying, "Oh, how can he be a
virgin if he's got a girlfriend?" You
You know, straight away, bro.
I clocked it straight away. I don't know
about you. I clocked it straight away,
bro. When he was sucking his dick every
time I was calling him what he is, what
he was, and what he is, it's so obvious, bro.
Then the obsession came again with me
like, "Bro, sort your gayness out, bro.
I don't swing that way.
I literally don't swing that way, bro.
I literally don't swing that way.
[ __ ] [ __ ] Gay little [ __ ] I
am coming off here, bro. After tomorrow,
I am coming off here, bro. 100%.
I'm going to I was just clown tomorrow
and then I'm coming off here, bro.
So, they can't try and talk [ __ ] And
then I'm definitely coming off here, bro.
[ __ ] weird stalkers, bro.
Getting happy over someone losing 10
pound. They really are life's losers, bro.
They're literally life's losers. I've
got your email anyway, Steven Howard. So,
yeah, cuz they're gay, bro. Do you not
understand? It's cuz they're [ __ ]
batty men, bro. They're gay.
They're [ __ ] gay lords. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. Don't worry.
I'm coming off her after tomorrow
anyways, bro. When this clown don't show up. Yeah. So,
I'm not even that hungry. I just bought
it cuz Greasy bought it. The chicken.
I could still eat. I could still eat if
that makes sense.
So, it's not like I won't be eating it.
So, what will happen if I come up here,
Stephen Howard? Will they stop stalking
me every day?
What they'll do is they'll probably try
to find you on Reddit, but they can't
find me on Reddit.
They can't find me on nowhere, bro,
because they don't know what subreddits
I go on. So, yeah,
the losers will be [ __ ] Yeah.
What do you mean never, Steven Howard? Never. What? Yeah.
Starve the [ __ ] in it. Starve the losers
cuz think of it reason they would do it
unless they were gay.
Like realistically Steven Howard yet the
only reason they would do this is if
they were gay.
Think of it, bro. I messaged someone
today um the person I was talking to all
day yesterday cuz I wanted to talk to
them to see you know whatever. So you're
invested. You're interested in that
person. No. So for these people to do
what they do every day, they must be
gay. They have to be back. There's no
other way. There's no They do it for reaction.
No, they're gay. No, they're [ __ ]
There's a big difference. There's not
going to be no fight tomorrow because
the little [ __ ] [ __ ] ain't going
to show up. And after tomorrow, I'm
making a new channel, bro. 100%. I am
making a new channel after tomorrow.
when this [ __ ] don't show up.
I'm done with these retards.
You got my email anyway, Steven Hour,
lad. So, I'll send you a new channel. Yeah. Yeah, that's it.
Cuz I don't want Yeah. Even if I go live
every two weeks. Yeah. Every two weeks.
every month. I don't want them getting
satisfaction out of recording me. I want
to starve them of content. Do you
understand me, bro? So, obviously, if
they can't find you, then yeah, they
might still post, but they won't have anything new.
The little gaylords, the little [ __ ]
Red Star, Jamie, just absolute life bum
loser little virgins.
They won't have nothing then. So, you
understand, lad. So, it's best that way.
Trust me, bro. I know what I'm doing.
I don't want you. I don't want to. [ __ ]
you. You're not getting my ass. So that's that.
It's not my problem. Your closet is gay. Simple, bro.
No, no, no. Yeah.
You know what? So, um
cuz I don't want these people following me anymore.
I don't want these stalkers following me.
Yeah. I don't want these lo and I'm not
going to tell them about it either. like LJ,
Gay Thompson, Gay Farra, Gay Star, you
get me? I don't want these people
following me about.
They will not find me. They will not
find me. I've got a new channel and they
haven't found it. They will never find
me. The only reason they found me
because I linked it on Reddit. They will
never find me. They can't find me. I've
already got a new channel with cold
approaches on it and it's got zero
subscribers. They will never find me.
They're not God, bro. They're not
[ __ ] God. They won't find you unless
you link it to them or you put it out
there. They're not going to find you.
You know how many YouTube channels there
are? It's not going to happen.
I guarantee you they won't find me.
Well, I guarantee you they won't.
They won't find you.
Yeah, they'll never find me, lad.
right. It's on its way.
No, they won't find me.
They definitely definitely won't find me.
No, they definitely definitely won't.
There's people on here that have
Facebook chats about me, Grevy.
Like, it's 2026. Come out as gay. It's
not even like a a thing anymore in 2026
where, you know, you need to be ashamed or anything.
>> [clears throat]
>> just come out as gay.
You know what I mean? Grezy. Seriously, bro.
They seriously seriously need to come
out of the closet and get a life.
in it. Steven Howard
There's load there's so many YouTube
channels. They won't find you.
Trust me, they're [ __ ]
They're not good, bro. These people are
not god. You all you got to do is use a
different subreddit, post on Reddit, new
channel. That's it. They're [ __ ]
There's nothing they can do.
These are all homosexuals. Trust me. Yep. Yeah.
I give you I'll give you my new channel.
Um Greavves it. No. No. Yeah.
I unboxing my new um channel, bro.
I know these little gay weirdos follow me. [snorts]
Crazy. So yeah.
do a video to this Smokey Bear Gy
and when he doesn't show up, which he's
not going to show up,
then yeah, I'm off, bro. So, yeah. Yeah, bro.
Quite far this shop.
Yeah, they're proper gay, bro.
Proper proper guy. >> Yeah.
gay boys. That's what they are. Pack of >> [laughter]
>> Yeah, man.
[clears throat] Come on, man. We came here, bro.
We [snorts] need caring on it. We need
No, he didn't won the money game. Go
away, nonslegs lover. And no, he didn't
win the money game. I showed 5.7 grand
and he showed daddy savings years before
that and he can't show anything now. So
yeah, see you later. N legs lover
or you can have a timeout.
Definitely didn't win the money game
against me. I won the money game, the
better looking game, the better life
game. Nice Stephen um Stephen Howard.
The better money game, the better looks
game, the better women game, the better
life game. I'm loads of games, bro.
Uh, quite expensive, bro. Yeah, man.
You reckon if I come over here? Yes.
Stop going for launch?
I don't think so, bro.
Yep. That's me, lad. That's me.
That's definitely me. And I don't target
disabled women either.
I'm better looking definitely. And I've
got more than them as well.
It's just like what Ronald Pump said.
It's exactly what Ronald Pump said. I
should have took his advice, bro. But
you know, I'm still going to. Don't worry, lad. Yeah.
Yeah. Gay, bro.
They're [ __ ] proper gay.
proper proper proper gaylords.
I mean, they fancy me in it, Steven
Howard. I can't be that much of a mono
if they fancy me, bro. Think of it.
Jesus Christ. You can't be that much of
a M if you've got a bunch of [ __ ] men
wanting your ass every day, bro.
Must be doing something right.
Is that right, bro? Strange. Sad bastards.
Very, very sad bastards, lad.
Yeah, we'll see if this guy comes out tomorrow anyways.
And then I'm done with these people, bro. 100%.
Cuz some of us have got a life.
Isn't that right, Stephen Howard? Some
of us has got a life, mate. Some of us
has got a life.
I'm not, mate. I'm not going to be bored.
I'm not even balding. So stop self projecting.
So many self-reflectors on this community.
Do you remember that account that come
in earlier and said, "Oh, none of your
families have ever none of your families ever worked."
And I'm thinking, "What the [ __ ]
You don't [ __ ] know anyone in my
family what they do and what they
[ __ ] don't do.
Mad self projectors.
Mad mad mad self projectors
and the [snorts] thing is even now like
you ask them. Yeah. Even like this
[ __ ] Joe. Yeah.
They say they go for you every day
because of things you've said. But think
about it, bro. If they really had a
better life than you, they would just
live their life.
They literally would live their life and
not they would do the opposite of what
they're doing. If someone's a wrong in
there or they think someone's a a pedo
or they're a nons, they would literally
do the opposite as to what they're doing.
>> Yeah, they will. They will. They will
literally do the complete opposite.
Okay, think about it now. Um,
Stephen Howard. Yeah. So, say someone
new comes on the community. Yeah. and
they start saying mad stuff and they
they do mad stuff. What am I going to
do, bro? Stalk them every day for 4
years or am I going to live my life?
Think about it, bro. Just think about it
for a second.
Would you live your life or would you
stalk someone for four or five years?
And in four or five years, you can build
a nice body, you could travel to different countries,
uh you can meet the love of your life,
or would you be stalking a rando on
[ __ ] YouTube for four or five years?
Cuz I know what I'd be doing, bro. I
know exactly what I'd be doing.
So weird, is it, bro?
They are [ __ ] weird, man.
That's so weird.
But that's just a way um for them to
like justify their gayness
and jealousy by saying, "Oh, well, yeah,
you said stuff about people's [ __ ]
kids." So that's why like if they say
that, they think it justifies it because
they're gay and they're jealous. They're
jealous and they're gay and they hate
themselves as well. But by saying that,
they think in their head that it
justifies it. That's how [ __ ] stupid
they are, bro. So, yeah.
[ __ ] weird, bro. Very weird.
I'm 6 minutes away. Grievy. Yeah. [ __ ] hell.
I got the same as you.
I agree. I got the same as you.
I'm not even hungry hungry, but I can
eat. Does that make sense? >> [laughter]
>> You remember we she's fit.
[laughter] You know they used to say
they used to say that she was fit. [laughter]
Well, this woman on Reddit said, "Yeah,
Grezy, that I don't have any um human decency
cuz I got a you know what in the al
anyway." What do you think, Grezy? Is
that not having human decency?
I think they're quite selfish, you know. You know,
Nah, I'm not gay like you.
No, but I think they're kind of selfish,
you know, Grezy. It's like they want to
completely leave you without, don't they, Grezy?
So, that's not having any human decency.
I think you would do the same thing, Greasy,
if someone was coming on to you. I think you would definitely
don't like Ley. You would.
You would, wouldn't you?
>> [clears throat]
>> She said that um if she knew me in real
life, she'd pepper spray me. This person
on Reddit we
Is that funny?
That it's lucky we don't know each other
live. Are they trolling?
Why am I a fat bastard?
I wanted to copy someone else. We were
They were talking about fried chicken
and it made me want one and and I found
this really nice chicken shop that I got
from the other day. But I've also got
some chips. So, please have the chips, ma.
Yeah, have some with some chips. Some
salad and chips, ma.
I was copying
What was I doing? [laughter]
Yeah, you can have the chips. But I just
want a chicken. No, have some of the chips, please.
>> I'll force you to eat, ma.
>> No, but please have some. [snorts] Yeah. One sec.
>> Uh, one sec. >> Yeah.
>> Thank you, [ __ ]
No, no. [laughter] One second.
A minute. Yeah.
Oh, chips. Look, Bob. Have some chips.
They're hot, are they? What? They're not
They're not cold, are they? They're hot. Right.
What are you doing? Can you show here?
>> Oh, I got a phone. I got fire breast. I
got an egg. And I got a fire.
You did have some chips, lady. A nice there. I'm what?
I'm a bit copycat.
Lady thinks I'm a copycat.
Lady said I'm a big copycat. Mate,
you don't Why? It'd be interesting to
see what they say about incelss.
Well, just look at yourself.
You're the biggest incel going, lad.
You don't need to look it up, lad.
You're the biggest incel. Just f
look in the mirror.
Look where is this? Look,
I mean upstairs.
I I don't I only pick your mom, show you.
I picked your mom. Yeah. [snorts]
I picked your mom. [snorts]
Yo, another one that needs to get off
YouTube and get a life.
You've been on here for [ __ ] years every day.
I'm coming back.
I'm going to play it up.
>> [clears throat]
>> This is nice music.
M. It's not dry. It's crispy. [snorts]
Do you remember who used to eat like that crazy? M [clears throat]
I want to ask AI about white knights.
to ask them about white knights
and people that defend the women even
though women don't like him like a
certain virgin we know
The only thing you
is that the people that defend women
don't get women. Women don't like them.
do not find that the most maddest thing
that they don't women don't like them.
They've had less women than you or
they're virgins or they're not none of
them none of them get women and they
still stick by their side and stuck up
to them. Never understood that. Never never did.
Women history do not like them
and they still stick up for women.
Never understood them guys. Never did
I was virgin boys. Definitely a white light bro.
Joe Virgin boy is a proper white man lad. [clears throat]
How many times did how many times did
people on Lord J's channel say the word
skin today? And how many years have they
been doing it? And that answers that
answers your question.
How many times do we hear your skin?
How many [ __ ] times a day do we hear
the same repeating [ __ ]
Does that answer your question? [snorts]
They defend women, but women don't like them.
But they have no bad words to say. [ __ ] Jeez. It's bad.
I'm too busy nibbling on chicken. Oh,
Timmy said that you're toasty, by the way, Dusty.
I can't listen to this Timmy, bro. He
[ __ ] fries my brain, lad.
>> [clears throat]
>> Oh, Clint is just a self projected
little low life. He's another Ly Mong.
He's another He's another Ly Mong. Don't
mind him. He's another self projector.
Another Another one that's been bullied in school.
Is that why?
There's no point trying to like explain
anything to Timmy, bro. He's too
disabled. There's no point trying to
explain anything to him.
There's no point trying to explain
anything to him, bro. It's pointless. Pointless, lad.
I got three pieces of chicken. [snorts]
What's your opinion on that, Grezy? Again,
let's hear it one last time.
Greg, you got three pieces of chicken
and chips, dusty, and I got the same thing. [clears throat] [snorts]
I'm on the left piece now. Yeah. >> [sighs] [snorts] >> Yeah.
KFC's got the best chicken, bro.
This is okay, but
it was better the other day to be fair.
KFC's chicken's better.
I don't KFC's got the best chicken
though. That gy.
Yeah, pieces. Yeah, I think it's KFC
pieces. KFC's pieces are best. Um,
This bit's a bit dry. The leg bit. The
leg bit. Yeah. What did you call me?
A big fat copycat. That's not nice.
Can you have some of the scraps?
really. It was all right the other day.
>> Uh, [clears throat] it's called It's called One sec.
It's called Chickflick.
It sure is.
He sure is. Captain,
why am I attracted to children? I'm not
attracted to children.
Why do you keep repeating the same [ __ ] It's 2026.
Yeah. Is that Yeah. KFC's
Yeah. So, what's the best fried chicken
then? Um, Dusty.
I've never liked children, but your
boyfriend non legs does.
But your boyfriend non legs does. I'm
done anyways after tomorrow. Yeah. If
this guy shows up. Oh, no. Jobly. Job is
good. Chicken Dusty. Have you ever had Jobly?
Yeah, I've had Jobly. Job is nice. Job.
I used to go there when I finished work.
Dusty when I used to work. Yeah.
Yeah. There's one in Leicester Square.
It's nice. I used to have a lot of deliveries there. Anyways,
see you later, lad.
I know. And he's just a [ __ ] virgin. Lo, [clears throat]
Whether he does turn up or he doesn't
turn up, I'm quitting, bro.
Cuz I'm talking to this person now and I
want to like, yeah, I need to do [ __ ] in
life now. So,
can't be arguing with retards. Can't be
entertaining retards every day, lad.
Uh, there is no arrange time. That's why
I'm going to do a video tomorrow.
I don't think we did arrange a time. We
arranged a place but and the day we
didn't arrange a time. Was it Was it 1 p.m.?
I'd have to check, bro. I'll do a video
first thing in the morning anyways. Yeah.
Okay. 1 p.m. Yeah. Okay. [snorts] Okay.
Doesn't matter anyways, bro.
I'll be there. So, [ __ ] idiot.
And then I'm done, bro. I am done with these retards. >> [sighs] [snorts]
>> This is a proper disabled community, you
start. It's proper proper disabled.
It's proper disabled.
He's going to be at that field. He ain't
going to no [ __ ] field in Tottenham,
bro. [ __ ] off.
>> What you trying to do is get LT
involved. It's so obvious.
>> Yeah. Well, we'll see you tomorrow
anyways, bro. So, yeah. And Field and
Tottenham. I don't think so, bro.
I don't think so, Grezy. I don't think so. We'll see anyways.
And he's not going to win either.
Trust me, he's not going to win. Just
like Joe. Joe wouldn't win either.
Just like Joe wouldn't win,
you know. No, I'm going to do a video
and if he doesn't reply back, I'm not going.
I don't have to do anything.
So, I'm going to do a video. He's not
blocked. And if he agrees, if he still
confirms it, I'm going. If if I don't
hear from him, I'm not doing it. Simple. So, yeah.
Take another W until what? The next
time. And the next time, and the next
time, and the next time.
You just need to [ __ ] this gay community
off. It's gay as [ __ ]
That's what you need to do. You just
need to [ __ ] this gay [ __ ] off, bro. That's it.
[clears throat] Yeah, I know, bro. I know.
Gay, jealous, sad bastards, bro. That's
what they are, literally. [snorts]
See, Monty got off. You see,
people have different like [snorts]
times when they get off. I'm done, bro. [ __ ] done.
Off to tomorrow. So Yeah. Bye-bye. Now
I know he's a sad bastard.
He's a lavry mong.
Steven Howard is a lavry mong. Yeah. [clears throat]
Yeah, man. [snorts] So yeah. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
I guess that teaches me right for being
a copycat, don't it, Grezy? Getting dry chicken, huh?
All cuz I wanted to fit in.
Yeah, I am. Yeah.
Yeah. Does that serve me right for being
a big stinking copycat? [snorts] Yeah.
Used to troll trip rates as well, didn't you?
You poor [ __ ]
Didn't you? You poor [ __ ]
I'm having um beef and gammon tomorrow. Yeah. Yep. [snorts]
[sighs and gasps] [snorts] Yep. >> [snorts]
>> Yep. [sighs]
Oh, she's just she's just responded.
No, she just messaged me first. Um, not
responded. She just she just messaged me first. Greasy, one second.
Let me reply back.
See, Peter Belly's going to be having a
busy life soon. Peter Belly can't be on here, you know.
I'm too busy collecting. Yep.
Uh, what do you do?
You go and get a life.
That's what you do. You go and get a life, lad. Yep.
Nah. [clears throat]
Everyone's copying. Yeah.
What's everyone being today, Grezy?
What's everyone being today? Hat.
is that Q Greaves that I'm collecting.
Grieves, is it cute that I'm collecting
or do you not agree with it? Yeah. Yep. Movie. No. Nope.
Always wanted your phrase.
Monty will come back when he gets stumped.
A lovely question.
Oh, his little northeast dialect. Grezy. Greasy,
you're a troll. [snorts]
a lovely Christian
here. A lovely Christian, eh?
Um, no. I went to do a bit of food shopping today.
Um and come back. Yeah, I know.
He's taking the piss out of us. Yeah, he is. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, we've never seen him with a woman,
have we, Mr. Fraud?
We've only seen him singing women.
Could you imagine Lord J doing a cold
approach? Steven Howard
grieves in. It would never happen.
It would never ever happen. Do you know
what? Yeah, we we should actually ask
him to do one, bro. See if he can do it. No,
his anxiety wouldn't allow it.
His anxiety literally would not allow it.
Reckon you could do it, Grezy. I would approach sober.
I [ __ ] did at the [ __ ] train
station. [ __ ] um on Thursday. First
one in months.
First one in months.
It was the first one in months. I about 10 sober.
I think you could greasy. I think you could.
I think you could, lad.
You should try. You might meet a lovely Christian.
It would never happen.
It would never happen, lad. I'm in a I'm
on a [ __ ] toilet now. Serves me right
for being a [ __ ] copycat.
Yeah, Greasy. Get yourself down. Um, aesy.
What way do they say it like in a northern accent?
That sounds so weird.
What What do they have a northern accent
when they were saying it? Oh man,
I have my electric blanket on 247. question. [laughter]
Me and LT should go to waxy. Isn't it dusty?
My waxies was fun on Thursday, man.
I made a new friend.
I got a number. I think I think I got
one. How many numbers did I get? I think
I got one. Yeah,
it was [ __ ] Rams, bro. For Thursday.
You tried going there on a Saturday.
It is [ __ ] packed.
Can I take you to Waxies? Squeezy.
I take the wax to the gy.
I'm going to send it to my um I'm going
to send it to my army friend. I'm going
to say get yourself that maxis lad.
We just pretend it's today. And look at that video.
Do you remember we that account there
said poor [ __ ] He used to say them
army [ __ ] for laughing at you. And he
refrazy them [ __ ] for laughing at us.
Do you remember? Oh, I thought miss him
cuz I'm muted.
Do you remember them were laughing at
us? We do remember
laughing at us. [laughter]
You [snorts] know exactly the account
I'm talking about, don't you, Grecy?
You can't come off of YouTube and the
prime grooves of content. Pucker [ __ ]
You love that you gre. Yeah. [snorts] [laughter] [clears throat] Look
lovely Christian. But you're not Christian. Greasy.
You're not Christian. Oh gosh.
Oh gosh. Oh my god. Look at the state of
this [ __ ] toilet.
That will teach me for being a copycat.
Oh my god.
See It's not good being a copycat. Jeez. Damn. Hello, Copycat.
Oh, you [ __ ] coffee.
You have a big fat stink coffee. Copycat.
You're a big fat stinky copycat.
Are you going to say it again, Greasy?
He mentions that name.
You big fat stinky copycat.
You're a copycat.
You're nothing but a [ __ ] stinky dirty copycat.
Oh, it's so nice.
Groovy. Put the electric blanket on.
Warms up the cover. Yeah. Oh gosh.
A lovely Christian.
But you're atheist. Greasy.
You're an atheist. So [snorts]
maybe I'll give her to Nonsque Greavesy.
He won't message her, will he? If I put
the number on YouTube, like no one's
going to message her, are they crazy? Nah,
no one's going to stop. No one would
want to stop Peter Belly like finding
someone, would they? Greasy.
What do you think, Stephen? I You got to
watch out for the virgin.
You know when you meet someone grievy,
you got to watch out for the big virgin. [snorts] Nothing.
Nothing happened, lad.
Birmingham end of the month to finish slug.
Oh [ __ ] sake, Gregy. This has been
going on for years. Even with this Timmy
thing. How many times has this guy said
he's going to go to Birmingham to [ __ ]
um you know [ __ ] fight Slug.
This has been going on for [ __ ] years, man.
I thought this was going to stop in 2026. Grezy Yeah,
I might give nons legs this woman's number.
What do you think?
What do you think, Zard? >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, it's true. >> [snorts] >> Yep.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
What is that?
Because they're all Cuz they're all nons like him.
That's why Steven Howard. Because they're nons. Yeah.
That's why, lad. [clears throat] Yeah,
he is disabled.
Yeah, I know. I know. He's doing the same thing. Yeah.
I just think he needs to get laid me.
I just think he needs to lose his virginity.
Been saying it for years, lad. Oh yeah.
What's up, bastard? Good. Yeah,
maybe [ __ ] nonsense can go to waxies. Dusty Do
d do d do d d d d d d d d d d d d d d d
I want to come back. Yeah. This.