There we go, man.
Yeah. See, I told you, bro. He's a
[ __ ] idiot, man. Yeah.
Nothing, bro. Nothing. Can you hear me? Yeah.
What the [ __ ]
Oh yeah, no one cares about them
self-rejecting comments, bro. That's not
going to trigger anyone either. I know
what you're trying to do. You think,
"Oh, just because I'm [ __ ] mad at
this guy not showing up, you're going to say stuff."
Nah, bro. That's not going to bother no
one because they're just self-reflectors
on Lav's channel. So they, like I said,
they can't get anyone mad. They what
they do. Yeah. Is because you're [ __ ]
swearing and going [ __ ] mad cuz this
cunt's not showing up, they think that
they're going to self-reflect their life
and somehow it's going to trigger you. Nah, bro.
Old age ugly fat pensioners on YouTube
24/7 can't trigger no one, bro. They
just talk about themselves. I am pissed
off at this [ __ ] not [ __ ] you know,
showing up though cuz what the [ __ ]
I thought he actually would have grown a
pair of balls.
But yeah, them um them self-reflecting
comments don't bother me, lad. You're
wasting your time. The lavry mongs are
one the lavry mongs are the ones on YouTube 24/7.
Middle-aged ugly sing over women. Bro,
that ain't my life. That ain't my life.
So they can't they can't trigger me,
bro. They they seriously can't get to
me. These people
wasters. That's what they are. Wasters
trying to put their failure life onto other people.
Jesus Christ, bro.
So now we've got one to go now.
One more to go now, lads. Simple.
Do they actually think like listing all
of the things that they don't have
themselves is going to bother anyone?
They actually think that talking about
their own lives is going to bother anyone else?
Nah, bro. The [ __ ]
No job, no girlfriend, no prospects.
They're literally just talking about
their own lives.
They are literally talking about
themselves, but they're just a lot older.
They love talking about themselves on
there, bro. Seriously, man. It's such a
lame It's a lame attempt to try to trigger someone
talking about themselves. They're an
expert at talking about themselves.
They really are, bro. [ __ ]
So, he's not turning up. TJ's
should just be ignored. Starving for
social interaction. This is the only
interaction outside his mommy has
another self projectum. These people on
YouTube talking to each other all day every day.
Is there anything that these people say
that aren't about their own lives?
Like is there literally any original
thing that they say that's not about
their own lives?
I generally don't think there's one
thing they've ever said that does not
apply to themselves.
No girlfriend. These most of these
people are ugly virgins. Skint. These
people are skint. No friends. They got
no friends. No girlfriend. Well, we've
seen what these people act like when a
new woman comes on the community.
Yeah, bro. Yeah, I will. I will. I'll
call out whoever I want when I want.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'll do what I want
when I want, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'll
do what I want when I want. 100%. 100%,
bro. I'll do what I want when I want.
>> Yeah, man. I'll do what I want when I
want, bro. Whenever I want to, however I
want, in what any way I want. Yeah.
Yeah. If someone's talking [ __ ] on
YouTube and Yeah, I will. And I'll be
going to Nottingham soon anyways. So,
when I announce I go to Nottingham, you
will know where I am. It's as simple as
that. I'll be going to Nottingham soon anyways. Yeah.
calling everyone out. I called two
people out. I'll be in Nottingham soon
anyway, so you'll know where I am. So
that's that, bro. Yeah.
Your your emails are very very nasty,
bro. Very very nasty.
It's not my fault you're biased, bro.
Why are you saying mad stuff on the
email, bro? Do you know why I didn't
even email you back after that? I was
like, "Bro, you're not even worth it,
bro. You're literally literally not even worth it.
Like, you're just a biased." But don't
ever cry about these people being biased
anymore. Don't ever ever ever cry about
these people being biased anymore,
please. I don't want to hear it anymore.
You know, when you turn up to places and
they say that you're [ __ ] white and I
don't care anymore, bro. Don't talk to
me about biased people anymore.
Yeah. Please do never cry about biased people anymore
because you deserve it.
Well, bro, listen. Your boyfriend said
to me today that he's going to be
meeting me in Tottenham.
Well, your boyfriend or Smokey B. I
don't know why I said your boyfriend,
but he said he's going to be meeting me
in I'm just waiting to hear from him.
I'm just waiting for the thumbs up. Simple.
I'm not [ __ ] around today, bro. Seriously. Yeah.
Yeah. I won't dare turn up, bro. Go back
to crying over your boyfriend being
called a virgin. Just like Jo. Go cry
some more. Go cry some more when I call
him a virgin, bro. Go cry some more,
bro. Go and cry some more about your
boyfriend being called a virgin. Go cry
some more and have a panic attack. Just like Jo.
Go cry some more, lad.
Go cry some more, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. I Well, I definitely will be, bro.
I'm not scared of you. Like I said, go
back to bullying women, bro. You don't
You don't scare no one, bro. You're not
scary. You don't scare no one.
Literally, you don't. Go back to
bullying women. If this [ __ ] comes on
today, I definitely will be meeting someone today.
I definitely [ __ ] will be meeting someone today.
And that is a promise. I will do what I
[ __ ] want to do. Yeah. Simple.
You [ __ ] little biased [ __ ]
You gave yourself away, bro. You gave
yourself away. Too obvious, bro. It's
too obvious. You gave yourself away. are
so obvious, bro. You gave yourself away
as a troll. Too easy. Too easy, bro. Too
Oh, was you, bro? How's really was you?
But because I leave the house every day,
so I don't understand how that's possible.
He was waiting around me around my area.
Well, that's not possible, bro, cuz I go
out the house every day. So, I don't
understand how that makes sense.
But that's fine anyways, bro. Because if
you bump into me, you'll know what
you'll get. So, it's as simple as that.
You know, you'll know what you'll get. That's that.
So, that's it, bro.
Yeah. You'll know what you'll get.
Waiting for me when I leave the house
every day. How's How did you bump into
me then? Why didn't you bump into me
What? Because you don't like the truth?
I told you straight. You're a biased [ __ ]
What? cuz you don't like the truth that
you're a biased bastard. You are a biased [ __ ]
You are a biased [ __ ] Defending your
boyfriend for having a girlfriend and he
hasn't even proved he's [ __ ] But I
don't see you on anyone channel um
saying about the [ __ ] 19year-old and
times I've actually proved I've had sex.
A disabled girlfriend ain't sex. What I
have shown is sex. Just because you're
too you're you're know you're um you're
too stupid to understand that your
boyfriend is a virgin. A disabled
girlfriend don't prove that. What I
prove have proved I am not. And you're
not blocked by any of these people.
Yeah. You're not blocked by any of these
people. Yeah, bro. That's fine, bro.
That's Oh, no one spoke about your kids
anyways, but bro, that's fine anyways.
Yeah, that's fine anyways. Yeah, that's
fine. Anyways, no one spoke about your
kid either, so but anyways, I don't give
a [ __ ] Anyways, yeah, I'm not going to
make it to seem like I'm scared of you,
bro. No one's scared of you, bro. Not
one person is scared of you.
Maybe Natalie G's scared of you, but
that's about it. Not me, bro.
Definitely, definitely definitely
definitely definitely not me. And no one
spoke about your kids, so stop talking [ __ ]
Yeah, stop talking [ __ ] And yeah,
that's it. Yeah.
Oh, I'm definitely coming to your ends.
I'll go where I want, mate. I will
travel from the east to the north. Bro,
I will do what I want when I absolutely
want in my Spider-Man t-shirt. Oh, yes,
I will. Shouldn't you be defending your
boyfriend when I call him a virgin? Oh,
don't say that about him. He's got a
girlfriend, fan. He's got a girlfriend,
fan. Oh, don't say that, bro. He's got a
girlfriend, bro. He's got a girlfriend.
You little [ __ ] Don't ever ever ever
try to complain about bias people ever again.
Don't ever ever ever bro [ __ ]
complain about bias people. You're
defending a virgin.
I got bullied out of school. Well,
really did I, bro.
Bro, do you know that that school, bro?
Do you know Do you really want to know
what happened about that school thing?
Yeah. You listen, LT? No one's been
bullied out of school. You don't You
don't even know what school I went to.
So, how can you know I got bullied out of school?
How could I, bro?
How could I get bullied out of school
when you don't even know about my when I
went to school and that?
Oh, I said I don't Oh, yeah. I said I
don't believe you have kids. Yeah, I
don't believe you got kids. Yeah. Oh,
was that what you meant? Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. I said, "I don't believe you got
kids." I did say that. Yeah. I don't
believe you got kids. And what's what's
the business? I don't believe you got
kids. That's the business. Yeah. And
what's the business, bro?
Yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Bro,
when I that school I do you know I
didn't only go to one school. Yeah.
I didn't even go to one school and bro I
was racist to the whole of that school.
Yeah. Against you know what? It wasn't
black people and no one.
They only acted hard when they were in a
group. Yeah, that's true. But I didn't
get bullied out of school, mate. I
literally said the P word and they did
nothing. The whole of Bro, they only
acted hard when they were in a group.
Yeah. Cuz Muslim people aren't about
nothing unless they're in a group. Yeah.
No one got bullied out of no school.
Definitely definitely did not get
bullied out of no school at all. No one
has ever bullied me in school. That's
never ever happened. I was being you
know what to Muslims. Yeah. And I come
back in the next day and they only
started acting hard when they were in a group.
You know how bro you don't understand.
I'm not even going to say too much on
here, bro, because glasses. But I used
to say the most maddest maddest stuff
and they would only act hard when they
were in a group.
So yeah, you don't bully no one. You
don't know nothing about anyone's school
life. You you little Listen, Mr. Bliss,
you little 40-year-old wasters only know
about your bullying experience that
you're trying to put onto me. Yeah.
You're trying to pull it onto me. Yeah.
Yeah. You're trying to put your bully
victim life onto me, bro. And it's not
it's not going to work. I've never been
bullied by [ __ ] no gun. What the
[ __ ] That is self projection at its
finest. I swear you literally Yeah. Just
just think of stuff I saying and then
just copy it, lad. Bro, don't worry
about what LT done 100 years ago cuz you
will never be doing nothing now. Simple
as that. Didn't LT get backup? Didn't LT
have backup when he done all of these
things. Yeah, that's another thing you
don't want to mention. Didn't Mr. LT
have backup when he was going around the
gap? That's something that you don't
want to mention. Yeah.
So yeah, but yeah, I don't believe
you've got kids. So yeah, I did say I
don't believe you got kids. Yeah, cuz I
don't believe you got kids. And [ __ ]
what, bro? You're not going to write an
email to me. Yeah. Start saying madness
cuz I was saying that you're a biased
[ __ ] and then think I'm not going to say
anything back to you, bro. Like who?
Really? Re really really?
Yeah. What did I What did I say to you
on the email? What did I say to you on
the email? What did I say to you on the
email? Why are you not talking about
your boyfriend calling me a virgin? Yeah.
Yeah, that's what I said to you. I said,
"Why are you not saying that you're fast
enough to suck his dick when I'm calling
him a virgin? You're quick enough
girlfriend. You got a girlfriend fan."
And I said to him, "Bro, the guy's
calling me a virgin. Haven't you got
anything to say about it? You're fast
enough to suck your boyfriend's dick
every time I'm calling him one. Did I
not say that? Did I not say that?
Did I not say that? Did I not say that?
Show everyone the email.
You know what I'm saying? You're sucking
off your boyfriend's dick every [ __ ]
day. Every time I try, I can't even say
anything back. Harry, it got It got so
It got so bad every time I open my
mouth. Bro, he's got a girlfriend, bro.
It's immature, bro. He's got a
girlfriend, bro. But then when I'm
showing my dick being sucked to me
[ __ ] in women's beds naked. Oh, you
paid for it. It don't count. Like, bro,
come on. What? Cuz you didn't like the truth?
What? You didn't like the truth? That
you're a biased [ __ ] You know, just
because I you're shown to be a biased
[ __ ] Yeah. It's as simple as that.
Simple, bro. What's What's the business?
I said that you're being a biased [ __ ]
and I felt left out. You're fast enough
to suck his dick every time I call him a
virgin, which he is a virgin. But why
are you not talking about him when he's
calling me a virgin? Oh, you paid for
it. It don't count. You paid for it. But
bro, you're moaning. How many times have
you complained? Yeah. That you went to
Liverpool and people said, "Oh, you
didn't go there." You went to Nottingham
and people said, "Oh, you didn't go
there." How many times did you complain
about these people being biased? How
many times? How many [ __ ] times?
Yeah. And guess what, bro? Guess what? I
would batter you. Well, you do care cuz
you keep butting in, then shut your
mouth then. Every time I call him a
virgin, butt your mouth out then. Butt
your big nose out then. How about that
one, bro? Yeah. If you really don't
care, then stop sucking dick. I will
call him what I want to call him. Simple
as that, lad. If you really don't care,
then why you butting your nose in? Why
are you butting your big nose in? Oh,
bro, he's got a girlfriend. And you done
it more than once, bro. You done it more
than once. If you're If you're If you're
really So, you're not So, you're not
interested in the arguments. Okay, then
then don't say anything then.
Then don't say anything then. Don't say
anything then. Don't say anything then.
If you if you if you're not interested
then just don't say anything then. Just
do not say anything then. Simple.
Yeah. And I will put the link out. Sorry
man. I got distracted. Yeah.
Coming out with all of this mad [ __ ]
And you know why I didn't even reply to
you the last time? Because you're not
even worth it, bro. And you think when
people say that they're scared of you.
Ain't no one scared of you, bro. You know.
Yeah, but what about But but listen
listen, but what have you I shouldn't
even be defending this [ __ ] to be honest
with you, bro. But what have you done,
Mr. Biss, despite knowing people's
addresses? So, you can al you can sit
there and say that. Yeah. Listen, listen
listen listen. I'm not even defending
this [ __ ] Yeah, but you can sit there
and say this. You can sit there and say,
"Oh, this person ain't done this." But
what have you done? But what have you
done? Despite knowing where people
lived, but what have you people done?
No, no, no. But listen, listen. One
second. One second. One second. One
second. One second. Stop trying to [ __ ]
stir. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold
on. Hold on. One second. Stop trying to
[ __ ] stir and say, "Oh, well, oh, why
haven't you done this or why haven't you
done that or why haven't you done this?"
But what have you done despite know
where people live? Nothing. So shut up.
So shut the [ __ ] up. Oh yeah, I'm a
bully victim. Yeah, more excuses. Shut
the [ __ ] up, bro. Shut shut up with your
excuses, bro. Shut up. The only bully
victims are you people on YouTube.
They're the only bully victims.
>> Yeah. Simple as that.
>> Hold on. So you're calling You're
calling people out telling telling that
you're going to meet everybody? Yeah.
But then every single time for years,
you've been doing this to me. I'll come
to your house and you don't come
outside. So So what now?
>> When did I When was the last time I
called you out? What you What you
>> I never said you called me out. I never
said you called me out. I said you're
calling other people out apparently. I
don't know why.
>> Yes, because the smoky bee's talking
[ __ ] So I said if you got to my face.
>> Okay, no problem. Okay, so how come you
don't give me that then? How come you
don't give me that? I've been wanting
you for years, bro.
>> What do you mean you've been warning me
for years, bro? Talking about my children.
>> Listen, I'm not scared of you, bro. You
need to get that through your head. You
need to get that through your head, bro.
>> I don't want you to be scared of me. So
then can we meet him? I'll come to you.
Listen, I'll be Well, listen. If your if
your guy if your guy says that he's
going to meet I'll be in Tottenham today
anyways. If your guy says you meet me,
I'll be in Tottenham right now. You will
never ever be in. You will never be in
my bro. I promise you I will. I promise
you I [ __ ] I've been all over the
country. So, I definitely will. How many
times How many times have you promised
and swore in everyone's life that you're
going to turn up and not done it? How
many times have you done that?
>> And how many times have I had turned up?
So, bro, come on. Come on. This is 2026.
This guy agrees. This guy agrees. I'm
coming to you. Why are you shouting? Let me talk.
>> How many times over the years have you
said and I listen, you know, I don't
even like Shagger. But here's the thing.
You called out everyone from Scotland,
right? Shagger was the only one that
said, "All right, PJ,
>> I'll come meet you." Yeah. Make sure you
get to Glasgow. What did you do? You
went to Edinburgh instead of Glasgow.
This is the type of dumb [ __ ] that you
do all the time. Yeah. Yeah,
the time I went Manchester
wouldn't get that one Manchester
likes to wait.
The time when you went to Manchester,
are you forgetting the time before
Manchester when he came to Birmingham
and you didn't go there? Stop. Stop.
>> Okay. And then and I went to Manchester
two times. So why did he meet me?
>> I can't I can't speak for that coward. I
>> I was in his actual place where he said
he liv So well no where he claimed to
live. But I'm just saying
>> I had no and I had no money as well. Why
don't you let me let Why don't you let
me talk? Why don't you let me talk? Cuz
you know I'm going to break you down
very easily. So here's
>> not going to break me down. Not at all.
>> Listen. Listen. Let me talk then. So go
on. Like you keep talking about people
should come and meet you. Blah blah
blah. You you try to meet people. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Tell me one time. Tell me one time
you've organized it and said, "Okay,
let's meet on such and such date at this
time at this place." Yeah. And you've
gone there. Tell me one time. Cuz you
never done it with No. No. No. No. You
went there. No, no, no. You turned up in
Manchester sporadically. You did not let him know
and you didn't go to Liverpool then. I
don't believe you went Liverpool. Okay,
we're going to play this game now then.
Yeah. Now you're changing.
>> I don't believe you went Liverpool.
>> I don't believe it's you. I don't
believe you went Nottingham. You just
turn up there. I'm going to I'm going to
do what you're doing now. Yeah. I'm
going to do what you're doing. Yeah.
Yeah. We're going to play that game.
>> Now you sound like a child cuz that's
not exactly We're going to play that
game. We're going to play that game.
We're going to play that game. We're
going to not work. That's not
>> Listen, we're going to we're going to
play that game, bro. We're going to play
that game. How many times did you go
live in these areas? Why you always
How many times did you pro How you turn
up by yourself? Forget all this. You
didn't turn up many times. I turned up
many times for you. I turned up many
times for you by myself. Yeah. Why do I
need to by your rules? You're scumbag.
>> What about him? What,
>> bro? You didn't You didn't go live. You
didn't show you was by yourself. You
don't know this. I'm going to start
playing this game. I'm going to start
>> Well, then play it. Well, here
>> I'm going to start playing the game that
you're playing then. Simple as that, bro.
>> That's not even what I said. You're
You're totally changing everything here.
Yeah, cuz that's not even what I said. I said,
>> I went to Manchester two times live and
the guy was on YouTube. What? What's
your point? What's your point?
>> I said Wait, wait, hold on. Did I say
you never went to Manchester?
>> I never said you said Oh, it wasn't
arranged. It was
>> No, no, no. I said I said every single
time when you've got a problem, right,
you sporadically turn up somewhere and
then this and then and yeah, they're
cowards for not turning up anyway. So,
I'm I'm saying that, but I'm going to
keep it real and I'm going to say you
you don't say, "Okay, I'm going to turn
up on Saturday." And me, at least me, I
organized it with these dudes, Shagger,
all these people. I organized it with
them and they
What do you mean they wouldn't agree? If
you if you if you said right now if you
Aren't you supposed to be meeting
someone today? Yeah.
And you agreed to come to my
neighborhood out of all places.
>> He that was his um he he drove.
>> All I'm going to say is I know for a fact. Yeah.
>> He chose location. He
>> listen listen listen to me. I know for a
fact the minute I heard that you that
you're saying that you're going to come
to Tony. I knew it's not going to happen
again. I know location.
>> I know no one ain't coming. No one ain't
coming down to my neighborhood like
that. It's not like
100% coming downhood. If he comes I
won't be doing it.
>> Go then. What time is it? I will be
doing it. I don't care.
>> I'm at my parents house right now. So,
what time is this going to happen?
>> That's all good, bro. That's what
>> What time?
>> It's 1 p.m. I just need him to come and
confirm it. Simple as that.
>> Okay. And what time are you? Are you Are
>> 1 p.m.
>> And what you require him to start uh
with all these stipulations, you require
him to like uh go live and
>> No, show your face. Just show your face
on it. Just show your face. Show your
face. Confirm it.
>> You know he's not You know he's not
going to show his face though.
>> Not like, bro. Not literally, you
[ __ ] idiot. Just that's not what I
meant by show your face.
>> Oh, here it is. Here this here this
forget all that
show. That's what I meant. Okay, cool.
What's the time you lot are saying
disagreement? What is the time of of it?
>> 1:00 p.m.
>> 1:00 p.m. Yeah. Okay. Here's this. Why
don't you both turn up at 1:00 p.m.?
Right. And then you can hear from him.
I'm not going to go there.
>> No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. This
is what you do all the time. You've done
this with me and Terry. You've done this with me.
>> I was supposed to meet someone on
Thursday. He didn't show up. You [ __ ] idiot.
>> I don't know about that, Bob. I don't
watch. I just heard the news now today.
And I'm and I only got your channel now.
Listen to me. Listen to me. Listen to
me. I only got your channel now and I've
only been told about this this morning.
I saw email. Well, the email was from
yesterday, but I saw it this morning and
I only got your channel now. So, that's
why I'm on it. Now, hear this though.
Yeah. You guys are both saying 1:00 p.m.
It doesn't require him to turn up and do
all this because what you do is even if
he did turn up and he done all your
requirements, then you will sit in your
house saying, "Oh, that's good for him.
You're not going out."
>> If I go there, he not going to show up.
So, bro, like
>> No, no, no, no. I promise you. Listen,
listen to me. Listen to me right now.
>> Listen to me right now. Listen to me
right now. If you turn up, you will not
waste your journey. The point is that
you will not waste your journey if you turn up.
>> Okay. Okay, bro. Listen. I'll have I'll
have both of you. I'd rather have both
of you, bro. I've chat you're chatting
nonsense because you've done you've done
this with me and you've done this you've
done this with me and Terry you done
this with me and Terry you said yeah you
said months ago yeah that you will meet
me Terry and Mark right in turn
>> I was the only one that turned up I was
in your live stream and you were still
at home and then you were saying and
then you were saying Tony has to come
and meet me and then you will come heard
from the guy all day so until we hear
from him. I am not leaving. Do you
understand? In your thick head. Do you
not understand? If I don't come now.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. If he comes, why
not? You got free pass. You got free
travel. Why not?
>> Because I don't play games. Cuz I don't
play no. What you're doing is what
you've always done. No, no, no. What
you've done, what you're doing is what
you've always done. Yeah. You
>> supposed to come in the door like a
month ago or 3 months ago. He never
>> Listen, PJ, nobody should go to your
door. Let me just say this. Let me just
say this. Let me say this. Nobody should
go to your door because you've got a
track record of never stepping outside
your door that's better looking than you bro
and then when they turn up at your
address then you start saying people are
hiding so nobody
should go to the location
just tell him to come on YouTube today
and then I'll come on the loc to the location. Yeah
>> 1 p.m. Yeah. So he should he should come
on and just say that he's on his way. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. All right.
>> Okay. I'm I'm going to I'm going to
message him on his Huh.
>> Yeah. There you go. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. All right. Cool. I'm going to
message him on his uh thing right now.
Yeah. And hopefully he gets back in touch.
>> Yeah. We'll be waiting.
>> 1:00 p.m. So that's what 11 Okay. 3 hours. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> I believe you're not coming anywhere.
>> Okay. Believe what you want. Believe
what I know that he's not going to be on YouTube today.
>> So what you going to say when he's not
on YouTube today then? Are you going to say anything?
>> Oh. Oh, by the way, where in Tottenham?
What? Tottenham train station or something?
>> No, it's it's it's a field.
>> What's the field name? That's my area,
so I know everywhere.
>> I forgot. But he said a field.
>> Are you talking about
>> Are you talking about Bruce Grove? Are
you talking about Bruce Grove or MP um
Northland Park? NPK.
>> I can't even remember what he said. He
said a field in it. He just said a field.
>> Well, there's loads. There's New River.
There's loads around there. So So what?
Tell me now. Cuz I live all right near
all them places.
>> I forgot what he said, but I'm just
going to be live there anyways. So, uh,
>> I I want to know all the details now.
Yeah. So, there's no [ __ ] I don't
want to hear any I don't want to hear nothing.
>> Well, you know the day. You know the
time. Where is it?
>> Yeah. You said today 1 p.m. Yeah. But
where in Tottenham? I want to know.
>> I want to go.
>> Why does he want to be in Tottenham anyways?
>> I don't know. That was nothing to do with me.
>> I don't care if I'm just saying it's a
bit weird, isn't it, mate? Cuz you live
there, don't you? I'm not scared, bro. I
don't I don't give a [ __ ]
>> I live there. My whole family live here,
though. My whole family live here. My
parents live here. I'm just I'm I was
just here for the weekend.
>> Yeah, that's good. That's good.
>> Yeah. And I'm going home later on today.
So, what I'm saying is you're I want to
know. I just Oh, man. I I just know it's
not going to happen. I just know there's
no point in me.
>> Okay. But it's not going to happen
because of him.
>> So, all right. All right. Cool. I'll say
it right now.
>> I'll say it right now. If he comes on
your your stream and he says he's on his
way coming, you ain't got no excuses
after that. No.
>> J. No.
>> You're not going to say start make Oh,
you do this. You get a newspaper and
time and all this nonsense. You ain't
going to stop. >> Yeah.
>> All right.
>> And and and and if you don't turn up today,
>> why can't he just join? Why can't he
just join now? Like we're talking. So
what the [ __ ]
>> I don't know.
>> Yeah. I don't know actually. What when
did when did he when did he organize
this with you?
>> Um last week. I think it was last
Wednesday or Wednesday or Tuesday.
>> Oh, see I'm only I'm only find out this
morning. Yeah. And I was like no. So,
he's known about this. He's known about
>> Was he on yesterday or whenever he was on before?
>> He was on before. He wasn't on yesterday.
>> And he 100% >> 100%.
>> 100%. He said that, bro. Cuz he was cuz
he was cuz I said, "Yeah, cuz he was
talking [ __ ] in it." I said, "Oh, if you
got anything to say, say it to me." And
then that Joe F. I said I'll be in
Nottingham when I'm in Nottingham.
>> I don't know what I don't know what
people think, but you can't just roll up
to my like neighborhood like that and
then think that that's not going to
happen. And it I know this for sure.
I've lived here all my I've lived here
all my life. My parents live here still.
>> You should we should blame him for
that time. I just know it.
>> Listen, you know my neighborhood here
yet is like you know those riots that
kicked off and stuff. There's been two
riots here. I don't think people know
about like the history of my area and
that. You can't just roll up like that
and think that you're going to It's
cool. Anyways, I I would love to see it happen. Anyway,
>> it's going to be, bro, if this if this
guy actually like says anything today,
if he actually comes, I'm actually going
to It's going to be a Tottenham takeover, bro.
>> You reckon?
>> I'm taking
and you see your video pissing me off, bro.
>> He was talking recklessly about my
cousins and that as well, is it? Yeah, that video.
>> No, I wasn't. Yeah, you were. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I was saying, you know, I
know cuz I showed I showed him it. Yeah.
And and I promise you
>> I said I don't believe you've got I said
I don't believe you.
>> Yeah. That's cool. That's cool. That's
cool. That that don't mean nothing to
me. Yeah. But I told you don't mention
anything to do with children. My
children ever again. Yeah. And you're
still doing it. I told you
listen to me. When I left you alone.
Listen listen to what I'm saying. When I
left you alone ages ago and then you was
living in Stratford for that whole year
or whatever and I left you I never
bothered you and I gave you my word and
I told you I'm not going to pull up over
there. Yeah. Even when you wasn't
admitting that you you were living
there. I told you I'm not going to pull
up and I left you alone. noticed that
you wasn't really doing all this bad man
running your mouth stuff to me cuz you
don't know how it would have went. You
know the type what was happening before
behind the scenes when people were just
waiting around your area for you. Yeah.
And you wouldn't come outside, right?
And no one gave notice. No one came
online and done any videos. You knew I
left it alone, right? And all of a
sudden because you know you're back at
your mom's over there. Now you've been
talking tough again and doing all this
madness and now you're talking about my
cousin. Like you don't know what
happened last time when he pulled up out
of the house. Did Did any you had your
tenants when he was by himself and you
had your tenants? Was he scared? Was he
>> What? Why are you talking about 100y old
stuff, bro? No one. No one cares about
that [ __ ] bro.
>> No, no. I'm asking you a simple
question. No, no, no. Don't deflect.
It's a simple question.
>> You keep talking about people. Just
listen to me. You keep talking about
people need people and all that for you.
Nobody needs anyone for you. Yeah.
>> I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
>> But that's the honest truth. It's the
truth. I live in the real world. You
listen. People have been shot and
stabbed for a lot less than what you've
said on the internet. Right. So when
you're when you think that people need
to abide by your little rules, Yeah.
after you've talked about people's kids,
talked about people's race, just
disrespectful in general. You don't
think that the rule world don't work
like that. Oh, we need to have a
one-on-one fight. Now, no, I give
one-on-one fights to friends that I have
arguments with. Do you know what I mean?
People that I know that I've had
arguments with, I give that to them.
when you disrespect and you want to
cross the line and do all this extra
stuff. Yeah. Do not expect people to
follow any rules. Now, I I gave you the
benefit of the doubt and that's the same
as you though. That's the same as you though because
No, no, no. I can talk. Listen, listen.
I can talk reckless because I can back
my talk and I can say it in your face.
You can't. You know, you can't say
nothing like that to my face. I can say
I've been willing to trying to say it to
your face. I climbed in your house. I
broke into your house twice. Willing to
say it to your face. And you run away
one time. Remember when I came to the
park? You ran away. I was willing to say
it to your face that day as well when I
was in the park late at night at times
when you ran away. Remember, do you
remember when you ran away? Do you
>> Do you remember when you ran away when I
started yelling? Do you remember that?
>> Yeah. Yeah. 10 years ago. I remember.
>> No. No. No. I don't mean Listen, I mean
literally you ran when I told you over
the gate, you ran. >> Yeah.
>> 10 years ago. It really was. I've been
I've been on this place for 5 years.
Five years. So, how's it 10 years ago?
>> You've been on here for 5 years. cuz you
haven't been on it for
>> since 2020. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Since 2020. That's when I talking about
ancient stuff, bro.
>> It's It's boring, man. >> Bro,
>> that's your deflection tactics for you.
>> No, it's not. It's just not relevant to
anything cuz if you come down and you
broke the house, you know what time it is.
>> So, so wait, hold on, hold on, hold on.
>> You know what would happen? Wait, hold
on. Hold on.
What would happen is you call the
police. Yeah. And you and you get a
panic button. That's what would happen.
Don't act like Listen, listen. Don't act
like you would ever come outside cuz
I've gone. You've gone. You Why should
your business listen windows?
Listen. No. No. You listen to me. I
think your friends going to break
windows around there and and get away
with it. Bro, you bro, I would chase him
and I would jump on him, bro. It wouldn't happen.
>> You old stuff, bro.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. So why is it every
single time we've been to your house, me
or him or or one of my cous
with my mom, I got arrested. I would
have, bro, I would have went outside and
I would have kicked the weapon off him,
bro. I don't care about 10-year-old stuff.
>> Listen, listen, listen.
>> Whilst you whilst you and your mother
and your sister was in your house live
streaming, I come and smash your um hit
your window. It didn't smash. I tried to.
>> Yeah. No, no. I tried. I intended. No,
no, no. Why didn't you come outside then? Then
>> I don't care. 10y old stuff.
>> Why didn't Why didn't you come outside
instead of going
>> if you and your mother?
You would know what time it is. You
would know what time I've already done
it. You just know what time it is.
>> I have already done it. I don't need to
do it 10 times. I've already done it. I
have already done it. I've done it more than once.
>> But if you do it again, you know you're
a good boy once again. You good boy. You
would never do it again. And that is me egging.
All right. Cool. PJ, forget smoky beat.
I will meet you. How about that? I I
will meet you right now. Just damage.
Just damage the house. No, no, no, no,
no. I don't need No, no. I want to
damage you. I want to damage you. I
don't want to damage no house. I want to
damage you. I don't want to damage the house.
>> This will do it and I'll be I'll just
come out and smash your car. I will just
smash your car up. Let's do it. Let's do
it like that.
>> Sounds good. It sounds good. Hey,
listen. Forget Forget Smokey B. I will
meet you today.
>> I will damage the house and keep and do
it again in 2026. Why you change?
>> Let's do it in 2026 and leave your car
outside and see what I do.
>> Listen Listen.
>> See what I do to your car. See what I do
to your car. Just do it. Come on,
>> PJ. Get on the train right now to
wherever you want and I'll meet you.
Let's see in6.
>> Listen to me. Listen to me. Listen to
>> Whoever you want, big man.
>> Go outside your house right now. Yeah.
And go to any location you want.
>> 26. Bring your friends with you. My
drive to wherever you are. Come on. Come
on. Big man. What you waiting for?
>> Stop talking over me and listen to what I'm saying.
>> Listen. Listen. Listen. You going to
come and do what you done or not? Big
man. Are you going to come and do it or
not? I'm going I'll be waiting for you
all day if you want to do it.
>> No, no, no. Let's leave your mom out to
the police car. Come on then. Come on.
>> You run to the police. That's you.
That's That's a fight.
>> So, you're not doing it in 2026. So, sh listen.
>> Simple as that.
>> Listen Listen to me. I listen to me.
Just listen to me. >> Yeah.
>> Leave. Let's leave your mom away. Let's
Let's not let her witness anything. You
leave your house. I don't mind even coming.
>> Bro, I No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Let's
let Let her witness of it, bro.
>> No, no, no, no, no. That's cowardly. No,
no, no. That's on your phone. You offend
a coward. You're offend
my mom wouldn't bring this to me
smashing your faces.
>> I gave I gave you his address. Listen,
we're not going to do nothing. You're
weak. You want your mom to save you.
We're not going to do nothing, bro. Shut up.
>> You want your mother to save you? Listen.
>> You keep talking, bro. You keep talking
about Tottenham, but your your friend is
the one that keeps telling people to
meet him there. That's the only reason Tottenham's involved.
>> You understand?
>> Right. So, what I'm saying is, yeah,
right now, leave your house and go any
location you want. Yeah. And I will live
I'll stay on this live stream with you
and I will jump in my car and I will
drive directly to you. I just want you
to leave your mom's house. That's it. I don't care.
>> No, don't be taking pride in it, bro.
So, do it again in it. Do it again.
>> Look, I want to do it dirty, bro. Like,
what I want to do to you, I want to make
sure you can't call the police. I want
to shut you up forever, bro. I want to
shut you up forever, bro. You don't
understand. PJ, I would break your
little knock. Come now. Come out with
your car. Come now with your car. I'll
come now with your car. Knock on the
door. You big man.
>> No, no, no. I'm not knocking your door.
No. No. When you're doing eyed ugly
[ __ ] [ __ ] with a mushroom, you
little weak. You're not going to do nothing.
>> Exactly. Now we turn into this.
>> You little weak with your little weak fy boy friends.
>> Stop using my culty boy about nothing.
He's not going to do nothing. Listen,
>> Why should people get themselves nicked for you?
>> Bro, I'm scared of you. You little
weakling. You little [ __ ] weakling.
Shut up. You little weak [ __ ] [ __ ]
off, bro. Stop talking about 10 years ago.
>> I'm the [ __ ]
>> You're talking 10 years ago. Let's talk
now. Come on.
>> I said I'm willing to come to you right now.
>> Bro, you're not going to break no little
[ __ ] You little weak man. You wouldn't
even get your hands on me, you little weak boy.
>> Shut up, bro.
>> I'll head butt you straight in your jaw.
You [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Come on then.
>> Old an old tiger man you
>> talking about 10 years ago. So come on.
>> Listen, I'm coming. So what I'm saying
here, just leave your mom's help.
>> Are you going to smash the windows again?
>> No, I'm not smashing nothing. No, no.
I'm not no. Forget that.
>> I don't want to do that. I don't want
your mom to witness anything. Yeah.
>> I want my mom to witness you getting
[ __ ] up or a cow loser getting [ __ ]
I want my mom to witness your crutch.
See, that's your crutch.
>> Make sure you keep Make sure you leave
that car outside that door as well. Make
sure you leave that car cuz you're not
getting back in that car.
>> Why are you shouting over me? You're not
getting back in that car. Do you
understand? I'm telling you now you're
not getting back in that car, but I'm
going to smash up your car as well and
I'm going to spit all over it. Come on
then. Come on. Come on. Come on. Make
sure you leave that car outside as well.
>> Listen, I said I have no problem coming
right now. Yeah. I just want you to leave.
>> [ __ ] break up that car. Spit all over
it, bro. Yeah. You're not going to keep
coming on YouTube stalking people,
acting a bad man. You're not going to do
it, bro. You're not going to [ __ ]
coming up my ass, bro. You understand?
>> You just agreed. You just agreed to meet
and smoke in Toten. Yeah. I'm saying you
don't have to go to Tottenham now. Just
leave your mother's house, uncle. Walk
around the corner. Just go to Listen,
listen. Listen, listen. No, no, no. Cuz
you keep bragging about 10 years ago.
You keep bragging about 10 years ago.
So, do it again.
>> Do it again. My mom has openly said
anyone to come here. My mom's openly said anyone.
>> Yeah. And your the same mother that had
a panic button and was your mom would
call the police as well. Your mom's not
big. Your mom would call the police as
well. She has three. Your mom would call
your mom. Listen. Listen to me, bro.
>> My mom had three sons. is hard.
I'm from Tottenham. She has three sons
and she has [ __ ]
guns. She would need to know police.
Yeah, cool. But you would never come
here to Tottenham. You would never come
here. You would never come here.
You would never in your life. You would
never in your life come here. I'm at my
parents house right now. You would never
in your life come here. But what I'm
saying is, listen, forget all this. This
is irrelevant arguments.
>> No one's ever going to come to
Tottenham. Okay, bro. Whatever.
>> This is this is irrelevant arguments.
What I'm saying is, yeah, just walk
somewhere away from your house now and
>> old woman like in her 60s, bro.
>> But you know, your bad boyfriends are
not about nothing.
>> Like a little Greek boy. What did you
tell about that little Greek boyfriend,
Stablo? The little weak [ __ ] the kebab eating [ __ ]
>> the [ __ ]
>> Did you tell everyone about him?
>> What? Did you see him? Did you see him?
>> Did Did you tell everyone about him?
>> Did you see him?
>> Did you tell everyone about him?
>> What do What do I need to tell? What?
that that that you got some little Greek
boy waiting outside the [ __ ] front
door and that. Do you tell anyone?
>> Because I'm I'm not a snitch. I know
what he had on him.
>> I'm not
pathetic. Actually are, bro.
>> I wasn't the only person, by the way.
That he wasn't the only one. But yeah,
>> one of them. It was one of them.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And And my cousin was one of them, too.
[ __ ] Listen, and this is why people
think that you don't have kids, bro.
It's not even to try to annoy you.
>> Who cares? Who cares,
>> bro? You're still online in 2026 TRYING
TO ACT BAD. It's embarrassing.
>> No, I came on No, no. I came on to ask
you, why are you still calling people
out when you avoided me all these years?
>> The guy was talking about me. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. So,
same to my face.
>> Okay. And and I've done a lot worse than
those guys. So, how come you've never
ever once decided to come and meet me then?
>> It's as simple as that, bro.
>> Oh, forget meeting me. I say I'll come
to you. Just leave your mother's house.
That's all. I don't even care if I only
said what you have.
>> I don't even care. No, I'm not. I don't
I'm not I'm not coming there to smash
windows. I don't want to come there to
smash windows. I want to come there to
to see you face to face. I'm not
smashing windows. I've done that before.
You've done nothing back to me. I've
done it multiple times before. You've
done nothing back to me. So why do I
need to do it again?
>> You actually think I need to do it
again. Well, obviously clearly you clearly actually seriously seriously
>> you offer everyone else up here, but you
don't accept it with me and you do all
these deflection tactics on purpose,
right? So you don't have to meet me.
Yeah. You keep telling me come to your
mother's house so your mother can save
you. No, no, no, no, no. Because your
No, no. What you want is your mother to
be a crutch. Yeah. So she can save you.
Yeah. And then she can call the police.
That's dry snitching. If you're about
something and you're not a coward, walk
around the corner. Listen
to me. Listen to me. You know that's
what she's going to do. She She's your
mom. She's I'm not even I'm not even
insulting. I'm just saying but but your
mom wouldn't call the police now.
>> No, she wouldn't. No. No, she wouldn't.
She has three sons. She had a husband.
>> An old woman wouldn't call the police now. Okay.
>> My mom's not calling police, mate. And
no one would come and do that to my
house. How about that?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Your mom wouldn't call the
police cuz your mom's Superman is it? Yeah.
>> No. No. It's not even that. No, not even
that. It's because my hus um Sorry. My
mom's husband lives at home. Yeah. And
she's got three sons. She's got three
sons. And she's got a bunch of cousins.
I've got a bunch of cousins that all
live in Tottenham. A bunch of them.
Like, so who's really why would she call
the police when she could just call her
um what's it? My dad's sister who lives
two roads behind where my parents live.
Why would she call the police for?
>> So, you need to settle down, bro. You
talk some mad [ __ ] bro. Honestly,
>> you're the one that's talking [ __ ] I'm
saying I'll come and meet you. I will
stay on this live stream.
>> Settle down. You need to chill out.
Listen, I would stay on this live stream
right now and drive all the way to just
all I need you to do is just go outside.
That's the problem. You always stay
inside your house and then even when I
do come and knock and do everything what
you ask, you still don't come outside.
So, what's the point in that?
>> I thought you were expecting this guy to
meet me so I can come today.
>> Forget him, man. Forget him. Forget him.
Forget him. I will give you my I will
stay on this thing right now. I won't
take it off. I'll stay on this thing
right now and I will I will show you. I
will drive the whole
>> I I want to be I want to meet both of you.
>> Yeah. So, you know, you're just chatting
[ __ ] I knew you weren't coming to
catch. I want to meet both of you.
>> You know, when I heard today, yeah, this
morning that you were supposed to be
coming to Tottenham. Yeah. I said
instantly, he's not coming to Tottenham.
That's it. Like, I there's no It's never
going to happen. Yeah.
>> I've offered you money. I've
>> It's never going to happen. Yeah. I've
been literally to so many different places.
>> What? Sporadically, and you just turn
>> Another thing is Another thing is Yeah.
Not to change the subject, let me just
tell you something. Yeah. I was like,
>> "One second, one second. One second. One
second. I was live 4 days ago. Yeah. Do
you remember that time I went
Middlesber? That Trevor Dawson is still
changing the subject and still talking [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I know you went there, but again, they're
>> still talking [ __ ] So why someone's
going to travel 5, six hours away? Why
would anyone come to Tottenham? Come on.
>> No, no, no, no. Because you because
Tottenham is not the same as Middles,
bro. That's why.
So I don't even I don't even know why
you even asking stupid questions.
>> I'm not saying it is. I'm just saying.
So why would I go there?
You go to Middlesbrough unannounced.
Yeah. And you did go there. I'm I never
once said that you didn't turn up to
Manchester and all these places. I I
know you have. But what I'm saying is
these guys are cows. Cuz if you done
that to me and just turn up unannounced
or whatever, I would have someone even
if I can't physically be there, I would
have someone turn your head turn turn
your turn your [ __ ] jaws off. Yeah.
But what I'm saying is, right,
you said the the middle of the thing,
right? You went there sporadically. You
didn't let him know even even a few
hours before that you were going there.
just randomly turned up and you called a
man out and he didn't turn up. All
right, cool. But even if you did that to
me, that's not going to happen. Even if
you just turned up
my name trying to make it seem like it
doesn't even if you go listen.
>> No, no, no. I just said I just said I
just said you're always saying, "Oh, you
come and you're trying to lie."
>> No, no, no. No, no, no, no. I'm
critiquing. I've told you I'm not
biased. I've always been objective. I'm
critiquing both of you cuz I'm saying
you on one hand. Yeah. You didn't let
nobody know that you was going to turn
up there and you turned up there. And
him on the other hand, he knew that you
was there and there was nothing. He
didn't even attempt to even at least try
and meet you and then to see if you
would turn up or or or still stay around
or not. So yeah, that's cowardly cuz I I
don't respect [ __ ] like that. But I'm
saying if you was to do that to me,
yeah, randomly and just didn't let me
know nothing. And someone messaged me or
or sent me some type of message on
YouTube or whatever it is yet and I saw
it and and said that you're in Tottenham
right now. Even if I couldn't physically
be there. Yeah. I would have someone meet you.
>> That's it's just easy as that.
>> There's no in a wheelchair. When has he
ever said he's in a wheelchair?
>> I knew he was a bit older, but I don't
know about wheelchair.
>> You need to settle down. You do. This is 2026
>> today. You've just offered out that
smoky bee, right? And you said in
Tottenham, right? So, how come?
>> And he said he said Tottenham. So, yeah,
that's why he wanted He picked it. He
>> Okay. Okay, cool. So you you you you
agreed to that, right? I'm saying so I'm
saying you don't even have to drive to
Tottenham. I'm sorry. Uh get on travel
to Tottenham anymore. You don't have to
do all that. Listen to me. Just go
across the road. Just go to a road
around the corner from your house and I
will stay on this live stream right now
and drive there to that road.
>> You're you're pathetic, bro. That's what
you are. You're pathetic.
>> really really my kids Listen, you've had
my kids names in your mouth for too
long. And I told you last time just like
I don't care what you got to say about
my kid today. Bro, you're talking about
people myself. So sh stop trying to take
the moral high ground. It's not going to work.
>> Who do you think you are? You keep messaging me.
>> It's not going to work.
>> Wait. Wait. You keep Who do you think
you are? I I I don't even bother you.
Yeah. You're angry about something what
I said when I was in the last. I emailed
you. Why are you being Let me talk.
Number one, I'm a grown man. I don't
care about the stupid childish immature
behavior about oh who's had sex with
who. I don't give a [ __ ] about all that.
All I You're angry because I said
something just after Christmas on your
live stream when I was last on your live
stream and I stated that he's got a
girlfriend. He's not
>> and I stated
one second. I promise you I'll give you
No, I'm Listen, we can't do this. And I
said to you what I let me have 2 minutes
to explain myself here and then you can
have your two minutes. You can have 5
minutes. Okay. So this is my 2 minutes.
Let's start. Okay. So
>> loving this by the way.
>> Just after Christmas. Yeah. We was
having a discussion on your live stream.
You kept on saying he's a virgin. I
said, "Listen, man. I'm a grown a grown
man. I don't care if I don't like the
guy. I don't care if I hate the guy and
all the rest of it. It's just logical,
perfectly logical to understand that two
people that's above what? Above 14
that's been together for a while has
obviously done the deed, right? That's
just normal behavior. If you ask anyone,
I don't even know this community. don't
even know anyone here. They would they
would side with me. But I said that to
you just after Christmas. It's not like
I had a private message with you and I'm
trying to wind you up and all that. No,
I just said that on the last live
stream. And what you've done is you've
had that harboring you've harbored all
that animosity in
>> You've done it a couple of times as well.
>> No, no, no. I Well, that's the last time
I said it then. Whatever.
>> Yeah, that's So, are you blocked on this channel?
>> Wait, hold on. You've harbored all this
animosity for for a couple weeks and
then you I don't know when you're upset,
when you're when you're miserable, you
you start doing videos saying all this stuff, right?
>> Here's the thing. Here's the thing.
>> Are you channel?
>> I have not messaged you and started
saying these things. I said it on your
last live stream.
>> Are you on your channel?
>> No, I'm not.
>> So, why have you not brought up all of
the women I've been with? He's called me a virgin.
>> No, no, no, no, no. You seem to care
enough when I'm This is the thing with you.
>> I watch you. I don't even watched him.
So, you have seen where he has called me
stuff within years. Bro, stop talking
[ __ ] bro. Even if it's not real because
you I just find it a bit strange how why
do I need to
defend someone for showing they've had
sex? It's just bias bias. >> Listen,
>> if you let him call me a Why would I
call him one?
>> Your lack of
>> That's not fair. I've proved I've had
sex. He hasn't.
>> Listen, listen.
>> Is it cuz you're biased? Is it cuz
you're biased? Yeah.
Do you just find it hard? Do you just
really find it hard to comprehend?
>> I find I find it I find it No, no. You
know what? I find it hard to comprehend.
>> told you numerous times.
>> You're letting someone that's proved
they've had sex be called a virgin, but
someone that's got a girlfriend that's got disabilities.
I find I do find it hard to
>> Is this the type of arguments that
you're having at 28 years old? Because
these type of arguments I wasn't even
having these type of arguments when I
was 18 or 15.
>> You're biased. As simple as that. You're
biased. These are no your world and my
world is completely different. These are
these are the things that bother you.
Yeah. This is childish to me. I don't
even care. I don't care. Like, do you
not understand? I've told you this numerous times.
>> I don't care enough cuz you say about it.
>> Yes. Because when you're saying stupid
[ __ ] like that, then I'm going to
>> He's calling me a virgin when I prove
I've had sex.
>> And guess what? I've never seen these comments. I
>> Yes, you [ __ ] have. Yes, you [ __ ]
>> You going to tell me where I see him? I
don't watch him. I watch you. So, how
would I know?
>> Okay, bro. you. Oh, whatever.
>> You think I watch him?
>> You've never gone on a live stream where
he's saying that I'm this and I'm that. No,
>> I've heard your live stream when he's
came on and said this, but to me it's
nothing. I don't care. That's like
someone that's like someone calling me a
[ __ ] I don't care. Like whatever.
>> I never You guys are You guys are
basically arguing and you're telling me
that you are not disabled. Like you guys
are arguing over [ __ ] [ __ ] that it's
irrelevant. It don't even mean nothing.
>> Yeah. Yeah, man. Okay.
>> It doesn't mean [ __ ] Do you think I
care? Someone is honestly if someone
called me these things. Yeah. I would
not give two [ __ ] I would
say that you would
>> I don't even think I'd even respond. I
don't even think I'll respond and I
wouldn't be sitting down thinking about
it for weeks getting myself angry about
it. That's the honest truth. So when
you're getting me involved in your
childish nonsense. Yeah. It's I feel
sorted cuz I think to myself number one
grown adults even a teenager it's just
normal behavior. If you've been with
someone for for a while, you don't have
to be with someone for a while. People
have one night stands. I don't care.
Have you ever seen me come on here
saying I like I'm I'm curious to know
about you. I don't care about your your
[ __ ] life like that. I don't care.
Why would I care?
>> So, but back to the other thing though.
You called out Smokey. Yeah. You keep
saying that you meet just uh what's it?
What's that guy's name? Joe or whatever,
right? You said that you'll meet him.
You're willing to go. Was it Nottingham?
You said Yeah. Not him. When I'm ready.
>> Oh, when you're ready. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, okay. When you're ready.
>> Yeah. I'm not going to go out my way, am
I? Why am I going to go out my way? >> Because
I don't I don't know about that
situation. So, anyway, you said when
you're ready with that. Yeah. Okay, no
problem. So, what I'm saying is how comes
you make it a problem for me to get my
hands on you. You said something that
like I would I would love to see you
face to face. I promise you right now. Yeah.
>> If you if you was acting like if you was
acting like that with that prime guy,
soft and all shaky shaky with that prime guy,
>> it will be just it'll be like about 100
years ago again, bro.
>> No, no, it's not 100 years ago. You was
a grown man. You was a grown man. It's
not like he was a kid.
>> He was a grown man. Yeah.
>> I've never acted like that in my life.
Only to my dad. When my dad done that to
me when I was a little kid. I've never
acted like that. I've had worse worse
than you in that. I've had worse than
you in that. And I never I never crawled
out like like caring cowering over over
myself like that. >> Yeah.
>> I've been caught slipping in front of by
myself when there's a few people or
whatever and I've never said, "Oh,
>> why you beating me up?"
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> You have. So what?
>> Yeah. Nice, man. Yeah.
>> All right. So So what I'm saying is I
will come right now. All I want you to do
>> I'm not I'm not meeting you. Simple.
>> Why not?
>> Cuz I don't want to. And Smoky Bee's not
meeting me. So simple.
>> Just like what Lord J said. This guy
didn't meet me Thursday. That's why
Smoky B is not meeting me. Now Smoky
Bee's not meeting me now. I'm not meeting you.
>> How about that then?
>> That's fair then. No. >> Typical.
>> Typical coward tactics. This isn't it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro. I'm I'm I'm a
coward. Okay, bro. Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Well, we all know anyways. This is what
you do all the time. Anything was
we don't care about you people. You're
so irrelevant that we don't even care
about you, bro. So when you say we, I
need to I need to I need to say that to you, bro.
>> If you don't if you don't care about the
>> One second. One second. Sorry. Hold on.
>> Okay. Okay. So Smokey So Smokey Be is
not meeting me today. The guy didn't
meet me Thursday, but I'm not allowed to
not meet you.
>> I don't know what happened on Thursday.
>> [ __ ] off, mate.
>> So it's all right for you to It's all
right for these people to run away from
people and get away with it. Get [ __ ] mate. >> Listen.
>> Oh, of all these people here, I've been
trying to meet you from ages ago. It's
you that always let me down. And then
somehow people think that I'm the
talker. I've come to your house. I broke
into your house to come and see you and
and you still ran out. So what? What do
I need to do more?
>> Anyways, I'm done with this anyways.
Yeah, I just kicked him. I'm done with
all of this anyways. We're not playing
these silly little games anymore.
You get kicked and you get kicked.
Typical [ __ ] bro. This is what happens
when they try to draw people in. Yeah,
it's not happening, bro. It's definitely
definitely definitely not happening.
[ __ ] this, bro. We're not doing this
again. So, what's the time now? 11.
And we haven't heard from him. Yeah. To
[ __ ] with all of you, bro. To [ __ ] with
all of you.
Simple. To [ __ ] with all of you.
So, that's two people.
That's two people now. Yeah. Let's done this.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm a coward. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Nice, bro. That's cool. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yep. Yep. All right. Cool. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm done with this anyways, bro.
we're not going into a whole new year
with this [ __ ] again, bro. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that. This is what they do. This
little [ __ ] community. Yeah, they
they they like to talk [ __ ] about people
and then you call them out and then they
don't do anything. Then someone else
gets involved and then tries to replace
that person. Yeah. [ __ ] off, bro.
Seriously, [ __ ] off, man.
Yeah. Yeah. [ __ ] that. Absolutely [ __ ] that, bro.
Yeah. That's that. Anyways, it's not
happening. Sorry, Grezy.
Yeah, it's not happening, bro. Sorry.
Just as I predicted. So, yeah.
Yeah, just as I predicted,
which was obvious to be honest when
people asking you to show two grand and
all of this [ __ ] Yeah.
That's same [ __ ] bro. It's just the
same old [ __ ] with these people. It's
the same old [ __ ] bro. It's the same
old [ __ ] with these people.
Literally, if your friend, whatever you
want to call him, agreed and gave me the
thumbs up, I would have went and then
you would have both had your chance.
Simple as that. So, that's it.
Oh my god, these people are hurting my brain, bro.
Mad, mad, mad, mad, mad, mad, mad. Really mad.
Anyways, bro, to be honest with you,
Yeah, self projector. Bye-bye.
I've had many wins, bro. Many wins. Many
wins. Many wins. I've had many wins.
Okay, then if it's [ __ ] okay, bro.
Whatever. I don't care. We're done
anyways. Yeah. Simple as that.
Yeah, it's as simple as that, bro. It's
as simple as that. And do you know what?
I'm not even going to do the Nottingham
thing now, to be honest with you. I'm
not even doing that now. Yeah, I'm not
doing it now, bro.
I'm not meeting anyone because the guy's
gone quiet and he's not been on today.
So, that's how I won. Yeah. With two
different people in the space of a week.
Yeah. Anyways, I'm done with this
anyways, bro. I'm very very very very
Yeah. And here's the thing, LT. If you
want to camp out people's houses and try
to catch people slipping and you're more
than welcome to do that because you're
not going to stop me. You're not going
to stop me leaving leaving the house
every day. So if you're actually if you
actually want to do that, bro, that's on
you, bro. And you'll see exactly what
will happen, you know? So that's it.
That's all I'm saying to be honest with you. Yeah.
You can bring up 5 10 year old [ __ ]
It's just all irrelevant. It's very very very relevant.
Yeah, that's nice, bro. Anyway, I
shouldn't have even been on here today,
bro. Do you know the only reason I come
on here today? Yeah, it's because of
this [ __ ] [ __ ] And I weren't going
to let him come on here and start
laughing saying, "No, no, no, no." But
we just we we know the score now anyways
with you jealous weirdos.
We know we know the score now we use.
So, yeah, I'm done anyways. Yeah.
Yeah. Anyways, bro, I should know better
to be honest, but this guy was just
pissing me off. So, yeah. Yeah.
And that's it. Yeah,
but thank for thanks for um clarifying
it anyways, LT, man. Thanks for
clarifying it. That's all you had to do
via the email. Still don't quite believe
you though, where you where you said
that you've never seen him call me.
Uh where you've never called me. Um Yeah.
Yeah. where you've never seen him call
me a virgin. Don't believe that for a
second. But yeah,
don't believe you, man. I don't believe
you. I'm sorry, man.
I'm done with this [ __ ] anyways, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm done anyways, lad. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
I'm done with you weirdo little closeted
gay jealous people. Anyways, lad.
Little weirdos need to get a life.
Simple as that.
So that's that, bro. Yeah. Yep. Yep.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Whatever.
Sad closeted gay little homosexual
people. You got a lot of [ __ ] to sort
out in your life, bro. Do you understand?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, man.
Yeah, whatever, bro. Yeah, cool.
S little jealous little gay people. I
would have thought in 2026, you actually
would have got a life, bro.
Only been live for now. It doesn't even
seem like that, bro. To be honest, an hour. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You're right, bro.
I've never met anyone. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Yeah. Okay. I've never met anyone. No.
Yep. Yep. You're right, bro. Whatever
you say that makes yourself feel better,
bro. Yeah. Whatever. Whatever you say.
Whatever you say, bro. Whatever you say.
Yeah. Whatever you say, man.
Don't know. Don't care. I don't care
about any of these people.
You can get a life and come out the
closet. A lot of you people. That's what
I think. That's what I think to be
honest with you. Yeah.
I've been live longer. Oh yeah, I did
have to make a deal. I was about to say,
bro. Yeah, I was about to say. It seemed
too short, isn't it? Yeah. Yeah, man.
That's that. Anyways, yeah, that's that. Yeah,
sad little bastard. Lot of sad bastards
on this community, bro. It's It's
madness. It's actually madness. Yeah.
[ __ ] gay. I don't know. I don't
understand how people older than me can
then sit and do this for years. Bro
just be like gay little [ __ ]
homosexual jealous people. It's [ __ ] mental, man.
Need to get a life. Honestly, you need
to get a life. I went out last week.
Yeah, it's a madness.
Sad little bastards.
Sad sacks of shits. That's what these
people are here. So, we're going to give
it a little bit more time and I'm off here. Yeah.
So, that's that. What's the time now? Quart. Yeah. Yeah,
sad sad sad losers.
Sad losers on here, bro. So,
I got thingies email anyways. So, give
him uh give him the new channel
cuz think about it, bro. I can stay on
here, Greavves. Yeah. I could stay on
here for another Okay, let's say let's
say I stay on here for another another
year. Yeah. And I'm like calling these
people out every single day and I'm
meeting them and I win some and I lose
some and then then what's the whole
point of it within the whole year when
it's just going to start again? You
know, they've already shown what they're
about as well.
They're trying to just like trap you
every single time. Yeah. They're trying
to say, "Oh, you're this, you're that."
And they It's all to try to It's just
basically ent trament to try to get like
another person involved. It's just
disabled. All of this is just so
So so so so disabled.
Like it really really is. Just all of it
is just [ __ ] disabledness on here, bro.
Oh my god, my brain hurts. Ah,
my little brain hurts.
I don't believe you've never seen him
call me a virgin though, Alt. I don't
think you would have seen it. You would
have definitely seen it at least once.
I don't believe you, man. I have to say
I don't believe you lad
cuz that's a lot of stalking and [ __ ]
for all of them years. I don't believe
you bro. But that's what you're saying
then that's it is it
strange isn't it?
Cuz I'm sure you would have seen it
once. You must have seen it once.
And I've never seen you talk about any
of the [ __ ] women I've been with. So,
I mean, I don't know, bro.
I'm sure you would have seen it. I'm
sure you would have seen someone um
I'm sure you would have saw someone
calling me something,
you know. So, that's it.
You're all sados on air. No, I will not
be going anywhere.
No, I will not be going anywhere. The
only thing I'll be doing is leaving this community.
No, what I'll be doing as I'll be coming
off. That's what I'll be doing.
So, yeah, we're going to wait a little
longer. See if this [ __ ] says anything.
I don't come here trolling people.
I don't comment on trolling people. I've
got four I've got about four or five
more accounts coming on here stalking
me, recording everything I do every day
because they're undercover homosexuals
because they're [ __ ] undercover gay
boys. I don't st I don't I don't troll anyone.
We come on here talking about football
bets and these [ __ ] [ __ ] harass me.
So big difference. Absolutely big
I'm not the one sat there with a
recorder every single day from the time
I wake up to the time I go to bed like
certain batty men.
Yeah. No, not me. I don't troll anyone.
I don't [ __ ] troll anyone on YouTube.
What the [ __ ]
No, no, no. A lot of a lot of people on
here, bro, need to really come out as
gay, bro, at this point.
literally at this point. Yeah.
Your your lives are [ __ ] Like you're
sat on here harassing people every day
trying to get people nicked. What a
loser. These people on here are proper
proper down and out losers. All cuz
their lives are [ __ ] up. You notice
every single time we go live, bro, we're
just talking about football bets and [ __ ]
Sad, sad, sad. Life's losers. Anyways,
so this is the second person that's
stunned us now.
Brother, everyone knows the story about
why I'm not going. The guy has not been
seen on YouTube all day. So, no, I'm not
going when someone has not been seen on
YouTube all day to answer your repeating question. Yeah.
Simple as that.
Yeah, bro. Stop calling people a M
that's better looking than you.
Stop calling people that are better
looking than you a m lad. It's It's 2026. You know,
stop calling people that are better
looking than you, lad. [ __ ] retards. Anyways,
>> yeah, I'm better looking than you, lad.
And I've been with more women than you.
No one cares what [ __ ] fat old ugly men think.
I don't take offense from fat, ugly
self-p projectors, lad. You don't need
to add the no offense bit at the end
cuz we we've seen what you people look
like. We've we've actually seen what a
lot of you people look like. So, don't
worry, bro. I don't take offense.
And you are [ __ ] something else.
[ __ ] fat, very ugly. It doesn't
matter what you say, bro. It doesn't it
doesn't mean anything. Like when I was
saying when I was when I was on Lauria
and they were saying that this that and
the other like literally bro bro bro bro
bro bro bro bro bro bro bro bro bro bro
bro bro bro bro bro bro bro you're being
honest about yourself you people are
very ugly we have seen you people bro
Jamie Thompson nons legs we have seen a
lot of you ugly people you can't troll
anyone by talking about yourself
we have seen your disgusting looks and
that's where the jealousy comes from
think of it you you fat ugly people are
on YouTube 24/7. No life, no girlfriend,
no family. Trying to talk about other
people that's got a life. Trying to talk
about other people that actually Yeah.
are trying to do the best in their
situation because you're fat, cuz you're
ugly, cuz you're depressed on YouTube.
20. Tell me I'm lying, bro. Tell me
right now I'm lying about any of these
people that are on this on on this L J
channel. Baby unattractive, don't leave
the house, no money, bums. Literal bums,
bro. Anyone on here can tell me that I'm
lying about any of these people. Never
been seen with a woman. Got no family.
We all saw what they done over Christmas
as well. Come on, bro. Come on. Come on.
Come on. I'm not chunky. I'm not
overweight. But you people are fat.
You're obese. I tell you an example. You
people are fat and ugly. No one cares
what ugly, hopeless losers have got to
say about anyone else. You're self-projecting.
I'm speaking to someone I met last week.
Think I'll be meeting them very soon.
[ __ ] don't need to be on here talking
to a bunch of [ __ ] losers. Life's
losers that talk about themselves.
Brother, you are obese. That's my
answer. You are obese.
You are fat and ugly. Stop self-projecting.
Look in the mirror. You are chunky. You
are fat. You are ugly. You are a manta.
That is you. Stop talking about yourself.
M. you ugly you. You everything is you. In 2026,
you need to understand everything is
about you. It's no one else. It's not
me. It's not someone younger than you.
It's not someone better looking than
you. It's not It's not someone that can
go out and meet women unlike you, bro.
It's you. Get it? There you go. You got
a lesson. Consider yourself lucky, bro. Yeah.
And now I'm hearing some of you people
in [ __ ] wheelchairs. Jesus Christ.
Let's let's say uh well it's not
hypothetically because you actually are.
So no no no no. You need to rephrase
that. It's not hypothetically. Most of
you people are overweight and you are
ugly. Yeah. A lot of people are. And
does that change the fact? Well, A, I'm
not overweight and b I'm not
unattractive. again. Stop self-p
projecting. You're not going to put me
down to your level, bro. I'm way better
looking than you people will ever be, lad.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Good. Uh, no. If I've
had if I've had you blocked, if I've had
you blocked Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. That's good then. That's good.
Yeah. Good. Good. Thank you. And you
haven't been blocked. You was unblocked,
you [ __ ] [ __ ] for the past two
hours. So, yeah, that's good, man. Yeah. Good.
Yeah, that's good, mate. Yeah, that's
very very very [ __ ] good.
Good, bro. Yeah. Yeah, that's very very
very good. What? What park?
Bro, no one cares, brother. I'm better
looking than all of you. No one cares
about fat. Listen, listen, listen. Okay.
Okay. Listen. Why don't you come on
camera? Why don't all of you people come
on camera? It proves my point, bro.
You're fat and ugly. Looking at Jamie
Thompson. He wasn't blocked, Grezy. He
brother. Brother, you people are fat and
ugly. Stop self-projecting your ugliness
on someone that's better looking than
you. Had more women than you, got more
money than you. Stop it. Yeah. Stop it. Simple.
Put link up. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Put
the link up. Yeah. Yeah. Probably want
to arrange this properly to be fair.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
It's funny how you people don't show
your faces cuz you're [ __ ] ugly.
You'd rather talk about people that are
better looking than you. This is what I
mean with you people. Yeah. You'd rather
talk about people that are better
looking than you in hopes that you make
them feel like you. Bro, you listen.
People like you, Mr. Bliss. You're on
YouTube 24/7. You're fat. You're ugly.
You're a waster. You don't leave your
house. You're just a batty man. Some
ugly no woman getting [ __ ] You know
what I'm saying, bro? How about suck
your mom? You don't even try to ask me
questions, bro. Yeah. Anyway, Smokeoky
B. What's the location?
I can't comment on you. You're not blocked.
Oh, it's a fake. It's a fake, bro. It's
a fake, bro. Bro, it's a fake. It's a
fake. I knew it, bro. Bro, it's a fake.
It's a fake. He's not trying to come on,
bro. He's not trying to come on. I swear
to God, my dead dad's not trying to come
on, bro. Record it right now. It's a
fake. One second, bro. Let me put my
screen recorder on in case anyone thinks
I'm lying. One sec. He's a fake, bro.
It's a fake.
He's a fake, bro. It is. One second. Let
me get my scooter on, bro. Anyways, one
sec. One sec.
This is what I mean with this disabled
community, bro. This is what I mean with
this [ __ ] gay community. This is why I
tried to get away from it, bro.
That's definitely definitely definitely not him.
One second. I don't have you blocked, do
I? One second. You're not blocked. This
is what you little [ __ ] do on here.
Every No one's blocked. No one's
No one is blocked, bro. This is what I
mean with these little fat retards. These little
recorder two seconds.
Okay, I'm recording it now. One sec. See?
I'll upload it right now.
I will upload it right now, bro. One
second. Two sex.
This is what I mean with this gay [ __ ] community.
with this gay [ __ ] ass community. One
second, brother. I am better looking
than you fat. Isn't it funny how we've
never seen you people with a woman?
Projection. Never seen you people with
money. Bro, I'm better looking than you
fat slobs will ever be, bro. Don't own
that, bro. There you go.
One second. I'm putting up now, bro. 2 seconds.
One sec. It's coming up, bro. It's
coming up. It's coming up.
He tried to put a nude up. LT, you
[ __ ] [ __ ] It's not even him. One
second, bro. It's It's coming. I'm
uploading it now, bro. One sec.
You'll see exactly who's trying to join.
There you go. Go on it. It's a short.
Nope. It's fake smoky bees, bro. Trying
to put noobs up.
This is what I mean with you people,
bro. This is exactly what I mean with
you [ __ ] disabled ass people. I'm
done with this [ __ ] after today, bro.
There you go. It's right up there now.
It's on It's on It's on there, bro.
Yeah, the video's there. Look.
There you go. It's someone trying to
pawn bomb the [ __ ] out of me, bro. Yeah.
I'm done anyways, bro. Yeah, [ __ ] this.
[ __ ] this, bro. This is this is the [ __ ]
that these people are doing on here, you know. See?
Told you, bro. They're just [ __ ]
spastics. It's a [ __ ] community, bro. I
told you. I knew it straight away, bro.
This is what they do on here, bro. I'm
done with these [ __ ] pathetic [ __ ]
jealous fat morons. Bro,
did you see it? Did you see it? Greasy,
it's him. Bro, are you a [ __ ] [ __ ]
bro? Are you a [ __ ]
Have you not seen the account name?
Bro, I can't be these people, bro.
I I I I can't meet these people, bro. I
can't meet these people.
I can't, bro. They They're hurting my brain.
Oh, bro. I'm I I can't, bro. I can't.
I can't with these people, bro. They're
actually hurting me, bro. He's not
blocked, you [ __ ] His main is not
blocked, you [ __ ] [ __ ] I unblocked
him this morning.
He is not blocked on any main, bro. He's
not blocked on his main. Do you want me
to prove that as well, Grezy?
This is what I mean with these disabled
people. When they take an L. Yeah. This
is what they This is what I mean, bro.
It's a [ __ ] disabled community.
They're so disabled.
When they take L's, people will make
fake accounts of them trying to like
It's This is a disabled community, bro.
very disabled community.
I'll put a community post up right now
if you want.
There you go.
One second. I'm going to put a community
post up right this second.
Right. He's not blocked on anything.
This is what they do on here. They're
retards, bro. This is what I'm saying. One second.
Community post done.
Community post is done, lad.
There you go, Grezy. It's been uploaded.
He's not blocked.
Not blocked at all, lad.
The screenshot. Oh, just on a community post. Look.
Okay. Yeah, one second.
I don't know community post, but Okay.
Yeah. One second.
No one cares about the prime thing, you
fat ugly bastard. Stop deflecting.
One second, bro.
Oh, wait. Is it Maybe he might be
blocked from my other account. One
second, bro. I'm confused as [ __ ]
Hold on. Is it him? Yeah. One sec.
Oh, yeah. I'm live on my other account,
aren't I? One second. Maybe
he's not blocked from joining. One
second. Is he blocked?
No, he's not blocked. He's not blocked
on my on this account either. He's not
blocked. No, he's not blocked on either
of them. I knew he hadn't been blocked.
He's not blocked.
He's literally not blocked on either of them.
Nope. He's not blocked on either of them.
I thought maybe this. No, he's not blocked.
So, yeah, another Billy bullshitter. Another
Another little Billy bullshitter.
Anyways, bro. Yeah. Learn your lesson.
Learn your lesson to never call people
out again. You [ __ ] stupid little
[ __ ] And that's that. Yeah. Cuz you're
not about that life and you'll never
ever be about that life. Yeah. Just like
when you was asking people to show you
two grand before you meet them. You want
people to show you two grand before
before they meet them.
Why would you want someone to show you two grand,
bro? No one cares. Shut up. You're
boring. It's 2026. It's boring. Yeah,
but he's not commenting anymore. Okay.
Yeah. Yeah. I read what he wrote. One
second. Let him comment again.
Okay. Let him comment. Let him comment again, bro.
Bro, we know it's a fake. We literally
And LT knows it's a fake as well. So, I
don't know why he's pretending it ain't,
but he knows it's a fake. You okay?
Oh, is it you? Yeah.
Yeah. Well, it's a fake, man.
Brother, you need to stop calling people
a M that's better looking than you. It
doesn't change the fact that you're the
Ma and this guy that you're talking
about is is better looking than you and
had more women than you.
You need to stop calling people that are
better looking than you a manta lad. It
don't change the fact that you are the
biggest one going and you've never been
with a woman and you can't get a woman.
You need to stop calling people that are
better than you, lad. Listen, what
numerous women have called me. No, no,
no. One woman called me who I didn't
approach. But I've been with more women
than you. So that proves I'm better
looking than you. And I've never had to
simp like you, bro. You heard a woman
with daddy issues about 10 years ago
call me because she was insecure. Why is
it that a M has had more women than you?
Why is it a M can show their face? Why
is it a M have had more girls than you?
Cuz you're the manta, the all time
manta. You understand me, bro?
Numerous women. I've been with numerous
women. You [ __ ] little [ __ ] You little nerd.
You little nerd, bro. Imagine being you
and never being with a woman. A little
virgin on YouTube. Imagine being a
little [ __ ] virgin. Little fat [ __ ]
like you on YouTube every day. Little
low life. Imagine being some fat stinky
bastard that's never been with a woman.
I know what one I'd rather pick.
There you go.
Yeah. LT, what do you want, bro?
Imagine being a [ __ ] stinky little m
bastard like you that can't get a woman.
That's funny, isn't it? Imagine calling
someone a bunter, but they've been with
more women than you've ever been with.
Imagine that. That's saying something
then, isn't it, Land? [ __ ] [ __ ] >> Hello.
Yeah. Hey, it really is him.
>> Yeah, it's a fake him, bro. What's up?
>> No, no, no, no, it's not. I'm subscribed
to his channel. Yeah, the main channel.
Yeah, I'm subscribed to him.
>> He's not blocked. He's not blocked any other channels.
>> I'm subscribed to it and he's put up a
short of him showing you that he's tried to join.
>> Let me see.
>> Yeah. Go on his main channel. You see it for yourself.
>> On his main channel. I only know about
one channel, Smoke, and that's where he
showed the No. No. I guess cuz he just
made a new one. So, I'm saying main
channel. the one that like you might
know or whatever.
>> I'm on the channel where he's showing
his bank account and he's putting the wins up.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Go look on his shorts.
That's the one I just saw.
>> I'm on these shorts, bro. There's
nothing there. I'm on it right now,
>> brother. I've just commented on on these things,
>> bro. I swear to God, I'm on it right now.
I'm on it right now, bro.
>> Wait one sec. One sec.
>> I am literally on it right now, bro.
As we are in this conversation.
He hasn't up uploaded. [ __ ] all, bro. I
haven't left that channel for about 10 minutes.
>> It was up. It was up there.
>> But it's not up there now.
>> Yeah, he might have took it down, but
it's him, man.
>> But he's not trying to join, bro.
Because I've just shown who's tried to
join. I've just put a video up on it.
>> All right, cool. So, you you have to get
ready now. He's saying that he's he's on his way.
>> But it's not him.
>> It is. I just told you it's him. It's him,
>> brother. It's not him.
>> What am I going to lie for him for?
Brother, I have been on the guy's
channel for about 10 minutes.
>> Yeah, I saw a video. I saw it. I saw it.
That's the reason why I'm joining now.
>> Do a community post then right now then.
>> Oh, man. What's with all these
stipulations? He just done it. I don't
know. I think he took it down.
>> See what I mean, bro? See what I mean?
>> No. No. Listen. Listen. I think he took
it down. I saw it for myself. That's why
I'm on it,
>> bro. Bro, it's not there. It's literally
>> I guess he took it down. I don't know. I
literally I just wanted to see if it's still there.
>> Tell him to join now then. Okay. Tell
him to join now. I'll put the link up.
He's not kicked. No one's kicked.
>> You don't understand, bro. No one is
kicked. No one's blocked. No one.
>> The last comment I saw him say in your
um chat, he said that he's on his way,
>> brother. Brother, the link's there. No
one is blocked. I swear to God, on my
mom's life, no one is blocked.
>> Why is it all difficult on here, man? You
>> Why is it all difficult? Because the guy
is nowhere to be seen, to be heard of. That's why.
>> He's the one making it difficult. He was
just in your comments here and he said
that he's on his way. I saw it for myself.
>> Oh my god, bro. It wasn't even him.
>> No, no, maybe there was a fake account
here that tried to do all that. Yeah,
I'm not I'm not disputing that, but I'm
saying his actual main account. I saw it myself,
>> bro. You're giving you're making me lose
brain cells, bro.
>> I just agreed with you that maybe it was
a fake account that come initially and
done whatever they were trying to put
nudes up or whatever. But I'm saying he
he actually did try to join as well,
though. He put um he put
>> Bro, I done Oh, but I done a video.
>> You done a video with Yes. But I'm
saying that's Yeah, that's probably the
fake one. The fake person that's trying
to do nudes. Yeah.
>> There's an account here trying to join
right now. Yeah. Called
>> Hey, cover the screen. You can cover the
screen. You know,
>> M. Why are you running away from
>> Told you, bro?
>> It's the same [ __ ] It's none of them,
bro. I know. That's what I'm saying.
>> Listen them. Listen one second, bro.
Yeah. Oh, that has gone on.
>> And the Somalian pirate business. You're pathetic.
>> At least I don't beg a fat woman like
you. I am.
Imagine you weren't bigger women on the internet. [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> You spoke about your kids.
>> Yeah. And I spoke about you, bro. And I
spoke about you. Yeah.
>> Don't even
have a trust in your mother. And you've
not pulled up.
And you done nothing. He spoke about
nothing. Did Prem do nothing too then?
Huh? Who? Go on. Did they do nothing too?
Did did Lord Jay and Prime did they do nothing? They
>> went to his door, didn't they?
>> Yes. Yes. And I ran inside his house.
No, you haven't.
Pathetic little [ __ ] And if I ever got
my hands on your Somalian head, I'd
squash the [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I would.
Stick to begging ugly women on YouTube.
Stick to begging ugly women cuz you
can't get along.
Fat virgin virgin.
>> Put your camera on now. Put your camera
on now. I'm almost up and I'm better
looking at you and more women. And I've
never resorted to begging a woman. Why
don't you go back to begging?
>> Why don't you go back to fat boy?
>> Put your camera on
these people and you have to cheat to
call people. You are a little guy
and you done nothing. You Somalian [ __ ] pirate.
>> I'm not Somalian though. So now you're
>> Somalian. You are Somalian.
>> If I was Somalian I'll be proud of Let
me see that account. Let me see.
>> You are Somalian.
>> Is it Bulgarian then? Isn't it gypsy?
>> One second. One second.
>> Yeah. And what are you going to do about
it? So I don't need to do nothing to a
Bulgarian gypsy loser
wearing [ __ ] 3D glasses.
>> Shut the [ __ ] up. Cotton picker.
>> M is a
>> Yeah, there we go, bro. All right then.
All right, bro. I'm leaving. I'm leaving
in 10 minutes. Yeah. Well, I'm leaving.
Yeah, I'm leaving in 10 minutes, bro.
Yeah. All right. [ __ ] this.
>> You're going there now? Yeah.
>> Yeah. 100%. All right. We'll see. I'm
leaving a 10.