So yeah, let's see if we hear from this [ __ ] today.
This little fatty. Or is he all talked
just like the rest of him?
He's not blocked. He was blocked, but
I'm blocked him.
But you know exactly what's going to
happen in it. It's the same [ __ ] with
these little mobs. They're too disabled
to create a different atmosphere.
There we go.
We'll see, won't we?
If this [ __ ] comes on here and is still
up for meeting. Yeah,
[ __ ] better, dude. Cuz I didn't want
to [ __ ] come on YouTube for a while
to entertain a bunch of closeting homosexuals,
but obviously I said I was going to do
something, so I will. Same people every [ __ ] day.
Same [ __ ] jealous people every day.
I'm just waiting for this [ __ ] to um see
if he's going to come on, bro. so I can
show him up. Yeah.
Same repeating people,
same atmosphere, same comments. Yeah.
They really need to get a life.
They really really need to get a life.
He better do cuz I wasn't going to go
live for [ __ ] ages because obviously
I've got stuff to do now and that. So yeah,
can't be on here with these wasters
every day sadly. But I did say I was
going to meet this [ __ ] So he's not
blocked. So don't let him try and say,
"Oh, he's blocked." Cuz he's not
blocked. He knows his channel.
Yeah. So we just need um confirmation
and then I'll And the timing needs the
time and I'm and I'm there. Simple. Yeah, man.
But if you're not going to do it, stop
talking [ __ ] about people on YouTube.
It's as simple as that. If you got
something to say, well, say that you're
never going to stop these jealous people
talking [ __ ] So, but you know,
I was silly thing to say to be honest. Yeah.
Proper proper gay lords, bro. They're
proper [ __ ] homosexuals.
Same repeating jealous gay people. What
the [ __ ] bro? Does anyone put [ __ ]
gambling videos up anymore or what?
No, they don't.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Right, bro. Yeah,
right. I only gambled£10 yesterday.
Hey, do you see these people getting so
happy yesterday that I lost £10?
Imagine that, bro.
I know. I started feeling really bad for
these people, bro. I actually feel
sorry. They They have definitely had
some kind of bullying in school in their
life, bro. You're happy that someone's
lost 10 pounds? Are you [ __ ] for real? 10 10
[ __ ] pounds. What the [ __ ] They're
life's losers, bro. Actual life's
losers. You know, even £100, if you lose
£100, some can say, "Oh, well, you can
go for a night out with £100." But but
£10, that's barely the the price of a of
a pint now.
That's how bad it is. That wouldn't even
buy you a round of drinks in London.
They will even buy a round of drinks for two people.
Kind of mad when you see that way, isn't it?
They're [ __ ] life's losers.
They are disabled. They're proper proper
They are, man. They definitely are disabled. But
yeah, this fat ugly people indigo that's
got nothing going for themselves.
That's why I sat on YouTube 24/7.
So, we'll wait for this [ __ ] anyways.
Yeah. When am I going to go to
Nottingham? Uh, I haven't decided yet,
but I will be going there. I will be
going there cuz I want to go there
anyway. So, we'll be going there. Don't
worry about that.
And you can see what this Joseph Ferrar
is all about as well.
which is nothing.
So yeah, just like this smoky beunt. Yep.
So yeah, man.
All in all, maybe like
Two and a half hours.
See you later, Fatty Thompson.
Come out the closet, gay boy.
Um, yeah. All in all, like on the train
from the train station, it's about an
hour and 40 minutes, but getting there and that,
yeah, probably about 2 and 1/2 hours.
But that's like the whole journey from
here. It's not like if you're talking
just the train at the train station.
Yeah. About an hour and 40.
I wouldn't mind going there, bro. Get on
an approaching session. The ratio is
good there as well.
So, I don't mind, bro.
I go [ __ ] I ain't going to those [ __ ] leads.
[ __ ] that, bro. I'm not going to those [ __ ] leads.
There's a reason for it, but I I don't
mind going again, bro. Seriously, I seriously don't.
Like I said, the ratio is good. So,
yep. Just need to come out the closet.
That's all these people need to do,
Indigo, is just come out the closet.
Seriously. Seriously need to come out
the closet at this point.
It's kind of mad, isn't it, bro? Indigo
to have these people the so many people
obsessed with you. Is it strange, huh?
That chicken was awful yesterday, man.
That serves me right for being a big fat
stinking dirty copycat, don't it? Yeah.
Don't know why they don't just come out
as gay. Like I said, it's 2026, bro. Not even like, you know. Yeah.
Jealous. Jealous and gay. Indigo.
I think they I think they fancy me. I
think they're jealous. And I think they
hate their own lives as well. I think
it's three different things.
I think it's three things.
I think they're gay and they fancy you.
They're jealous and they hate their own
lives as well.
Yeah, that's what I think. I think it's three things.
Yeah, definitely, bro. Definitely.
I'm only on here today to see if this
[ __ ] is going to come on. So yeah. Yeah, bro.
No, no, no.
Just got my cup of [ __ ] here.
Yep. My cup of [ __ ]
Could you imagine you got any of these
people approaching women on the street sober?
It would never happen. They would have
the balls. Also, I think that's another
thing that they hate as well, that you
can like go out and you can actually
like meet women and stuff and their
anxiety would never allow it. That's
another thing that I think they're
jealous of as well. Cuz think about it,
Indigo. Yeah. You got V and stuff. Yeah.
They're begging women on [ __ ]
YouTube. They're begging women on
YouTube, bro. They're probably [ __ ]
ugly as [ __ ] They don't leave the
house. They don't socialize, you know?
Yeah, but I mean like people like V and that.
Yeah, but I mean people like V and other people, bro.
Not just them four gay people. I'm
talking about other people
that might not be gay like V and that.
See you later.
Come out the closet.
You get me? Yeah,
I'm talking about people like VNA uh VJ.
Yeah, definitely, bro. Definitely. No,
no. I'm just going live, Greg. See if
the cunt's going to going to come on, you know.
What's up, bro? That chicken was
horrible yesterday, Grezy.
I've got myself to blame for that. Being
a big fat, stinky, dirty copycat.
KFC only from now on. Jobly. Yeah.
What are you having for dinner today,
Grezy? I'm having roast dinner.
Roast beef, roast gum.
I was watching, grievy, I was watching
some vintage porn last night.
And you're not going to believe I had
about four wanks in the space of 40 minutes.
watching the same vintage porn movie
back in the day, you know, 19 I think it was 1977
when you couldn't see the westernity in
their eyes. Greavesy,
you know, now you can see the westernity
in their eyes.
It's in the eyes, Grezy. The eyes never lie.
It's the eyes, Greasy. The eyes. The
eyes never lie. Yeah.
What do you think of that? We
only watch Vintage By.
That sounds so weird like Adban said,
but there's a reason for it.
There is a reason for it.
A lovely Christian Greasy. That's cute, isn't it?
Get yourself down waxies, lad.
Grezy, get yourself down waxies, lad. Yeah.
So, what's the chances this cunt's going
to come on here today and agree and that
it's not happening, bro?
You won't beat me, bro.
You will not beat me.
They started with me, bro. They kept
they kept talking about me and [ __ ]
bro. I didn't even start it. So I
thought, okay, we we'll we'll do that
way, won't we? Mo,
I made myself a lovely copper.
>> I brushed my teeth as soon as I woke up
and I waited.
>> Yeah, ma. I got a Spider-Man cup.
>> They just sleeping.
>> Cuz they're having a sleep.
>> Look, I don't know who the [ __ ] this is.
No, it's a man.
>> Look, you said he needed a barber.
I didn't say executing.
>> His hair clips on. Mom,
that chicken was disgusting yesterday.
>> It was,
>> but it was nice. The the other day I had it.
>> So, what's the best chicken KFC if you
Well, fried chicken. Well, yeah.
>> Say so. Yeah.
>> And Jobly is nice. You would like Jobly
because there's no Greece, Mom.
>> Yeah, but it's no there's no grease.
>> It's like a ch Lester Square.
>> I don't think there is anyone nearer than that.
>> Uh Horn shirt. >> Yeah.
Yeah. I can't I can't wait till the for
the lovely roast m I'll be waiting patiently. 3:00.
I bet that's going to be nice. That smoke's going. Yeah.
>> Yeah. And I'll buy I'll buy I'll buy it
next time. Yeah. So, we'll have it again
in a month.
>> I stopped I stopped going um for
roasting is when it when they started
putting the prices up. [ __ ] £44.
>> But that's everything though. And
there's a lot more. >> Yeah.
No, no, no. That's mad. That is That is
mad. Did you like the Hulks more roast?
That was so nice, isn't it?
>> It was big. >> Really been to >> Okay.
>> I like Turkish food as well. I like
Turkish wings. You do it. I don't think
I prefer than Indian though. >> No,
>> I love Indian food.
I love um but yeah, that fried chicken
was not good.
>> Yeah, I will do. I will do.
>> Yeah, I will just leave it.
>> Yeah, the the football bet didn't um
win. It's only10, is it? So, I don't
mind. I don't even That's not even
gambling fucking£10, is it? Really? Can
you class it as that? >> Yeah.
People's probably spend more than the
lottery in it. Well,
>> cuz I didn't want to do it. Listen,
because I said I weren't going to do it
anymore and I didn't want to do it. I
could only justify£10 because it's like,
well, if you do 10 or you don't, what
difference is it going to [ __ ] make?
>> I'm saying that number three. >> Yeah.
>> Not one two lines.
>> Yeah. It's disgusting, man.
>> I've never done a lottery in my life.
Maybe I'll try it one day. Pick the numbers.
>> How many numbers do you pick?
So what five would I would pick?
5 8 11 two 17
>> and the bonus. >> Um 25.
>> I don't think it goes to 25. The bonus or does
>> um so then
one second. One second. Um, Benny then >> Benny,
>> I'm going to have to check that. I don't
think the B goes on the boy made on the ring.
>> Yeah, I got your mark.
Are you okay, lady?
That would teach me for being a copycat
yesterday. Is it?
>> I got Shine on the 27th. Yeah,
>> you're coming as well. You're watching
the new scream with me, mama. >> Why?
>> I sleep with fat. Look. No, but look who
I sleep with. He's very cuddly. Crash.
I want him. >> Scooby. >> Yeah. >> Spiderman. >> Why?
>> Next thing Crash is going to have a baby.
Yeah. Yeah. The bubba. >> Yep. Mom.
No, I'm not having a breakfast cuz I'm
having a big roast dinner. So, that will
ruin the appetite, won't it? Yeah,
I know what this person on Reddit said
to me. We I said
they said having a woman control one to
control a woman is bad. She said, "Yeah,
I get you. To be honest, I used to just
collect women and compare them." And
then she wrote, "Oh, dang. I thought you
wanted to find someone to love and to be
loved. I don't think I can help you
then. I'm sorry. I hope you change where
your values are at, though, so you can
have a good life." Nope.
Just a collection.
What's wrong with a collection, Greasy?
I I already am loved. I'm loved by Crash
Bandicut. That's all I need.
You know, you should get yourself a dog
grievy like King. They're very loyal.
They don't cheat. They don't answer
back. All they want is walkies and to be
fed and they'll love you forever.
They're so loyal, Grezy. Unlike women,
you can't trust them devils,
Grezy. They're the devil. You can't
trust them bastards. Seriously.
So, get yourself a dog. Honestly, Grezy,
I'm I'm actually being serious.
He sleep next to me.
Yeah, I was watching this vintage porno,
right? And this woman, she uh she was
with this guy, I don't know it was her
husband, and then she went without Adam
to the cinema and then she started
having sex in the cinema. Grievesy,
does that happen in real life?
She started like um
giving a [ __ ] in the cinema and
getting [ __ ] That that that don't
happen in real life. Surely not, Grezy.
Nah, Greasy. Surely not. You don't just
[ __ ] go out. Your husband's at home
and that nah. In the [ __ ] cinema.
And then the guy paid. And then on the
way out to the cinema, the guy paid her
five five bucks for a shag.
She's like, "How much have you got?"
He's like, "Oh, I got 25." And she was
like, "Oh, just give me five." Yeah,
right. Does that happen in real life?
It's in the eyes. The eyes never lie.
Now I can't even
people loud because as soon as I look at
their eyes, it is it's just like they're
just like NPCs. Greasy.
You can see the westernity in their eyes.
This is the eyes.
The eyes. The eyes never lie.
But men don't have it. If you look at
men's eyes, they don't have it.
They just look like [ __ ] Star Wars [ __ ] droids.
That disgusting westernized look.
Too much Tik Tok in it. Yep. So westernized. Grezy.
Well, I met a love Well, I've met a
lovely Christian now. Grezy, you should
be happy for me.
No, I'm talking about the eyes in her on
on her face. They've all got the They've
all got the same westernized look.
That dirty westernized look they give you.
Men don't have the same look as they
have. Why is that?
They're addicted to their smartphones.
They've got a relationship with their smartphones, lad.
They're addicted to social media,
Instagram, and I don't post on Instagram and that.
Yeah, you can see the westernity in
their eyes, Greezy.
It's like they look Oh, I can't explain
it, bro. But it's just the same look in
their [ __ ] eyes. Men don't have it in their eyes. Nah.
Well, this Christian woman, you know, um
she watches Love Island, but she hasn't
been a [ __ ] or anything, so I don't care
what people watch.
I mean, what's the chance you're going
to find someone that doesn't use social
media? I don't think so.
I really don't think so. Okay.
But yeah, there's a lot of people that
watch that Love Island. Yeah.
All right. Did you Did you see um Grezy
HS tick- tockie met Harvey?
Harvey smashes up things apparently.
Yeah, Harvey smashes up things. Yeah.
H says Tik Tocky. I love that. You know, Yeah.
So, why do you reckon they all watch um
Love Island? Um Grezy.
Yeah, that's him. Yeah. Poor [ __ ]
Yeah, he met him. He's done a video with
HS Tik Tocky.
So, what do you reckon they all watch um
Love Island to fit in then? Or could
they generally like it? I've never
watched it in my life, but I know people.
No, I'm not disabled like you Ly Mongs.
So, do you reckon they watch it uh cuz
they like it? Greasy. just to fit in.
Nah, I'm not disabled like um you lavongs.
Come on, Smokey. Where you at?
So, this is what you do. You come online annoying people
and then when people want to meet you.
Yeah, of course you do. And then when
people want to meet you, you disappear.
But this Christian once said that she
was watching Love Island the other day, but
she wasn't she hasn't gave any [ __ ]
vibes yet, any stuck up vibes or
anything like that. So,
see you later.
Get yourself a job before telling other
people to get a job.
These people really are disabled. Greasy lad.
Do you still think this Christian
person's all right, Grezy? Yeah.
I'd always love to meet somebody, you
know, the exactly the same age as me,
but you know, we can't always have that
happen, you know. Not that there's
anything wrong with a 23 year old. It's
[ __ ] that's well all right, but you
know, it's still like be good if you
could meet somebody the exact same age
as you, you know. I don't know why, but
doesn't always happen that way.
We usually sadly. Yeah.
Yeah. Hey, you got blocked from Lord
J's, didn't you, Grezy?
They all ambushed you, didn't they? And
then they blocked you, poor [ __ ]
Did they ambush you? Oh,
white. Oi, Greasy. Yeah, I've got a
little I've got a little challenge for you.
I've got a little challenge for you. Buy
some white Captain Morgans
and finish the bottle in the same day.
There you go. I've done challenges. I
used to drink white Captain Morgans all the time.
That's a little challenge. Greasy.
No, she didn't. And see you later.
See you later, lad. Get kicked.
Another lovely mong.
Yeah, gre do that.
Yeah, Captain Morgan white. Yeah, it's
Captain Morgan rum, but it's Captain
Morgan Morgan's white rum.
It's very, very hard to get, but it's
[ __ ] very strong. I used to have it
all the time when I was like 23, 24. I
used to have it all. I don't know how I
used to have that, you know, now looking
back on it. I don't even really drink
rum nowadays. When I drink, it's just beer.
I used to have the white one. Oh, but
the next day, Greasy.
But the [ __ ] next day, mate.
Yeah, it is. It is easy to finish a
bottle of it. That's But the white one's really strong.
Beer does give you a big belly, but you know,
yeah, beer does give you a big belly,
but the thing is, yeah, you don't get
any um you don't get any hangovers with it.
That's the good thing about it. No hangovers,
whereas the rum gives you horrible hangovers.
Yeah, I don't really drink. When I do,
it's just beer.
I just I just stick the beer usually.
So, why is everyone watching um Love
Island now? waves it.
What' you say?
Oh, bless you.
Did it Did it become a trend?
Did it uh Did it become a trend then, Grezy?
Did it become a friend?
All right, Indigo, go on Lord's Day now
and ask about this smoky bee, bro. Oh,
strange is it lad? So what was it? Was
it similar to the shovel cole thing then Grezy?
So is it similar to that then? Is that
what you're trying to say?
I [ __ ] hate that kind of [ __ ] you know, bro.
I hate trends.
See you later, lad.
So, made me laugh on the AI bit. greasy.
I was like, "Oh, if you said you didn't
like her, people, the kids would tease
you." They would say it to avoid being teased, greedy.
But everything I said was spot on anyway around insecurity.
Um, to fit in. I Everything I said come
up an AI cuz it's so obvious. It's the
name. It was too obvious
to avoid being teased. briefly Yeah.
Oh, have you seen that [ __ ] Greasy?
Yeah, I'm sure you've seen on Instagram.
This guy is trolling like Arsenal fans
and that and they they said, "Fuck off
now before we do this, before we do
that." Have you seen it? I I've seen
been seeing it quite a bit lately. over football.
They get violent like that over football.
Kicking the ball around. It's always
seems so silly to me, you know. Always
seems so silly to me.
It just always has. I've never
understood that whole football rivalry
and that. I've never just never did. I
was speaking to someone about it the
other day on when I went out drinking.
I've never understood it. I really have
Like the violence and that it's to me
it's so stupid.
Like I can understand if they put like a
big bet on and they lost, but they're
not. They're not the players. They're
just watching it and they're mad about
them. It's just it's just
another trend in it. Another trend. I've
never liked football and I'll never like football.
just never understood it, bro. Never did.
You should watch Green Street Grievy if
you never have. And you know that kind
of [ __ ] did used to happen back in the day.
West Ham and that mad over football.
He is mad.
But people just used to like football
or like saying, "Oh yeah, I've been
abroad. Have you been abroad?" And and
stuff like that.
What is that? What you mean?
No, I was saying it to you, Grezy,
because you haven't been you haven't
been anywhere really. You haven't been
to many places in it and you're my age.
I'm not shaming you if you have or you
haven't. I just said that you said that
you wanted to go to Scotland and you never have. So yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. See you later.
Yeah, lots of copycat trends going
around. Isn't that right, Grezy?
Do you know what I want to get? I want
to get a nice bit of fillet steak,
Grezy. Yeah. And make like a fillet steak baguette.
No, they never drop their standards. Morning England.
What do you think of that, Grezy? Making
like a Phillips steak baguette.
Is that something you'd be interested in seeing? seeing, Captain?
Yeah. Fin steak is nice in sandwiches.
It's very expensive steak, Gezy.
It's the most expensive one.
You know, I like Phillips steak, but the
thing is the reason I prefer sirloin is
because sirloin's got the fat.
Do you get it, Grezy? Um, sirloin's got
the fat. Philip doesn't have the fat.
It is nice. It is really nice, but
there's no fat. That's the only thing
with it. So, I think they're even sandwiches.
That steak yesterday, Gre, I finished it
in about 5 minutes. It was delicious.
I haven't been a I hadn't been able to
eat steak for a little while because
where my like tooth was healing and that in it
where my tooth was healing um
yeah it wasn't uh when you'd bite on it
and that it still feel sensitive the
tooth that got extracted. So I could
only bite with like one um on one side
of my mouth.
So there's no point eating state then get me.
What do you think, Grezy? Does that
person who I'm talking to still seem
good? Do they still seem okay?
The first I met on Thursday less.
But the problem with it now, Grezy, is that um
when you're this age, they expect too much,
you know, and and well, not them, like
her specifically, but the thing is the
thing is at this age now, the age we are
at now, they expect people to have a car
even when they don't drive. They expect
people to do this, people to to do that.
And whilst they're still living with
their [ __ ] parents, bro,
they expect all of these things. Like
I'm not saying her, but I'm saying like
generally. And they're like they've got
a lot less. They'll probably be in a
worse position than you, but they expect
all of this. You get it?
That's the pro That's the That's the problem, bro.
There's a reason. There's a solid reason
why like I don't have um
a driving license, bro. There's a reason
cuz it's pointless driving in London.
But obviously there is a reason, but
obviously if you say that to someone,
they will just see as you're a [ __ ]
bum. I don't know a greasy. Do you have
your driving license?
Do you have your I don't think you do. No, but obviously
obviously there's a like I said, oh,
there's loads of like transport and
that, but obviously if you say that to
someone, they'll just see you as like a bomber. Yeah,
is what it is. Eh,
it is what it is. Why?
Why? Bless you.
Why not? Bless you.
Yeah, I'm done with this [ __ ] today. Anyways, this
I'm going to
Oh, with your little ticks. Bless you. Then
what ticks do you have?
Yeah, I'm just on large now. Um, music.
Was that lush?
He's making excuses now. Oh, he's making
excuses. He's trying to say if you
didn't say, this is what I mean with
these little retards on this community,
bro. Oh, I said if you didn't turn up
for a fight on Thursday, bro, I already
turned up, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
I was live. We usually didn't see it.
Yeah, cuz you was sleeping, mate. I was
live and the guy didn't come on once.
You [ __ ] stupid little prick.
What a [ __ ] idiot, bro. You see what
I mean? But they start This is what I
mean with the people in this community
yet. They start [ __ ] that they can't
finish every time. They start [ __ ] that
they can't [ __ ] finish, bro. What a
[ __ ] bro. What an absolute [ __ ]
About, oh, I didn't turn up. I was
[ __ ] live, you idiot. And the [ __ ]
didn't go on my live stream once.
You know what I mean? They're all
[ __ ] [ __ ] on this community, bro.
Proper proper [ __ ]
you know? And he's going to be the same
as well. Greavesy Joe F. He was already
saying, "Oh, I'll see you when I see you."
They're all the same, bro. They're never
going to meet anyone on here, bro.
[ __ ] if I didn't turn up on Thursday.
I wasn't. I was there Thursday, you
[ __ ] [ __ ] And the [ __ ] didn't come
on. [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
But yeah, you don't have you don't have
verbal tick screams here. You don't have Tourette's.
You don't have verbal ticks.
No way. I believe motor ticks, but
there's no way you've got verbal ticks.
I've never ever met anyone in my life
with [ __ ] verbal ticks. I've met
people with motor tick.
Yeah, I've met people with motor tick. never.
There was an account that wanted to meet
me on Thursday that never come on a
hangouts that never spoke and I was live
out and he didn't come on.
What the [ __ ] And that's your reasoning
for not meeting. You're a [ __ ] idiot,
man. You're an absolute clown. Stop
starting [ __ ] you can't finish. It's
embarrassing, isn't it, Greasy? Stop
starting [ __ ] that you can't [ __ ]
finish. I was live, bro, on Thursday. I
was live 10 minutes um 10 minutes to
6:00 and I was live until uh 6:15
and the [ __ ] didn't come on. [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah,
they're absolute mongs on this
community, bro. Absolute mongs on this community.
They really are mons, bro.
and Joseph Ferrar's not going to be
meeting anyone either. So yeah.
Yeah. And this that that account done
the same thing. That account done the
same thing, bro. It's boring now. Very
very boring. And that Jo's not going to
meet me either cuz he knows he won't win
against me, bro. He's some scrawny little [ __ ]
He's a scrawny little weak man just like his boyfriend.
So I mean, you know what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah. He that account done the same thing, Grezy.
What they want you to do? Yeah. What
they want you to do, Yeah. is go to an
exact place. Yeah. Yeah.
They want to go and they want you to go
to an exact place so then they can say,
"Haha, we made you go there. We control
your life." That's what they want to do,
bro. That's literally exactly what that
Jo wants to do. I can see through these
people. I know what they're about, bro.
I know what they're about.
I was born on a day, bro, and it wasn't
yesterday. Why do you think the [ __ ]
won't meet me in Nottingham?
Nottingham's 70 mi away from him and
it's 150 mi away from me
and it's the same the northeast. So it's
the same direction. It's not like I'm
going to [ __ ] Brighton and I'm
telling somebody to meet me from from
[ __ ] Bristol. It's the same
direction. That's the whole point of it.
You get me?
It's like Stoker Manchester. There a
train ride away in the same direction.
You get me?
And look at this smoking me. Not a [ __ ] peep.
[ __ ] idiot, bro.
And then I'm not I bet you he doesn't
get stick for not showing up. Grezy.
So yeah, same same [ __ ] with them, bro.
Same [ __ ] with them.
It's the same [ __ ] with Peace.
Usually very bad. Very bad.
Why don't you go Why don't you go to the
um the fish shop, Greavves, and get
yourself a nice Savoin chips?
I like that. A nice savoy chips, Grezy.
I'm a bit hungry now to be fair, but
I can't have anything because I'm having
a roast dinner.
Oh, bless you then. We
not sure. Would you would you say the
Would you say the pieces of chicken
where you went what what you got
yesterday was better than the than than KFC? No. Oh, bless.
So, what do you think? KFC's fried
chicken's the best fried chicken gezy probably. Yeah,
I reckon it is, bro.
As it stands. I mean, there probably is
places that are better, but I haven't
come across Well, Job is good, but yeah,
people say that, "Oh, it's soggy. KFC's
chicken soggy in that greasy." But the
thing is, yeah, if you go anywhere else,
uh, or they say it's salty, if you go
anywhere else, it's just going to be dry. So, yeah,
I like I like a middle breast from KFC, Greavesy,
you know, like a nice middle breast.
I don't know. One second.
Oh, do you watch that? Uh, Natalie karaoke greasy.
Yeah, you know who it is though. It
know who it is, right? No, nothing.
Laugh. They just linked to her channel
and I went on it.
All right. I went on your um community
post yesterday and I saw where you was
having McDonald's where you was watching
the Monty drama. Grezy, it made me laugh.
Yeah, it made me laugh, lad. You had two
You had two chips,
you fatty. You had two two portions of
fries in you, Grezy. He was watching it
on the telly, weren't you?
This [ __ ] then. Oh, bless.
Yeah. One second.
I'll just wait, Grezy.
Yeah, I'll just wait.
You You'll wait.
Yes. Till they get a life. Grooy.
Be realistic. P
Gy be realistic. P
be realistic. Okay. Oh [ __ ]
Yeah. Get him back on here.
Get him back on here, Grezy.
I wonder what happened to him.
Do you miss his little voice, Grezy?
Do you do you miss his little dialect?
His little accent. Bless you.
At least I'm not the only one getting trolled.
No, he must do by now. He must do. I
haven't seen it. No. Sometimes he just
comes off of YouTube for a bit cuz I
haven't seen him anywhere.
I haven't seen him anywhere, lad.
Wow, these people are so bitter.
I wonder what these people look like, Grezy.
Yeah, that's funny, man. Oh, I like that
Chewca sound effect.
I wonder what these people look like,
Grezy, that are talking about people's
looks every day. I wonder, eh, I really, really wonder.
probably a lot a lot more uglier than
anyone that they're trying to call
anyone else. Probably probably the case, Greasy. Probably.
Yeah. Way uglier. Way skintter. Way
everything. I mean, there's a reason why
they're on YouTube 24/7, Greasy.
There's a reason why they're on here 24/7.
And it's not cuz they're living their best life.
[ __ ] sake, man.
So, is anyone going to call this guy a
bottle job today? Greasy, for not showing up.
I hope people talk about it today. Greasy
and not be biased.
What do you think? Wave there.
What do you think, Grezy?
So, you're saying that you'll wait
Greasy, you'll wait, will you?
H, how long will you wait for?
So, when you said you couldn't cold
approach when I asked you yesterday,
Grey, is it because your little anxiety
wouldn't allow it?
Is it because your anxiety wouldn't
allow it? Bless you.
Bless your life. Bless you.
[ __ ] bless you.
Yeah, but look, I've done it and I've
met a Christian Greavesy.
But I met a Christian. You know That's
no one saying anything about Smoky B yet. Nope. Nah. heat.
I need to go Burger King again at some
point, Grezy, and get that that burger
again, but the chicken one this time, Grezy,
it will be lush, won't it, Greavvesy?
There's a Burger King, a bus ride away
from me, Grezy.
It's about 10 minutes on a bus cuz other
one got closed down.
But I'm going to eat in. I'm not going
to order it, Greasy.
Cuz it just comes cold when you order it. Grezy.
Grezy. I think Chev's fit.
I think they're a bit more now. I think 1.75.
Greasy. I think she's fit. Greasy. Any
opinion on that, Grezy?
Yeah, I saw I've seen that as well,
Indigo. I've seen it.
Yeah, I think she's fit.
There's no big day because the guy's not
turning up. Lj's already said it.
And ready to shut the trolls up for good. Bro,
how long have you been on this community?
You're never going to shut these jealous
trolls up. The [ __ ] You'll never shut
him up. They'll always continue to be
jealous and talk [ __ ]
You must be new on this community, bro.
Cuz I've met I've tried to meet loads
and loads of people and I've met people.
You'll never shut these gen people up
unless you leave. Yeah, you must be new
on this community, mate. Cuz I've met
tons of tons of people and tried to make
people for years.
And yeah, the guy's not showing up
either. Typical typical [ __ ] house.
Start something that he can't finish.
Well, no. If I don't hear from him,
no, obviously not.
Why am I going to do that if the guy's
not coming on typing or not hearing from
him? Why am I going to do that?
I didn't even want to come on YouTube. I
weren't going to come on YouTube today,
Grevy, if it wasn't for this um punt.
Well, that's not going to happen. So, yeah,
I'm not just going to turn up somewhere
when we've not heard from the [ __ ] all
day. Isn't that right, Grezy?
You know, this is so disabled. All of
this, it's so [ __ ]
Oh my god. This is such a disabled community, bro. Madness.
It's They're so disabled on here, bro.
Yeah, I'm live in it. I'm waiting, bro.
No one He's not blocked either. He isn't
blocked. And if you think he is blocked,
you can go on L J's. He's not a L JS either.
He's a [ __ ] ass, bro.
He's got a lot to say behind the
keyboard, just like his boyfriend Joe.
Then Joe's not showing up either.
So that's two [ __ ] houses. That's
another thing they've got in common.
They're all [ __ ] houses.
on this community. That's another thing
they've got in common. They're all [ __ ] houses.
And after this, I won't be on here for a
while, Grezy, because I'll be living my life, bro.
So, I won't have time for this [ __ ]
I'll come back occasionally and I'll go
live and that if I when I'm when I can't
be bothered to do anything else, but I'm
literally done after today for a little bit, bro.
[ __ ] knows for how long. But yeah,
some of us have got [ __ ] to do in their
lives, bro. Unlike these [ __ ] sad
cases, the gold laws. So yeah, that's that. Bro,
I shouldn't even be on here today, but I
thought I'm not going to let this [ __ ]
try and get the try and get the last
laugh. I'm in.
You get me, bro?
And you'll see the biasness today as
well, um, Greasy, because no one's going
to say anything either.
No one's going to say anything.
When this doesn't show up,
I fancy a milkshake, you know, man. McDonald's.
Well, it's not going to happen. It's not
It's not going to happen.
He don't have the balls. He ain't coming
to London and he ain't going live in
London. He ain't got the balls.
So, it's not happening.
I don't believe any of them, bro. I know
they're not turning up.
Just like that. Joe Joe's never turning
up because he's an ugly bastard
and he's not going to show his face
because the moment people on here show
their face. Yeah.
Right. It it it's they can't do that,
bro. Because then they can't talk about
anyone ever again, just like the bomb couldn't.
That's why they don't show up. That's
why they will never show up, you know? Yeah.
Yeah. They say she's attracted.
That's funny, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. I saw that advert in [ __ ] ugly.
I don't know why you get called for not
liking that attractive to be fair. Yeah.
Well, we know why
they let you slug off everyone else,
don't they, Greavvesy?
They'd let you call other women ugly and
not say anything about it. They wouldn't
look at you like you were weird, would they? Greasy.
They used to tease you if you said that
she wasn't attractive. That was the
funniest bit. To avoid being teased.
They said it to avoid being teased. Yeah.
To avoid being teased. Yeah, man.
Right. I'm still a law J. And where is
this smokey [ __ ]
Tell this [ __ ] to put the link up.
Tell him to put the link up, bro, and I'll join.
I just need to know where this [ __ ] is.
Want to knock his [ __ ] block off.
I want to knock his [ __ ] block off.
Tell him to put the link up.
Well, I'm going to do it somewhere else.
You're a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Put the link up.
Right. One second, bro.
One second, lad.
What are you talking about? You [ __ ] stupid girl.
Oh, [ __ ] Dewey.
Where's your [ __ ] boyfriend? Your boyfriend.
I was [ __ ] live. You [ __ ] stupid gun. Yo,
what the [ __ ] is going on? Where's your boyfriend?
Where's your [ __ ] boyfriend?
Nah, I ain't like you. I don't put my
hood over my head when I go on a plane
biting my teeth like you. You [ __ ]
You [ __ ] [ __ ] No, but seriously,
where's your boyfriend? Your boyfriend's
supposed to be meeting me today.
I was live on Thursday, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] And the guy didn't come in. He
Was he in the park? Was he live in a
park? Did he do a video at the park? You
[ __ ] [ __ ] Listen, I'm I want to go
to North London today to meet your
boyfriend. We're waiting for him. We're
waiting for your boyfriend. Don't run
away. Don't run away. Don't run away.
Oh, and that's why that's why you said
about you coming on Sunday because you
knew your boyfriend weren't going to
turn up. Well, guess what? You're banned
from England and you're banned from
London. And if I find out you're and if
I find out you go to Birmingham, if I
find out you go to Birmingham, I'm going
to knock your [ __ ] eyes out your
head. Do you understand me? You stupid little [ __ ]
You [ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] Yeah.
You [ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] Yeah, you
Sorry about that, lad.
>> Oh, Mr. Magcoo.
What are you doing here?
>> Yeah, bro. Uh, he's a [ __ ] man.
He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
Told you they're all the same on here.
Oh, sorry about the echo, lads.
What the [ __ ] bro?
No one is showing. What the [ __ ] bro?
Hold on. I need to go. Let me do this live. Oxide.