that back up now, bro. Yeah, man. Yep.
There we go.
So, he didn't even turn up himself and
they're saying that I've took it out.
Typical, bro. It's so typical with this community.
It's completely completely typical with
this [ __ ] community, bro.
It's That's why it's called the disabled
community. You see? That's why it's
literally called the disabled community.
He didn't turn up himself.
I was there waiting for him to do a
[ __ ] tell me where he was. He He
wasn't there. He was trying to learn me
with LT and then they act like they've
won. This is what I mean, bro. They're
disabled on here, bro. Proper disabled.
He was trying to learn me with LT and he
couldn't even show where he was.
And they're trying to say, "Oh, I didn't
turn up." Bro, he was trying to what he
was doing what he was doing.
I need to get some food now, bro. My
food's ready. My roast dinner's ready.
Um, basically, uh, what he was trying to
do, he was trying to lur me. It was so
obvious. If it was so obvious,
no, I didn't record a video. No,
no, he wasn't there. He actually wasn't
He was trying to get LT to do his dirty work.
He was trying to get LT. Why was he at
the park? Ask yourself that question.
Why was he at the park?
Why was he at the park? Where was the smoky bezy?
This is disabled, bro. Anyways, I need
to go eat this food now. Anyways, so yeah.
Did he do a video? No, he didn't. Did he
show where he was? No, he didn't. So,
there you go.
And this is why it's called a disabled community.
One sec. I've got to eat this food. I'll
be back later. I got a roast dinner I'm eating.
I'll be back later. Yeah, 100%.