Yo, I'm not going to be live long.
Oh [ __ ] Yeah. Oh, stop to that channel. Dude,
I need to delete these [ __ ]
these lives on here, bro. Yep.
story. I was eating. Yeah.
Sad, sad, sad, bastard. 54.
Sorry about that. Oops.
There we go. Yeah.
Just the same old [ __ ] Ben. Same
projecting people ain't got no life.
Same people obsessed with Peter Belly.
Just the same old, lad. Just the same
old. How have you been?
[snorts] I'm actually going to be coming
off this [ __ ] Um, Ben anyways, lad.
I might come back like every two months.
Go live once every two months. Yeah, bro.
This is the same [ __ ] on here, Ben.
It's the same [ __ ] with these people on
here every day, bro. I thought in 2026
they were going to get a life. I went
out drinking Thursday, Ben.
Yeah, I went out drinking Thursday. I
got some numbers and [ __ ]
Yeah, man. Back to life. Back to reality.
Weird on here, lad.
It's quite scary, Ben. I've got a lot of
people obsessed with me on here, lad.
I don't know how many times I have to
say it. I don't swing that way.
I don't swing that way, Ben. You know,
so that's that, lad. Um
yeah, Luc not on him. I tell you, Ben,
you just come and stay, don't you?
Bro, [ __ ] hell. You are a sad
bastard. Stop talking about yourself
and stop telling people um that their
words mean nothing when you can't even a
simp you can't even talk.
>> Yeah. You and your boyfriend didn't show
up either. Another one of your
boyfriends didn't show up. Your
boyfriend Smokey B didn't show up before
telling people that they were sad
bastard and reta. Where was Smokey B?
Nowhere to be seen. So shut up.
Yeah, because you was trying to lur me
with LT. You think I was born yesterday,
bro? I actually was there as well. But
you think I was born yesterday like you,
you thick bastard.
So obvious, bro. So so so so obvious.
I'll tell you who the sad bastard is.
your [ __ ] boyfriend for not [ __ ]
showing up when he was supposed to and
trying to get other people to fight his
battles. How about that one?
Yeah, bro. I'm terrified. Yeah. Yeah.
Terrified. I'm as scared as him as you
are as scared of talking. Yeah. Terrified.
Yeah. Terrified, lad.
Terrified, bro. I'm [ __ ] myself.
Don't even mention that name, bro. I
[ __ ] myself, bro.
No, he didn't show up.
The guy didn't show up
because I was supposed to be meeting
Smokeoky B. That's not how arrangements work.
Yeah, I'm I'm scared, bro.
Jo, your word means nothing. You can't
even talk. You're scared of talking, you
bastard. Don't call me a sad bastard
when you're scared of talking. How can
someone take anyone's word that can't
talk? Your word has never meant nothing.
And like I said to you, bro, any laughs
you think you get out of me, I get more
laughs at you back. All I got to do is
go on LJ's channel and just laugh at the
rejects. I get more laughs out of you
than you get out of me.
Like the Lyongs believe that I get more
laughs out of you sad bastards than you
ever get out of me. You have B3 and he's
there. You said it, bro. The arrangement
was to meet Smokey B, not LT. So, yeah.
Yeah. Okay. I never left the house.
Yeah, man. Yeah.
So, where was this guy then?
Yeah, bro. I watched from a distance.
Yeah. Yeah. Where was this smokey be
then, Grezy? Where was Where was this guy?
Nowhere to be seen.
Nowhere to be seen, lad. So why did he
get a pass? So why did this guy get a pass then
when I was supposed to be meeting beating him? [snorts] Hm.
Yeah, but he didn't show up, lad. No,
no, no, no, no, no. But the thing is,
Grezy, he didn't show up.
The thing is, bro, he didn't show up himself.
Why? Because they're scared. Because
they're scared, bro. That's why he's
scared. That that, bro, when that
Smokeoky be was talking about Tottenham.
Yeah. It was too obvious. It was you
couldn't make it any more obvious. Yeah.
If you tried, you know, I know all the
roots. I'm I'm I'm well traveled, bro.
Yeah. Think about it like this. Think
about like think about like this. Yeah.
Milton Kees goes to Houston. Okay.
Houston's in North London. Okay, I get
that. But why is he talking about
meeting someone in Tottenham? That
doesn't that doesn't make any sense. Why
would somebody from Milton Kees or Northampton
be wanting to meet you in Tottenham?
Doesn't that seem a bit fishy to you?
You know, he made it too obvious, bro.
Made it too obvious.
All he had to say is, "I'm not meeting
you. I'm not meeting anyone on here." Jesus Christ.
I did go.
I I I did go.
I did go. He didn't go.
Somebody from Milton Kees wants to meet
me in Tottenham of all places. Somebody
said to me, "Oh, I'm scared to step foot in Tottenham."
I'm scared, bro. I'm from London. Why
would I be scared to Some stupid random
account said that. He said, "Oh, I'm
scared to I'm scared to step foot in
Tottenham." Um, even if it wasn't for a
fight. I was like, "Bro, really?
Really now, man? Really? I've been to
the most dodgiest areas in [ __ ] London.
Why would I be scared of going there
just cuz I was going there?"
Yeah, then don't believe it. Is it?
Yeah, that's Don't believe it.
Did he prove he was there?
This is the same thing that's always
going to happen, Greavvesy. You
understand? And this is the same thing
that's always going to happen. Yeah.
Someone calls you out, you call someone.
Yeah, but LG didn't win because I didn't
arrange to meet him. Even though he
turned up, I He didn't win because I
didn't arrange to meet him.
No one said they were meeting him. So, not really.
Not really because the agreement wasn't
to meet him.
So, and what's going to happen is if you
call someone out or they call you out,
this guy's always going to get involved.
And it goes around in circles again. And
it's just so very boring, lad. It's so
very, very boring. And then, Grezy, it
just goes around in circles again.
And that's what all that's going to happen.
You have zero life experience if you
think you can just build with your
victim or and get and not get robbed.
Brother, I'm from London.
Yeah. Yeah. Just remember that. I'm from
London, bro. So, yeah, I think I could
go around Tottenham when I want when I
want. Yeah, I I think I could. Yeah,
bro. I'm from London, so I kind of know
a bit more about London than you. So,
yeah. Yeah, bro. I've been to some
really, really, really dodgy places.
No, I'm not from Essics. I'm from
London. Yeah. Something that you would
never ever ever go.
You know, the thing is I went to Brixton
when it was dodgy. About how many years
ago was it?
When was it 12? How old am I now? It was
13 years ago. I went to Brock Brixton.
Um actually Romford is London. It's
actually classed as uh London actually.
And I'm not from Essex either. Anyways,
I'm from um I went to Brixton 13 years
ago when it was dodgy. It's not dodgy
anymore. And I was 15. I was 15 and I
went to Brixton by myself and it was
dodgy. Yeah. I don't think I'd be scared
to go to Tottenham, bro. As an adult, if
I needed to go there for whatever
reason, I would [ __ ] go there.
You're You're talking to me, bro. Yeah.
Nope. There's not another L taken
because Smokey B didn't show up. See,
this is what I mean. You just twist
[ __ ] Anyways, this is what these people
do. They just twist [ __ ] when we all
know that this guy didn't even show up himself.
He didn't even show up himself. So, how
could I take an L when he didn't even show up?
But I I take the L even though he didn't
show up. Okay. Yeah.
I knew he went crying to LT, bro. I knew
he went crying to LT. Nothing I'd say is
is is is false on here, lads.
I was scared of Timmy and Tiger. Okay,
bro. You keep telling yourself that.
Yeah. Yeah. You keep telling yourself
that, bro. You keep living in the past.
You keep telling yourself that, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. I'm scared of everyone, apparently. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, bro. And the thing is, Jo,
let me tell you something, lad. when
when if I go if I went to to if I went
to Nottingham to meet you, you're not
going to show up. You are just another
smoky bee that's not going to show up.
So, stop pretending you're going to meet
this person and meet that person just
because LT is going to do it. You're not
going to do it. You are literally not
Yeah, I've got anxiety, bro. Yeah, you
people don't even leave your house. A
lot of you haters. Yeah, bro. I've got anxiety.
Joe, you're never ever going to meet
anyone. Just like Smokey Be. So, I don't
know why you keep acting the big man on
here when you will never meet anyone.
You understand? You will literally never
ever ever meet anyone.
Never in a million years are you ever
going to meet anyone.
Listen, listen, listen, listen, listen.
You are never ever going to meet anyone.
Stop talking [ __ ] You are never going
to You're never going to meet anyone.
Oh, I just had a lovely dinner by the
way, Grezy. Some nice beef and um gam.
Oh, it was so tasty.
Joe, you're never going to meet anyone. Ever.
You will never ever ever ever meet
anyone. Won't be long before someone
gets hand. I've heard it all before,
lad. I've heard it all before.
I've heard all of this for the past 10
years. It's boring now.
I'm going to put the link up now. Anyways,
o grey. I had gam. I had beef. I had
Yorkshire. I had roast potatoes. Yep. Yeah.
One second. I
don't go on my live.
Yeah. Yeah. Whatever, bro. Whatever.
You're never going to meet anyone, Joe.
Joe, you're never ever ever going to
meet anyone. I said to you I would meet
you in Nottingham and you didn't want to
meet me. So, it's as simple as that,
bro. And your boyfriend didn't meet me today either.
So, simple as that. Another one of your
boyfriends. You know what I mean by that?
You're never ever ever ever ever ever
going to meet anyone. You're scared of
talking on a panel for [ __ ] sake.
Stop it. You're not going to meet anyone
ever. Trust me. Trust me. You're never
going to meet anyone. You're never. And
I already told you why I'm not going to
[ __ ] thingy. You know,
I already told you why. Because I know
what you're trying to do. I know exactly
what you're trying to do. It's not even an excuse.
You'll meet me in Spain. Yeah, you're
just being stupid now.
Yeah, you're just being stupid now.
You [ __ ] idiot. You're never going to
meet anyone, mate. You're just like your boyfriend. Nons. Yeah,
that's why there's like literally no
point even being on it. I'm off tomorrow anyways.
Yeah, but Nottingham's not a random
place though. It's not a random place
because it's on the way to you and it's
only 70 mi away from you and it's 150 mi
away from me. Just give it up, Joe.
You're never going to meet anyone. You
can't even come on a panel and talk.
You're never ever going to show your
face cuz you're [ __ ] ugly as [ __ ]
Just give it up now. It's boring. Come
on. You're not about that life. You're
really really not about that life.
You're really, really, really not about
that life. So, just stop it.
Please, just stop it.
You ain't about that life. Yeah, I'm
trying to put the link up. Hold on one sec.
I'm trying to. It's not letting me. Why not?
You're talking [ __ ] Joe. No, no, no,
no, no, no, no. You're You're talking
[ __ ] You're You're just talking [ __ ] now. [snorts]
How do I share the links another way?
Oh, no one cares what people have said
and done. Bro, you're obsessed. Get a
room. Come out as gay. No one cares if
I've done and said stuff. Do come and do
something about it, Joe. Come and do
something about it today. Come and do
something about it today. If you're if
you're so asked what people have said
and done, come and do something today or
it doesn't bother you. It's as simple as
that. Like your boyfriend was supposed
to do. Yeah. If it affects you that bad,
come and do something about it, big man.
Simple. And if you're not going to No,
no, no. Do you know what it is? Yeah.
Because we're sick of you little
autistic little weasels keep using this
as an excuse. Ret t and it's just
boring. Yeah, he wasn't. Listen,
Smokeoky B, he wasn't there. He wasn't
But listen, anyways, Joe, um, I'll be
off here from tomorrow, so you can keep
thinking about all the things I've said
and done, and I'll be living my life.
So, I'll be getting the last laugh,
you know? I'll be I will literally be
doing the I I I'll be doing the complete
opposite. So, you could be obsessed with
me all you want. From tomorrow, I'm on
this [ __ ] I'm going to meet this person
soon anyways and that. So, yeah, bro.
You I I love the fact that I'm still
living in your head. Um, you know, rent
free. That's That's fine, bro. That's fine.
Yeah. You and your little boyfriend,
your little gay boyfriend. You can talk
about me all day. It's fine, bro. It's
fine, man. I'll be living my life
anyways. So, that's it.
[ __ ] how the [ __ ] did I come on this
weirdo community, bro? Jesus Christ.
Yeah, that's fine, bro. You're buffing
out someone younger and better looking
than you that's got more money than you.
You can laugh all you want. You can
laugh all you want, but guess what? I'll
be living my life younger than you,
better looking than you, more women than
you, and you'll be on YouTube, so I'll
get the last laugh. At the end of the
day, I'll be getting more laughs out of
you could ever get out of me. Younger,
better looking, more money. Look at you
people on here that's shown your faces.
Come on, brother. Look at Let's be real
about the people on here that's actually
shown their faces. Keep fake laughing
all you want. It's not going to change
the fact I'm better than you in every way. Better.
Trust me, bro. It's not going to change
the fact I'm younger, better looking,
got more money, not afraid of talking.
You can laugh all you want. And a false
laugh. What? A false laugh at that one.
It's not going to change the fact that
Joseph Farra is the gay boy that could never talk.
A gay boy that can't talk is not someone
that can laugh at me. Do you understand?
Some little scrawny little [ __ ] like
you. Some scrawny little gay [ __ ] bag
that wears next can't laugh at me. Do
you understand, lad? So do it all you want, bro.
Some little northern little [ __ ]
stick insect that's scared of talking.
Yeah, bro. Crack on. Crack on.
Younger than you. Better looking than
you. We've seen what you people look
like, bro. Come on. Said it not. Don't
need to repeat all of this again. You
sure you're not laughing at your [ __ ]
selves? Come on, bro. Come on.
You don't You beat yourselves up. Yeah,
but none of you show your faces, do you?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh,
bro. You're scared of talking, brother.
You're just an obsessed one like your
boyfriend. Nons legs. You're both very
ugly. And I can't wait to be off of
here. Still living in your heads. More
money, better looking. But guess what,
Joe? You will never meet anyone cuz
you're a [ __ ]
You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] You will never
meet no one. Think you was already
making excuses when I said I was going
to come to Nottingham. What did you say
again? Oh, I'll catch you when I catch
you. What? Oh, I'll catch you, brother.
Your scrawny insect [ __ ] arms could
never ever ever ever do anything to me.
You're a scared of talking little
[ __ ] Stop talking. Stop giving it
the big. You're a [ __ ] scared of talking
little man. We've already seen what you
look like now, bro. Yeah, we've seen
what you look like.
You're just a little gay man who's
scared of talking. Yeah. Oh, bigger than
you. Yeah. Yeah. Much bigger than you.
Let's let's let's think about it. I'm
not scared of talking like you. I've
actually turned up to meet people unlike
you. Think about it. Think about it.
Think about it. Think about it. One
second. One second. Hold it down a sec.
Yeah. Everyone. Yeah. Do you remember
when I had problems with people in this
community? Yeah. And I went Manchester.
I went Middlesborough. I went [ __ ]
here. I went Do you think you could ever
come to London and mention my name? Just
Just think about it. Forget LT. Think
think of Forget anyone else here for for
a moment. Yeah. Do you think you could
ever ever come to London and start
yapping about me? No, I don't think so.
Because we're in a we're in a different
catch to me. I've been up north. I've
been here. I've been there. And I've
been running up my mouth, running up my
mouth. You was nowhere to be seen, Joe.
You was nowhere to be seen when I was
live in all of these places. Oh, but we
do it differently up north. You're
[ __ ] [ __ ] up north that will never
meet no one. That's what you are. You're
just a little [ __ ] up north. Yeah. Do
you even remember when I used to [ __ ]
go around traveling? Where was you big
man? Where was the big man? Where was
the big man? Nowhere to be seen. So shut
up. Yeah. So shut the [ __ ] up. Oh, next
time I'm in Leeds or Newcastle, [laughter]
bro. Make it Make it believable, bro.
Make it believable. Listen. Listen. I've
been to Leeds once. I've been to
Newcastle three times. I've been to
Sheffield three times. Where was you,
big man? Tell everybody where you was.
Tell everybody where you was when I was
in them places. You was nowhere trying
to meet anyone. You weren't actively
trying to meet anyone or setting anyone
up. You northerners just aren't about that life.
Literally like you northerners are just
not about that life. I'm sorry. You're
not. You're really, really, really not.
You can go on about LT all you want.
When have you ever come to London to try
to meet me? Go on. Go on, Joe. You
northerners are just not about that
life. It's fine. It's okay. I'm just
stating facts. I'm not trying to wind
anyone up there.
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. You're an idiot.
You're an idiot. Next time I'm in
Newcastle, next time I'm in Leeds. [clears throat]
Really, bro? So, what about So, what
about all of the other times I went
there? Okay, Joe. So, what about all of
the other times I went there? I was
actually live in Newcast. Okay, answer
this question then. Okay, answer this
question then. Yeah. How comes when I
was live in that hotel room? Yeah, one
second. How comes when I was live in
that hotel room? Yeah, I was live I
don't know a couple of videos in
Newcastle. Why was you not trying to
meet me then? Ask yourself this
question. If you're this big hard man,
can you answer me? That's self
projecting. Anyways, can you answer me
why you did not actively try to meet me
when I was in your city? Then
uh Smokey didn't meet me. Smokey didn't
even leave Milton Kings. Smokey be
didn't even turn up themsself. Yeah. Oh.
Oh, you didn't have an issue with me. [laughter]
Bro, come on. All of the things that
I've said was years ago before I started
traveling. Stop trying to talk [ __ ]
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
All the mad [ __ ] that I said was years
and years and years ago before I even started traveling.
You're talking shite, man. You're talking shite.
Yeah. So, where was So, where was this?
Where was this Smokey B then, LT?
Oh, you didn't know I was like that?
Okay. What? So, when did you learn then?
About four months ago, bro. When I when
I stopped. Yeah. Was it like maybe two
years ago or what? Come on, bro. You're
not about that life, bro. You're really
not about that life. No.
You're a sad bastard, bro. A sad sad bastard.
So where was the smoky bead then NLT? Huh?
[clears throat] madness, bro. Absolutely madness.
Absolutely [ __ ] madness. Yeah.
This is madness, bro. This really is you know.
Yeah. Don't start biging up him, bro,
because you talk [ __ ] about this guy
behind his back. You call him a sad
bastard. You call him this. You call him
that. So don't try to uh don't try and
suck up to him, bro. Cuz you talk [ __ ]
about this guy like you talk [ __ ] about
me. So stop being too faced
causing your own hair loss. I don't have
any hair loss. Autumn, you're the one
that uses filters.
Yeah, you're the one that uses filters, not me.
Yeah, he didn't travel. He didn't even
leave Milton Kees. And this is exactly
what I mean with this community. This is
exactly what I mean with you retards on
this community. I am done after today. 100%. Yeah.
Yeah. It's not letting me put the link
out. I don't know why. You didn't go
anywhere, Smokey. Shut up. If you went
anywhere, you would have done a video.
You didn't go anywhere. You did not go
anywhere. The only person that was in
that park is LT and it wasn't it was not you. Yeah. Simple.
Yeah. One second. I'm trying to put the
link up. It's not letting me. Why?
No, we didn't go to the park.
You didn't show up anywhere.
You didn't show up anywhere, lad.
Yeah. Yeah. Whatever, Joe. Whatever.
I need to redo the stream and put the
link up cuz it's not letting me. One
second. [ __ ] annoyed. Hello. Hello.
All for the link copter.