Let's try again.
There we go. Lovely. Works now. Yay.
Why the [ __ ] not?
touched it again.
I don't know why it wasn't um letting me
put it out. Yeah,
there we go.
You are not coming in. Get banned.
Sad bastards. But yeah, I'm definitely
coming off of here after today, bro. 100%. Yeah, man.
100 100 million and 1%.
[ __ ] this, bro. Yeah. Hello.
>> I'm worried about your mental health. Your hand.
>> Your boyfriend. Your boyfriend didn't
show up, man.
>> He did. He shot me a video. He was in the park.
>> Oh. Oh. Can I see the video?
>> Why you weren't there?
>> Well, if he's there, if he's there, then
LT would have saw him. He's He's not there.
>> He He went to the park, didn't he?
>> Wait, does Smokey be and LT have beef?
>> So, they saw each other.
>> Well, Smokey B was walking in the park.
I don't think he knows what else.
>> Oh. Oh, but so they saw each other then?
>> I I don't know. I don't think Smokey
>> He didn't.
>> I don't think Smokey knows what LT
looked like. And I don't think L knows
what Smokey looks like.
>> He did not leave.
>> They may well have seen each other
walking around the park. Well, that's a
bit impossible because he didn't he
didn't go to London. He was still in
Milton Kes. So,
>> he was walking his dog. He sent me a
video of him walking a dog some meat
place and he's walking his we dog.
>> Nope. Nope.
>> Why did you lie and say you were going
though? That's crazy.
>> I was
>> I was in Tottenham. I wasn't in a park.
>> How can you go to Tottenham? She eating
a roast dinner
>> when I come back.
>> I ate roast dinner at home when I came
back. Oh, more likes. Come on, people.
>> It's not people. You don't have taken
one hell of a
>> guy. Says the guy that can't spell. Says
the guy that lies about everything about owning
>> the guy who can't spell.
>> Yeah. Okay, bro. Okay. Okay.
>> You're taking a hell of a lot of L's on here.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> This last like
>> Why do you lie so much? Why do you lie
so much, man? You lie a lot. Got your money stopped.
>> That's not going to work, bro. Try again.
>> It's not going to work. It's not going
>> You record.
>> The thing is, the thing is, the thing is
you're broke as a joke. We know that.
>> You do not own properties and you don't
have any money and no one's got my money
stopped. I've got more money than you.
>> Okay. Why does it bother me? So,
>> why? Here you go.
>> That's why you're sat on YouTube begging for money.
>> Starting again.
>> Yeah, bro. It's so bad. Yeah.
>> It's bad. It's bad. It's bad. Like Smokey,
>> you called Smokey Be.
>> You know, you know the thing is, you
know, the thing is, yeah, you need to
tell Smokey Be that when he's trying to
set someone up next time, at least make
it a little bit less obvious.
>> What do you mean, Sad?
>> It was too obvious.
>> What do you mean, sad?
>> He wanted to meet me in Tottenham of all
places, and he doesn't even live in
London. Come on. What is What is the chances?
>> I don't I don't see the point of it, man.
>> You don't see the point? Well, who who
lives in Tottenham? LT.
>> I don't know. Well, Smokey doesn't live
in London and he wanted to meet me in
Tottenham. What's the What's the chances?
>> I don't think Smokey B knows LT.
>> He does know he does know. He
>> knows the account. I don't think he does
know him. He does know him.
>> So, you think them two are speaking in
the background trying to set you up? >> Yeah.
>> So, you weren't in Tottenham today?
>> I was there just I was wait I was
waiting for him to show me where he was.
But you just said there now that you
thought them two were trying to set you up.
>> Yeah, that's why I wanted them to show
me where he was.
>> So you were at the park that LT was at the park.
>> I wasn't in the park. I was in
Tottenham. I wasn't in the park.
>> So where were you in Tottenham?
>> Just around.
>> Just around. It's really not good for you. >> Yeah.
>> All these all these lies. And now
the biggest he didn't even leave. No, he
didn't even leave Keys and L.
>> He didn't even leave Milton Keys kind of
set you up. It's crazy.
>> He didn't even leave Milton Keys.
>> He did. He sent me a video.
>> He didn't. No, he did not.
>> He didn't send me the video
on his channel.
>> He would have put it on his channel.
>> All these lies. P is not good for you.
>> Yeah, man. You need to stop lying about
owning properties with your skin. If you
own properties, why are you so skinn?
>> If you own properties, why are you so skinn?
>> Some [ __ ] some [ __ ] someide
[ __ ] with no license. Make it make
sense. Make your life more believable.
>> Well, I'm asking you how
>> are you? Cuz you um How are you? Cuz
you've got no money and you beg for
money every day on YouTube and you don't
go out. You don't buy anything. Are you listening?
>> Yes. DJ puts on a stone island jumper
right now and it fits him. I'll leave you.
>> We've heard all of this before. We've
>> Why wouldn't you just put a jump?
>> How about this? Why don't you Why don't
you Why don't you buy a medium t-shirt
right now and let's see if it fits you?
>> Cuz it would buy a medium right now and
let's see if it fits you. Come on.
>> Come on. Why don't you fit me? You get a
medium right now and see what it looks
like about you fat self. Go get your
diet. Go and lose some weight.
>> Very, very self-conscious about
self-conscious, brother. I'm better
looking than you. You're the one that's
got four eyes and ginger.
>> You're four eyed ginger. You're four.
You're a [ __ ]
>> foureyed ginger with a bad back. You're
obese. One second. One second. One sec.
One second. You're obese.
>> You are obese. You're obese. You are
obese. You're trying to lose weight.
>> You're obese trying to lose weight.
>> Your clothes don't fit you anymore.
[ __ ] self projector. See you later.
And this is exactly what I mean with
these people in this community, bro. And
why I'm coming off of it. It's a load of
[ __ ] [ __ ] They're wasting my time
today. They wasted my [ __ ] time
today, bro, you know, as well as
Greavves time and a couple of other
people. This is the same [ __ ] on here.
Yeah. Where where was where was where
was where was Smokey BLT? Where was he?
Wasn't I supposed to be meeting Smokey
B? Where was he? Come on.
Listen, Autumn, you look like an Oompa Loompa
and you use filters. You use filters and
you look like a [ __ ] Oompa Loompa.
And you're talking about me.
And And you're talking about me, you
Oompa Loompa looking [ __ ] ugly skit.
And you're talking about me? You're
talking about me, you overweight Oompa
Loompa. Seriously, get a [ __ ] grip.
You know that's that, bro.
I'm not your [ __ ] mate. I'll never be your mate.
You [ __ ] fat ugly [ __ ]
Right. I went on someone's community post.
Well, I need your verdict on something. Um, Greavesy.
Yeah. No one's owning nothing. Listen,
but do you know the thing is Joe? Yeah.
Do you know the thing is Joe? Everyone
laughs at you people. Your your
society's rejects. You like your You're
so like people like you, Joe. Yeah. You
don't even fit into society. You're so
ugly. You're so bullied. You don't
That's why you got no life. That's why
like you you lavy mongs. Yeah. Listen.
That's why you lavy mongs don't go out
cuz you're so unliked, ugly, and bullied
that like you don't even fit into
society. That's literally how bad it is.
Like you're such society's rejects that
you think you come on YouTube laughing
at other people. You fat ugly [ __ ] bastards. Yeah,
ugly people on YouTube 247. That's all
the evidence I needed. Oh, I got a
message back just now, by the way. Um, Greavvesy. Yeah.
Yeah, they're wasting my time as well. Anyways,
listen. Right. Can I read this to you,
Greasy? I need your verdict. Right.
Right. I need I need I need your verdict on something.
I didn't even got I haven't been on this
channel for ages.
And he said Ariana Grande.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. There was a difference.
The Ariana Grande thing was different. I
didn't start calling people gay because
they didn't find her attractive. There
was a big, big, big, big difference.
Big, big, big difference. You know, I
wasn't trying to, you know, hide what I
was by calling other people gay. No, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no. Big, big, big,
big difference. I've just gone to these
community posts with this little
copycat. And then isn't it funny that
Grezy as soon as I went on AI, it told
me everything that I had said.
I didn't call people gay because they
didn't find her attractive. That's
that's the copying bit. I just seen this
now, bro. No, no, no. You literally was
copying. Anyone that goes on AI
will see that it was a trend. It was it
was it was a it was literally a trend
back in the day
to avoid being teased greasy
to blend in with the crowd,
>> wasn't it? Wanted to blend in. >> Yeah.
And then some ugly incel living with his
mom soon to be 30 with a massive nose.
Brother, you're in your 30s, no teeth,
and you live in a bedit owned by the
council. Don't try and [ __ ] blame the
[ __ ] Don't Don't Don't try to play
the [ __ ] ball high ground.
What the [ __ ] bro? Weird. Hey. Yeah,
that'll be on the grande. I didn't stop
calling people [ __ ] games. They
didn't like her, bro. I'm not a copycat. Yeah,
one second. I'm doing something here.
Never bullied as much as you, Joe. Never
ever bullied as much as you. Basically,
anyone that goes on that Lord Jongs,
anyone that does, they're literally life
losers. Anyone that goes on that channel
is literally life's losers. Literally.
LT, imagine PJ walking through Tottenham, brother.
Oh my god, you a [ __ ] I'm from
London, bro. We're not all housebound
like you. Jesus Christ. >> No,
I've never been bullied in my life, Joe.
I'm not like you and your boyfriend.
So, I've never I've never been bullied.
Sadly, lad. He would
I'd get robbed. What? For no reason. Why
would somebody rob me for no reason?
Nah. Listen, LT, let me tell you
something. I said this uh earlier when
you didn't even hear it, bro. I went to
Brixton 13 years ago when Brixton was
bad. It's not bad anymore, but it used
to be bad. And I was 15. 13 years ago, I
was 15. I wasn't even scared one little bit.
I was not scared one little bit. And
Brixton back in the day was worse than
Tottenham. It's not as bad now. And I
was 15 and I wasn't scared. And I've
been there since, but it's not as bad
anymore. So why would I be scared as a
grown man from bro? You're talking to me, bro.
You You're talking to me?
Yeah. Yeah. I will show you it, Joe.
When you come in here and you talk and
and you're not scared of talking, then
I'll show you whatever you want. Yeah.
Brixton used to be really, really bad. Really bad.
Trust me, it is. Not so much anymore,
but it did used to be really bad. And I
went there as Yeah. as as as a child by
myself as well.
So yeah, man. Why would I be scared of
going to [ __ ] Tottenham at 28 years
of age? Come on, bro.
Seriously, you know.
Yeah, but bro, I don't
Maybe I'll do a video of me walking there.
Walking around there, you know. What do
you think, Greavvesy?
What's the verdict, Greavesy?
A copycat or not a copycat? Greavesy.
>> Hey, listen. Why don't you come in the
panel and talk? You're not scared, are you?
You're not scared of you.
We've never heard this Joe talk. How comes
he's a lavy mong? One sec. Yeah,
this is just
a [ __ ] place.
That's what this is.
He hasn't anything. Oh, another one.
These people are so [ __ ] You know, Steven Howard,
so so [ __ ]
But yeah, I didn't say um if you didn't
like Ariana Grande, you're gay. No. No.
That's the big difference.
Yeah. That's Yeah. I'm not a copycat
like certain people. Yeah.
But I'll be off tomorrow anyway. So,
you're going to have to find someone
else now, Greasy, to give you content.
I can't be on here with you little retards anymore.
Sat online all day on YouTube 24/7, no life.
It's mad, isn't it? And then you try to
talk about other people. It's mad. Yeah,
but I wasn't speaking to people and I
wasn't going out around that time. So,
now now's a different story. Now is a
You people sit on YouTube for years
stalking men. You're [ __ ] gay, bro.
Proper proper gay.
Yeah. After this live stream, I'm done.
I'm done. Literally from today, I am done, bro.
Yeah, I got your email anyway, Stephen Howard. So, yeah,
that's that, bro.
>> Yeah, bro.
Nah, Joe, you're No, no, no. You You and
your boyfriends are gay. Your whole
channel is dedicated to me. You're a gay
lord. You and your little boyfriends.
You need a room, lad. I don't, like I
said, I don't mind I don't mind um
booking you that room.
I don't mind booking you that room for
you and your uh the other three of your
boyfriends, lad. I mean, like I said, I
don't mind. You can all get it out your system.
Yeah, get it out your system, man. I
don't have I don't have a channel
dedicated to men like you do, you gay boy.
you absolute gay boy.
And the thing is, LT, you're very
foolish. You know,
you know, emailing me about um saying
about how like you and USA crack jokes
about me. You know, it's ridiculous,
isn't it? Because you don't understand
that I know more than you.
I literally know more than you.
So, you're talking to someone that knows
more than you, bro. How does that even work?
You know that's silly saying something
like that. You're not talking to some
random idiot on YouTube, bro. You're
actually talking to me.
Someone that literally knows more than
you do. So, how could you even how could
you even try and use that? You're crazy.
You're absolutely crazy, man.
I think you're trying to like get me mad or something.
How can that get me mad when I know more
than you do about the whole thing? Like
it doesn't make sense.
Was that supposed to get me like [ __ ]
mad or something? Bro, you're crazy.
Yeah, you're crazy, man.
But like I said, you got my email
anyways, bro. So, um that's that.
Yeah, that's fine anyways, bro. But she
was the one that went running to the
police. I've spoken to her best friend.
She's not about that life, bro. She
really, really is not about that life.
Trust me, she is not about that life
because I know a crazy [ __ ] when I see
one and someone would be egging you on. So,
yeah, that's good for him, Joe, man.
That's that's fine. No one really cares.
Yeah, that's good for him, bro. But do
what you want, but don't try and act
like this [ __ ] was not running to the
police three times. Like, come on, man.
Come on. Their best friend's not a liar
now. Come on. I don't know what what you
get out of that.
You can you can if you want. I literally
don't care, bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't really care.
You can do whatever you want to do. I
literally do not give a flying [ __ ] you know.
Brother, this is 2026. How are we lad? Yeah. Well,
yeah, bro. Yeah. Really? Really, bro?
Well, you need to stop making it like
this person's bad when they're not bad.
Why would you even do that to someone
when you know they're not about that life?
You know they're not about that life. So
why why are you trying to make it seem
like they're about it when they're not about it?
It's just silly, bro. Because you're
just making people seem about it when they're not.
It's just silly. Very, very, very, very
if you think about it. I don't know why
you would do something like that. You know,
even if I was a woman as well. Even it
wouldn't make a difference even if I was
a woman. So you're mad you are. You're a
crazy [ __ ] You are, lad.
Cuz they're not bad, bro.
They're really not bad. They would never
meet anyone ever, whether they were in
this country, whether you [ __ ] went
[ __ ] America or No. Uh, the most I'd
probably do is set you up at the very maximum.
Come on. Come on, man.
Yeah, I think so, too.
Yeah, I'm not about that life. Okay,
bro. Yeah, I'm not about that life. Okay.
you stick to getting into USA Izzy's underpants.
It doesn't matter, bro, if she's a
female or not. Even if I was a female,
she would do the same thing.
Even if I was a female, she would do the
same thing, bro. Just like her little
ex. Damn it. Do you think he would ever
say anything to anyone's face?
The chubby little Homer Simpson looking [ __ ] idiot.
Come on, bro.
I can talk [ __ ]
I can talk [ __ ] when you're trying to
[ __ ] style. I can. Yeah. I don't give a [ __ ] bro. Bless you.
Bless you in life.
LT bless you.
Bless your life, lad. Bless you.
So, you have friendly chats with
somebody that lives in a different
country than you. One second.
[ __ ] sake, bro.
This is a weird, very weird about nutrition.
What the [ __ ]
My mom says the same thing, Indigo.
My mom says the same thing.
Bro, I got a lot of people obsessed with
me. He's not the only one to be fair. Yeah.
I'm not I'm not racist.
Fo was being racist today.
It was V that was being racist today.
No. LT, you do watch a lot though. You
seem to know so much what goes on. You know,
this is all mad. I think I'm going to
start my Lego um Greavvesy when I come
off of here. I got Lego and stuff I paid
a lot of money for and haven't even
started it yet. Well, the the new one I
bought I haven't started. Yeah.
LT is an undercover copycat.
Did you know that?
He's an undercover copycat.
Didn't you know that?
But he's very undercover with it.
He's a copycat. Yeah.
Oi, why didn't you why didn't you do
anything about that um Jamie Thompson
that was stalking you, LT?
Why? Why don't you do anything? You said
that he was stalking you before. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, loads of copycats on here. H.
Go on, bro. Go on. Answer. No.
Get yourself down waxies lad.
Get yourself down to waxies lad.
I got this person's number
in waxis. I got a few numbers in waxis.
[ __ ] Need a place to go, lads. No copycat.
He was getting bullied by these Scottish lads.
Yeah, he was. That was true. He's
getting bullied by these Scottish lads.
Oh, she's talking about kids.
She said, "Oh, do you like kids and
that?" I said, "Yeah, I don't really,
but that's what they want to hear in
it." Not in that way. Not in a nons way, but
they meant like, "Um, do you want
children?" That's what they meant, I think.
Just tell them anything in it.
So, I've got people to be meeting, you
see soon. Um, Stephen H. I've got a life
to be living.
I can't waste it on some [ __ ] little
virgin that lives in a [ __ ] council
bedset owned by the [ __ ] council.
some little virgin. Do you understand?
Yeah. Got [ __ ] to be doing, lad. Have to
leave these copycats. Exactly. Yeah.
Yeah. But Eli, you're a bit of a copycat
as well because when I was eating pork chops,
you started uh you started having a pork
chop place, didn't you?
Yo, another stinky copycat, Altie. We're
all They're all copycats on here though,
lad. So, it's, you know, nothing to be
um Yeah, you're a little copycat. What's up,
you stinky dirty copycat?
Hey, don't tell me how to pronounce
things. You can't even talk. Joseph,
you're a lavy mong.
Joseph, you're a lavy mong. So, what are
you going to do after? This is how sad
these bastards are here. Do you know
what they're going to do now? No, I'm
not going to be on it. They're They're
just going to turn on each other.
That's what they do. They'll just turn
on each other.
>> Yeah, but you need to be careful, LT,
because you don't know the kind of
people that I know.
I can get I can get Yeah, I can get
someone on you. You wouldn't believe
that I know them.
I'll get HS on you.
Then what are you going to do about it?
You know, I know HS.
Yeah, I know HS. You know, HS tick tockie.
Yeah, he'll do you, mate. [ __ ] do
you. I actually do know him, you know.
Then you'll be [ __ ]
Nope, Joe. cuz I've got a life and I can
meet other women unlike you and your boyfriend.
But you, when I'm at it, you're all
going to switch on each other after a while.
I'll get HS on you, LT.
Then what will you do? Hm.
Yeah. And I've had more women than you
and I've got more money than you and I
don't have to go for disabled like you
and your boyfriend. Is that lovely, Joe?
That is lovely.
Yeah, I know he's backwards.
He just needs to come out as gay.
That's all he needs to do is just come
out as gay.
That [ __ ] Jamie. They just need to
come out as gay. They hate that. They
hate the fact that they're gay.
You know what it is, Stephen? How? They
If this person stops responding, well,
after two days, well, then I'll just go
out and meet some more [ __ ] people.
Simple as that.
What's the big deal?
Yeah. No, definitely definitely won't. Nope.
And even if that was the case, I'll just
go to waxies and get more.
Get yourself down to waxies, lad.
LT is a copycat.
Yeah, I might go to Waxies.
Well, he didn't. He's [ __ ] Well, did he
say that? Well, he's a bullshitter.
He's a bullshitter.
Yeah, they all want my ass and I don't want them.
I do definitely think these four need to
come out though.
[ __ ] sake. It's 2026. Just come out.
[ __ ] me. I would never have my channel
dedicated to another man.
Don't I don't care how many times they
reacted or they didn't react. I just
wouldn't do it, bro. That just shows
they got nothing. Like this Joe F and
that. It just really shows they ain't
got nothing. Believe you me, bro. Just
sat in. Got anxiety. Trust me, bro.
Trust me. The truth comes out in the end
anyways with these people. So
too easy. Too too easy.
But yeah, they are they're closeted.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. Listen, listen, listen,
these people record stuff from the time
they wake up to the time they go to bed.
They're gay. They're literally gay. That
is gay, bro. They They stalk a man more
than an obsessed
straight man is with a female that he's
in love with. They're gay. They're
They're gay, bro. They're They're
They're just gay.
I'm not talking about the people that
come on here typing. I'm talking about
the stalkers. I'm not talking about the
people that type. I'm talking about the
channel, the channels dedicated to
another person. They're gay, bro.
They're literally gay. Oh, here's
another thing. Oh, you didn't know what they done?
They went on um
they went on Reddit pretending to be a
woman. So, I messaged them so they could
have got my new channel. Bro, they're
gay. They're literally mentally
obsessed. Like, they literally are
mentally gay, bro. They're mentally obsessed.
They really are, lad.
They really, really are. That Red Star.
Go on that Red Star channel. Go on that
Red Star channel. That Jamie Thompson
channel. They're gay, bro. They're gay boys. Trust me.
Definitely. Definitely. Definitely.
They are, bro. Trust me.
I would never ever put this amount of
effort into a [ __ ] woman.
And that's saying something.
And that is saying something. When they
casually do it every day to men, they're gay, bro.
They do it to men. They're gay, bro. Definitely gay.
Definitely definitely gay.
Yeah, I don't need to do anything, lad.
I'm not going on that channel. And after
my life today, I'm done with these
little [ __ ] So, that's it.
You didn't answer my question though, did you?
Where was that smoky bee fellow? Huh?
No, I am leaving, but I've got to get on
with my life. I've got people to be
meeting and [ __ ] to be doing. I'm sorry,
man. Some of us have got a life on like these people.
Sorry man. Maybe I'll come back in a month.
Oh yeah, something like that. Maybe I'll
go live in a month. But sorry man, I've
got [ __ ] to do. We can't all be like
Lord J's waste of followers. Sorry man.
Self projecting again.
All right. Do you want to know what
these people said about um
about my mom out here?
I'm glad she was listening. It just
shows they don't know anything about anyone.
But I wanted to know what where was that
Smokeoky Bee fellow?
That fellow. He's a horrible little
This guy come on here. I think it was
was it yesterday or the day before
saying about how oh your family lo or
loses they've never worked. I was like
my mom's worked all her life. My
sister's worked for years and and I've
worked as well. So what the [ __ ]
Yeah, it just it's just self projected
on here, bro. What the [ __ ]
My [ __ ] mom's [ __ ] retired. So yeah,
you're a crafty little fellow.
You're a crafty fellow.
Yes, she has worked all her life. Yes, she has.
No, no, no, no, no. She literally has.
Has your Did your mom One second. One
second. Let me ask you this question,
LT. Did your mom bring up three kids by
herself without a father? No, she
didn't. No. No, she didn't. My mom did.
My mom did. Yes, she has worked all her
life. Yes, she has. And she bought her
three kids by herself as well.
So, your mom didn't do that. I don't
think your I don't think your mom could
do that, to be honest.
I don't think your mom could do that. No
offense. I don't think many people's
moms could. And how did she get money? She worked.
So yeah, you shouldn't people shouldn't
talk about people that they don't know. Yeah.
People shouldn't talk about people that
they don't know.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah, that's
good, man. I'm just saying. Um and
you're saying I've not worked. Uh yes, I have worked.
Yes, I have worked. you know.
Yes, I have worked a couple of times. So,
what bro? What's your point?
You want the link? Sure.
So, yeah, that's what my mom did. So,
and my sister's always worked as well. So, yeah.
You don't need to quiz me about
employment, but I'll put the link up if you want.
That thing that I done with the
delivery, um, Stephen, not many people
on here could do that. See, it sounds
easy, but it isn't easy. A lot of energy
knowing like how like, bro, trust me,
they wouldn't be able to do it. Trust
me. Trust me. Trust me,
you know. Trust me, bro. They wouldn't.
And they say And they say that I've
never worked. They say that I've never
worked. What the [ __ ] They say that I
never [ __ ] worked.
Bro, I was literally working literally
last year. What the [ __ ] are you talking about? Clowns. Absolute clowns.
None of these people would have been
able to do that ever on this community.
I'm sure I'm sure they wouldn't. Jesus Christ.
You're not coming in VR, you little self
projector. Bye-bye now.
So, anyways, I told you about my mom. I
told you about me. So,
why do most of you people in here not work?
Uh, why have you It doesn't What do you
mean it's not a proper job? It's still
working. So, now it's not a proper job.
Of course, it's a proper job, you silly goose.
>> You silly goose.
>> Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Are you going
to let me talk? >> Yeah.
>> Okay. Let me turn this down. Right. So,
you said you had a job. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> You like Do you want to go into this or
you definitely have a job yet?
>> Why? Why not? You little fell.
>> Okay. Okay. So, your tenants wasn't
didn't have a Uber Eats job. Yeah. And
then sometimes when they when cuz
they're self-employed account.
>> Wait, listen. Listen. They're
self-employed. So what they done is they
gave you the was it the app on the phone
or something and they let you when when
it wasn't working they let you go and
earn a little bit of money on the side.
So that's not legitimate work.
>> No no listen listen.
>> That's like me doing scrap metal and say
oh I work you are you going to let me
talk or go only
>> what you're talking about was 4 years
ago. Secondly last year I had my own account.
>> You had your own account. Okay. Okay. All right.
>> All right. All right. Fine. Let's go
through the interview. Um let's go
through the employment process because I
know I know about this very well. I
don't think you know how it works.
>> Are you
This guy doesn't know how No, listen.
Listen. Before you Before you You try
and quiz me. Yeah. Let me talk. Let me
talk. Let me talk. Before you try to try
to quiz me, it's an app and you work and
and you can cash out at any time. You do realize that?
>> Yeah. I know. It's self-employed. It's a
>> Do you know how do you know how the app
works? I don't think you know how it
works, isn't it? I
>> I don't I don't know 100% how the route
uh like the the how everything goes on
with the app. No, I don't. Yeah, I'm not
even going to pretend, but I know how I
know how the employment process works. I
know how that works.
>> Get paid. Okay. All right. Okay. Okay.
Okay. All right. So, you're saying so
was is so what I said earlier just now
>> about um you allow the tenant allowing
you to use his u phone or his app or
whatever to make a few sales or whatever
here and there or deliveries here and
there. Are you telling me that's false? What you
>> No, that's No, that's true. But that was
3 years ago. 3 four years ago.
>> All right. Cool. So now you're saying
you was actually employed by then now as well. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Not sure.
>> Okay. What was the process of you being employed?
>> What do you mean was I filled out an
application? Uh criminal record check uh
NI number. Um
they asked a couple of like address and that.
>> Bro, I can show you the email if you want.
>> So So you you you done all of that yet
and they just accepted you without going
I'm going to
about recruitment consultancy and stuff
like that. Right. So I'm going to I'm
going to go through this right now. You
see when you apply for any job before
they even before they even Okay. So they
will look at your CV your application.
Yeah. Before they even contact you or
make any contact with you, they're
already doing their research on you
behind the scenes. They're doing small
research. They're not doing intense
research as as in straight away.
>> Sorry. Are are you trying to say that I
like I didn't have it? I mean I got the app.
What I'm trying to say is they instantly
do a um a search on you. So even if it's
a it's not like a big search. It's not
an enhanced search is what they do.
Criminal record check. I had to pay for
>> Okay, that's after. No, no, but I'm
saying before they done all that
criminal record check stuff, when they
if they see your application or CV and
they're interested in hiring you, before
they go to even contacting you, they
want to make sure you're just co they
want to make sure you're kosher bas
basically. So what they do is they they
um they search the internet different
things, you know, your social media.
>> This is they give this job to most
people, bro. This is not like what
you're talking about.
>> Where where did where did you get your
skills from? Where did you get like cuz
you know when you're being employed and
stuff, right? They want to know about
your experience and at your age. See if you're 16.
>> You see if you're 16 years old or something, right?
>> Okay. Like they know that you're not
going to have that much experience or
anything. So they would, you know what I
mean? by this job is different, bro.
Okay, look it up. Okay, go on the
application if you don't believe me.
>> Oh, no. No. Talk me through it. Go on.
>> They didn't ask any of that stuff.
>> It's Uber. No, it's a delivery job with
Uber Eats, bro. It's not like that.
>> Okay. Okay. All right. All right. All
right. But what I'm saying is Okay. So,
so do you know about How do they pay you
then? Is it through P A Y? What?
>> No. What? What will happen is Yeah. I
don't You work here. Listen, you work
and then every order you get, you get
money in it and they either pay you
every Monday or you can cash out every
day. But if you cash out whenever you
want, they charge you 50p.
>> Okay. So that makes sense.
>> So So that's a self-employed job. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> So that means you have to file that
means that you'd have to file for a UTR
number. Do you know what that is? >> No.
>> A unique taxpayers reference number.
>> I know you had to like declare it and
that if it was over certain amount you
had to declare it. See, when I was, you
see, you see, just before my my second
child was born. Yeah. And I had I
already had a legitimate job anyways.
And then I started doing um personal training stuff.
>> I had to get a UTR number, which means
I'm self-employed. That means I could
work whenever I want and stuff, right? I
had to get a UTR number. Obviously, I never declared
>> all of my finances with them and stuff
because then I would be getting taxed
more. So, I'm saying you didn't get you
did they didn't tell you to do it cuz
that's the first thing that they did put
a policy on that and tell you then you
have to make sure you have a UTR number.
No, they didn't.
>> So, you're basically just paying. You
just get everything for free then, isn't
it? You just you just go through life.
Yeah. Just [ __ ]
>> So, so you're telling me I'm lying then? So, I
>> I don't even listen. I think I believe
you now, actually. Okay. No, no, I think
I think I believe you now. No, simply
simply because I had it misunderstood. I
thought you said that like I thought
they was actually employing you as a as
an employee, but it sounds like it was
more it was more of a self-employed
thing, but then you didn't you didn't
like go through the right protocols as
being self-employed to get a UTR number
so you can file for taxes and get like
>> Yeah, there's a reason I don't want
Yeah, there's a reason I don't work. I
already told people that anyways and
we're not getting into that anyways, Joe.
>> All right. So, how how long did you have
this job for then? Cuz I'm sure it
wasn't for long.
>> Um, a little while.
>> No, no, no, it wasn't. I didn't know I I
didn't even know about this show. That's
why when you were saying it, I thought,
"Oh, you talking about that time from
ages ago when you just done an odd like
I don't know, every day a day here and there."
>> No, just a little while over the summer.
>> No, no, no. How long roughly? You should
>> over the over the summer.
>> What's over what? 3 months. What? Four months?
>> Two months.
>> And And in that two months, how often
did you how how much times did you go
and like earn?
>> A lot.
>> In that two months,
>> it was time. It was a lot. It was tired.
>> That's a lot. Now, if you ask me my
hours at work, I can tell you off the bat.
>> Like 10 10 hours three times a week.
Like in one day,
>> you say that's a lot. 10 hours three
times a week. You You think that's a lot?
>> You know how much energy it takes, bro?
It's not like your job where you're
[ __ ] just like sitting around.
>> But I go to a gym every morning on a
weekday. Don't tell me about energy and
stuff, mate. Cuz like, you know what I mean?
>> Okay. Try it then. Try it then. Let's see how
>> What do you mean? I'm I'm a fit person.
What you telling me to try? I'm not like
you. I don't sit around and like let
myself go to waste, but I'm fit. I can
run for ages. I can Yeah. Like, you know
what I mean? I play football. All of
that. So, now what?
>> You know, you're a naughty fellow.
>> No. All right. Fair enough. Okay. Okay.
No, no, no. You know what? I had it I
had it misunderstood. So, that's my
fault. Okay. So, you was basically
self-employed then. Yeah.
>> All right. So, then how how do you go
about looking for another job then?
>> Because on your CV, do you even have a CV? >> Yep.
>> Well, I'm not going to tell my business
online, bro. Come on now. It's not your
B. Listen, it's not it's not it's not
it's not even much to say like it's your
business. I'm just generally wanting to
know. You have a CV. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> What do you Okay. What do you put down
for key skills?
>> I can't tell you that.
>> What do you What do you put down? What
do you put down for references?
>> I can't tell you that, lad.
>> What' you put down for education?
>> Yeah. Okay.
>> It's a secret. It's a secret.
>> Yeah. You have a CV? Yeah. And in this
current day and age as well. Yeah.
Everyone has to have a LinkedIn as well. So
>> why are you so why are you so
interested? I know what that is by the
way. That that's like a that's a website in it.
>> Yeah. It's like a social media page.
>> I've seen I've seen certain
>> Yeah. Like so you see me certain people's ones.
>> No. No. That's that's why I don't really
want to be baited up as well cuz they
will get me. So basically
>> they'll get you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So basically what it is is
like LinkedIn you would have
>> I can't use proper punctuation. Joe, you
don't even use full stops and [ __ ]
commas. You [ __ ] idiot.
>> Instead of someone having to always seek
jobs, you would always get when you've
Okay, so you see me. Yeah, I swear that
Joe guy said he's got a master's degree.
Yeah, I don't have a master's degree. I
got the one before that. So, I've just
got a normal I'm a postgraduate
basically. I didn't go for the masters,
right? So, I've I'm basically still part
of the illumin um university alumni. So,
you see I get all of these like offers
sometimes. You do you do realize you do
realize right 95% of the people here
don't work 95 you do realize that is it before
listen I know that most listen here's
another thing here's another thing
listen listen to this listen to this
>> I know you see when you're being
employed and stuff yeah number one I
know for a fact yeah it's all about
interpersonal skills and also your um
your exterior as well right now most of
the [ __ ] on here are sitting there
like how you you can't have black teeth
and get employed I'm Sorry. Like I'm
just being I'm just being honest. I'm
just being honest. No. No. But here's
the thing. I do know that there is a few
there is a few legitimate person people
in here that obviously do have jobs.
Yeah. Especially if you've got children.
I don't understand anybody in this current climate
>> that would not have a job. If you've got
children, okay, if you're a single
mother, I understand that. I'm not
blaming. I'm not blaming women for being
a single mother yet. I'm talking about
men. I'm talking about as men. Men. I'm
aiming at any women. L doesn't work and
he's got kids. So,
>> well, we said that though. Yeah. Well, I
mean, me personally, I me personally,
>> I don't see it around me. Like, even
even my friends here that are still like
doing what they shouldn't be doing. Even
they got it got to a point for them when
they said, "All right, [ __ ] it. Let me
just get self-employed or let me do
something." Like, do you know what I
mean? Because they can't keep doing
that. Like, I'm trying to not like speak
so blatant on here, is it? But
>> I got friends obviously as well that do
what they're not supposed to be doing.
But even at a point in life when they
started having kids and that they
realized and they said, "Ah, yeah, I got
to get something now." Like just
something he doesn't have a job. He even
>> Yeah. I don't understand. I don't
understand. But maybe he can um maybe he
can uh Wait, how's he go on holidays then?
>> He saves his benefit money up, lad.
>> Nah, but benefits don't pay that much
for you to be saving up.
>> But these holidays are cheap. Dirt
>> No, no, no, no. Once you have children,
listen to me. Listen to me.
>> They are.
>> Listen. No. No. Listen to me. These
children No, no, but listen listen, please.
>> These children are not babies. When
they're babies, they're they're more uh
it's more cheap, right? Once they get to
a certain age, like I'm talking like
over five, basically, and they start
running up and down. They want to start
doing stuff and all that. Yeah. No, it's
not cheap. Nothing's cheap. Nothing is
>> He don't Well, well, he doesn't work, so
he doesn't do He doesn't own properties
like he claims. I don't care anyways,
but I'm just saying I really don't care
anyways, but yeah,
>> you get me. But I'm just saying me
personally. I I I wouldn't know. I
wouldn't don't I don't think I would be
able to survive.
>> Stop being a labyrin. Stop being a labyrin, bro. >> Who?
>> This JF. He's such a dick sucker, bro.
It's annoying, man.
>> What do you say?
>> You just chat [ __ ]
>> Well, anyways, that's what I wanted to
do is qu you about the the thing.
Actually, no. I do believe you now.
>> I do believe you.
>> Well, you should have believed me from the start.
>> No, no, no. No, no. I No, no. I thought
that you were you meant that you know
cuz there was a time when you told me
that the tenant like borrowed you his
stuff. Yeah. So I thought you was
talking about that and you you trying to
use that as a thing to say
>> yeah but why but the thing is say for
example now I was using someone else's
account. I'd still be working anyway.
>> Yeah. But it's not the same as saying oh
yeah I've got a legitimate job. It's not
it's not the same. It's like me okay
it's like me saying okay um I've got a
weed factory in my house and I make all
this money every 2 months or 3 months to
grow it and all that. Yeah. And that's
like me saying oh yeah I've got a job. I
got legit. You know what I mean? It's
not the same, is it? I'm making That's
making dirty money.
>> You want to go to waxies? >> No. >> Why?
>> No, he left.
He left. He doesn't want to go to wax. He's dusty.
Right. Let me respond.
Yeah, I am
uh boring. and
see you later. Self projecting. Bye.
One second. Let me put the link up. Waxies.
Waxies is good, lad.
There we go. Yeah.
Don't miss me too much, Grezy.
Yeah. Waxies. Yeah.
Get yourself down waxies, lad.
Yeah. You show me 12 grand cash or your skin.
You little lavry mong.
You little lavy monk.
Joe's a lavy mong. Everyone,
where's Kieran, man? [ __ ] sake. Uh,
he lives in Yorkshire.
He's a Ly Mong.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah. Going to be boring for you
when I'm not on YouTube, isn't it, Joe?
You're going to have to switch on each other.
That's You're going to have to switch on
your boyfriends. You're all going to
have to switch on each other. Lovely.
After a while though, probably a couple of months.
It used to happen with the gov and all
of them people they used to switch on
each other when people stopped
commenting on YouTube.
Uh certain people they would just switch
on each other. Yeah.
That's what's going to happen.
You can keep laughing at me all you
want, lad, but it's not going to change
the fact I'm younger, better looking,
and got more money than you.
You can keep laughing all you want, but
deep down, you know, the false laughing
is just about yourself. You know,
you're just laughing at yourself. But
keep the false laughs up, lad.
You know, you can't laugh at someone
that's younger and better looking than
you. It just doesn't work. But that
makes you happy, lad. Keep doing it.
Someone younger and better looking than
you that's got more of a life than you,
you're laughing at.
How does that make sense?
Show us your face. I'll have a big laugh right now. H
Yeah. Yeah. Let's see your face. Why
don't you come in here and have a chat
with me? I'll put the link up just like
what LT done. You're not scared, are you?
I told Kieran about you. Uh he was like,
"Oh, that Jo seems all right, but if
he's up nonslegs his ass, he might just
be one of he might he might just be
another one of them." I said, "Yeah,
he's a lavy gay boy." I had to told K I
had to tell Kieran about you.
He's a little gay boy. Kieran is a nod.
He defends his boyfriend when he gets
called a virgin, but he didn't come back.
So, he'll be back sooner. I said he's
he's a little lathery mong. He defends
his boyfriend. When I call him a virgin,
he cries about it. [ __ ] Yeah, man.
Well, you [ __ ] clearly do cuz every
time I call him a virgin, you seem to
have something to say about it.
If you really didn't like someone, you
wouldn't care if you really you would
just let them be called what they're being called.
If someone's if someone's calling LT
something right now, do you think I'm
going to defend him? No. If someone
calls him a virgin right now, do you
think I'm going to defend him? No.
Because I don't care. I don't like him.
So why would you continuously
defend someone three or four times that
you don't like? Make it make sense.
It doesn't make sense. If you do not
like someone like I don't like people,
it does not make any sense. And don't
say that it's because of how you see it
because that's not the that's not that's
not true either. Yeah. Simple.
We're not going over this again either.
And you're obsessed anyways without the
whole nons things. The whole launch legs
thing. You're just obsessed anyways.
Your whole channel is dedicated to me,
lad. I think you're a bit obsessed.
Yeah, I think you're a bit obsessed, lad.
Well, I I can I can I can explain it
again because being in a relationship
does not mean you've had sex with
someone. If that girl was disabled and
she can't consent to sex like his
girlfriend, it makes perfect sense. Now,
speaking of things not making sense, how
many times has he called me a virgin and
how many times have you said anything
about it? A girlfriend with disabilities
has not does not mean he's had sex. I've
asked AI, bro, and it says the same
thing because a girlfriend don't mean
he's had sex. However, I have shown my
dick getting sucked. I have shown me in
women's beds naked. That is what you
shouldn't be able to get your head
around. Not a girlfriend. I've explained
this to you multiple multiple times, but
you don't understand it in your thick
head. Yeah. Which is what Kieran
basically said. You're just wasting your time.
Like, bro, he a girlfriend
is not sex. What I have shown is sex.
You're there's no denying it. Simple,
bro. And another thing with you LT as
well, bro. I don't know how long you're
on here or whatever, but I'm pretty sure
you have seen. Well, then a girlfriend
ate sex then. Simple. If a [ __ ] and
being in women's beds not is not naked,
then a girlfriend ate sex. A girlfriend
is not sex. Simple. And it's as simple
as that. If a [ __ ] and being in being
naked in women's bed, you have never
seen me have sex, brother. You have seen
me get [ __ ] You have seen women
admitted to sleeping with me. You have
seen me more than nonslegs. Shut up.
Shut the [ __ ] up. And you have never
seen him have sex. And you have never
ever seen him put he's brother. You have
never ever seen him have sex ever. He
could have erectile dysfunction for all
you know. How do we know that this guy
has got hasn't got erectile dysfunction?
I got a [ __ ] and I was women with
women that I didn't paid for pay for.
Shut up, bro. I've shown more than a
[ __ ] girlfriend. I've shown more than
a [ __ ] girlfriend. A [ __ ] is more
than a disabled girlfriend. And LG, you
know I'm right as well. You know I'm
right. So, hold on. Was a 19-year-old a
prostitute? Was Sig a prostitute? Was
that [ __ ] woman in [ __ ] Nottingham
a prost Nottingham and Manchester a
prostitute? So what are they all
prostitutes? Shut up you bias [ __ ]
[ __ ] about oh you ain't seen this,
you ain't seen that. [ __ ] off you little
batty man. A [ __ ] disabled girlfriend
ain't sex. [ __ ] little bias [ __ ]
Shut up, bro. Shut up, bro. You talk so much [ __ ]
Listen. You don't know, bro. Joe,
listen. Listen, listen, listen. We don't
know. We know that I'm not a virgin, but
you haven't said anything about it. And
that's the thing, LT, bro. Like, that's
why I said that you need to get a room
with nods legs. That's why I said get a
That's why I said, bro, get a get um get
a room. I I eat every day, but Well,
they Well, I I mean, if you didn't eat
food, you'd be dead. You have not seen
him have sex with his girlfriend. You
haven't seen it. You have seen me get
[ __ ] and you have seen me in women's
beds naked. And that's why I said not
legs is your boyfriend. Cuz you're
defending him. You're defending him. LT,
that's your boyfriend. Bro, why do you
think you come at me so aggressively?
Cuz you know I'm right. You know a
disabled girlfriend ain't sex. Shut up,
you biased [ __ ] And then you try and
sit there and say about how, oh, oh,
I've not seen him call you a virgin,
bro. Because No, no, no. Because I just
don't like biasness people. I just don't
like biased people. I literally just
don't like biased people. Like that's
Bro, it doesn't get to me. I just don't
like biased people,
bro. Just suck his dick already. I told
I told you this. Listen. Okay, let me
put it this way, LT. Yeah. Okay, let me
Okay, let me put it this way, right?
Let's just stop for a second. Yeah. If
you generally generally had something to
say about me calling this guy a virgin
and that was your opinion and ret and
you don't believe it, that's one thing.
But you would have a lot to say about
him calling me a virgin. Someone that's
shown more than a girlfriend and that's
why you didn't like it cuz you know I'm
right. You literally know I'm right,
bro. You literally know that you're a
gay boy, LT. You know that's your
boyfriend and you know that was you
sucking his dick and that's why you was
trying to say, "Oh, it doesn't count cuz
it's a prostitute." Bro, it doesn't
count cuz he's a prostitute. Bro, it was
more than a disabled girlfriend that he
never even proved he had sex with. You
[ __ ] [ __ ] That's why you couldn't
say anything to me, bro. Cuz you know
that you were sucking up his dick. You
were sucking up his dick, bro. Every
time I tried, bro, every time I called
him a virgin. Yeah. LG was like, "He's
got a girlfriend, bro. Who's got a
girlfriend? Don't. No. Stop sucking
dick, bro. You need to stop sucking
dick, bro. A girlfriend ain't sex, but
what I've shown is sex, but you would
never admit it cuz it's biasness. It's
And that's the thing. Yeah. Steven, they
call you a troll. This is what made me
laugh. Yeah. They called you a troll.
They literally were saying that you're
trolling me. You're trolling me. They
were saying that you was trolling me,
bro. I literally went on Timmy's and you
was the only one that spoke the truth
when people was trying to call me a
virgin. You was like, "Well, how can he
be because of this and that and this and
that and this and that?" Cuz it's a But
then they were calling you a troll.
That's That's why I didn't understand, bro.
Brother, I [ __ ] showed more than a
disabled girlfriend. I've showed more
than a girl that can't consent. You
little gay boy. Go suck your boyfriend's
dick some more, lad.
I asked it. I asked it, bro. And it said
there's a chance that he is a virgin.
I've already asked it.
LT, you were sucking your boyfriend's
dick. Don't call him that. He's got a girlfriend.
You got a girlfriend, bro. Every time
you call him a virgin, they started
crying. Go and suck his dick.
Go and suck his dick, bro. No disabled
girlfriend that he ain't proved he's
[ __ ] is any [ __ ] more than what I've
shown. [ __ ] no girlfriend is more
than that, bro. I've shown me getting a
[ __ ] [ __ ] me being in bed naked
with him, and then you're going on about
a girlfriend. What the [ __ ] bro? You
need to stop sucking dick,
you know. So, okay. Okay, LT. So, it
doesn't One second. Let's go by your
logic then. So, what I shown didn't
count because there were prostitutes,
but a disabled girlfriend counts. Okay.
Let's go by your logic. Let's go by your
One second. One second. One second.
Let's go by your logic. Yeah, because
you're this smart guy and you've got
this degree. Okay, bro. So, every single
woman that I showed was prostitutes,
bro. Jealous of that guy, bro. Bro, bro.
So, prostitutes don't count, but a
disabled girl counts,
bro. He hasn't showed Oh, look. He's
defending his boyfriend again. He's He's
sucking dick again. LT sucking dick.
I knew it, brother. He has not shown
more cash to me. I've been more places
than him. I'm better looking than him.
I'm better looking than you as well. I'm
better looking than both of you. I've
got more money than both of you. I've
got more of a life than both of you. And
guess what? I don't need to copy I do
not need to copy other people's [ __ ]
holidays. He has not shown more money
than me. I've shown more money than he
will ever have. He showed his daddy's
savings about 5 years ago and kept
uploading the same video. Shut up, you
little dick sucker. I'm better looking
than both of you. You're clapped, bro.
You're clapped. Clap. You're both
virgins. You ain't got a child. You
ain't got a child. You're clap. He's
clap. That's why you suck each other's
dick. That's why you're [ __ ] obsessed
with my sloppy seconds. [ __ ] out of
here, little gay boy, bro. That's why
you come on here pretending that you've
got bloody kids when you're [ __ ]
sucking his dick. Chasing my sloppy
seconds. You [ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] [ __ ] off.
Nah, Joe. We'd rather laugh at you.
someone scared of talking who puts up
fake whims. Let's all laugh at the sad,
weak little [ __ ] like you. Let's laugh
at the gay northerner that can't talk.
We'd rather laugh at you, lad. Cuz at
least us two could actually talk. We'd
rather laugh at the sad fake pension poverty northerner.
Think about it, bro. We We would rather
laugh at the gay northerner, the scorny
little [ __ ] that can't talk. We'd
rather laugh at you, lad. It's more funner.
Brother, listen. I've shown more money
than your boyfriend. Do you know your
boyfriend? That dick you like to suck.
I've shown more money than your
boyfriend. And it was my money as well.
It was my money. I've shown better
looks, better life. I'm better looking
than you. I'm better looking than you,
you ma. You're the one that [ __ ]
comes on here. Yeah. Begging women, you
[ __ ] clap looking gorilla. You
[ __ ] ugly [ __ ] And you're calling me
a M. You're the one trying to [ __ ]
You're the one begging my sloppy
seconds. You m of a man. Go suck your boyfriend's dick.
[ __ ] You [ __ ] little wanker. You're
not better than me, bro. I have been
with more women than you, bro. More
women than you. You're ugly. You got an
ugly nose, ugly eyes, bro. Shut up, man.
You're [ __ ] ugly, bro. You [ __ ]
ugly, man. Go sucking nonsleg's
boyfriend. Dick little gay boy.
Shut up, bro. Go suck up your
boyfriend's dick. I'm calling him a
virgin. Go suck up his dick some more,
bro. Give us another essay.
You're calling people Charlene's kid is
Why are you calling people's kids
monties, bro? That's not nice, bro.
You're only You're Bro, you're just
You're just You're just salty cuz my
sister rejected you, bro. You're the one
Why do you tell everyone on YouTube how
you stalked my sister,
bro? Come on, man. You stalk my sister.
You stalk my sloppy seconds. [ __ ] me, man. Simple.
Joe, why don't you come on a panel and talk?
Why don't you come on a panel and talk?
You scared little Northerner? Why didn't
you come and meet me when I was in Newcastle?
You scared, terrified Northerner.
One second. Someone's messaging me. But hold on. M.
No one likes your picks, bro.
It is easy work, lad. How the [ __ ] did
that escalate? Listen. Oh, right.
Here's what I'm going to do. Yeah.
Right. I'm going to book this room for
one, two, three. I'm I'm going to I'm
going to book a room for five of you
people, bro. And fill your boots. Just
fill your [ __ ] boots, lad. One sec.
Fill your boots, man. Feel your boot.
Fill your boots, lad.
Fill your [ __ ] boots.
Yeah, man. Yeah.
You just come out as gay, bro. It's
2026. Just come out as gay. Yeah.
Oh, from a black man. So now he's being
racist. Oh, coming to mouth from a black
man. Joe, you ain't got no family. You
gay boy. That's why you've got a channel
dedicated to me. Cuz you want my
attention. Cuz you're a little gay boy.
You ain't got no family. You little gay
boy. You're just like nonslegs. Gay me.
You've all got no family. Family gay
[ __ ] Familyless gay [ __ ] That's
what we're going to call you now, lad. A
bunch of gay boys with no family. That's
what you are. You hate that word, ain't
it, Joe? Bunch of gay boys with no
family. You could never come to London
ever, bro. Like, I've come up north yet
all of them times. Gay Joe with no
family could never do that. Gay Joey
could never do it, bro. He could never.
He could just never do that. He could
just never do that, bro.
Yeah, man. I love it.
Joe, you got no family, bro. You're a
gay boy. You're a little gay boy. >> Yeah.
>> But no, seriously, bro. Do you want to
do you want to suck this guy's dick, LT?
Nah, bro. My sister would never go with
that ma. That [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] LT,
my sister would don't go for ugly
people, bro. They did not go with ugly
bro. LT's two butt is, bro. Bro, he's
ugly. Why do you think he Why do you
think he [ __ ] begs my sloppy seconds,
bro? He's [ __ ] a m. Why do you think
he never shows his face, bro? LT is a
[ __ ] m. A big m. And he's not going
to do anything about it. He's nothing
but a [ __ ] m. You understand, lad?
No one wants to suck you, you ugly m.
The only chance you've got is your
[ __ ] boyfriend. Nons legs. [ __ ] you.
The only bro, the only chance you've got
is [ __ ] nonslegs, lad. To be fair,
the only dick you're [ __ ] The only
what what the only thing you're getting
is nonslegs is dick,
bro. I don't females on it. Listen, LG,
let me tell you something, bro. Let me
tell you something, bro. Let me tell you
something here right now. Yeah. Now, the
thing is, bro, uh I don't go for women
online, bro, because I'm not socially
awkward like you. I haven't got anxiety
like you. So, bro, I don't simp I don't
simp over women online, you see. So, I
actually go out and meet people. So, I
mean, I I wouldn't be doing that. I
mean, you can if you want, but yeah,
we're not all we're not all like you,
bro, have to, you know, go uh uh stalk
people sloppy seconds or simp women on
YouTube. We don't I don't get down like
that, bro. Maybe you get down like that,
lad. But I don't get down like that,
I don't get down like that, bro. I
really don't get down like that.
There's there's someone new in the
community if you want, lad.
Bro, who have you s Oxo
Jane? Uh Autum. When I went for Autumn
like two months ago, you went straight
away onto me, bro. Yeah,
you do. S, bro, there was another one.
Oh, Scottish Stacy. you do.
Yeah, but you're this good-looking guy,
bro. Yeah, whatever, man. Yeah, bro.
Your cousin is going to be knocking on.
Oh, yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah. You keep telling yourself that in
it, bro. He's going to be knocking on my
door. Okay, bro. Yeah. Good luck with
that. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Good luck with that, bro.
Yeah. I'm sure, bro. I'm sure. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm sure. Yeah,
you're hilarious, bro. You're hilarious.
You're Do you know what? It's funny,
bro. That is really, really, really funny.
Yeah. Bring who you want, bro. No one
cares. Even Laney said the same thing as
well. Bring who you want. Just cuz you
don't like the truth, bro. You're not
going to try and fatten people and think
they're scared of you. No one gives a
[ __ ] No one gives a [ __ ]
No one really gives a [ __ ] bro. Just
cuz you don't like hearing the truth.
Yeah, good, bro. Get who you want. No
one No one's asked. No one gives a [ __ ]
No one gives a monkeyy's [ __ ] Simple.
Why? Cuz you don't like the truth,
bro. You're biased. It's as simple as
that. You're biased. You're biased.
You are biased, bro. It doesn't matter,
bro. Listen, get your cousin on my door
and you'll see what will happen today.
It's as simple as that, bro. Stop
talking about kids, bro. You must be a
pedophile or something. You keep talking
about kids. Just get your cousin on the
door and and we'll see what will happen
today. It's as simple as that. Yeah.
Get your big man cousin on here. On here
like a big man. Okay. Whatever. Yeah.
Okay. Big man cousin. Get your big man
here today and see what happens, bro.
Okay. Whatever. Big man. Big man. Stop
talking. Big man. Uh but please don't
run to the police. Please. literally do
not want runa please. Please if you are
going to do something like that.
All cuz I'm telling you that you're
sucking your boyfriend's dick being biased.
Really, bro? Really?
You know? Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Whatever, bro.
Whatever. And it will teach you to stop
looking big on YouTube, bro. So, just do
what you say you're going to do. That's
fine, man. And I want to teach you to
stop big being big on YouTube and stop
[ __ ] stalking me. I don't want you. I
don't want you, bro. Yeah, you are the
biggest bun. Your whole family of
bunters. Your f You got the family of
bunters. Bunter. The bun tailers.
Taylor the bunters.
Come today, big man, and see what
happens, bro. Really? Really? Come
today, bro. The bunters. The Taylor
Bunters. I want to see what this family
is all about, bro. Yeah, man. Come on,
bro. Nah, we don't do it like the Taylor
Munters. The Taylor Munters. The Taylor
Swift bunters. Get your cousin, bro. Get
your Get whoever you want today, bro.
Come on, bro. Get the Taylor bunters.
You be cute. You won't be able to run
away either, lad.
Yeah. Yeah. Shut up, bro. Your whole
family are ugly, bro. The ugly Taylor. Shut up.
Yeah. [ __ ] it, bro. Your whole family is
the ugly Taylor. The ugly Taylor family.
The ugly inbredad family. The ugly
tailor. Isn't it matter? I'm the only
one that can say like this, bro. Yeah.
The [ __ ] ugly Taylor boys that wants
nons's dick, but you're going to get
your [ __ ] cousin, bro. Do it. Do it.
Yeah. Come on. Bring the [ __ ]
bunters. Yeah. Go on. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Will you? Will
you? Yeah. Really? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah,
yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. With
about 100 people. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Really, bro.
Really? Yeah. Good luck with that, bro.
Good luck with that. You're going to
learn. You're not going to keep looking
big on YouTube for women, bro. I've had
enough of your [ __ ] for about four or
five years. Four or five [ __ ] years, bro.
four or five [ __ ] years.
Yeah. If you want to do what you got to
do, bro, do it. But don't start crying.
Do not start crying. Do not start crying, bro.
Sick of you, bro. Keep [ __ ] [ __ ]
stirring and stalking people and ret and
all of this [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] you.
Absolutely [ __ ] you, bro. [ __ ] you.
Just cuz you don't like the truth. Can't
even answer me. Yeah, you can't even
[ __ ] answer me. That's the thing.
You're lo, bro, you're just like this
Jamie Thompson. You're just like this
nod, bro. You're all the same. I swear
down. You're all You're all bent for me,
bro. Like, I swear to God, bro. Yeah,
you're actually all gay for me. I don't
want any of you, bro. I don't swing that
way. I don't want you. I don't want Joe.
I don't want Not legs, bro. I don't I
don't want you, bro. Do you not
understand? I don't want your ass.
You're not going to get my ass, bro.
Just come out. Come out. Simple.
Yeah. Guess what, Joe? You can't even
talk and I went to your city.
Yeah, bro. You can keep doing that, lad.
Yeah, bro. You keep doing that, bro. You
keep doing that. You keep doing that,
bro. Yeah. You keep stalking because you
got no life and YOU GOT NO KIDS.
Your little bro, tell your little gay
cousin. No one No one's gonna slap no
one's mom. Your little gay cousin ain't
going to slap no one, bro. Your little
gay cousin, you don't even do nothing,
bro. Shut up. Your little gay cousin
ain't going to do nothing. The only one
that's going to be opening door to me,
not your gay cousin. Shut up. You're not
about nothing, lad. Come out the closet.
Going to slap my mom. Your little hot
debt gay cousin. Your gay boy is going
to slap my mom. Do it, bro. Do it. Do
it. I bet you he does not. And I bet you
none of your family does. And I and I
guarantee you none of your family will,
bro. I guarantee you your cousin will
not be slapping nobody. Thank you very
much. You [ __ ] stupid little idiot. I
guarantee you he [ __ ] won't.
You little gay boy. What did you say?
You're going to stalk me. You're gay,
bro. You're gay. You're actually gay,
bro. You're actually gay. What did you
say? Let me go. I'm going to keep
stalking, bro. That's Bro, this is
exactly what I was saying earlier. This
is exactly what I was saying earlier,
bro. Yeah. This is exactly what I was
saying earlier. You're gay. You're
actually a gay boy. He ain't got kids,
bro. I'm telling you. This guy's not got
children. He's gay, bro. I'm telling
you. I'm telling you. He He He literally
has not got kids. He's gay. He's a gay
boy. He's like nonsakes. I told you.
They're all the same. They're all bent.
They hate the fact that they're gay.
They literally hate the fact that
they're gay, bro.
You're going to come in an old woman's
door. Really, bro? You and your little
rejected family, your little bully
victim family. No way, bro. Is that happening?
No [ __ ] way.
[ __ ] weirdo, bro. Imagine back in the
night you would have said the things he has.
Yeah, bro. Whatever. Yeah, man.
You literally went Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Stop making
empty threats, bro. I've got I've
actually got it where you said you're
going to stop when when you're going to
stalk people. You're going to stalk
people. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
You're You're going to stalk people.
You're going to stalk people. Wow.
Sounds a bit gay to me, bro.
Sounds a bit gay to me.
Anyways, we'll let this bad man see what
he's going to do, bro. Anyways, we're
done with this guy. Anyways, we're done
with you, bro. You're boring as [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Of course he is, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. Of course he is. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Of course he is. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Of course he is, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Of course
he is. I don't want your ass, bro. And
I'm not going to give you my ass either.
You understand? Stop trying to look,
bro. Stop trying to look good on for
YouTube in 2026.
I don't want your ass, bro. Leave me
alone. I don't want you. You're not
giving me my ass crack. Go away, bro.
And it's And that's the thing as well,
bro. I love it. Yeah.
How about that life, bro? Come on.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. You're boring. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You're boring. You're
boring. You're literally boring.
You are boring. Bye. You're boring. Bye-bye.
[ __ ] proper boring, bro.
Proper proper proper proper boring. This
is what this is why people don't waste
their time on you, you know. This is
exactly why people don't waste their
time on you people. This is exactly what I mean. Yeah.
Madness, bro. The proper you need to get
a hobby or something.
Well, I was never afraid to begin with.
I was never ever ever afraid.
Never afraid. It was just I didn't want
to, you know, certain things. Anyways,
bro, you need to get a hobby. Anyways,
that's what you need to get. You need to
get a hobby.
That's what you do. You need to get a
hobby, bro. It's 2026 and you're still
trying to look big on the internet.
You're still trying to look big for the
Don't you worry about whether my mom's
in or not, bro. Go away, you little weirdo.
That's all you need to know, bro. Just
go away, you little weirdo. Don't worry
who's in and who's not in.
You [ __ ] freak. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Whatever. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Whatever, bro.
No one cares. You're irrelevant.
Yeah. No one cares. You're irrelevant.
No one cares. You're irrelevant, bro.
Stop trying to look big on YouTube in
2026. You're boring, kid.
You're [ __ ] boring.
Yeah. Yeah. You're boring. You're
proper. Proper proper boring. Yeah.
So boring you are, bro.
Proper [ __ ] boring.
All right, this person's replied back. Yep.
Nah, I just told the guy no, bro. Yeah.
Like, bro, you you don't understand. I
don't swing that way, bro. I'm trying to
like, you know, get with my life and
stuff. And you know what I'm saying?
[ __ ] weirdos, bro. Weirdos.
Absolute weirdos, lad. Yeah.
Proper proper weirdos on here, bro.
Proper proper weirdos on here.
100% weirdos. To think of it in the
first place, why are you even getting
involved with other people's fights when
it's got nothing to do with you?
When it's literally got nothing to do
with you. Why are you getting Why are
you trying to get involved in other
people's fights? You need a hobby, bro.
Everything that you're saying
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Whatever you say, bro.
No one cares about you, bro. You're irrelevant.
You're irrelevant, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm this. I'm that.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Bro,
you got this normal life and then you're
saying that you're going to stalk
people. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Begging dudes. Who have I begged to
suck? Oh, bro. You're weasel, man.
Listen, like I said to you, man. Yeah.
You're another Jo Joe Jo. You're another
Virgin boy. You're another Red Star.
That's literally all you are. That's
literally all you are. You're
irrelevant. You are literally
That's how bad it is. You're actually irrelevant.
You are. You actually are irrelevant.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Whatever, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Whatever. It's not happening, lad.
Yeah. Yeah. It's not happening.
It's not happening, matey. So, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You
keep telling yourself that anyways, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You're a man that says you're going to
be stalking me, bro. Let that sink in.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Remember you said that you're stalking
me, bro. A man saying that you're
stalking me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Yep. Yep. Whatever. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Anyways, I'm coming off now. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm coming off today,
bro. So, if you want to really get
anyone to do anything or whatever, it's
not going to go it's not going to go the
way you planned it anyways. So, if you
know what's good for you, um you're not
going to be trying anything like that
because I've actually got somebody to
speak to now and I've actually got a
life unlike you. So, um yeah, I'm going
to be leaving you now soon. I'm going to
be leaving you now anyways. Yeah. So, um
kindly get a life and kindly get a hobby
cuz you desperately desperately need
one. See you later. Bye-bye now.