Right,
we got half hour left.
So, I can't be on here too long because
I'll lose brain cells. Oh, here we go.
You get the link then. Oh gosh.
Is the link not working or something? Uh, copycat.
Who's a copycat?
So, anyways, when are these people going
to come off of YouTube and get a life?
So, yeah, Grezy, I was getting attached again basically.
But what did that account say before
about me getting attached? Grezy,
what did the account say? Do you remember?
I don't cry every day either, mate.
What did the account say, Greavvesy?
Was that the same Was that Was that the
same account that said that you're a
poor [ __ ] Greavvesy? Or was it a different one?
Was it Was it the same guy?
Was it the same guy, Grezy?
Um, I watched The Strangers chapter 3,
bro. It was meh.
I like the little masks. Greasy, did you
Did you see it? The Strangers chapter 3?
I watched it on Valentine's Day. Yep.
I watched on Valentine's Day, bro.
It was meh. Now we got Scream 7 coming
out on the 27th. Is Scream 7. Scream 7
on the 27th. Yay.
Yeah, I'm leaving. I'm leaving again,
bro. Coming back to this [ __ ] See,
Grievy was so desperate for content that
he's been deprived of, he he took it
upon himself to message me on Instagram.
Bless you, Grezy.
Is that cute getting attached again, Greavesy?
She seems like a nice person, bro. So, I
thought, you know what? I might not add
her to the collection. Who knows? But
no, she doesn't. I was expecting that I
was going to get ghosted and [ __ ] bro.
And I was going to I would have been
pissed off. If I got ghosted, I would
have been pissed off.
And then but usually nine times out of
10, you would get ghosted. Even if you
was speaking to someone for 7 8 days,
whatever, you would get ghosted. Which
brings me on to my main point of why you
need to meet people as soon as possible.
Which is what what which is why you you
you should meet people as soon as possible.
Unless they're in another country or
they've got some [ __ ] mad this going
on or mad that going on or there's some
big reason then yeah, you need to meet them ASAP
so you can reel people out. Do you get it?
I'm sure I've had it before, but I can't
remember exactly. But yeah, I've met
people um whose numbers I've had for
like three weeks a month grievy, but I
popped I popped up out of the blue. So
I'd speak to them for like four or five
four days and then I pop up two weeks
later. There's never people I've had
constant conversations with that's met
cuz texting is not for that. That's why
you have to meet people. You see,
you meet people. Texting is just like
saying And uh you know what I'm saying?
Oh, Greavves. I had to stick it on this
tenant [ __ ] Oh my god. Yesterday uh
the other day, bro, I had to stick it on
this tenant bad. I stuck it on him
badly, bro. I should send you the voice
note. I put him in his place. Good and proper.
Good and [ __ ] proper, bro. I was at
the cinema. Yeah. And I didn't even
realize he was trying to be racist.
I didn't even realize until I went back.
I was like, "Oh [ __ ] you're trying to
be racist now. [ __ ] that. I'm getting
lady's phone and I'm [ __ ] voice
noting you." Yeah, bro. He was trying to
be a proper proper [ __ ] So, I had to
put him in his place. And yeah, I
haven't heard anything since.
Trying to be racist to Oh, okay. But
then the thing is, Greasy, then they
wonder why people don't like certain
people like from certain cultures. Then
people start wondering why, you see,
Grezy, then they start wondering why
people are um people are um
some people are racist. But then people
wonder, do you understand? This is what
ah he was just trying to basically just
play games and stuff, bro. It wasn't as
much as calling people. It was it was um
Yeah, he was he was being a [ __ ] bro.
What what he done No, no. What he done,
Grezy, was he was asking me, right, what
was it? I can get it up here. He was asking me
for 50. He was asking me for £50. And
I'm getting pissed off because I said
this to someone the other day. Why does
people always look at me for money? When
people have got no money, they always
look at me. And it's so [ __ ]
annoying, bro, when people look at you,
you know? And in his case, even more so
because come on, we know that people
from Pakistan know loads of people.
You're telling me he doesn't know one
person that could that could lend him
50. I'm sick of people looking at me.
You know, you know what I'm saying? And
and a few people do it as well. And it's
it does get annoying. It does get
annoying, bro. You can understand if the
person didn't know anyone or then maybe
you know but what you don't know anyone
in your community that can that could
give you 50 all the people that you know
you don't understand in their culture
they're like brothers they're like best
best friends once they meet one they
they stick together you don't understand
they're not like they're not like
English people bro and stuff they they I
know how their culture works bro because
I know many of them
So, but then he's coming to me. He He's
He's coming to me. Do you understand?
Why the [ __ ] are you coming to me, bro?
And I clocked what he was trying to do
straight away. I'm too smart for that.
They must really think that we're the
stupid ones. They must really, really,
really think we are the stupid ones. So,
I come back from the cinema and I read
it properly. I was like, "Oh, [ __ ] that."
And they lie so much that they forget
their own lies.
What he's trying to do, Grezy, is get
the money so we can give back to the
other people who claimed I owe them
money. Am I right or am I right? But I'm stupid, apparently.
Am I right, Gregy? Or am I right?
Come on. Come on, Grezy.
Come on. You know, Peter Melly wasn't
born yesterday, was he? You know, it's
too obvious. It's too obvious.
They they make they make it too obvious.
Certain people they just they're so
silly that they make it too obvious. How
do you think I can reel people out, Greavvesy?
How do How do you think I reeled How do
you think I reeled that Jo out,
Greavesy? How do you think I knew what
he was about? You remember when he was
doing the girlfriend [ __ ] again with
Nlegs? I knew Oh, straight away he's a
lovely monk. Was I wrong? No.
Soon I can reel people out, bro. like
easy, you know?
I wasn't born yesterday, mate. Was born
on a day and it wasn't yesterday.
Then he was trying to be racist, but
then they say that we're racist. He was Yeah,
they're very nasty people when they
don't get their own ray, grievy. Muslim
people are very nasty when they don't
get their own way.
Very, very nasty.
Trust me, bro.
I know what they're like.
It's not letting me let you in.
Whoever's trying to join, it's not
letting me let you in, lad.
[ __ ] it now.
I think I found my mama. Greasy.
No, it was um it was a tenant,
Greavvesy. Uh Ben, it was a it was a
tenant um from the house. And what it
was pissing me off that people was
always looking at me for money. And I
was saying this to my mom as well. I'm
sick of people always looking at me. Um
especially when someone, you know, is is
a Muslim and they would know people.
They do know people. Muslim people know
loads of loads of people. And the
money's coming from somewhere because
when they used to pay me rent, where
where they getting the money from? I
said, "Go ask one of the million and one
other people that you know." Yeah.
Stop looking at me for money. It's
[ __ ] annoying, bro. So annoying, you
know, with other with someone else that
does it, a certain person. It's not all
the time. And he doesn't know anyone. He
generally doesn't know anyone. So, and
even that gets annoying. But when you've
got someone right from Pakistan when you
know they know people, you know that
they're you know like don't don't look
at me for money. Then I just clocked on
that he's trying to get £50 so he can
give to the other tenant that claim that
I owe him money so he can try to get the
last laugh. I'm not stupid bro. I'm not stupid.
Yeah, bro. I would tell anyone Yeah.
Anyone that has a business, never ever
deal with Pakistani people ever. As a
whole, bro, I'm telling that straight away. Jesus Christ.
And do you know what he tried saying?
And And I sent him I'll tell you what he
said, right? And I and I'll tell you
what I said back cuz I was in the
cinema. I was busy. And I didn't even
realize what um what he said until um I
had come back. He said um obviously I
said I can't owe it. I can't lend you it
and that which I can but I'm not giving
him money. Um he says he says that's the
reason white guys always die alone. So
then I said to him, hold on a minute. I
didn't even realize you started being
racist. I said, listen, bro, I'd rather
be a white person and die alone than be
a thieving Pakistani that steals
people's after shave and steal people's
t-shirts, which you still haven't
admitted to stealing yet. They stole
like a£100 after shave from mine. No one
admitted it. So, bro, like I'm pretty
sure at least at least if there were
white people out there that die alone,
they're not thieving like the
Pakistanis. Um, he didn't like that
because he knows I'm [ __ ] right
because they stole my aftershave, bro.
One of them stole it when I weren't in
the house. So, I mean, yeah, but white
guys might do, but white guys don't
steal like the Pakistanis. Um, he didn't
like that. And then and then they lie so
much that they don't even realize that
they lie so much. They don't even
realize the lies that they've told
previously. And I'm thinking, bro, like
you're you've stole people. And you know
the thing is, Ben, they still haven't
admitted who done it. It's not even like
they done it and then they admitted it.
Then it would be like, oh well, it's
shitty they stole something, but they
admitted it. They're still trying to act
like they didn't steal it.
So, I mean, yeah. What the [ __ ] How are
you stealing people's after shave? How
is one of you stealing people's after
shaves and then trying to then ask
people for £50? That doesn't make no sense.
[ __ ] off. And what they would have done
is they would have kept the £50 and they
would have gave it back. I'm not stupid,
bro. Yeah. I'm not [ __ ] stupid,
you know? Wasn't born yesterday, lad.
And I don't know where they live. Uh,
and that's the thing. Cheeky, bro.
And I said, "Bro, I don't play your
stupid little games. Stop messaging me.
I don't play." Do you know? Do you know
the thing is, Ben? Yeah. Are you still there, Ben?
I avoid dealing with people if I have
to. I don't like dealing with people,
bro. I don't like people. I don't like
dealing with people. I don't like
relying on people, you know. I really,
really, really, really don't. I can't
stand people, Ben. I really can't, bro.
Stupid time wasters trying to play games
all the time. Um, I'm sick of people,
bro. I'm really, really, really, really,
really sick of people. Um, I speak to
like three or four people, bro. I'm sick
of people. And then I said to him, then
he says to me, Ben, he says, um, he
says, you know, £50 is nothing. I didn't
even, and I did respond back on the
voice, but I told you what I responded.
I'll tell you what I responded. He said,
you know, £50 is nothing. I didn't even
remember any money from our past. If you
were thinking this way, but you could
have tested my words, but you chose the
other way. I said to him firstly, um,
bro, you're talking to me. This is what
I used to say to LT a few times because
I think they forget who they're talking
to. You're telling me £50 is nothing.
Bro, you used to have £80 to last you
the whole month when you got your wages
cuz you sent money here, you sent money
there. You had £80 to last you a month
every month. And you're telling me £50
is nothing. You are telling me £50 is Yeah.
If £50 is nothing, how did you bro that?
And then he says to me, but but then it
gets worse. Then no, no, no, it gets
worse. I said to him, he said to me, I
earn three grand a month. I live in a
big room alone. I pay 6220 W and you
think I'm playing with you for 50 grow
up, brother. I said, bro, firstly, uh,
you don't get over three grand a month
because I've lived with you. So, no, you
do not. And if you do, that's great
then. You don't need £50 then, do you?
If somebody's getting over three grand a
month and they need 50, then you need to
stop doing drugs or whatever you're
doing with your money, bro. Cuz let me
tell you something. I've been on the
same money now for many, many months.
And I don't need to borrow money off no
[ __ ] I can't remember the last time I
needed to borrow money off someone
and I don't get [ __ ] three grand. So
if you're getting three and a half grand
a month, bro, you need to stop doing
[ __ ] heroin or whatever you're doing
with your money cuz your your stories it
doesn't make nothing you're saying makes
sense. And then the thing is Ben is the
white guys are so bad that he's the one
asking the white man for money. Isn't
that funny? Isn't that funny? He's
saying about how white people are this
and white white cuz he's generalizing
white people. But he's on the white
man's phone for £50.
You don't make any sense, do you? You
really really need to go back to [ __ ]
school and learning English or something
because bro, you're asking the white man
for money. And wouldn't that tell you in in in
itself about what what your people are
like really if you're asking me for £50?
So [ __ ] off, bro.
Don't ever deal with um Pakistani
people, Grezy. Bro, sorry if that Oh,
Ben, sorry if that sounds racist, but
bro, I've had many, many dealings with
them and all they everything that they
do, there's always an ulterior motive
with them. There's always an ulterior
motive with them and they're just Yeah,
they're just idiots, bro. Just never
ever deal with them. But if I if I if I
was ever like I was ever if I was ever a
landlord again, I would never have
Pakistanis. Never, ever, ever. And it's
not even because how they live or
whatever. It's not even just that. It's
the the the the games that they play that.
And that's what it is. And it's like,
yeah, people will [ __ ] you over, bro.
And in in the heartbeat this day and age, Ben. Yeah.
I hate people that play games. I hate people, bro.
I seriously seriously hate people
dealing with people like that. You know
what I mean? There's another person as well.
They're quick enough to ask you for
favors, but when you need something,
they're nowhere to be seen,
Ben. They're nowhere to be seen.
Won't get into it, but Yeah. Yeah, bro.
but I'm right what I'm saying though. Is
it Ben? I'm right what I'm saying.
They lie so much they can't even keep up
with their like own lies. I'm I'm What
I'm saying is right though, is it Ben?
What I'm saying is true though, is it?
bringing skin color into [ __ ] The [ __ ]
bro. Guy's an ill
hate people, bro. I really hate people.
I only speak to Ant-Man and Christian,
Izzy, Reevesy, and obviously my mom and
like a couple of other people, but the
other the other people are not every day.
The other people are not every day.
So I don't speak to anyone else, bro.
See you later.
So yeah, man.
Yeah. What's your opinion on um Monty
man being a copycat then Greavves it?
What's your opinion on that?
Can he can he can he tell you can he
give you the reason why he thinks these
people are gay and and jealous? Because
I can give the reason but he can't give
the reason can he? I don't think he can
give the reason. Can he Gy? I can give
You want me to give you the reason why I
think that? Because he can't. Cuz he's
too stupid. He can't.
I can give it
because if they weren't gay, right, and
they weren't jealous of someone, they
wouldn't spend all day on YouTube
stalking people. They'd have a life of
their own. Um they would be with their
woman. there'd be uh you know they
wouldn't be on here doing this just like
I haven't been on here for what was it
eight days I've been too too busy
talking to someone
just like Monty man's being a copycat
saying that the people on here that do
this like Red Star V and all of that
they're gay and jealous and he's just
like copying me because that's what I
literally said I literally said that about them
because it's obvious because if they
weren't gay and they weren't jealous
they wouldn't sit on YouTube every day
wasting their life away harassing people
and stalking men. Simple as that. But
then he's trying to copy what I'm
saying. You know what I'm saying?
Of course they are low lives, bro. They
wouldn't be on here if they had
anything. They wouldn't be on here doing
what they do every day if they had anything.
Why do you think so many people left?
But their money man copies what I say.
Come on, bro. Do you think anyone could
pay me to have a channel dedicated to
another man? We do think
you could pay me to have a channel
dedicated to another man. No way, Jose.
I'll just message [ __ ] I'll just
start talking to [ __ ] Christian
[ __ ] Izzy, bro.
I would just go out and meet new people.
So, you need to look at it from that
aspect as well. You know what I'm saying?
If they had anything in their lives,
they wouldn't be seeking attention and
reaction from men every day on the internet.
So then Monty man copies what I say cuz
he's got no mind of his own.
I feel like I'm the leader on this shy
and everyone just copies what I do.
You get what I'm saying? I feel like
everyone just copies what I do.
That make sense?
You little copycat.
I haven't been on here in 8 days, lad.
And I'm coming off in a minute. I mean,
I haven't been on YouTube for eight
days. When was the last time you took
eight days off of YouTube, Timmy? When
was the last time any of LJ's followers
took eight days off of YouTube? Yeah,
that's what I thought. I could answer it for you.
Yeah. Yeah. And I'm on here talking to
Greavvesy. I'm on here talking to Dusty.
I'm on here chilling, bro. I'm not on
here stalking men. I'm not on here
having a channel dedicated to another
man, am I? So, what? I am on here. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, I am.
The first time in 8 days. And I'm not
stalking men. And I don't have a channel
dedicated to men. So, what? What?
Simple as that. Bro,
why do you think people's hating on
Monty's fry up? Do you think they were jealous?
He says that they're jealous, but I mean
I've every single woman that I've been
with has been better than that. Natalie
G. I mean, I don't know about these
people. They probably are jealous, but
not me. I'm [ __ ] not jealous of that.
I think he's told me before that I'm
jealous. I'm jealous. But I've had
chances to be with her before him. But
I'm jealous. Bro, the woman I'm speaking
to right now is miles and miles and
miles and miles and miles better.
I would send [ __ ] um Greavves the
pictures, but he's going to he's going
to do reverse image. Yeah,
he's going to do reverse image and then
he's going to find them and he's going
to message them.
Bro, could you imagine that, bro? If any
of these clowns found out anyone that
you were speaking to?
That's just giving a million [ __ ]
bullets in a shotgun. Is it?
Yeah. They be on it like a [ __ ]
butterfly on [ __ ] on a summer's day,
bro. For real.
Yeah, they would, bro. 100% they would. right.
Kind of hungry. I don't know what to
get, lad. Cool.
I'm just going to have the steak later.
Greasy. Okay with you, boss.
He's so Hey, this this banger is so
stupid, Harry. He says that he wouldn't
go out drinking by himself.
He wouldn't do he wouldn't go out
drinking by himself, but he would sit on
YouTube by himself on a Saturday talking
to losers. But he wouldn't go he
wouldn't go drinking by himself. I
haven't had a full English for ages,
bro. But he wouldn't go out drinking by himself,
but he would sit on YouTube talking to
losers by himself. Think of it, Grevy.
Look at all of the times I went out
drinking by myself. I had a laugh. I had
fun. I met other people.
Why wouldn't you go out drinking by
yourself? If you're in somewhere like
London, you're going to meet people.
You're going to hang with people.
Why wouldn't you go out drinking by
yourself? People go traveling by
himself. This guy is He's got He's
obsessed with people, bro. Bro, he's
obsessed with people having no friends
when he ain't got any friends himself.
It's like he he lets that dictate his
his whole life, bro.
So weird, isn't it? And the thing is,
Grezy, even if he was out with a friend,
they still make up excuses. Oh, you
don't know the person? How many times
have I been out with a friend and
they've said, "Oh, you don't know them."
Or, "Oh," so it's like, "What the fuck?"
Can't remember them, bro. Can't remember these people.
Yeah, you can't win with him, bro.
So, what are you doing? Some food shopping.
I could have a full English now, bro.
But I'm too late for it.
Oh, I don't know what, bro. Starving, man.
What about some nuggets from McDonald's?
We is that okay with you, boss?
Maybe some like nuggets from McDonald's or something.
That Philly burgers back at McDonald's.
Greavves. The Philly steak thing. Stack
thing. Yeah, I'm not going to get that.
I'm going to get nuggets because the
burger when you get the burgers, it
always comes cold.
The burgers always comes cold. I don't
know what I'm hungry, bro.
Don't know. I'm I am hungry.
Yeah, it is pretty stinking to be fair.
Yeah, I'm not ordering burgers and stuff
from McDonald's ever again, bro. It's
just too or Burger King or McDonald's
cuz it's too cold. It comes cold, bro.
So unless you get like the nuggets,
everything just comes cold. So it's pointless.
You get me.
Could go to a chicken shop, but I kind
of have to travel there, bro. It's so
long. [ __ ] hungry, bro.
Let's have the steak now and then just
have like some chicken later. music maybe.
Oh, bless you then. If you're going to
get back in shape, bless you.
Maybe I could just have some steak now.
I reckon that's the that's the that's
the thing. Yeah. And then maybe get some chicken later.
What do you think? Does that sound like
a good idea, Grezy?
So, what will happen if these people
find out? Um, she and Izzy, Greavvesy. H.
What do you say? What happened?
They wouldn't do anything, would they?
They wouldn't do anything, bro. Would they? No.
Now, what would they do?
What would they do, Harry, if these
people found out someone that I was
meeting and stuff or like talking to or
dating? What do you think these people would do?
What would they would they
would they would they do it out of jealousy?
Would they do it out of jealousy? Greasy.
Yeah. Yeah, they would, wouldn't they?
Out of jealousy in it, Greavvesy. Yeah.
See, if they if they found her a year
later, Greavesy, then it wouldn't
matter. Do you get it? The longer you
you meet them, the longer you you you're
speaking to them, the more chance that
even if they did see anything, uh they wouldn't care.
You understand? But obviously if you
just met someone and they saw that,
they're like, "What the [ __ ] You get it?"
Trust me, I guarantee you if you met
someone for 6 months, Yeah. and they
found out all this [ __ ] they wouldn't
leave you, bro. I don't think they would leave you.
I don't think so. Nah.
Well, they must be jealous, bro. To sit
on the internet every day stalking men
for years. They've got to be jealous of
something cuz I [ __ ] wouldn't be
doing it. I certainly wouldn't be
stalking men online for years and years
and years who I've never met.
But each their own, I guess.
I just couldn't imagine doing it. I just
it just wouldn't cross my mind cuz I'm
like, "Okay, I've got a life. I can
speak to people. I can do whatever I
want. I've got my own life to live, so
why am I going to waste my years
stalking someone on the internet, bro?
That's weird as [ __ ] Especially a man. So,
they've got to be gay or jealous, if not both.
But like I said, Monty man copied me
with that saying, didn't he?
Nope. No crown court for me, de lad.
So, you've got a life.
You got all of this money. You can do
this, but then you'd rather waste your
life. Why do you think I don't come on
here much anymore, Grez? I haven't been
on here what, 8, nine days. Because it's
a waste of life.
It's a waste of life talking to idiots.
You know what I'm saying? Why do you
think, bro? Cuz it's a waste of time.
Waste of life.
So much you can do with your life, bro.
as you know, you've only you only and
you don't need to even do anything bad
like you know it's like
UK asylum if you looked on if you looked
at Yeah, I know. I've got I got your
notifications Grezy. If you got this
if you listen to L J. Yeah. Right. If
you listen to L J. Yeah. Greavvesy. If
you listen to If you listen to If you
listen to L J, bro. Um, he was saying
that I've wasted my 20s on here when
I've done more than him in 3 years than
he's done in his whole life. Like, think
about what I was doing when I first was
on here, bro. I was going gym. I was
traveling. I was doing this. I've still
got my Amsterdam videos. These people
were doing nothing, bro. These people
stood they were sat in the same chair in
the same boxes and and I've wasted my
20s, bro. You're you're in your 40s and
I've done more than you at 28. And that
doesn't even need to mean that doesn't
even need to mean traveling, bro. That
doesn't even need to mean that. No, you
know what I'm saying?
Trust me, way more than he will ever do
and ever have on YouTube or not on YouTube.
Do you get what I'm saying?
That is just proper self projection.
Proper proper. That is proper self projection, bro.
That is I just been doing stuff, bro.
I haven't been gambling. I told you I
was done with that [ __ ] I've been
speaking to Christian Izzy, Dusty.
Yeah, I've been speaking to Christian
Izzy. So, I don't need to speak to
anyone else. I don't need to come on
here. I went on here today to tell Monty
to keep my name out of his [ __ ] mouth.
That's what he needs to do, bro. Keep my
name out of his [ __ ] mouth.
Don't make me come to [ __ ] Birmingham
with a Spider-Man t-shirt and [ __ ]
give you a punch in your [ __ ] [ __ ]
mouth. You get me? Cuz you won't like
it, mate. I travel with a Spider-Man top. Yeah.
Trust me, you wouldn't like it.
No, I'm not. I'm going in a minute. I'm
going to cook my steak and then I'm done. Bro,
I'm not going to come back for a little while.
I got better people to be talking to. Yeah.
Nah, just brings back memories, you know.
Dojo and Yoda is downstairs by the way,
Greavvesy. So yeah,
I wasn't fat to begin with.
So I I I I don't know whether I have or
not because I wasn't fat to begin with.
Possibly, but who knows?
So I can't be wasting time on it now anyways. So yeah.
So yeah, that's how you know that's how
you separate me from these people. I'm
not talking about like how hard can it
be and people like that or Charlie and
them because they can just come on here,
you know, but I'm talking about the
people on L J's. They have got no life,
bro. No [ __ ] life whatsoever. Trust
me, they want YouTube straight away.
It's madness, bro. Madness.
And they want YouTube straight away.
So what if she says to me, "Gre, yo, you
have to become Christian." Nah. Nah, mate. No,
I don't really use Reddit anymore either
to be fair.
Why? Why am I going to go on Reddit, bro?
Why am I Why am I going to go on Reddit,
Dusty? What can Reddit tell me? H
what what can they tell me, bro? They're
[ __ ] biased. They There's double
There's one rule for one, one rule for
another. So what's the point? They make
excuses for women. So why why is anyone
going to ask them for advice?
Furthermore, why does men ask anyone for advice?
Dusty, why do men ask anyone for advice
knowing that the the double standards
that exist nowadays? Is there any advice
anyone could give anyone?
Cuz the chances are you're not going to
find an impartial person. So why? You
understand what I mean? you grey.
The amount of [ __ ] they used to say
about my text messages, bro. My text
messages were fine.
Like I said, there's there's rules when
it comes to men. There's certain rules
that go for men that don't apply to
women via texting.
And that when I was talking to Christian
Izzy, it really made me think of it. I
was going to do a video on it,
Greavvesy, a last video. So
yeah, what if someone speaks to you for
f for three months and they were just
using you for attention?
Say you met someone tomorrow. So what
what what then?
I think people need to wake up. But
yeah, that's why you can't ask them.
That's why you can't ask people for advice.
You can't ask people for advice.
The only thing you you have to do is
take like three, four months off of it
and that's it. Like me now, bro. When I
go out again, I go out again. I don't
really care what happens. I know the
game, bro. You see? I know. I know the
game. You get me?
Right. All right. Do you want to see the steak grievy?
He was trying to replace me with Tony,
wasn't you, Grevy? But it wasn't really
working, was it? It wasn't really
It wasn't working, lad. Yeah.
You already found your mama. Easy.
Yeah. I'm going to make my steak on mushrooms.
When are you going to go out on a piss? Crezy,
when are you going to go out on the
piss, lad? H
when are you going to go out? See, when
you got beggar banging these, you got
beggar begging these ugly women on
YouTube. Peter Belly has never had to do
such a thing.
Oh, bless you. Then one day in summer. Oh, bless.
Yeah, I'm going to make my [ __ ] steak
now. I'm hungry. Hungry.
I need to go to gym soon, bro. To be fair. Right. Yeah.
I'm going to make this thing, bro.
Have you been seeing that Canada Goose
uh trend going, Grezy? Everywhere I go
now, I see people wearing Canada Goose Canada goose.
Must be some sort of copycat trend. No.
Yeah, I see a lot of it, bro. colored
and you see that or maybe you won't see
it but yeah
this is copycats
you never ever follow trends
never ever ever have I followed a trend bro
yeah yeah but the thing is with no but
the thing is with color the goose it's
so obvious that people are copying with
it's like it's like it it's been going
for [ __ ] donkeys is and a lot of
tracks you don't like. But with the kind
of the goose, it's so obvious it's just
copying copying another person.
I I have a night track suit. We've got a
I've got a night track suit, lad.
No, I got a night track, bro. One sec.
Right. That's my steak.
I need to season it. I'm [ __ ]
starving, bro. Not even bad.
Put some black pepper on it.
Some black pepper. Salt.
How's that? How's that looking, boss?
Bet you didn't think you was going to be
getting a cooking video today, did you? We boss. and salt.
Yeah, see me, bro. I can't be like you
little virgins sat on YouTube all day.
Got ain't got a life.
But even when I'm on YouTube now, I'm
I'm I'm simply just cooking, aren't I?
Green. Simply just cooking.
have to put some butter on it.
I like you little virgins.
You're not right.
Still calling people M that are better
looking than you.
Still calling people M that's better
Damn. You people never change.
quite sad to be honest with you. Okay,
the steak goes under the grill now. Greasy. Okay,
I need to I need to cut the mushrooms now. Yeah. Yeah,
you still there, Greavves.
Can't believe you messaged me on
Instagram. Poor [ __ ]
At least someone cares about me.
You poor [ __ ] Poor [ __ ]
He messaged me.
>> He messaged me on Instagram. That's funny. One second.
Maybe when I meet Christian Izzy, we'll
do some live streams. Would that be okay
with you, boss?
Is that okay with you, boss?
So, I'm just slicing the mushroomies.
I found some digestive biscuits. Squeezy.
Yeah, I fancy some digestive biscuits.
Yeah, we need to stop these trends
though, Dusty. That calendar goose trend
is still going, you know.
It's so copying.
[ __ ] hate copycat trends, bro.
You seen it in it, Canada Goose. It's
just copying people that have got no
mind of their own. I just rock a Marty
jeans, sick silk coat. No one has my
style, bro. Cuz I'm not a little copycat.
I'm not a little You remember You
remember Grezy? You remember Grezy? You
remember Grezy? I'm I'm not My name's
not Grezy. I'm a little copycat.
My name is not Grezy. Look, just done
some mushroom slice some mushrooms. I'm
I'm not greedy. I'm a little copycat. >> Greasy.
Yeah, but the thing the best part is Dusty is
the best part is Dusty is they're only
wearing it to fit in. That's the thing
that they're only wearing them jackets
to fit in. They've got absolutely no
mind of their own.
You must have no mind of your [ __ ] own.
No mind of [ __ ] own. Imagine that.
And I don't mean like shop at the
[ __ ] charity shop where Virgin boy
goes, Dusty, the little shitty ugly
virgin globes that he wears. I mean you
can just wear like a Marley jeans, um
some vapor trainers, you know, six silk
coat, you know what I'm saying, bro? You
know, you can wear that kind of stuff.
>> You don't need to wear that cheap virgin
[ __ ] that he wears cuz he's too skimp to
afford anything decent.
Know what I'm saying, bro? There's other
things you can wear. Good quality. Not
that virgin [ __ ]
Oh [ __ ] I forgot my [ __ ] charger. [ __ ] virgin.
There he is.
I don't know whe to have a egg with the
steak or not.
What do you think, Grezy?
>> Oh, mate.
Want to start hitting the club soon
again soon. hit the clubs again soon.
Maybe March is so cold, is it?
It's so cold.
What's Why is it so high?
Yep. I'm cooking a delicious steak.
That's maybe why I don't look as
Maybe that's probably why I don't look as unhealthy
cuz I've been having like steaks and
stuff. I had a take I had a curry yesterday but Yeah, bro.
No double chins for me, lad. Not like these thous.
I can't believe Monty actually thinks.
Yeah, there's a lot of people jealous of
Well, say that they probably are
jealous. It's like I was saying earlier,
they probably are. Don't forget, a lot
of the people in this community are virgins.
>> A lot of the people in this community are virgins.
So they probably will though. Look at
look how desperate they are. They are
>> I ain't [ __ ] jealous of that though.
>> You know what? I think the only thing
you'd get from Natalie Yeah. I think the
only thing you you'd get from Natalie
Dia is like a [ __ ] if he was like a
100 Guinnesses in. Bro, I swear to God
if he was like a 100 Guinnesses in. I
think that maybe you'd get no job.
Yeah. No one cares what these fat ugly
people think. People are stupid. These
people ain't got a life. These people
are [ __ ] fat and ugly themselves. No
one cares what these people think.
They're self projectors. But yeah, the
only thing you'd get from Matt G, bro,
is a [ __ ] if he was 100 down. You
know, there's just some like [ __ ]
greavves that you wouldn't even that you
that you wouldn't even that you wouldn't
even um you wouldn't even [ __ ] them, bro. Like,
you wouldn't even [ __ ] them. You would
just get like a [ __ ] from them. I
don't need to show you, bro. You should
stop judging other men, you weirdo. You
should show everyone what you look like.
You should stop judging other men, you weirdo.
I don't have an I don't have any other
opinion than he's just a self-reflecting idiot.
That's the only opinion I've got is he's
a big self-reflector.
Is that right, Grezy?
You're just a big self-reflector.
I mean what else is there to say you know bro?
Yeah he will meet me. Well he never said
that because I'm subscribed to his
channel. So he never said that.
So stop making up rumors.
Monty never said anything like that
because I have some to his channel and
there's been nothing. So stop making up stuff.
Never said that. But I'll put the link
up anyways if people want to join.
Yeah. UK silent, bro. That's me and my
beard. I know, bro.
I know. It's lush, isn't it, bro? My beard's lush.
Yeah, my beard. What do you think of my
beard, M? I like it. I think it's sexy.
Me. Sexy beard, bro. I love my beard.
Oh [ __ ] Oh.
>> Yeah, man. He just needs to keep my out
of his car, you know.
Monty Monty calling people ugly.
I've been with more women than him. I've
said this multiple times as well. He
doesn't process in his thick brain, bro.
They've never looked like Kaye and
they've never looked like Natalie.
Why would I trim it up a bit, bro? I'm
not It's It's cold.
Why am I going to trim it up a bit? If I
go meet someone, I will. When I go out
again, I will.
Yeah, when I go out again, I will. But
I'm not going out for I don't know.
Well, I do go out, but I mean I'm drinking.
I'm just cooking this lost steak.
Oh, he's put a gambling video up. I've
been watching that. This is what you
should do, bro. You should bring it back
to [ __ ] 2015, man. Where you used to
do them gambling videos and stuff.
That's actually something to watch. Not
this back and forth calling people a
virgin when you were virgin yourself.
That's all boring, bro.
What is this community again? Grezy.
Right, the mushrooms on now.
Put the mushroom on. Now
I tell you what, I've been eating quite
a bit lately though, Grezy. The curries.
They're so addicting.
are addicting, bro. In the winter, they
addictive, man. They're so [ __ ] addictive.
What the [ __ ] Yeah,
I was looking at that thing yesterday again.
She's not [ __ ] as good as people was
[ __ ] making out. She was crazy. She
wasn't as good as people was making out she was.
I swear to God, bro. Sorry to bring it
up again. Nowhere [ __ ] near as good
as they're [ __ ] making it out. And
certainly not as [ __ ] And certainly
nowhere near as [ __ ] good to start
questioning people's [ __ ] sexuality
if they don't like her.
And what's that called? We being a what?
What's that called? Yeah,
I didn't know I was gay, bro.
I didn't know I was gay, bro. Jesus
Christ. I didn't know that.
I didn't know I was gay, you know.
Never. I didn't I never knew I was gay.
Cuz griev I've had like a guy in
Manchester before like follow me to my
hotel room and tried to get on the bed.
I've had so many offers. I mean I would
have thought at 28 28 years of [ __ ]
age you would have took them you would
have took someone up on their offer if
you was attracted to men. Would you
[ __ ] not? We see
I would have thought you would have took
someone up on their offer.
I'm not [ __ ] gay. The [ __ ]
How am I [ __ ] bro?
Well, I might get three pieces of
chicken today, Grezy, for the chicken shop.
Oh, it was years ago in Manchester. The
guy I couldn't It was hard to tell the
guy to go away. He kept um
he kept like following me about it. It
was weird, bro. I don't swing that way. Like,
sorry, I don't swing that way.
Nah, sorry, bro. I don't I don't I don't
I don't swing that way, lad. Nah,
this steak is looking quite nice.
Cooking the mushroom.
I like my steak a certain way. You know, Grezy,
but curry is my favorite food. Oh, you
should have saw me down in that
vindaloo, Grezy. I was a bit ill, by the
way, Grevy, the other day. I was a bit ill.
I could have done with a nice vindaloo
and a nice shot of Samuka.
That was that was fun. Will it? >> Yeah.
>> Remember chat GBTs? I was laughing
whilst I was reading it.
>> Would you like to see some more
Amsterdam videos? Greasy.
Go to uh you're not coming your band.
See you later. Like I said, we want
people that can have a genuine uh a
genuine debate, a genuine u conversation,
not self projectors. Like we want like normal combo, right?
Projecting fat looking people.
We don't have them people in our channel, lad.
We don't have them people on our channel, sunshine.
Well, I'm going to season it one more
time. This lovely steak
waiting on the mushrooms down there.
You know what I'm saying? You're not
coming in. See you later. Are you s bastard?
>> They're not coming in. I'm not stupid
like wanting to let [ __ ] read on.
>> Oh [ __ ]
Sorry about that, lad.
The mushrooms are still cooking.
Should I have an egg with it? Should I not? Nah.
Sometimes I have an angle sometimes.
Most of the time I don't.
Depends how my stomach is, you know.
Can't do some cheeky [ __ ] asked me if
I lost [ __ ] weight. Fat to begin
with. The only people that was saying
that I was fat and [ __ ] porky and
that was people that were obese themselves.
So, it's it's a copycat community.
It's a copycat community, but it's also
a self-reflecting community
where people talk about their own lives
and they're [ __ ] good at it as well.
Oh, did you see? Hey, I agree. Yeah,
LJ's apparently gambling. Yeah. On on
the on the live stream and now all of a
sudden Timmy's put gambling videos up.
What does that tell you?
Yeah. Oh, that's why he's starting to
put he's putting these videos up.
Oh, that makes sense. [ __ ] copycat, dude.
That's good now. That's why. Oh,
be ready in a minute. I'm starving. Oh god. No.
That is delicious.
Do you like to taste boss? >> No.
>> Come on. You have to wait.
I put some black pepper on specially for you.
No, that's No, look. Yeah.
That's not blood, is it? Yeah.
He's been touching.
Is it nice?
That's a nice bit of steak. Hey, cheers. Yeah, man. about it.
More chicken. What? Because she's sick.
What a bit of a chance.
It's a nice one. Ladies,
my mom doesn't like you on YouTube, but
I can't deprive your content. Far like
you want to see what I made my neighbor. Oh [ __ ] Um,
do you think
I can eat that in about 2 minutes, bro?
Tell you what. Yeah.
This is how you're supposed This is how
I like steak here. I like it a little
bit pink, but no blood.
Little bit pink,
but no blood. I like most people. So you um
why Timmy put a gambling video up
as soon as LJ started gambling?
L gambling and all of a sudden Timmy's
put a gambling video up.
Bit strange though. H
that's [ __ ] weird, is it?
Any opinions on that?
I don't What a [ __ ] I haven't uploaded video month.
Any opinions or no?
Almost finished this crazy. M
have a couple of cups after this.
That's probably why my body looks better
cuz I eat lots of steak now, don't I?
Well, I eat lots of steak.
I look better with it.
Would you like to see the plate now? Grezy boss,
would you like to see it now, boss? What about
That was yummy.
You know why? So, I wasn't rushing on
purpose. I just actually really enjoy
it. I'm uh
where I've got um where I've got clear
airways uh where I don't smoke, I've got
clear airways, so I can't turn on from
food. You see, I can swallow that.
How did that statement look with you? [ __ ] D. Yeah.
Oh, lovely. That steak was lush.
That steak is [ __ ] beautiful.
I could live I could live off steak, you
know, I could actually live off of it.
I like savo chips though. I'm trying to
cut down on like the chips and stuff,
the coms, the savoy and whatever, but
like the sub lawyers, but bit hard.
Oh, has my mama messaged me?
Who's my new mama, Grezy?
Who's my new mama?
I've got a new mama, don't I? Or no,
lovely couple of [ __ ]
I can eat to stay properly now cuz I got
no tooth problems.
Is that cute? Let's see if my mama moves. Yep.
my little collection. Collection.
So, would you would you say that there's
would you say there's a there's a
there's a there's a lot of white knights
on Reddit then? Would you say there's a
lot of white knights on Reddit?
They did a lot of simps.
Oh, that was [ __ ] the business. Now
I've got a lovely cup of [ __ ]
I don't know why I always like a cup of
[ __ ] after I've ate, you know,
just goes down nicely.
Okay, but do do you agree with me
though, Greasy? how it's one rule for
one and one rule for another. Like you
try to meet a woman within four days.
Oh, you're moving too fast. You're
moving too fast. Yeah. Yeah. Even if you
speak to them for a month, they can
still [ __ ] ghost you and not meet
you. But then when a woman wants to meet
a guy straight away, there's no problem.
Literally, it's like I was saying to you
before, USA's first message to me was
her first message to me was
um hi, do you want to meet on Tuesday?
Hi, do you want to meet on Tuesday? Does
Tuesday work? First message, first SMS
message. But yet, when I want to meet
somebody in 5 days, they say that I'm
coming on too strong.
It's not fair, Gregy. It's not fair.
Why is it one rule for one and one rule for another?
Yeah. It doesn't matter if she was on holiday.
She doesn't I mean yeah she was on
holiday but I mean
there's people that I'm sure there's
other people that I've met as soon as possible.
Okay so let's okay I can let me try and
think of someone else.
I'm sure there has been other people,
bro, where I've met
where I've um
where I've um where I've met them quickly.
I'm sure there's been other people.
Sure there has.
Definitely definitely sure there has been.
But it doesn't really matter though,
does it Grezy? Cuz like I said, there's
nothing wrong with speaking to someone
for a week and trying to meet them after
a week in my opinion.
Cuz if someone's generally I feel like they
they're either going to meet you or
they're not going to meet you. You don't
understand with Christian Izzy, bro.
She's very she's got a lot of stuff
going on. I'm not going to tell you
exactly what's going on, but she's we
speak all the time and that, bro,
whereas these other people are not. So
why the [ __ ] or
you know it's like
but either way if you try to meet
someone quick they'll say you're trying
to meet them too quickly. If you're
trying to meet them too slow then
they'll say that oh you're not fast
enough. So, what I'm what I'm saying,
Greavesy, is if you ask people for
advice, they're going to they're either
they're always going to tell you you're wrong.
Even if you do the opposite thing of
what they tell you, right, they're going
to tell you that you're still doing it wrong.
They're always going to make excuses for
them. So, I don't think there's no point
in asking anyone for advice, you know.
I still I still don't see the point to
be honest with you.
What who's who's going to give you
genuine advice, Grezy? What? 10% of
people, 15% of people.
Who Who Who's going to give you it then? 15%.
Maybe you'll get 15% of people that will
give you genuine advice,
but that's about it, bro. maybe 20%. Maximum.
So, what I mean, if you went on Reddit
right now, they would just So, they
react differently, Greezy. Uh, they're different reactions.
They're different. Yeah, but they're
just Yeah, but they're just going to
white night though because they don't
understand your situation.
Like, here's the thing. Okay, Grezy.
Here's the thing, right? Here's the
thing. you like they react differently.
So, some of them will go mad. If you
show like a woman doing you dirty,
they'll just go mad and just start
blaming you. Or some of them will just
dismiss your struggles. Some of them
will um say that like you're moving too
fast and then when you move slower, they
still [ __ ] you over anyways. So, they
react differently. It depends.
But, bro, I I was saying it yesterday. I
wasn't ready yesterday. I still can't
stand women. I still hate them. You
know, I'm only giving this [ __ ] newy
the the benefit of the doubt. I still
feel the way I do. I just don't say it.
I don't know how any normal person
can't. To be honest with you, I I don't
know how how any normal person that
isn't completely brainwashed can can sit
there and and defend them. Bear in mind,
I've had women and I've had sex. So, I
mean, I'm not a virgin. So, I mean, how
anyone can can sit there and defend them
the way they do is beyond me when
they're worse than men, but people still do it.
It's weird. I when I went out last when
I was doing approaches last the the
first went out, there was a lot of [ __ ]
Yeah, I was on I was on Reddit. Yeah. Days ago.
Yeah. Days ago, bro. And that was the
first time in ages.
But their attitude has got worse. I
don't know how they can bear in mind
I've got a life. Uh you you understand
Grievy is that I've got a life. So
aren't I being unbiased if I've been
with women and I've had sex and I don't
understand how people can sit there and
and defend them. They are proper [ __ ] bro.
They really really are proper [ __ ]
And that's that's an unbiased opinion.
And people still sit there and defend
them like they don't do these things. It's weird. >> So
>> I had one on I had someone on Reddit say
that there's still good women out there.
I said, "No, they're [ __ ] bloody,
isn't?" Yeah, you can stay in the
background. You're not coming in.
They'll teach you for being a dirty,
stinky copycat. Copying L J gambling.
LJ was gambling and now you're putting
gambling videos up. You stinky dirty copycat. [ __ ] meow.
What a stinking dirty copycat.
[ __ ] absolutely no mind of your own.
Look at this Grezy. One month ago, he
put a gambling video up until today when
L when he found out L was gambling. And
all of a sudden, he's put quite a few videos up.
Hm. Bit strange, isn't it?
You've got absolutely
You've got absolutely no mind of your own.
>> You little copycat. Are you a little copycat?
>> From Smokey B.
>> Uh, stop talking [ __ ] to me. Why are you
a little copycat?
>> [ __ ] I said to you, meet me today. You
>> Bye-bye. We don't get into these
autistic repeating arguments. That's
what I mean. You can't have a normal conversation, bro.
You can't have a normal conversation.
So yeah. Anyways, what I was saying,
Grezy, is they they still defend them
like they're not complete [ __ ]
Do they do it because they think women
are going to sleep with them
by defending them? Do they think women
are going to [ __ ] them or cuz the irony
is, Grezy, is the people that do all of
this are always people that have had
less women than you. That's how tragic
the whole thing is is that there always
people that women don't like.
Oh, I would have loved that guy to come
up to me on that TikTok, bro. I would
have said, "Yes, I am harassing people
and I'll keep doing it." Even though I
wasn't doing it, I would say, "Yes, I
am. You dirty little scumbag little
white knight. I'm the biggest world's
I'm the world's greatest harasser by
your own [ __ ] I'd love, you know, I'd
love someone to come up to me and do
that, bro. If I'm approaching someone, I
would love someone to do that to me.
I'd say yes, I'm [ __ ] damn right
harassing girls and you're going to do
nothing about it, white knight. That's
what I'd say. Just to be a [ __ ] because
I don't like white knights. I don't like simps
really. Well, I did comment on it, lad.
I did. I don't like that white knight
and [ __ ] I don't like it because the
thing is, Grezy, when you know what
these people are about women and stuff,
it's like they're defending them like
they're [ __ ] babies.
You don't you you you don't you won't
understand, bro. You won't understand.
But yeah, they're trying to defend them
when they're they're worse than men.
Women are worse than men and then they
got people defending them.
So, it's weird. But yeah,
I've already been with women, bro. I
never asked for your advice.
And there's plenty of people that live
with their mom that are in
relationships. So yeah, I mean women
absolutely do go near me and I've had
more women than you. But thanks for your
uh 2 p to be fair, bro.
Do you actually think that that's the
way women are? You know what? I'm not
even going to explain myself to retards.
This is why I don't really come on here
to be honest with you, Grezy lad. I just
can't be bothered. It's just the same
[ __ ] They the people on here are just retards.
They have absolutely no clue about women
and they have absolutely no clue about life.
They're clueless like Cludo the dog,
bro. They know nothing about women. It's
the same thing with in in with Reddit.
They've got no clue about anything. It's
It's tragic, bro. It's actually quite tragic.
Yeah. Yeah, bro. Whatever. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm not going to argue with you, bro. I
don't argue with idiots.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Exactly. Yeah.
You keep telling yourself that, bro. I'm
not explaining myself because all the
the same conversation I've already had before.
Um, HS and M. No, no, Ed Matthews. There
has been people trying to white night.
No, there has been, bro. There has been
in Ed Matthews.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro.
You keep telling yourself that. I'm not
having the same argument. I'm not having
the same conversation. I've already
explained all of this stuff before.
people living with their mom and then
there's another excuse and yeah we've
been through this before I'm not having
the same argument the same conversation
if you want to keep thinking that
so be it bro that's on you um there's a
double standard Ed yeah but yeah no
people have tried white knight and Ed Matthews bro
that has no no it has happened bro if
you watch the kick streams it has happened
and the people that don't do it they see
him as a threat
Yeah, bro. You keep thinking that. That
just shows that you don't know anything about women.
Yeah, that just shows that you don't
know anything about women if you think a
woman would go with somebody that lives
with their mom. Okay, bro. Yeah. Okay,
whatever. You keep thinking that loud.
You keep white nighting and singing
women and see where that gets you.
Because you know what? These people,
Grezy, will be on their deathbed at 90
years of age. And all that time that
they've wasted defending women, sticking
up for women, and women don't like them,
they will never like them, and they
don't sleep with them, they're never
going to get that time back. So really,
the jokes are on them. But listen,
Reezy, they don't they tend to not white
night if they see the person as a threat.
No, no, no. You, it's not about Ed
Matthews. It's like, okay, so if they
see someone as a threat, right, they're
not going to intervene. Like I've had it
before where people have tried white
night and I told them to [ __ ] off. Yeah.
It's the same people as or when they've
tried to get involved with something and
then they've stopped their [ __ ] because
they know that anyone that will give it
back to them, they're not going to do
that. And obviously, you know what I'm saying?
It's like them people that was on the
chair. They they stood they stood they
stayed they stayed um sat down and they
shut the [ __ ] up.
Yeah. They stayed at their they they
they stayed at sat chair and they shut
the [ __ ] up because they knew they
couldn't do anything.
Yeah, bro. You keep telling yourself
that. Yeah, you keep telling yourself that, bro.
No one cares. You shouldn't even be
worried about where I live. It's none of
your business. Worry about your own
life. You shouldn't care about where I
live, where I don't live. You need to
worry about your own life. You little
sad acts sat on YouTube 24/7 ain't got a
life. You need to worry about your own
sadistic, sad, pathetic lives before
trying to talk about other people. This
is why I don't come on here much
anymore, Greasy, bro.
It's the same [ __ ]
Yeah. You're not right about anything,
brother. You're not right about
anything. Yeah. You're on your break. Of
course you are. Yeah. Yeah. Of course
you are. Same [ __ ] Same people.
You don't know nothing. You don't know
nothing about women. You don't know nothing.
But I find it weird, G. But all of these
people that defend women, you've been
with more women than them. You've had
more women than them and they still try
to preach to you. It's mad. They defend
women, but women hate them. And you
can't. And you can't. No matter how many
times you say it, women don't like you.
And no matter how many times you tell
them, they still stick up for them.
They will still sit and defend women,
but women would never get with them.
They hate them more than they hate
anyone that they're arguing with.
They're bro it's some I'm telling you
it's some it's something that their
fathers put in their head at a young age
think about it bro your both of your
parents died right whatever my dad died
if you think about it bro I would say
most people have got their their fathers
are still alive I reckon bro I reckon I
reckon that it's something that their
dad has put into their head at a young
age what do you think
yeah well there are plenty people that
are in their 30s living at home and get
women. You don't know nothing, lad. The
pattern's in your head. Trust me, bro.
The pattern is in your head.
The pattern is literally in your head.
You don't know nothing.
Go white night somewhere else, lad. The
pattern is in your head that you're
noticing. It's not in the outside world,
bro. It's in your head. You don't know nothing.
These bro that the these people are so
pathetic. They're so they're lying to
themselves, bro. They really really are.
Bro, I've had more women than you. Ask
yourself why you're struggling with
women and you're pretending that you got a girlfriend.
Why don't you have a woman? Why have I
had more Why have I had more women than
you? You need to ask yourself that
question. Why have I been with more
birds than you would ever have? If what
you're saying is right, why have I been
with more women than you? You need to
ask yourself that question. Why are you
on it pretending that you've got a
girlfriend for 12 years and pretending
that you got a job? Think about it, bro.
If you're if you're at work right now,
come up come up on the panel and show us
you at work. Simple as that.
Yeah, of course you do, bro. Come on the
panel and show us you at work. And I'm
not going to respond to you if you don't
um if you don't do that. You're saying
you're at break. Yeah. You're saying
that you you're at your break. Yeah. Okay, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. Come on. Come on the paddle.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, man. Come on the paddle.
But yeah, I think it's people's dads
that have brainwashed them at a young age. Grievy.
I think it's it's the father figure that
brainwashed them at a young age.
Yeah, of course it is. H Shut up, man.
You don't have a girlfriend. You don't
have a job. Shut up. You don't know nothing.
These people are [ __ ] There's nothing
wor There's nothing more pathetic than a
white guy in a s.
I definitely You know what I'm saying?
Nothing more pathetic than a white
knight in a simp
because you know the thing is Gregy,
right? If I if I keep you know what I'm saying?
Whatever happens, right? Say like
whatever happens, my opinion is never
going to change. It's never ever ever
ever going to change. You do realize that
what you're white and I over women, bro.
Like the opinion is never ever ever
going to change no matter what. You do
realize that. I just don't talk about it anymore.
I hate the whole dating thing, the whole
women thing, the whole double standards.
cuz I hate all of it.
I hate all of it, bro.
That's probably why you sent me that
[ __ ] because you you knew I was going to
react to it. I hate white lights. I hate
all of that [ __ ] I hate men that try to
look good for women.
You know what? You know you know what
I'm like, bro. You know,
bro. Yeah, man. Hello.
you really know how to get me going,
don't you, Greasy lad?
I might have to block you on Instagram.
must be brainwashed at a very young age.
Griezy, I hate that white nighting. Do
you know? I think that is what will
really get me in trouble one day, bro.
If someone's going to try and white
and I think I'm just going to Do you
remember that American that tried doing
it, bro? The O'Neils.
He's like, "Oh, don't talk to her." I
said, "I'll talk to you the [ __ ] I want
in my own country. Thanks, [ __ ]
stupid little cunt."
And he said, "Oh, you're you're a big
man, are you?" I said, "Yeah, I'm a big
man when I'm talking to you." Yeah.
Yeah, I am. And there was about and
there was about six of them.
But, bro, never the way I the way I come
across, bro, the way I act now, it would
never happen. I don't think it would
Oh, there's just been some white knights
in the past, isn't it? Obviously
people that try to look good for women
when women don't like them. Embarrassing.
Nons does it as well. Nons does it as
well. Um Grezy,
he whites he white knights women.
It doesn't matter what position they're
in in life, they will still do it. They
could be virgins. They could actually be
well he is a virgin but I mean they
could be proper proper proper virgins
never in a relationship never even
kissed anyone and they'd still defend
women grievy they would still defend
women because they because they've got
no mind of their own they don't go
outside and exper and and and create
their own experiences
I can't defend them because of the way
that they are greasy do you understand
because of the way that they literally
are bro the for the reason I'm not
[ __ ] over this. Um, I've lived by
myself and it doesn't make a difference.
That's why I don't entertain the same
boring argument, lad. And I'm not an
incel. I've had more women than you will
ever have, lad. The only incel is you.
You fat ugly people begging women on the
internet. Use the incelss, not me, lad.
And I've lived by myself. I've worked.
It makes literally no difference. That's
just the norm. People that live by
themselves and they work as the norm.
That's not going to get someone a woman.
They're not going to jump in your bed
because you live by yourself, bro. Come
on. You don't know nothing. That's why I
don't get into these pointless
arguments, pointless debates, cuz you
got you don't know nothing. Who am I to
try to convince a bunch of [ __ ] white
knight losers? Who am I to try to convince you?
White night losers that have got no clue
about life. If you want to think the way
you think, that's on you, bro. I don't care. You know,
you've got no clue about women. And I'm
not your teacher. I'm not here to I'm
not um I'm not here to educate you. I'm
not your teacher.
Yeah. I don't want to have this
conversation with you, bro, to be honest
with you, because I know different and I
don't want to convince you anything and
I don't want you to convince me anything.
I don't really care. I don't give a [ __ ]
about them. I'm only speaking to one
person now and that's it, Grezy.
And if she does [ __ ] me over, which I
don't think she is, I'm done. I'm done,
bro. It's going to be more than 3 months now.
Yeah, I took three months off it. I
don't care. I literally don't even know
why we're talking about it. I don't
care. I know what they're like.
I know what they're about.
Not really, bro. Because you're just
talking about yourself. You are forever
single. You're the one pretending that
you got a girlfriend. Listen, bro.
Listen, listen. This is what I'm saying
to money, bro. Anything that you're
trying to say to me, it applies to
yourselves. So, the self-p projection is
not going to get at me. Whatever you're
saying about me is just about yourself.
Ugly, fat, no girlfriend. You people are
sat on YouTube 24/7. It's not going to
bother me. What you say is not going to
bother me, lad. You're not going to say,
"Yo, your [ __ ] calendar." You people
have showed, we've seen your looks,
we've seen you on YouTube 24/7. I've got
the evidence I need. Simple. I don't
nothing you're saying is going to make
me say, "Oh,
because I know the truth about you
people. No life, no girlfriend, no
family." That's why it doesn't bother
me. I literally can't get mad at it,
lad. Oh, it does make it true. It Well,
I'll put the link up right now and you
can come on then. If I'm wrong, if I'm
wrong, prove me wrong. Simple as that.
Then, if I'm wrong, prove me wrong. If
you're not fat and you're not ugly and
you're Show me what you've got in your
life, then, okay, [ __ ] all the looks and
[ __ ] Come on the panel right now and
show me what you've got in your life.
Come on. I'm not saying it. I know it.
You know what I'm saying? Grezy. I don't
say it. I know it. I know about you
people. How many times have you people
been doxed for your ugliness on air that
has come on here for years talking about
other people's looks only for you to be
ugly? I know it. I'm not saying it. I
know it, brother. I'm not saying it. I know it.
Because why else would you be sat on YouTube 24/7
with no life? If you got this perfect
life, why are you sat on YouTube 24/7?
You still can't answer me, bro. This is
my first time back on here in 8 days.
Cuz Monty was mentioning my [ __ ] name
the prick. Why are you on YouTube 24/7
if you've got this life? That's
something that you're never going to be
able to answer anyone cuz you know I'm
right. You know I'm right cuz you're fat
ugly ass people trying to bring people
down to your depressed level. I know
this stuff. I know the tricks of the
trades of what you people do. Yeah.
That's it, lad.
I know the tricks and the trades of what
you fat ugly people do on here 24/7 more
than anyone will ever know. No, I'm not
his mate, bro. I haven't been his mate
for [ __ ] months.
I don't even talk about the guy and he
starts mentioning my [ __ ] name.
I haven't been his friend for [ __ ]
months. He tried to blame me um because
Natalie G broke up with him because he
went on a night out with me
and that was my fault apparently. So I
was like, "Oh, [ __ ] you then. Simple.
No, I haven't been his friend for
months, bro. The [ __ ] He's an idiot.
Why do you think he can't come in? cuz
he knows I'm right. He can talk behind
people's back, but he ain't going to
[ __ ] say anything to me to my face, bro
on on a panel cuz he knows I'm correct.
He knows I'm right.
All right. You want to slag off Monty?
Ma'am, brother, stop asking me your
little self-p projecting questions. I'm
not answering your little
self-reflecting gay questions, lad.
Take it somewhere else. Yeah, I've been
with more women than you have and you
will ever have. Go ask yourself that
question and then you'll find out the
answers as to why you're on YouTube 24/7
with no life. Would a woman date you?
Clearly not, cuz you ain't got a girlfriend.
Simple. Women wouldn't date you. Stop
self-projecting. Take the self-p
projection away from my channel.
You got no girlfriend. You got ugly
looks, brother. It's you you're talking
about. I don't know how many times, bro.
My mom don't count. No, but your mom
counts and she's one to the body count.
I've not had my mom, but I've had your
mother and I'm sure your mom definitely
counts cuz she was sucking my dick and
licking my ass last night. So, your mom
definitely definitely counts.
My mom don't count, but your mom counts.
Your mom's a lot fitter as well.
Sorry, mate. You you literally open up a
can of worms for yourself there, lad.
Mine don't, but yours does. And your
mom's a lot more fitter than mine. So,
yeah. Okay. Well, when you finish your
make believe job tomorrow then, uh
later, you can come on the Hangouts and
show me all of what you've got then,
can't you? Yeah.
You can show me all of what you got
then, can't you?
You sad little simp bastard.
Little white knight. I wasn't calling my
mom fit. I was calling his mom fit. I
was calling his mom fit. If you if you listen properly.
Yeah, man. Okay.
I'm going to come off now and I'll be
back later. And you're going to join?
Yeah. Later. Okay.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, look what you've got me into now, Greavvesy.
How does How does she sound so far?
Christian is Greavvesy.
She was telling me some stuff, bro.
23 messages at 2:00 in the morning.
2:00 in the [ __ ] morning.
I still won't defend them, bro. I still
won't defend them, lad. No. Yeah.
I don't know how people do defend them,
but they do.
They do defend them, don't they, Greavves?
But yeah, the only people that haven't
stopped uh HS and stuff is because they
they see them as a threat.
You understand? So, they kind of
contradict themselves, Grezy, because
they don't like people that go for
women, but they won't go for anyone
that they deem as a threat. Does that make sense?
Does that make sense what I'm saying, Grezy?
Like, and I don't mean necessarily they
need to be big.
Like, no one has ever started on Why do
you think I've been up and down the
country and no one has ever started on me? Because
it's not necessarily that I can fight or
I'm strong. It's just they know that
they they wouldn't be able to go there.
Think about it. There was this guy,
Greavvesy. I saw him Weather Spoons. I
got his number and I'm sure I was
trolling him. And this guy is bigger
than me. He goes to the gym. Not much
much bigger, but he's bigger. I'm sure
he could beat me up maybe. I don't know.
And I'm sure I was trolling him.
Obviously didn't think I was going to
see him again. Um,
and I don't know what I I can't remember
exactly what I said. I know I said
something and he saw me. He just talked
to me normally, bro.
Because it's the way you carry yourself.
You don't understand. It's the way that
you carry yourself. So if they see that
you're I can't explain it. They're not going to
Why do you think Do you remember the the
argument in the Weather Spoons uh in the
actual Weather Spoons with the
Australian? Why do you think their
mother guys didn't really say much? Cuz
they knew they wouldn't win.
White Knights are also opportunists. If
they're not, then fair [ __ ] play. But
most of them are, bro.
Think about it, bro. Do you think if
Mike Tyson was harassing a load of women
on the street, anyone's going to go up
to Mike Tyson and say, "Oh, leave the
women alone." Do you think anyone's
going to do that, bro? Oh, picking on
girls. Do you think anyone's going to
say that to Mike Tyson, bro? Do you
think anyone's going to say that to The
Rock? You think anyone's going to say
that to John Cena?
Do you think anyone's going to say that
to [ __ ] Muhammad Ali? I don't think so.
I don't think so, lad. You know,
so they're opportunists.
They're opportunists, lad.
So many white knights. So many white knights, lad.
Anyway, what's your [ __ ] problem with
my [ __ ] beard, Grezy lad?
I like my beard. It's not even that long.
He's going to the barbers again soon.
Spider-Man had a baby with Mary Jane.
Oh, that's funny, bro. It
been washed a couple of times now. Easy.
Yeah. I don't want a collection. I just
want to find someone that's [ __ ] normal.
Is that too much to ask?
someone that's not a complete bullshitter.
Someone that's not a complete
bullshitter, but I still either way,
like I told you, regardless of my
situation, I would never defend them
because I know what they're like and I'm not brainwashed.
I'm not brainwashed, Grezy. So, no
matter what situation I'm in,
relationship, no relationship, virgin,
bagging 20 women a day, it doesn't
matter what situation I'm in, I know the
truth and I know what they're like. But
I wouldn't defend them ever, you know.
But that's that like
just don't believe in it. Cuz the thing
is it's not like they're babies. If it's
kids, kids are innocent. Greavesy. Yeah.
So let's just say a child that can't
defend himself or whatever. Someone's
picking on kids, then okay. But women
are not innocent.
They're not innocent. They'll never be
innocent. And if anything, they're worse
than men. So why have we got all of
these people defending them? That's my
problem with it. You know, so
that's the way I see it, bro.
What was that guy doing on TikTok?
Wasn't he just approaching them or something?
Wasn't he just approaching them? Yeah, man.
Approaching them, wasn't he? Greasy. Little collection. Bless you.
Bless you then, Greg. If you're going to
go to little quiz night,
welcome up to a message. How's
Christian? I thought someone on YouTube found her.
Yeah. I don't know why people defend women
when they're nothing but [ __ ] I don't
know why people defend them, but they do. Yeah.
Yeah. He had a connection. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, I'll come back and I'm and
I'm gone after today again for a bit,
bro. For Monday today, I'm not doing
anything. So, yeah. But that will be it.
That'll be it, lad. For a while. So,
yeah. We watch some of these videos that
Timmy's put up.
Yeah. I'll be back at um 4, bro. Yeah.
Maybe a bit later. Five, six.