Won't be long.
Don't expect this to be like an hour or
two hours. Won't be long. Nope.
Oh, I love this little thing I'm on.
It's actually quite cute.
Okay, so you actually are at work. Won't be long.
UK asylum. You can't take one day off of
YouTube, lad. You're the one You're the
one that can't take a day off of
YouTube. Not me, lad. Um, already been
proven. But anyways, um, I was thinking,
do you know what? Maybe I could add some
people to my collection today.
Go out and start the collection. But I'm
kind of on a uh detox. So,
I was going to go and cuz I've not got
any people with uh any I haven't got
anyone with curly hair. I was speaking
to somebody on on on on on the gram and
I'm thinking, do you know what? I've
never actually [ __ ] with someone that
has had had that's got curly hair or had
curly hair. So, I'm thinking that could
also be, you know, someone to to add to
the collection. you know. Um, and that's
that. No, I'm not going at it with that
virgin, bro. I said what I had to say
and that's it. No, no, no, no, no, bro.
Steven Howard wanted me to do a video
yesterday, so I thought, yeah. No, I'm
not going back and forth, bro. I'm not
going back and forth. No, no, that was
just a one-off, lad. Um, no.
Going for a [ __ ] haircut.
No, I'm not going to have my haircut until next week,
maybe. Yeah, I'm not I'm not [ __ ]
getting my haircut.
Nope. Might go women collecting today, Mr. Bean.
I'm not sure. I might go women collecting.
I don't have anyone with curly hair, and
that's a problem,
Mr. Bean. That's a That's a big problem.
So, I might go out today. Don't lie. No,
I'm joking. I won't, bro. I'm on I'm on a detox.
I don't like to drink that much. You You
see? Um that's that, bro. So,
nope. No gambling.
Well, I gambled yesterday with um the
free spins that they gave me. Turned it
into £57 and I couldn't complete the wagering requirements
cuz it's it was too much.
Like I said a million times, bro. But
that's how you know it's rigged. Isn't
it funny how you can turn £4 into
[ __ ] almost 60 quid when it's not
your money? But then when whenever it's
raw money, your cash.
I know. I need to stop drinking Coke to
be honest, man. I do need to stop. That
reminds me. So then and then when it's
your own money, raw money, you never win.
What the [ __ ] bro?
But no, no gambling, bro. No gambling.
That's how you know it's rigged. What's
the chances?£4 to60 on roulette.
What's the chances, bro? What's the
chances? Yeah. When you put 100, 150 and
you can't even double your [ __ ] money.
You can't even double it.
So, yeah, it's [ __ ] bro. >> Nope.
Go lovely in my little collection.
They would go lovely. They could sit in
between Sig and in between USA
just like Jar sits in between Yoda and R2-D2.
You understand? UK asylum. You could go
right in in between them.
Lovely. There's always there's always
room for more collections, you know,
just like Grezy collects Spongebob DVDs. Yep.
All right. I found out something new um
last night. UK asylum. I found out that
that this Trump that people was talking
about, his name is Donald Trump
and he's uh he's the president of
America. I didn't even know that until
last night. I I kept hearing this guy
Trump Trump. I thought it was some sort
of [ __ ] like instrument or something
and then I've gone and looked him up and
I was like, "Oh [ __ ] is that what they
were talking about?" See, I'm a bit
behind on all of these things. You see,
I'm a bit behind. Yeah,
I'm a bit behind, lad. No, I didn't know at all.
Nope. I didn't know at all.
Didn't know who the [ __ ] he was.
Yeah, man. I I didn't know who it was. No.
Yeah, man. I've got autism. I've got
agrophobia. I've got everything. Me?
I've got literally everything.
How did you know, bro? You're you're
you're a good doctor. I feel like going
to um I feel like going to a club today.
There's a certain club I feel like
hitting up. But sorry, mate. Peter
Belly's on a detox.
I mean, yeah. I've got every condition,
bro. Didn't you know that? I'm not like
you people normal. I'm not like you
people on here sat on YouTube 24/7
talking about people that you don't know
for 15 years every day. I mean, we can't
all be normal like you people, bro. Jesus Christ
sat on YouTube
every day for 15 years writing the same comments.
Not everyone can be normal like these
people. Greavvesy, leave me alone. Leave
me alone. Leave me alone. All right,
Grez. I'm on Instagram and I was
speaking to this woman and I I can't
stop looking at her hair. Her hair is
very, very curly. And that made me
think, do you know what? I've never had
somebody that's got curly hair,
Grezy. So maybe I need to add one of
them people to my collection. Somebody
with curly hair.
What's your opinion on that, Grezy?
A new addition, a new collection to the family.
A new addition to the collection family. Grezy. Yep.
Just a collection.
Just a little collection.
What do you think of that, Grezy?
A little collection. Yep.
I need to find somebody that's got curly
hair. Won't take long.
Rezy won't take long.
Um, what I was saying is, um,
I was saying something I forgot, lad. Yeah, man.
Yeah, man. Like I said, we can't all be
normal like you people.
We can't all be
We can't all be normal like you people
sat on YouTube for 15 years talking
about people that you don't know every
day. I can't We can't all be normal like
you, man. [ __ ] sake. Leave me alone now, man.
Yeah, I was on Reddit today. Agree. I I
wonder what question Izzy would have to
say about me collecting some new people.
Should I ask her? Never
going to continue.
Did you like that, Gre? I'm not going to
stay away. I'm going to continue.
Stay the hell away from us. No, I'll
never stay away.
It's like Coca-Cola. It's an addiction.
I'm drinking a can of Coke right now, Grezy.
Two cinnamon swirls for breakfast. Lovely.
Feel like going out today and causing
some carnage. You know when you're in
one of them moods, Grezy, where you just
want to cause chaos? You know,
I have to be good on a little detox. So, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. My the video griev is on the
main channel, lad.
It's on the It's on the main channel, bro. Yeah,
it was on the main channel, bro.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah, you was looking on the um the disc
channel where I go live. Nah, bro.
Well, that was just a one-off, bro.
There's no going back and forth with
these with with these with these people,
bro. That was that was all all I had to
say. That's it.
I said everything I had to say. So,
have I seen what Greavvesy looks like?
No, I haven't actually. What do you look
like, Grezy? Can you put yourself on
camera, please, if right now if you don't mind? Oh gosh.
right now if you don't mind. Ret the
Bear. I got Rupet the Bear trousers. Greavvesy.
Rupit the Bear for new prime minister. Get in.
Why do I talk to him? Um
because he's a lovely little fellow.
Why can't I talk to Greavves? He's a
lovely little Stitch fan.
I could ask you people the same
question. Why do you go on Laura J's
talking [ __ ] every time he goes live?
I mean, no one's really to ask anyone
anything on here, really, are they?
I mean, I find what you people do so
weird. But I'm not going to repeat
myself cuz I've said everything I've had to say.
Yeah, that's what I that's exactly what
I just said back to him. That's what I
just said to Greavves. I literally just
said the same thing. Why do they go on L
J's and they're all scared to meet him?
That's that's literally what I just
said. Why do they type [ __ ] about people all day?
They go on large J's and they they talk
about people that they don't know every day.
There's no sense to this. There's no
sense to this community.
You try to make sense out of it, you're
going to actually lose brain cells.
Isn't that right, Greavves? If you try
to find sense in this community. Yeah.
If you if you um try to find sense in
this community, you you're just going to
lose brain cells.
bit like the video that I said I made last night.
>> Yeah, of course you have, bro. Of course you have. I find
I find this community to be very very weird.
Why do you think most people are blocked? Grievy,
this community is so weird.
It is a weird weird community, bro. Okay. Mhm.
Okay, bro. Your point is
So, when are you on YouTube actually
going to get a life anyways? How long
you been on this shitty community?
I'm actually not going out today, bro.
Man, we've heard all this before, bro.
This is boring.
Yeah, man. I don't know who Emma is. So, no.
Don't know who that is. And I don't need
luck. I don't I don't try to get with
women on the internet. I'm not a s.
I'm not a white knight.
So yeah, I don't even know who that is.
I I'm not a s like your master lad.
No, I spoke about white knights and simps. So yeah,
my day. No, never. Ah,
no no no no no,
dude. Who the [ __ ] is that? One second.
Let me just go a new channel.
Bro, these people just make up mad [ __ ]
Yo, you can be on my Instagram all you want.
I don't I don't try to get with women on Instagram.
Who the [ __ ] is that? I've just gone on that.
Jesus Christ. This guy really doesn't
know anything. I'm They're just making
stuff up at this point. greasy.
Just literally making stuff up.
Yeah, he's a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Now
he's actually using fake profiles.
What a [ __ ]
Yeah, you'll never find any women I've
been speaking to, mate. I keep him far
far away from you white knights and you simps.
O, did you watch my video, Grezy?
Did Did you watch my video?
Did you Did you like the white knight bit?
Did you like the s bit?
Did you like it, bro?
She's not going to let you hit it.
She's not going to let you hit. Why are
you defending her? She's not going to
let you hit it. Why are you going mad?
She's not going to touch your penis.
It's true, though. Greavves is true.
Well, I've already told you I haven't
been speaking to her and I've never seen
her in my life. It's just [ __ ] that you
people in this community make up.
Yeah. Cuz you ain't got a life, so you
just make up stuff and make up stupid rumors. Yeah.
Now you're actually making up stuff and
going on fake profiles that I haven't
even spoke to in my life. You people
just get sadder and sadder and sadder.
I don't try to get with any woman on Instagram.
Never have and never will. I'm not white
lights like you people. I'm not simp
They're not going to let you hit it.
Ain't it, bro?
Yeah, I just don't know. That's all I'm
saying, bro. I'm not going back and forth. But yeah,
you got a lot of people singing over
that autumn rose. Um, Grezy,
but how many years do you reckon they're
like, how many years do you reckon it's
going to take for them to realize that
singing is not going to work? 2 years, 3
4 years, 5 years, 6 years, 7 years?
Like, what age do you think they're
going to get to before they realize that
women aren't going to sleep with you cuz
you're trying to look good for them?
What what what odds would you put on the ears, lad?
They try to look good for women.
It's [ __ ] embarrassing, bro.
Honestly, yeah, if I was feeling to get
a [ __ ] today, if I wasn't already
speaking to someone, but I would just go
out. I would just go out and meet
someone and get some phone numbers and
stuff. Add some people to my collection. Greavesy.
There's a lot of people that's singing
over that autumn rose. I've noticed that
as well. There's a few people doing it.
That's how they give away that they got
no life and they're ugly. That they have
to simp over a woman on YouTube. Yeah.
Didn't you see the virgin's video
yesterday? Oh, how dare you call women
on the internet fat? Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Someone's getting feisty or bad.
And you're thinking in your head,
Rihanna is not going to [ __ ] you. Orin
Rose is not going to [ __ ] you.
They're not going to [ __ ] you. They're
going to leave you to still be a virgin.
And you're never going to get laid.
Doesn't matter how many times you defend
women. They're not going to [ __ ] you.
They're not going to get with you.
They're never going to sleep with you.
They're never going to date you. No
person. Get in your [ __ ] head.
They'll thank me when they're [ __ ] 90
years of [ __ ] age.
Jesus [ __ ] Christ, mate. They'll
thank me when they're [ __ ] 90 years
of age, bro. Still sticking up for women
to try to look good.
God, nothing worse than a white knight.
Nothing Nothing worse than that, mate.
Give me a thief. Give me a [ __ ] Give
me a thief. Give me a um Give me
anything. But not a white knight.
What a [ __ ] white night. I hate white lights.
I prefer [ __ ] you know, anything
other than that.
It's pathetic, bro. Pathetic.
Bro, you don't need to give me advice, lad.
You don't need to give me advice. You
need to give yourself advice.
Give Give that advice to yourself, lad.
You need to give that advice to yourself, bro.
Don't give that advice to me, bro. Oh. Yeah, man.
Yeah, bro. You don't need to worry about me, lad.
Trust me, you don't need to worry about me.
I've been with more women than you. I've
been Even if even if I never ever got
with a woman ever again in my life, I've
already had plenty. So, I'm all good. So, yeah.
I'm all good, matey.
But yeah, I don't know why we're talking
about this anyways. I don't really care, bro. You know?
Yeah. You need to be more than 6' 3,
though, to get anything in this day and
age. You need to be more than
good-looking and tall, matey.
I mean, even [ __ ]
Tik Tockers will get [ __ ] rejected.
So, I don't even know why we're why
we're talking about this. Anyways, I
literally don't care.
I don't give a [ __ ] So, yeah.
Pointless subject. Boring subject.
I'm about 510,
59 and a half, 510.
I know some black guy who's 5'8, which
actually shocked me to be honest. Yeah.
He hasn't. It says he's going to go
live, but he hasn't gone live.
It says upcoming. Yeah.
So many white knights. So many simps. A s.
A white knight. Ooh, a s.
A wild s appears.
A white s. A white knight appears. A s Yeah.
Do you remember when Monty man was
trying to say that he's taller than me?
He's not [ __ ] taller than me.
[ __ ] hell, mate.
Yeah, it says upcoming, but he's not gone live.
Yep. You can't. Oh gosh.
Won't be on here long.
Grievy won't be on here long.
Could you imagine Monty man trying to
read that chat? GBT.
Where the [ __ ] am I going to find
someone with curly hair?
And also, Grevy, another thing we've
never had is any black Izzies, have we,
Greavvesy? We've never had any black Izzies.
Do you know what? I don't think I've
ever got a black woman's number in my life.
Come to think of it, I don't think I
have. I don't know, bro. I don't think I
have to be honest
except that one person that one time
approached me but no I don't think I
actually have grievy.
I sw I I would remember it if I had
why I don't know I don't think I I don't
see them I don't really see them about
black is we bless
Is that cute? Greavvesy. No.
He said, "How can you deny Rihanna is
attractive? Easy. You just might not
like black women."
Am I lying, Grezy? Another
celebrity put on a pedestal.
Am I right, Greavves, or am I right?
Another celebrity put on a pedestal.
That is someone that's put on a pedestal.
It's so bad that you could go to Axis
today and probably most people there
would be better looking than her.
There's celebrities that are put on pedestals.
Like we said before, Grezy, trendy
things. When I'm when I'm out in When
I'm out again, um Grezy, I'm going to
show you the coach that these people wear.
I'm going to show you the coach that
these people wear. Yeah. The trend I was
telling you about.
Yeah. You'll see like one and then the
other one wearing it. Another one Yeah.
I'll show you what I mean when I'm next
in um when I'm next in town.
Okay with you, boss.
Oh, is he [ __ ] mate? Is he [ __ ] The
silly can. Is he [ __ ] mate? Is he [ __ ]
Smokey bees offered me some work.
I don't trust him.
I don't trust him as far as I can throw him. Greasy.
Yeah. Women are like, pick a mix. You
won't you wouldn't only have one sweet
in the pick a mix, would you? I said it
to this person on Reddit. They were
laughing. They said, "You made me You
crap me up." It's true. Most people that
get a pick a mix, they don't go for one
sweet, do they? When you go to a
restaurant, you don't get one thing, do
you? So why would you stick with one person?
What's so special about that person that's not
What's so special about that person than
than the other people?
Who's to to say that you're not a better
match with someone else, Greavvesy?
Do you understand, Greavvesy?
You know, you you you know,
who's to say that you're not a um
you know what I'm saying? Yeah.
right? Is this going live or what Yep.
But you still But the thing is you still
have people on Reddit defending women.
Jan Jan Joe, they make excuses for women
just because they're women.
Yeah. Stay away from that site if you're going to
um if don't don't ask for advice from them.
Never ask for advice.
I don't you don't ask for advice.
Don't ask for advice.
They just defend
They just defend women for the sake of it. Yep.
So, is he going live or what?
He was supposed to go live 20 minutes ago. Grezy.
[ __ ] hell. The virgin's 31 tomorrow. Jesus Christ.
31. And you're still a virgin.
I remember everyone's birthday.
[ __ ] hell. You still a virgin at 31?
That is That is embarrassing.
still a virgin at 31, mate. That's embarrassing. Would you
if you had to if it if you had a
birthday Yeah. and it had to be it had
to be the 20th or the 21st, what would
you pick? I think I'd pick the 20th
cuz I used to like the number 20.
Yeah, he was sing over that autumn.
Yeah, he was sing over autumn. Virgin
boy was doing it as well. I'd pick the number 20.
What would you pick? I'd pick the 20th,
not the 21st.
I used to like the number 21, but that
[ __ ] virgin's born on [ __ ] 21st.
That [ __ ] absolute [ __ ] virgin.
Yeah. So what? Yeah. Yeah. But he he
he'll probably admit he's a virgin.
You have to pick a number to put money
on. Would it be 20 or 21?
on the roulette table
number? But I used to do 21 as well cuz
it was second, didn't it? But I used to
bet second dozen.
£4 to [ __ ] £57.
What a joke, mate. Then you can't
complete the wagering.
And you can't complete the [ __ ] wagering.
20 black even seconds.
Do you remember that on the roulette table?
>> Yeah. My my I'm born the 27th, so I'm an odd number.
I prefer odd than even, but I like the number 20. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm just going to chill today. Um,
and I got some stuff to do next week.
Need to go to the pictures. Probably go
out for some drinks. Yeah,
I don't like drinking every week.
I would go out today, but nah.
No, I don't really gamble anymore. I
don't gamble anymore.
I don't really gamble anymore.
But yeah, I would went out today, but I
can't be annoyed.
Maybe I know it will be next. No, maybe
it will be March. Maybe. I said March,
didn't I? But
28th is Friday, is it? So maybe,
maybe the 28th. I don't know. Maybe.
Maybe. No, no, no. I don't think so. I
think maybe two weeks from now. I don't know.
Don't really like drinking anymore.
Yeah. What are you going What are you
going to watch, man? I'll watch the new
Strangers. I'm going to watch Scream on the 27th.
The new Scream comes out on the 27th.
So, I'll be in a cinema.
Do you know what used to happen? Yeah.
Whenever I used to go out drinking.
Yeah. Obviously, I used to drink rum and
that in it. I want to drink whiskey
again. I want to try whiskey again when
I go out again. But when I used to go
out drinking. Yeah. I I couldn't go to
the cinema for like two days after cuz
like the hangover and that in it. You
can't even think properly. You're trying
to watch the film and you can't even
think properly, bro.
So I used to like have to wait like two
two days before going cinema after drinking.
Do you know what I'm saying? Yep.
It has no benefits. That's why I rarely
do it anymore, but it's fun once in a
while. No, no. The only time I drew No,
to be fair, yeah, the reason I drunk
last time is cuz someone some someone
was pissing me off and they were giving
me a [ __ ] headache, so I thought,
"Oh, let me just go out and
it doesn't really have any benefits."
No, it's fun once in a while though.
It is fun once in a while, but rarely.
And I stick to beer when I go out now.
So, I stick to Guinness.
The stick to Guinness me.
Yeah, I don't really drink much anymore, bro.
You reckon you could get um You reckon
you could get alcohol poisoning with just Guinness?
Nah, I don't think so. I had a proper
bad hangover the second last time I
drunk. I couldn't even eat, man. I
ordered a takeaway. I couldn't even eat
it. I was being sick. Headache. Sick
headache. Sick. Oh, bro. I thought I was
going to die. It kind of put me off. But
if you just stick to Guinness, you don't
get the hangovers. That's why I just
stick to Guinness.
I had these shots my friend gave me,
bro. Oh, I thought I was going to die,
bro. I thought I was dying. Oh, a
takeaway back. I couldn't even eat it.
Well, I ate it. I nuked it up. When I
woke up, I just nuked the takeaway up
and I used to drink white rum casually,
you know, like you know, white Captain
Morgans. I used to drink it casually
with prime juice.
I used to drink it all the time. Like
white Captain Morgans's
the white one. The actual white one. I
used to drink it all the time when I was
like 24, like 23, 24, 20, 25, 26.
I used to drink it all the time, bro.
Like with the prime juice
used to get you really [ __ ] And the
hangovers the next day. Oh my god. like
anxiety slash like you eat like three
times the next day.
It make you really hungry the next day as well.
But yeah, I used to drink the white Captain Morgans's.
I used to have to get ordered in because
you can't get it from uh I used to have
it with like lime juice,
like lime prime juice. Oh, bro. used to
get get you really drunk. Really drunk.
Depends like you if you just stick to
beer, there's no hangover. If you even
if you mix the beer, you can mix beer.
Doesn't make a difference. If you just
stick to beer, you don't get no
hangover. Um if you stick if you if you drink like rum
and you stick to one rum, you get like
anxiety the next day and stuff. Um,
if you uh if you mix if you mix the
drinks, you're [ __ ] And if you have
shots, you're [ __ ] So, they're going
they go in categories. Well, I have baby
Guinness shots. I mean, I have a I have
baby Guinness shots, but not like
[ __ ] I don't have I have baby
Guinness shots, but not any other shots.
You need to eat the the right food
before drinking it as well. Like you
need to eat the right food otherwise you
just sick up black. I had you can't have
KFC or anything. You need proper food
before eating because you just sick up
black. I was having shot and I was sick
and up black.
Not even joking, bro. Yeah, you need to
eat the right food as well. Really?
That's good then, isn't it? Bless you in life.
Bless you in life if you stop drinking.
I gambled yesterday, but I don't really
gamble as much anymore.
It's [ __ ] bro. The industry is
finished. Elad, the industry, the
gambling industry is finished.
saying that I'm going to do a both teams
to score when the lineup's right. I'm
going to put like 150 on two teams, bro.
Yeah, I'm going to put 150 on two teams.
I got like 500 pound back sometime maybe.
>> Yeah, you do to be honest with you, bro.
You really do. Especially when you get
to my age.
Well, I've already done loads of stuff
already, bro. But I mean, I could be
doing more, obviously. Literally. Yeah.
And anything like gambling and drinking
will just hold you back.
Especially gambling. Gambling's worse
than drinking. Gambling's way worse than drinking, bro. Yeah.
Gambling's worse than drinking,
but I've already done like so much
already in my life, bro. So, yeah. Yeah.
You get me? Do no.
I don't know what I'm going to eat today.
Greek Greek green.
What am I going to eat today no?
No. I'm not getting a bagel, bro.
Too expensive. Greasy too expensive.
Rit the bear for new president.
Did you tick Did you tick rit the bear? That's funny. Yeah, man.
[ __ ] hell, man.
No, I don't know what I'm You know, I've
not had for ages a full English, but
it's too uh it's too late now. It's
12:46. I haven't had like a Weather
Spoons breakfast for ages.
No, I ain't had it for I haven't had one
for [ __ ] ages.
Reeves, you haven't had one for ages, lads. No.
What are you going to eat today,
Greavves? You're not going to have
another takeaway again. Surely.
Surely you're not going to have another takeaway.
Yeah, I ain't had a Weather Spoons
breakfast for [ __ ] a minute, bro.
It's too late now.
It's 13 minutes to [ __ ] one.
God bless. Having chicken and rice. I
might go to the chicken shop.
I don't know, bro. I don't know.
probably get a haircut next week, I think. Greasy,
is that okay with you if I get a haircut next week?
Is that okay with you, boss?
Well, obviously I'm going to get the
beard trimmed as well. What do you think
I'm going to do? Just get my haircut.
Beard's not even that long, bro.
The beard's not even that long, man. Come on.
But yeah, obviously.
You think that's long, bro? You should
have saw it a [ __ ] couple weeks ago.
Yeah, I know they do, bro. But they they
they they they do chips instead of the
um instead of the hash browns. It's not the same.
Yeah, I know what it I know it, bro. But
it's not the same.
I remember when I was in central London
doing the Uber Grezy. Yeah. I stopped
off. I started at the Weather Spoons and
I had breakfast there. I had breakfast
at the Weather Spoons
before starting the work.
I like that Jack Jones wanker Grezy. I
can't stand that Jack Jones.
I can't stand that [ __ ]
Yeah, I can't stand that [ __ ] He's annoying, bro.
You know, uh, how did I know who How did
I know who it was, Greavvesy?
He's annoying, bro.
Do you remember what I said to Triple H?
Why don't you go for a drink with Anna
Deck around Newcastle?
Be realistic, P. I said, I am being
realistic. You You live near Newcastle.
They're from Newcast. Why don't you meet
up and goes
on the G?
Be realistic P.
Grezy. Be realistic. P.
No, I think it'd be a good laugh.
Be realistic, P.
What? And he's going for a drink with an deck.
Why can't you go for a drink with other
hand and neck?
Be realistic. P.
He said that's not being realistic. Grezy,
so why are you collecting these DVDs?
Are you actually watching them or you
just collecting them?
Are you just watching them? shot.
You're just watching them.
So, you just collect them or you're
actually watching them.
Yeah, that's like me. I haven't I
haven't even started on the second Lego yet, Grezy. Yep.
I haven't even Well, I haven't even
started on the second Lego yet. I
haven't even touched it, Greavvesy. I
only wanted the little characters, the
little figures. But I need Chewbecka
now, Grevy. I need Chewbecka.
I need the actual Chew Becca figure with
his little crossbow.
Yeah, occasionally I gambled yesterday.
Uh, no, not yesterday. The day before I
lost I lost £100 sometimes.
Let me see how much Tube Becker is.
I think he's like £15.
I don't trust buying just the figures
though. Grievy cuz there was reports.
Yeah, I do like fish. There was reports of um
it them not being genuine. Them not
being genuine, Grezy.
So, obviously that's why I bought them
in a box. But here you get on Amazon. He's £13.95.
Jube Becka's £13.95 with his little crossbow. Greasy.
Oh, you can get Chew Becca and Han Solo for $25.99.
Han Solo. Yeah.
No, but I buy the reason why I buy the
Lego sets is because you know that the
figures are genuine. You understand what
I'm saying, Greasy? People are saying,
"Oh, this looks secondhand. This," but
obviously the Lego is brand new, in it.
So, you get what I'm trying to say?
But I don't think you understand what
I'm saying in it.
>> I don't think you get what I've already
got like over£100 in figures.
>> You You understand what I mean, Grezy?
Well, that's what some of the people are
saying. I don't know if they're right or not, but
Yeah. See you later, lad. Um,
yeah. So, that's what people are saying.
I don't know if they're right. I don't
know. But that's what they say. So, you
kind of have to buy the whole thing if
you want them to be genuine.
I've already spent about £200 on Lego, man.
There's got to be one.
There's still some that we don't have though.
Where's the Chew Becca one? I bet he's Yeah,
we got Darth Vader in it. We got white Darth Vader.
I like Chew Becca. I think he's my favorite.
What else do I collect? Griezy.
Well, I only What else do I like collecting?
Yeah, they're the stormtroopers. They're
only That's only 26 that one.
I could just locally go for a drink
today if I wanted to, but I like going central London. Um,
where's True Becca?
I'm just going to I'm just going to type
Lego Star Wars Chew Becca.
Chew back. Chew back. These names.
Do you remember Grezy? Poor [ __ ]
Do you remember Greasy? Poor [ __ ]
All right, I'm going to send you something.
I'm going to show you. Look, one second.
I'm going to send you this on Instagram. Yeah, greasy.
You want to see white Darth Vader? Yeah,
you can. One second. I've got him right
here if you Yeah.
I've got lots of little characters. One second.
This is on Amazon. Uh yeah, Amazon Instagram
white is here.
Where is he? Oh [ __ ] I need to turn
this here. One second. Look. A
this white Darth Vader. Yeah.
See, I don't know if his name is White
Darth Vader, but he's white.
They're just little figures.
Oh, no. This is wrong. This is Yoda.
This is Yoda's body, but we changed him
because you can't he can't sit down. Look.
Look. Yo, this is Yoda's body. But I I
changed their clothes around.
Yeah, I changed their clothes around.
I'm not drinking today.
I like him though. Looks
I'm not I'm not um I'm not having any beers.
I tell you what, I am having a [ __ ] snooze. Greavesy.
Okay with you, boss.
No, I was thinking of going out today, but
and having a having um adding some to my collection, but nah,
we got an arcade here.
We've got an arcade here, bro.
I went bowling like a month ago. Month
or so ago. It was It was fun. Yeah. Boom. Boom.
Yeah. Balden. Yeah.
Them army [ __ ] were laughing at us,
Grezy, mocking us. They don't come
anymore, are they? They don't go to the
pub anymore, do they? They've been going
for a while.
Yeah, they they be going for a while.
The army [ __ ] on a mission.
They're on a mission in it, Grezy.
Nope. Not for the past two weeks. I went
out two weeks ago.
No, I went out two weeks ago. Two notifications messages.
I'm not saying lad. I'm not saying I'm
not saying anything on here anymore
about um people and stuff and people
numbers are getting that.
I'm not saying. So yeah,
and I didn't go out for that reason
anyways. Even though I done it, I didn't
go out for that reason. I went out cuz
someone was annoying me. So
there's a with two sugars here.
A few people. I think there's a bit more
than a than a few people, mate.
Bit more than a few people. Yeah.
Oh, them stormtroopers. Yeah,
it's Jamie Thompson. It's that weirdo.
It's that weirdo Jamie Thompson.
Yeah, just leave them, bro. They're all
right, man. They're just They're just
undercover gays. They're just They're
just closeted gays, lad. I wouldn't pay
no mind to it.
They're just closeted homosexuals,
that's all, lad. Don't mind them.
They just haven't come out the closet
yet, and they don't know how to. Yeah.
But yeah, I don't really go out anymore
to be fair. It's very rare I do go out.
I know, bro. They're gay. Like I said to
you, bro, they're gay lords.
You, like I've said many times, you
wouldn't spend this amount of time
stalking a woman.
You wouldn't spend this amount of time
stalking a [ __ ] woman, let alone a
[ __ ] man. They're gay, bro. They're
just gay lords, isn't it?
Nah, it's not a blessing. They're just weirdos.
They're sat on here every day. I was off
of here for 10 days, you know. I was off
of here for 10 days.
I don't really come on much anymore.
They're on here from the time they wake
up to the time they go to bed.
They're weirdos on here, bro. They're [ __ ] weirdos.
Yeah, they're just weirdos, bro.
Yeah, they they just need to come out the closet.
Yeah, I'm just speaking to someone as
well, so I don't need to really be on here anymore.
Even if I mean even if I wasn't speaking
to anyone, I I still wouldn't. But you get me.
What do you mean, bro? Snoop
Snoop Snoop Doggy,
>> be careful. That was a bit
>> mama. Uh, there's a problem with the figures. The figures,
>> they're there, but there's a problem.
We're missing a person. Chewaca.
>> I know.
>> You're going to have to buy him, huh?
You're going to have to buy Chewbacca. About £500.
No, I'm joking. He's £13.95 just a figure.
>> You need to add it. Yeah, we have to add
it to the collection, isn't it, M? Okay.
He said you sold your phone for gambling
money and that's why. Yeah. Again, self
projecting. Sorry, I just read that, bro.
They're just Yeah, that's just self projecting, bro.
That's what it is. It's a It's a copycat self-projecting community.
That's all it is.
If these people [ __ ] had a life, they
would be on there 24/7.
If they had a life, they would be on
here 24/7, bro. Yeah.
Just like they say that you're a virgin,
the virgins themselves, I mean, they
call they still call me a virgin even
though I've proved I've had sex. I mean,
I still get people calling me a virgin.
It's an autistic disabled community,
lad. What do you expect? Yeah,
they're weirdos, bro. I just think they
need to come out the closet. A lot of
these people, they'll be much happier in life.
Much happier when they come out the
closet as what they are gay.
Apparently, it's pissing down with rain.
All they they all self-reflect, bro.
That's their life, isn't it?
Like I said, maybe I'll go out drinking
next week. I don't know. [ __ ] knows.
Maybe, maybe not.
Yeah. So they say Grezy, but
probably was. Yeah.
They ain't got a life. They're just fat,
ugly people just sat on YouTube every
day. They got nothing in their life, bro.
Yep. Of course they would. You could
come off of YouTube for 3 years and
they'd still talk about you every day.
They don't do it for reaction. They do
it because they're mentally obsessed.
There's a big difference between people
doing stuff for reaction and people
being mentally obsessed.
And think about it, Fire Stick. You
wouldn't even be obsessed with a woman
the way that they're obsessed with you.
And you you see how weird it is. Yeah.
Because if you put yourself in their shoes, right,
you wouldn't do you wouldn't be obsessed
with a woman the way that they're
obsessed with you. Think about it.
That's how you know they're jealous and
gay because no normal person would even
do that to a woman.
But they're casually doing it to men
every day on YouTube. No problem.
That's how you know they're just gay
ugly people with no life. Simple, bro. Simples.
It's simples, man.
They don't get paid for doing it. They
literally don't get nothing for doing
it. And they still do it.
You wouldn't stalked. And I was off
YouTube for 9 days. I was speaking to
someone as well. I speak to someone every day
who I'm going to be meeting soon anyways.
And then and then they're casually
stalking men on the internet every day
and they're not getting paid for it.
Weirdos, bro. It weirdos. Defo
launch legs is gay. Jamie Thompson is
gay. Red Star gay. Joseph [ __ ] is gay.
You know what that stands for? Joe F.
It's Joseph [ __ ] That's the That's
the F bit. He's Because he's a [ __ ]
isn't it? Joseph [ __ ]
Oh, that's what that's what F stands for. Yeah. Yeah, man. Yeah, bro. Um,
not really. No.
And they say that I'm a ma when I'm
literally better looking than them.
Anyone do you not find it weird how all
of these people that have been dock
share and all of the people that show
their faces are uglier than me? Do you
not find that a coincidence?
They're fat. They're [ __ ] ugly. Have
you noticed, bro? That's why they do
that's why they do this, bro. That's
another reason. If you see the people
that's been doxed and the people that
show their face, they're all the same
ugly looking people.
That's why they That's another reason
why they do it as well. Yeah, man.
That's that, lad.
Yeah. They can't go out. They can't
approach people. They can't meet people.
That's They're jealous of like different
things, bro. It's not just one thing.
They're jealous of loads of different
things, you know.
You're better looking than them. Um,
one, you got more money than them.
You got a life unlike them.
You know, I'm into I'm not going out,
but it's cold, bro. And the weather's
[ __ ] So, yeah. Mhm.
You get me? E. So, yeah.
But yeah, a lot of them have been docks, bro. Yeah.
And they're always fat, ugly bastards,
every single time without failure. Yep. live
going to come off soon. Did Did Monty go
live? Did Monty end up going live or not? Raining.
Yeah, he's a homosexual, bro. You can go
on my phone and you won't see any men on
my phone, lad. You will not see any You
will not see any men on my phone, brother.
Yeah, he's gay. To casually stalk a man
every single day for and you don't get
paid for it. You got to be gay.
Gay and jealous, bro. Like I said, you
wouldn't stalk a woman the way that they
um stalk you. Even a man that's obsessed
with a woman in love would not stalk
them the way that these people casually
stalk men every day for free.
That's when you realize, oh yeah,
they're actually gay in it. Yeah, they
got to be gay.
They've literally got to be gay, bro.
There's There's no other reason.
They're [ __ ] They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's a bit of everything. Jealousy,
they're gay. They hate their lives. Um
there it's a few different things, bro.
It's not just one thing, you know?
That's it, bro. Yeah.
And also, have you seen when they simp
over women on YouTube? When they beg
women on YouTube, that shows that they
get no [ __ ] It shows that they've got
no life. Um, and they get no [ __ ]
When they have to like beg women on the
internet, like Alton Rose, I don't know
if you know who that is, but people that
simp because they can't go out and meet people themselves.
They give their life that gives them
away as well when they're doing stuff like that.
That's why I don't go on LJ J's channel.
It's just retardation.
It's just retardation on that chat. They're retards.
Like I'm I've I'm making another channel
soon, bro. And everyone's coming on that
channel that's not from here.
Yeah. Simple. Simple, bro. Cuz if you
think about it, when I go live, I only
speak to a couple of people
to be fair.
I don't know what I'm doing, bro.
Probably just chilling, man. Just chilling.
It started raining in it. So, yeah. Nothing.
Nothing at all, bro. I don't think
it's raining, isn't it? Started raining.
Nothing in the cinema. So yeah, nothing.
Pretty much nothing.
I could go like nano or something.
Jamie Thompson and he's not American either.
That did make me laugh to be honest,
which it shouldn't do, bro, cuz they're actual retards.
It did actually it does actually make me
laugh, bro. To be fair.
They actually they actually give you
laughs. They say they laugh at you, bro,
but you're actually laughing at them.
You're getting more laughs out of them
than they're getting out of you. I I I
watched that virgin yesterday, non legs,
and I was pissing myself laughing, bro.
I couldn't believe what I was watching.
Someone having a [ __ ] autistic rage
in in a bed sit owned by the council.
I've not I've not seen anything as funny
in in a very long time, bro.
No, it's [ __ ] madness.
And it's obviously a cry for help. like
you can see it in in in his eyes that
he's he's severely depressed. Um, and
it's a cry for help. But obviously, I
couldn't help but laugh at the same time. Bro,
why am I going to go to pecking, bro?
That doesn't make sense.
Why am I going to go to pecking to go
cinema? That doesn't make any sense.
There's a cinema near me.
There's a cinema near me, bro. Why would
I go there?
No, just J. Yeah, I know who you're
talking about. No. Yeah,
proper fat in it, bro.
Yeah, I basically do, but I don't live
near Pekkham, bro. What the [ __ ]
That's nowhere near me. Um,
have you ever been to S Keys?
I remember I met Isabelle in Sorry Keys.
That little Weather Spoons.
the little weather spoons matey
by I don't know if it's still there by
the corner of uh by the um
is it Asda or Tesco? I can't remember.
So keys I only hit there in a minute, bro.
Yeah, I went there with Isabelle once.
Does it get packed packed?
There's a Tesco. Yeah, I knew it was one of them.
Yeah, I ain't been there for years, bro.
Do That's why I went to own that Kenzie.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
Stuck on the little [ __ ] Yeah,
I was a mad bastard. Well, I Yeah.
Is it Is it Does it get busy that pub
that SE Keys on a Saturday?
I just normally go central when I go out drinking. >> Yeah.
Yeah. I normally just go central
fire stick, but yeah, there's a Soie
Keys, Weather Spoons. Yeah.
Yeah, but that's where you get all the
[ __ ] That's where all the people are
at. You say it's too dear. Yeah, but
think about it, bro. Okay, it's £7
something for a pint of Guinness. How
many pints of Guinness are you going to
be having re realistically?
How many pints of Guinnesses are you
really going to be having realistically?
you're going to, you know,
you're not going to really have many
many. Let's just say you had 10
Guinnesses, which you're probably not. That's £70.
They can't water it down, you see.
Whereas when when you drink rum, they
water it down. I spent I spent like £30
on rum. Yeah. This Simmons bar. And they
didn't even hit me cuz they watered the
[ __ ] thing down. But if you have like
Guinnesses, I mean, I doubt you'll drink
10. But even if you do drink 10, what's
that? £80. There you go. sorted.
So, I've always gone central London,
bro. It's where people are. So,
I've never really stuck local local.
Saying that though, Romford's all right
for going out drinking. It's nowhere as
it's nowhere near as good as um um
central London, but it's still still a
good little spot.
Yeah, but that's what I'm saying. They
watered it down. They watered it down.
So, that's what I mean. But with beer,
it's harder for them to water it down.
And you can go like, well, I go drinking
Wednesday. I go drinking Thursdays. So
there's happy hour on Thursdays. I don't
like really Fridays. And well, Fridays
are all right, but I don't really go out
Saturdays. I always normally go out Thursdays
when I do go out drinking.
And you can get beer like £3. You get
like a bottle of beer for £3.
So you just obviously drink£3 pound
beer. I think the last time I went out
drinking I spent about50 4050£50
cuz obviously it's happy hour. I like
drinking on Thursdays. I don't like Saturdays really.
No, I don't really like Saturdays to be fair.
I like Thursdays.
I like a Thursday session. Isn't that right, Grezy?
Nice weather spoons on a Thursday.
I like Thursdays, bro.
Yeah, they do rob people. That's what they do.
[ __ ] robbing [ __ ] Is that right, Grezy boss?
Yeah, I like Thursdays, man. I don't
know about you.
Nice Thursday in April. In May,
I might go out I might go out St. Patrick's Day.
What do you think about that, Grezy? St.
Patrick's Day. Okay with you, boss.
Obviously have to run it past you first.
Run it by you rather. Okay with you,
boss. If I go out St. Patty's Day.
To be honest with you, bro, I don't
really like going to I don't really like
going out in I don't really like going
out in advance. Bloody hell.
I ain't won for a long time, bro. I really.
And even the odds on the football has gotten worse. Yep. Yeah, man.
I lost £100 on roulette two days ago online roulette.
I think when I gamble again, I'm just
going to put 150 on two teams.
I'm just going to put 150 on two teams,
bro. Like, whenever.
get to like 500 pound or something and yeah,
you can't win anymore, bro. You can't
win. Even the odds on the football [ __ ]
I don't know five both teams to score a
couple of weeks ago. It paid 220
224 from 20. It should have been way
more than that. Five teams. I got five
Five [ __ ] teams, bro. The [ __ ] PS5. Yeah,
that's good then, isn't it? I got an
Xbox and a TV. I don't use it though.
Yeah, I'm just going to stick like 150
on two teams, bro.
When I gamble again,
wait for the perfect lineup, you know?
It should pay about £500. So,
all right. It's so Do you know the worst
is online roulette fire stick? It's so
rigged. It's so [ __ ] fixed. I got 43
spins. Yeah. I got I got um I got I got
43 spins. Yeah.
I got 43 spins. Yeah. And I got it to
£4.37. I went on roulette with it. got
it to 60 pound then lost it trying to
complete the wagering. See how fixed it
is when they give you bonus money. Isn't
it funny how you always seem to win but
then when you put your own money in you
can't even double the [ __ ]
It's fixed bro. It's all fixed.
You know Grezy. You know
you know bro. You know
you [ __ ] know lad.
But do you understand what I'm saying?
So they've um
Yeah, it's just fixed anyway. It's just fixed.
They lost 800.
You lo How the [ __ ] did you lose £850 in
them arcades? That's mad.
You got money to lose, bro. You got
money to lose.
You got money to lose, Grezy.
Have you got money to lose, Greasy? Boss.
[ __ ] 8 fucking50. [ __ ] that.
That's not good, is it?
That's not good, is it? Griezy.
Has Franklin been put to the side, Grezy?
So, what do you think her opinion will
be that I'm collecting other people,
Grezy? Do you think she'll be happy
about that or no?
Do you think she'll be happy about that?
That's funny, bro.
To be fair, I might get a PS5 when
[ __ ] GTA comes out.
They [ __ ] It's coming out November
now, isn't it, Grezy? [ __ ] hell. It
went from May, now it's no [ __ ] November.
[ __ ] hell. Make up your [ __ ] mind,
won't you? Poor [ __ ] Pucker.
No, I'll just buy myself one. But
I'll just buy myself one. Bro,
it's saying November now. It was May and
now it's saying it's November.
So, [ __ ] knows, mate. I'll probably just
buy a PS5, too. I don't know. Do you
know why I got an Xbox? I've always been
PlayStation, but I thought, you know
what? I just wanted to switch it up.
I've got my Xbox there.
Uh, I've got a TV as well.
Is my TV good enough? Would you say, Greasy?
It's 55 in Samsung. Would you say it's big enough?
How are you when you lost that 850, bro?
When I lost that 100 pound, I woke up
here wanting to strangle someone.
That's one of the reasons I don't like
gambling, bro, cuz I go I go [ __ ] mad.
I don't care how much money I've how
much money I have or how much money I
lost. I don't give a [ __ ] I don't like losing, bro.
That's the TV there.
Yeah, Scooby-Doo's on there. Look,
my Xbox is there. Xbox. Xbox. Yeah.
Yeah. But I will end up doing something
one day, bro. That's the thing. That's
why I don't do it anymore. That's why I
rarely do it.
I don't care how much money I have. How
much I lost I only lost £100 and I still
have money. I still paid all my bills
and [ __ ] Doesn't make a difference.
Yeah. 55 in.
I hate losing, bro. I get angry and [ __ ]
I start seeing demons in my head and
that. I don't give a [ __ ] if it was only
£100, bro. I don't care. Simple. It's annoying, bro.
It's annoying, isn't it?
Yeah, I want to lay in bed for days when
I lose as well. It doesn't matter how
much it is. £50, £100.
I feel like doing more than that.
I feel like doing [ __ ] more than that, mate.
Do you remember when I smashed the door
greaves in? I got arrested
in the old house. Jesus Christ.
You remember that Grimsy?
I smashed the door open and that.
And I [ __ ] went out. I come back.
[ __ ] load of old Bill. Greasy on the
door. Load of old Bill.
Yeah. And I went out. I come back and it
was a load of old bill.
They arrested me for smashing my own
door. They dropped the charges and any
obviously, but they said, "Oh, we can
offer you a caution." I said, "Fuck off.
Take me to [ __ ] court." Are you going
to offer me a caution
when I smash my own door? That's my own
door. I smashed. It was my room. I'm
allowed to smash my own door.
criminal damage. Yeah,
he's run off, man. He got run off of YouTube. Yep.
You must you must have a lot of money,
Fire Stick, to lose £850, bro. You must
have a lot of money.
Yeah, they dropped it anyways. But still,
you must have a lot of money, bro, to
lose 850 quid casually. [ __ ] that.
Rather you than me, bro.
Yeah. Well, you must have because if
you're £400 in, you must have you must
have a lot of money to put £400 in a [ __ ] arcade.
You must you must do, bro.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
So, how much did you have left? How much
do you have left?
How much do you have left? You got
You got £131 left.
Yeah, I need to build my money back up
to be honest with you, bro. I need to
stop [ __ ] traveling and going on
holidays and [ __ ]
Really? How how much money do you have
left over every month after you've paid
everything? Would you say
I can't remember the last time I only
had 150 in my account? I can't remember,
bro. The last time
I've always got money, bro.
Yeah, it's the same for me as well, bro.
That's why I stopped playing it.
How much money How much money do you
normally have left over for everything?
pretty much same as me then. Pretty much
same as me.
But I don't really care about money,
bro. Like, as long as I've got enough to
eat and go out and stuff and do what I
want to do, then I'm happy. Do you get me, bro?
I'm happy. really happy. No stress, no
one to answer to, no nothing. I'm happy,
bro. I don't I don't know. Maybe it's
cuz I've already done so much in my
life. But I don't really care, bro. To be fair,
I don't really give a [ __ ] me
as I've got enough to
know what I mean. Yeah.
You get me?
Grand left. Yeah, bro. I need to save
some money, bro. [ __ ]
I need to save some money, bro. I need
to do I need to save some money though
for like this um Well, I have enough
money, but like I can start now with
this GTA thing. Yeah, as long as you've
got like roof over your head, you've got
over a grand, you've got food, bro, what
more could you want? Really think about
it. And don't forget, I've lived a good
life anyways, bro.
I've had everything. I've done what I've
wanted to do. I've gone out three times
a week. I've done madnesses. I've
probably done more more than a lot of
people that are [ __ ] 60, 70.
Yeah, exactly, bro. As long as you got like
you got enough to go on a date with
someone or go out and do whatever,
you're not starving, then that's fine, bro.
That's fine. That's fine, bro. Yeah,
you're not starving or anything. You're good.
But I used to be like proper skin, bro.
Like 6 years ago, Greavves, I used to be skint, bro.
But now it never happens. Never happens.
Never happens, bro. So, yeah. Burger,
Lobster. Yeah, it is expensive.
Yeah, I've been to a lot of restaurants,
a lot of nights out, a lot of [ __ ] So yeah.
So that's is what it is, isn't it?
I just like not having to deal with
people. It's lovely not having to deal with people.
Isn't it greasy? It's lush
not having to deal with people.
Oh, it's wonderful.
Nothing to answer to anyone.
Yeah, it's lovely.
Yeah, it was burger and lobster. Yeah,
it's expensive, bro. Mia. Yeah,
I hate people as well. Fire stick. Well,
most people. I'm like Grezy. We don't
like people. People are selfish. People play games.
Yeah. People are selfish. People play
games. People are headaches.
You didn't own anyone, lad. I've already
done a video responding to this anyways,
so I'm not repeating myself.
Yeah. Bye-bye now.
Yeah. So, um
Yeah. People are [ __ ]
Isn't that right, Grezy? Isn't that right?
Might have another suboid today. Greavvesy.
I just get like a sub, bro.
Yeah, he's he's Bro, but the thing is Yeah.
But the thing is, brother, I showed £5.7,000
in cash. I showed money in cash. And
every time I've shown these people
money, they don't show you anything.
But then they come back showing less
money, acting like they've won. You
can't win with them, bro. You can't win
with retards. That's why there there's
no point responding to these jealous
weirdos. That's why I don't respond to
them, bro. Just like they call you a
virgin even though you proven that
you've had sex.
So then you can't move with these
retards. You'll lose brain cells arguing with them.
Yep. Straight away, bro. Straight away.
Straight away, lad. Yep.
See, I don't what I do when I wake up,
my phone's always dead. For some reason,
my phone's always dead. My phone always
dies for some reason.
Um, so I charge it, go have tea, and
then come back like, I don't know,
whenever. I never My phone's always dead
when I wake up.
You're going to wake up one morning, uh,
Greasy, and there's going to be an
upload from Ali Law.
It's going to be bing. Or you're going
to be like, you just woke up and it's
going to be like bing. Ali law is just
posting a video. Bless. Bless you. Yeah.
Oh, is that cute? Greavvesy.
Do I go on YouTube? Yeah, I go on YouTube. Yeah,
but I don't go on my phone as soon as I
wake up. I need to get this new fold,
Grezy, what am I going to do? How am I
going to get this new fold, Grezy? What
am I going to do?
This fold's coming out in July.
Grievesy, what am I going to do?
I think I'll just buy it outright, bro.
It's not too expensive, is it?
Two grand phone. Greasy.
I'll pay. I I'll buy the two grand phone.
Yeah, I'll buy I'll buy a two grand
phone, bro. It comes out. Yep.
I don't know. I could get on contract,
but I don't really want to I don't
really want to go on contract.
I mean, I could just get a I just could
I could get a 2-year contract and just
pay like 60 70 a month. I think, you
know, as long as the phone don't get
stolen, you'll just keep up with the
payments in it. I mean, I'm paying £40
as it is for unlimited everything. So,
what's it 2030 more?
You know, the more the more I pay this
bill, Greavesy, the more the upfront
cost goes down. It goes down by two
pound every day.
Do you get me?
Or you could get a year contract. That's
like £180 a month, but then it's obviously
But that's £180 a month.
Two year. No, two-year contract because
you don't get the next one that comes
out. You wait 2 years.
There's not going to be difference in
the first in in in the one that comes
out. That's why I didn't get the seven.
I got a fold six. That's why I didn't
get the seven
cuz there's not going to be much
difference um difference. Yeah, they
come out every July. But yeah, if you
got a 2-year contract,
yeah, that's fine. Yeah. Yeah, basically.
No, no, no, no, no.
I like the Samson folds. They're [ __ ]
lush, breezy. They're [ __ ] lush. You
need to get one. They're beautiful. Absolutely beautiful. Beautiful no no.
What phone have you got? Fire stick.
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
See you later, Virgin. Really?
How much was it?
>> Yeah, I don't go out drinking every week
cuz you just I just don't think like
like you enjoy it more, do you? If you
if you go out drinking every week, you
just don't enjoy it
as much, do you?
Yeah. I think it was three weeks I last went out.
Oh, bless you then.
Bless you. So, what's the plan? Are you
just going to like quit gambling or what?
That's the reason I bought this Lego so
I could just like focus on something
else. But but I'm not addicted anyways.
I'm not addicted to gambling anyways, bro. Like,
no. But still,
it was because nothing was on in the
cinema. And January, I gambled a little
bit. Nothing was on at the cinema. There
was nothing to do. People didn't really
go out drinking cuz
everyone's skin in it. So,
everyone was skinn. So, I just kind of
gambled cuz I was bored. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
My little legs.
Yeah, I might get a battered sausage and
chips today. Gy, I've never had a battered sausage.
Might have a battered sausage and chips.
I don't know. Yeah.
Fasted sausage and chippies. Come on, sir. Oh, £500. £800.
No, just go. You're not going to [ __ ] me around again.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. M.
You're lucky to have won 800 and
something pound from [ __ ] 490.
850 from 490. You lucky [ __ ]
Yeah, it's quite kind of lucky to be
honest to win anything nowadays. You're lucky.
You're lucky, matey. You're lucky. Lucky, bro.
So, you're going to do um you're going
to do a football bet on Saturday.
You doing a football bet on Saturday or what?
LJ's got a picture up of me.
Pretty gay to be honest.
So gay these people. Um, yeah.
Anyways, I'm going to go in a minute,
lad. Yeah, cuz
do some stuff, bro.
Right. I'm going. Yeah. See you. Yeah. Um
I don't know. Been a long time. Bye.