You check and see how many little
virgins are on here. You little virgins.
Did they manage to get alive or on YouTube?
We'll see, mate. We'll see.
[ __ ] tasty mate.
Ah, he's such a virgin that one is he
mate showing off 200 pound. He's [ __ ] skink mate.
He's [ __ ] skink.
You know what I mean? He's [ __ ]
skinted on a [ __ ] skin flint, mate. UK asylum.
Skint and a [ __ ] skin flint.
Skint and a [ __ ] skin flint. If you
ask me, UK silent mate.
All right, listen, bro. Yeah, they gave
me free spins on this casino. Yeah.
Uh 43 spins, two sets of 20, and I got
it to £4 and then I got it to £57.
Oh mate, I've everything goes in the
evidence pack. I got it to £57. What's
the chances, bro? £4 to £57 when it's
not your money. When it's bonus money,
coincidence, is it mate? And they know
that even no matter what you get the
money to, you can't complete the
wagering. It's It's too hard to complete
the [ __ ] wagering.
Yeah, but I had to complete the wagering
before [ __ ] being able to withdraw it.
It's [ __ ] fixed as [ __ ] bro. Think
about it, bro. If you put £4 of your own
money in, you ain't getting it to no
[ __ ] 60 quid. You can put £300 in
right now and you lose it.
No. No. You need to complete wagering.
It's [ __ ] fixed as [ __ ] It's [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, I got 40 spins.
I got it to 4 pound 37 and I went on
roulette, got it to 57, but obviously I
couldn't withdraw it without completing
the rage room.
So that's how they got you by the
bollocks, mate. That's how they got you
by the bollocks.
It's [ __ ] fixed as [ __ ] bro. They
emailed me giving me these free spins.
Yep. That's how you know it's fixed. Cuz
if it's raw money, actual cash, you never win.
Oh, I got some free spins from the casino
and I turned £4 into 57
and then um obviously I lost it trying
to complete the wagering.
No, I'm not back gambling. Didn't you
hear what I just said? I said they gave
me free spins. I didn't put any money
in. They gave me free spins. Listen to
what I said, lad. So yeah,
I mean if you count that as gambling. I
didn't put any money in but yeah they
emailed me so I thought oh got nothing to do.
Wagering is like something you've got to
complete before you can withdraw it. Basically
you have to gamble a certain amount
basically. Just put it that way. I do
explain wagering. So yeah, £57
but for £4 and then you can't even
complete the waging because [ __ ]
bro. But that's just obviously to entice
people to gamble obviously.
But no, I'm not back gambling. Obviously not.
Had a nice Chinese today.
It doesn't let you delete your account.
I deleted my I I I closed my lad books
account. Yeah, but it doesn't let you
close this account now. I've tried and
tried and tried again.
So, I'm just going to get my mom to
probably just change the password.
You can't close this account now, bro.
They don't let you. They say they're
going to email you for further, but they
don't do it. They don't let you put
deposit limits on. They don't let you
close it. Trust me, I've tried a million
times. They don't let you. So, the only
thing you can do is get someone to
change the password. So, you can never
log on it again.
You get me, bro? Yeah,
that's the only way. Uh, I won't go I
won't go on it again anyways.
I won't be going on it again anyways.
So, don't worry about me, bro. Don't
worry about me.
Don't worry about me, matey. I'm no Timmy Eldridge.
And I'm not some [ __ ] little virgin
either. UK asylum.
I got something [ __ ] little.
I know they I know they should be when
my lad Well, I close my ladbooks account
down for 6 weeks. When it opens again,
I'll just do football bets on it. I guess
he was flashing 200. He's [ __ ]
skinned, mate. He's [ __ ] skinned,
bro. He's skinned in a [ __ ] skin flinch.
I spent [ __ ] like 200 pound yesterday
on [ __ ] gambling and food almost.
He's [ __ ] skinty skidfish.
He's [ __ ] kid. You [ __ ] kid me.
Do you know what, bro? I I watched that
video and I was pissing myself laughing,
bro. I was actually laughing my ass off.
These people don't realize yet. They say
that they laugh at us, but they're the
biggest laughing stocks going.
They're the biggest laughing stocks going.
They're the big I was actually pissing
myself laughing, bro. I was like, what
the [ __ ] am I seeing? Some of these
people, they're just laughing stocks.
They're just laughing stocks, bro.
He's a virgin character. And a lovely Savoy.
A lovely Savoy.
A lovely sunlight.
Yeah. Had a lovely shower.
Yeah. The lovely shower, mate.
Who the [ __ ] flashes 200? That's how you
know you're down bad, bro. When you're flashing 200.
That is how you know you're [ __ ] down bad.
Yeah, I'm not talking about it anyways,
bro. I'm keeping it private that. So,
yeah, I'm keeping it private, bro.
But yeah, basically,
I'd never show anyone what she looks
like. No one's ever going to know her
name. No one's ever going to know nothing. Yeah,
trust me, bro. [ __ ] that. It You know
what certain virgins like?
You know what I'm saying? UK asylum.
Do you know what certain virgins like, lad?
They don't even know her name, the the
letter of her first name, where she
lives, what she looks. They don't know
nothing. They literally don't know
other than she's [ __ ] Christian. So yeah. Yeah, man.
These losers will never find
will never find her.
Yeah, I woke up in a bad mood today. UK
sign. I woke up wanting to do some [ __ ]
I wanted to go and do some [ __ ] in
cuz I was still pissed off about the like roulette
day tomorrow Friday is it?
Who the [ __ ] shows 200 pound?
Who the [ __ ] does that, bro?
Nope. Smoking beer. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. I lost 100 pounds
yesterday, mate. Oh, bang yesterday,
No, bro. When I gamble again, I'm going
to put 150 on the football team.
Both teams to score on the football.
Um, no, I'm not I'm not into getting
into that [ __ ] Smokey. They gave me 40 spins.
Hey, Smokey B. This is how rigged it is.
Yeah. They gave me 43 spins. Well, two
sets of 20. Yeah. So, I got it to four.
Obviously, it's 10p um spins. Yeah. I
got it to £437
and I turned it to 57 on roulette. Yeah,
of course you did. When it's when it's
bonus money and not raw money.
Ah, yeah. Yeah. Really? And the thing is
smokey but I couldn't withdraw it
because I have to you have to complete wagering.
Yeah, it is for mugs. It is for mugs.
Yeah, it is for mugs. 100.
You're not gamble free. You was gambling
the other day.
You silly goose.
You [ __ ] silly goose.
Nah, you'll never quit. You'll never
quit gambling, bro.
You'll never quit gambling, lad.
I had a I ate the Savoy walking back
home. Um, Grezy, man, I was so hungry,
so I had it on the street.
Jesus Christ, nearly 3K. What a silly
goose you are.
So, are you still going to bet on the football or or nah?
Yeah, I need to go on holiday this year, man. 100%.
You still going to do the football though? No.
I'm going to do a nice both teams to
score maybe in a couple of weeks.
Put 150 160 on it.
Get that 500 pound back.
Okay with you, Greavesy boss.
If I do something like that once a month.
No, I'm not betting on the football. No,
no, no, no.
Bro, so what? Are you not going to bet
on the football anymore either, Smokey?
Bless you in life then.
Bless you if you've quit gambling. Poor [ __ ] Oh man. Remember
what I was showing you earlier, Grezy?
When they were calling each other gay on
the student form,
they were calling each other gay.
Calling each other [ __ ] gay.
[ __ ] Do you know what's so mad? Yeah.
Is this [ __ ] [ __ ] right? This launch
legs is flashing 200 pound. I'll just
I'll do a 200 pound spin on roulette
right now. But I've quit gambling. So,
but I'm tempted. I'm [ __ ] tempted, Grezy,
just to put 200 quid
on on a spin. Just to be a little cheeky devil, Grezy.
And I know that's definitely not okay
with Grezy, is it, boss?
Yeah, that's definitely not okay with Breezy.
I don't even need to ask. He straight
away know. Is it
breezy? That's not okay with you, is it, boss?
Okay with you, boss.
Yeah. So what I'm what? Yeah. But what
I'm asking you, are you still going to
gamble in football? Yeah.
I'm going to be going out with this
thingy soon as well. So I need money. I
can't afford to lose money. I can't risk
I'm going to I'm going to go bowling
with her. Griezy, we're going to go bowling together.
Ice skating. Bowling. How cute is that? Grezy,
how cute is that? Grezy,
I think that's lovely if you ask me.
Some lovely bowling graves there. Yep.
That's what I'm going to be doing.
That's what I'm going to be doing, mate. God bless.
That's definitely okay with me, boss.
Rezy, do you remember that? Uh
I'm going to make a hot chocolate in a
minute, I think.
That nons legs is a weird character,
Smokey. A very weird character.
I don't need to get myself a job, bro.
I've got enough money.
I don't need to get any job, mate. If I
needed to get a job, I'd have a job.
Simple as that. You nosy Parker. I don't
need to get myself no job, lad.
I literally can work when I want. I
literally could work if I needed to, but
I don't need to, bro. So,
I could literally get a job.
Bro, I've got more. I've got more to
survive, bro. I've got I've got I get
more to surv, bro. Bro, I get enough I
get enough to enjoy enjoy life. I've got
enough to enjoy life.
Trust me, bro. Trust me. Trust me, bro.
Trust me, it's a little bit more than surviving, bro.
Depends what you mean. Thrive.
Depends what you mean. I mean, I can
afford to go on holiday.
Can afford to do what I want.
What woman? I don't know what. Yeah, I
saw something about that. Some emo on
Instagram. I don't know what he's talking about.
Don't know what he's on about, mate. I
don't know any Emma. Yeah, I saw that. I
don't know what the [ __ ] he's talking
about. Talking [ __ ]
The [ __ ] He said, "Why are you
commenting on someone
someone called Emma on Instagram?
The guy is a [ __ ] Don't Don't speak
to anyone called Emma.
He's talking a load of bollocks.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
Bro, but you don't understand. No, no,
no. But you don't understand is the more
money you get, the more you spend.
So, it doesn't really matter because any
money you get, the more money you get,
the more money you spend. And you're
going to want more money. Trust me, I've
had all different kinds of incomes and
that's the way it works. The more you
get, the more you spend, the more you want more.
Doesn't matter how much money you get.
That's the way it is. That literally is
That's literally the way it [ __ ] is.
I was getting [ __ ] over three grand a
month and I'm thinking, bro, this ain't
even enough for me.
The more you get, the more you you'll
get comfortable with what you get. Then
you'll want more with any amount you
get. That's the way it works.
3K a month is minimum wage. No, it's
[ __ ] not. Three grand a month is
minimum wage. No, it isn't. No, it
isn't, bro. Yeah. 3K a month for doing
3.2K a month for doing nothing. Yeah. 3K,
bro. That's not minimum wage. Over three
grand a month for doing nothing is is is minimum wage.
I don't think it's minimum wage, lad. I
get less than that now. And I do all right.
I do all right, lad. And I get less than that now.
Three grand a month isn't minimum wage, bro.
Most bro, even even electricians
probably probably electricians get about
three grand a month or like [ __ ] um
what's the other one called? Brick layers.
How is three grand a month minimum wage,
bro? What the [ __ ]
What? So three grand a month for doing
nothing is broky money? Are you being
for real, bro? Most people that work
don't even have three grand by the time
they've paid everything. No, they
definitely definitely don't. They
definitely definitely definitely don't.
By the time they've paid everything,
they definitely definitely don't have
three grand for the month.
And there's not many people that get
more than three grand a month.
Uh unless like a [ __ ] dentist or some
[ __ ] thing like that.
Yeah, unless they're like a dentist or Yeah.
I don't get three grand a month now, bro.
You adjust to any amount of money you get.
Yeah. Who is this emerald on Instagram? greasy.
Don't know what the [ __ ] he on what the
[ __ ] he's on about. Nah,
see you later. >> Weird.
Bro, you're coming across like a
fantasist now, Smokey B. I can't lie, bro.
You're coming across like a fantasist.
Hate to break it to you, bro. You You
kind of are.
To be hon You kind of are, lad.
Most people don't even get three grand a
month. They certainly don't have it
disposable. How can you say what the [ __ ]
That's I know they're proper skin. I had
[ __ ] Virgin boy showing me [ __ ]
200 [ __ ] quid.
Yeah, Virgin Boy was showing me [ __ ]
200 [ __ ] quid, lad.
What the [ __ ] bro?
That is mad. Showing me [ __ ] 200.
What the actual [ __ ] I couldn't believe
what I was seeing.
People are obsessed with money on this community, bro.
I wonder why. I wonder why.
I wonder why. Doesn't matter what my
plans are for the future. What's your
plans for the future?
Isn't that right, Steven Howard Grievy?
Let's start hearing about these people,
these people's lives.
Don't you worry what my plans are.
That's for me to know and you to never
find out. It's not being like you might
think I'm being awkward. Yeah. Like you
might think I'm being rude and I'm being
awkward, but I'm actually not. Like I'm
actually really really not.
Might think that, but I'm actually not.
was trying to say I've never had nine
grand. I have had nine grand about two
years ago. I have had nine grand.
That's good, bro. That's good.
They are, bro.
That's good, bro. If that's true,
Smokey, that's good.
I bet you don't earn more money than a
dentist, though. Do you, Smokey?
>> You know what I'm saying, lad? I bet you
don't earn more I bet you don't earn
more than a dentist.
You think you do? Nah.
No, you don't, bro. Dentists are on some
serious money, bro.
Dentists are on some serious money.
So then what if you have all of this
money? Why are you on here, bro? You
might as well just go and live your life.
I mean, I'm saving money right now, bro.
And I don't really want to go out
drinking and [ __ ]
But when I'm going out again, bro,
um I'm not going to be on it. Obviously,
I'm hardly on it anyways.
Why don't you go live your life, bro?
[ __ ] know what I mean. Jesus Christ.
[ __ ] madness, isn't it?
Yo, people messaging me, bro.
One second, please. Bro,
I'll end up homeless. I don't think so.
I don't think so, lad.
I don't think so, lad. I don't think so.
Oh my god, man. Stop this [ __ ]
talking. Skin, skin, skin, skin. It
doesn't matter what I'm going to do,
bro. You shouldn't even be worried about
Jesus [ __ ] Christ. Why are you so like concerned? Hm.
You need to mind your own business and
worry about your own life.
Am I lying, Steven Howard? Man,
you you need to focus on your own life.
That's what you need to do, bro. That's
the only signs that I'm getting. You
need to mind your own business. And I
mean, and I mean that in like the nicest way possible.
You're always bouncing off of other
people's lives. I've noticed that with
the people on here. Yeah. They're always
more concerned about other people's lives
than than their own life. Just face
facts your skin. Yeah, that's boring,
bro. Way to kill the chat.
How long have you people been on this
shitty community saying the same [ __ ]
15 years. 15 years, man. Time to get a
life, dads. Time to get a life.
Yeah, that's good for you, bro. If
you've got all you need then, isn't it?
>> That's good for you then, isn't it, lad?
I was only six hours last night. One second. Yeah.
One second, bro.
See you later.
You always say how people are skin ugly
on their life, but you are just saying
what you are, so why? No, I'm saying
what you people are.
Nah, bro. I'm saying um No, you listen
listen to me, bro. You people are on
here 24/7. You can't take a day off of
YouTube. I was I was off of YouTube the
other day. Yeah. For 9 days. You people
couldn't take one day off of YouTube.
It's all you got. Don't even try and
deny it, bro. Don't even try and deny
it. You can't even take one day off of
YouTube. And that is bad, bro. For
people that claim that they've got a
life. Yeah. You people can't even take
one day off of YouTube. That's a serious
serious problem. I could go live right
for 24 hours right now, but guess what?
I can take a day off of YouTube,
you know? And that's and that's that, you know.
But no, I'm not saying what other people
are. I'm saying what you people are
and what you've shown what you are when
you've been doxed. [ __ ] fat and ugly as [ __ ]
So like, do you know what, bro? I could
never ever tell anyone about this community, though.
I could never ever ever ever like tell
anyone about this community, bro. I
don't think anyone I know real life
knows about it. It's so It's so
disabled. Like, you couldn't even tell
anyone about it.
Nah, bro. I wouldn't take it. Why would
Why would I work for you, bro?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. You are the
ones that have got no life, bro. You are
the ones that come on here every day harassing people.
It says a lot about your lives. And
that's all I'm saying. I'm not saying
any more about it. I've said what I've
had to say, but bro, Smokey Beam, why am
I going to work for you?
I'm really going to [ __ ] work for
you. Come on, bro.
Jesus [ __ ] Christ, Smokeoky B. Come on, man.
There's a thing called pride, you know.
There's a thing called [ __ ] pride. You understand?
You ask me if I work for you.
Jesus Christ me.
Yeah. Yeah. That's nice, bro.
But you people on YouTube 24/7 all day, every day.
So, yeah. You people on YouTube all day, every day.
Yeah. And you should be out there living
your lives. I don't even know why we're
still talking about this. Like, we've
already It's already been proven that
you people can't take a day off of
YouTube. There's There's We don't even
know why we're talking about this.
Yeah. Yeah. I hate the truth. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Whatever. We're not
talking about this anyways. Um anyways,
Smokey B. Why? Why am I insane, bro?
Okay. We're going to start kicking these
people now, bro. Cuz we're having the
same We're having the same um argument
with these sad bastards.
We're going to start kicking these
people now, bro. Having the same argument. Yeah. I'm second.
Hey. Hey, Biddy Dundy.
Who is this [ __ ] Emma? What is this?
Who's this Emma L is talking about?
Don't know what the [ __ ] he's on about, lad.
Have a little browse. No. Hello.
Because how do you know I don't already
get a a couple of thousand a month, Smokey?
Think about it, bro. I only tell you
what I want you to know. Think about it. You see,
maybe I get 10 grand a month now.
Maybe I get £300 a month now. You You don't know.
You understand? You don't know people's lives, lad?
You get it? Do you get what I'm trying to say?
Okay. So, what what Okay. So, what is it
then? What job is it? Oh yeah,
[ __ ] Emma. Who the [ __ ] is Emma?
Must be making stuff up, man. I've been
commenting on someone called Emma's [ __ ]
What a stalker, bro.
This is why I never have any serious
women on my Instagram. Grezy,
I never have any like women that like,
you know, when I meet women, I never let
I never have them on Instagram.
I only ever get their number.
You get me, bro? Yeah.
So, where would I have to travel to? Nope. Uh-uh. No, Grezy.
Why' you ask? Nope.
So, where would I have to travel to and
where would we be going? No, bro.
No intro or Snapchat. Uh-uh.
Uh, why do you ask?
Oh, no, no, no. She's not on Instagram.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. If I approach women,
if they don't give me their number, then
I go for the Instagram.
Sorry, the Snapchat. I never I never add
people on Instagram. I just don't, bro.
Unless they're just like friends and
make friends and stuff, but it's it's
number or Snapchat, but usually it's the
number nine times out of 10
cuz people can't be found on uh
WhatsApp. It's encrypted, you see, Greavvesy.
So, you can't find people. Um,
no, I don't have people on No. Uh-uh.
No, I don't have many people on
Instagram who I've approached.
Right, let's have a look.
Do you trust this Smokey B Greavvesy? Do
you trust this Smokey Be Steven Howard?
You didn't send me an email, Dad. I've
just gone on it.
Nope. You haven't sent me an email, mate.
Right. You haven't sent me an email,
lad. Yeah, I've got your email, but
yeah, you've emailed me, but you haven't said about
where would I have to travel to and from.
Sorry. Who would where would I have to
travel to and where would we be going?
>> No. What I think he would do. Do you
want Do you want to know what I think he would do?
I don't think anyone's going to get it.
But do you reckon what this smoky be is
going to do? Steven Howard Greavesy,
I'll give you chance to say it before me.
Really use your brain.
I can tell you
what I think,
but you have to guess first.
Copy. What do you mean copy?
He will set me up with London Taylor.
It's so obvious.
It's so obvious, isn't it? It has to be.
There's no there's no other thing. I
remember Mike Cariggi tried doing it
before with the GV. He's like, "Oh, come
and have come. I've got some work for
you in that. Got some work for you in that, mate."
Nah, bro. You would set me up with LT.
It's too obvious. It's too obvious, bro.
It's too obvious, Loki. It's too too obvious.
You know what I'm saying?
You need to wake up pretty early to fool
me. Is that right, Grezy?
No, you'd set me up, bro. It's too obvious.
So, we've been beefing on YouTube for
all this time. And what? You're just
going to let me work for you?
You know what? You're just going to let
me start working for you?
Well, what would you trust it? Greavesy.
Would you trust it?
Well, we'll ask Grievy. Would you would
you trust it, Grezy? I always have to
run things by Greavvesy first.
Really? Who Who do you think he's going
to set me up with?
Who do you reckon he's he trying to set
me up with? Wister, it's got to be LT,
ain't it? It's too obvious, bro. It's
too obvious. It's too obvious. It's too obvious, man.
Come on, bro. Look at what that tenant
tried doing the other day.
So what? Someone you're beefing with,
you're going to offer them work.
Yeah. Someone that you was beefing with
for ages, you're going to offer them work.
Do you want my opinion, Greavvesy? Uh. Uh-huh.
They're all [ __ ]
Daryl [ __ ] That's my opinion. Nah, bro.
Okay. If you if you if you give me if
you give me a month's up front, then
I'll then I'll and I'll work for you, Smokey.
If you give me a month's money, I'll
work for you.
No, no, seriously. Seriously,
if you can say if you can send me the
money, I I I'll come. I'll come. So I
know that like you're not full of [ __ ]
I think that's a good idea, wasn't it?
I'll come to the landmark.
Grezy, I'll go to the landmark
and sort business up with this fellow.
With this little fellow
greasy. This little fellow.
It's funny, isn't it?
Seriously, if you give me some cash.
I know. I know it. It seems almost too
good to be true,
doesn't it? Griezy.
But anyways, if you send me money, bro,
um I'll come.
You need to send me Wonga, though.
You have to send me money, bro.
And then I'll come and I'll work for you and stuff.
play noise. Yeah. You want to go for a
or do you want to do it dirty?
I want to do it dirty. Z.
>> I agree with you. Seriously, what if
these people find um Christian is he?
There's there's no chance in it.
I agree with you. There's no chance, is
there? Huh? He said there's no chance. today.
What if they
where's what if they find her greasy?
No, I don't think I don't think they can in it. No. Nah.
Do you Do you actually think they're
going to be able to do it? I don't think
so, Grezy. No, seriously. Do you think
they could actually do it? H
Did you actually think they could do it?
Music? But they've got nothing.
They've got nothing to go by. They've
got nothing to go by. No. No name. They
don't know where they live. They They
don't know anything. Is it crazy?
No. Do you actually think that they'll
actually find her? We
I love to laugh, Greasy. I love to laugh.
But seriously, Greasy, what do you think? Huh?
You really want to know what I think?
No, but seriously, Gregy, what's the
chances? Like 1% in it.
What do you think? Like 1%.
You remember you remember they started
messaging Sig music. They started messaging sick.
They got me good and proper.
Good and proper.
No, but do you reckon they could they
could find her now? Grezy.
Good. Good. Good. Lucy. Good.
That's an old That's an old
That's an old saying, you know. Greasy,
when you when you get someone good and
proper. Have you ever heard that? Yeah,
for sure. Oh yeah.
Do you not remember that old saying
they call me good and proper
usually good and proper?
Well, I mean, right now, Breezy, do you
reckon they could find her right now?
Right. They don't know anything. The
name, nothing, do they?
I won't slip up.
No, I won't slip up now. Trust me. Some little,
you know, I'm not some little [ __ ]
virgin. Some little virgin me, mate.
You got a virgin.
Uh, yes sir. Yes, sir. Yes, captain.
Do a big thirsty copy chat. What?
No, Greezy. Listen, listen listen.
What was you thinking? It was like a It
was um It was an approach where
Yeah. They're not going to get one.
Not even my friend knows her name, bro.
Not even my friend knows her name.
No one knows her name, bro. Only me.
Cuz she's my mama. Grezy,
listen. Greasy. Why did you ask if it
was an approach
like where where you could um where you
could hear uh where you could see their face, right?
You mean like where they could see their face? No.
>> No, I won't slip up, bro.
The only person they found was [ __ ]
USA is he? They found Sig because of LT.
I gave LT the number.
Nah, they know nothing, mate. It's like,
you know, when they, you know, when
they, you know, when they went on um
Fraser's um Instagram, Greavves, I was
like, "Oh, yeah, maybe maybe um they
didn't get what they wanted." And he was
like, "No, they got what they wanted, mate.
They got all the info they wanted, mate.
Do you remember that? I said, "No, maybe
they didn't like they didn't get any
they didn't get everything.
Maybe um they didn't get everything that
they wanted." And he was like, "No, they
got what they wanted, mate." It's true,
though. They greasy when they were all
following Fraser on Instagram. They got
what they wanted, mate.
Praise. They got the lot, mate. the [ __ ] lot.
What do you mean they could have
mentioned something like where they're
from or something? >> Like
you mean like they'll mention where
they're from and that in it?
That's what you meant, is it? >> Yeah.
Is that what you meant, Grezy?
That's what you meant, is it? Uh, Greavvesy,
answer me, Greavvesy. Answer me.
Arms greasy. I'm sorry.
And you you fly mast cuntsy.
What do you mean? They might have
mentioned something like their name or
where they're from?
Is that what you mean? Grieve, Z,
you know what her name is? Her name's Izzy.
That's her name. Izzy. I told you her
name. Her name's Izzy.
There you go. That's her name,
Greavvesy. Her name is Izzy.
and you you fly master [ __ ]
Do you remember that one, Grezy? And
you, you fly master [ __ ]
That was [ __ ] That was good, wasn't it?
Thank you, you fly master cat.
>> Yeah, you still waiting for an added R upload.
You're still waiting graves.
What's going on,
Gregy? Silly goose.
What do you say? So, the money that I
get for the baby Greavesy, I'm going to
put it all on number 17
on roulette. Greavvesy,
you're such a funny soul.
You silly goose. That's not even my
favorite number. You silly goose.
>> My favorite number is um 11. Oh gosh.
Grezy, can I put £100 on online roulette?
Is that okay with you, boss? Wey bossy
is that okay with you bossy
I'm going to put £100 on online roulette
okay with you boss
okay with You [ __ ]
Okay with you, [ __ ]
It's okay with you, boss.
Okay with you, boss. Grezy,
is that not Can I put 100 pound on
roulette Grezy on that?
Is that not okay with you, boss then? Huh?
I can't deposit without Greavves consent.
Grievy, I was going mad earlier. I
didn't tell you, bro. I was on Reddit.
Yeah. And they were making excuses for
women again. Grieves.
They were saying that, "Oh, they led me
on and stuff because they felt
uncomfortable." And they were making
excuses for women. Greavvesy, I've had
enough of this, you know, Greavves. this
whole dating malarkey.
I've had enough of this dating malarkey we
because they just make excuses for
women. So I'm saying Grezy,
why do they keep making excuses for
women? It was happening again today.
Greavvesy, I want an explanation.
Crazy. Why do they make excuses for women? H
Where is it?
No, it happened again today. Grievy.
They were making excuses for women. I
swear to God, I was going mad. Lady had
to calm me down. They were making excuses.
What? What do you mean? Can I blame
them? Do you remember? Stay the hell
away from us.
Stay the hell away from us.
Remember, Grezy. Nope. I want to continue.
See what I mean?
Stay the hell away from us. Nope. I
don't want to.
You remember she said stay the hell away from us.
Why am I not allowed to light boobies? Greasy.
No, but no. No. What I'm saying, Grezy,
is I messaged someone earlier that
didn't see the post or anything and I
showed like the women leading me on and
they were making excuses for them. I'm
sick of this. I'm getting sick of this.
They make excuses for women.
Greg, you know it as well. You [ __ ]
know it. You know they do as well.
Gregy, that's what annoys me about you
is they know. You know they do. You know
they make excuses for women.
They were saying that, "Oh, they led you on because
they fel felt uncomfortable." No, no,
no. Always an excuse. You get me, Greasy?
There's always an excuse.
Yeah, but Grey, you're not
understanding. We're talking about the
people on WhatsApp that agreed to meet me.
We're talking about people that just disappeared, you know.
Live showing cash.
Really? Let me have a little look. Maybe
He's showing [ __ ] bum change. See
[ __ ] showing 300 [ __ ] pound.
Showing fucking£300. He's a [ __ ] skin flinch.
He is [ __ ] skint mate.
Uh, wrong central.
Bro, this guy is actually making a fool of himself,
bro. I can't stop laughing, bro. He's
actually he's actually making a fool of himself.
And these are the people that are
supposed to be laughing at me. Dusty,
this is great content.
The guy is
showing literally bum chains, bro.
Mate, that's not even £1,000,
bro. That's not even a thousand. The guy
don't even have £1,000 to his name.
Yeah, you run out of 20s now,
[ __ ] Bro, he don't even have a
grand to his [ __ ] name.
What the [ __ ]
Ah, there we go with a 10. You don't
even have a grand, bro. He doesn't even
have a fucking,000, bro. Don't make me
go to the Don't make me Yeah. No, it's
not. It's not 1.5 grand, bro. It's not
even a grand. He's run out of 20s. He's [ __ ] kidding.
That's nowhere near 1.5 grand.
He is [ __ ] skin as [ __ ] bro. Jesus Christ.
No, that's not 1.5 grand.
That's not even £1,000. What the [ __ ]
Bro, is this guy really trying to flex
that money, bro?
Is he really Is he really trying to flex
Is he really really trying to flex that
small amount of money, bro? Jesus Christ.
Bro, what the [ __ ] He's literally been
paid his housing benefit and he's
flashing money like he's got money. Bro,
this is [ __ ] hilarious.
He's He's showing his housing benefit off.
What the [ __ ] That is [ __ ] embarrassing, bro.
Very very embarrassing.
very very very em. That's that's a funny
that's a funny 13 grand is it mate? Yeah.
Does he realize he's he's making a fool of himself?
He's actually embarrassing himself. He
really really really I've got more money
than that, bro. I swear to God in my
mom's life, I've got more money than
that. And he and he's trying he's trying
to flex his housing benefit. Bro, this
is embarrassing, bro.
Yeah, I've got more than that, bro.
Greavesy. I've literally got more than
that. No, I don't need to do that,
Grezy. Cuz I've already beat him at the
money game. I swear to God, on my
[ __ ] dead dad, my mom's life, bro,
I've got more than that. And if I
didn't, I say I I would say I don't have
more than that, bro. I'd say I don't
have that amount of money. I don't have
that money, bro. I swear to God, I I
have more than money than that, bro. But
the thing is, I done all of this two
years summer. Two years ago in the
summer, bro. I I got money out time and
time again, and no one showed me nothing.
Just a video from four years ago, bro.
So that's we're not playing their stupid
self-p projecting insecure games because
all that's going to happen is you show
more money than them again.
Then you show the money again and then
you show the money again. You put the
money back in the bank and then they ask
you to show the money again and it just
goes round and round and round and round in circles.
That is not 5.7 grand. Yeah. So like I
said, come back when you got 5.7 grand.
That is embarrassing, bro. Really embarrassing.
He's actually He's actually embarrassing himself.
He's actually embarrassing himself, bro.
It's funny to watch. He's embarrassing himself.
Yeah, I've got more money than that
ladder. P's got more money than that, mate. Oh,
pathetic, bro. It very pathetic. [ __ ] mad.
Yeah, bro. Red Star, stop this and stop
that, but yet you're the one that can't
show more than a grand. Isn't that
Doesn't that tell you something? Yeah,
Steven Howard. Yeah, this guy claims
that he's had 13 grand and he's got all
of this money, but yet he can't even
barely show more than £1,000. And I've
got more than what he's showing. I've
literally got more money than what he's
showing, bro. What does that tell you?
And I bought Lego. I bought loads and
loads and loads and loads of [ __ ] I'd
have a lot more than And I've even got
more money than him.
Yeah, the guy is literally skint, bro.
[ __ ] absolutely skint.
Absolutely skint, lad.
Bro, the guy's [ __ ] skinned as [ __ ]
That is that is embarrassing, bro. Very
very very very embarrassing.
So at 31 years of age, all you got to
your name is £1,100.
Sad times, bro. Sad, sad, sad times. And
trust me, Steven Howard, I have got more
than that, bro. I can get money out the
bank, get 50s out, but there's literally no point.
There is literally no point because they
already got beaten at the money game.
We're not playing the games again.
They've already been beaten at the money
game. Joe got beaten at the money game.
He got beat at the money game. Lo got
beat at the money game. They literally
all got beat at the money game.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
Pointless. Absolutely pointless.
That is That is [ __ ] tragic, bro.
Because Rihanna is not attractive. And
the only reason you're saying that
Rihanna is attractive is because her
name is Rihanna.
Am I lying, Grezy? I'm watching this
live stream right now. I can answer
that. Uh cuz Rihanna is not attractive.
Um she's actually quite weird looking to be honest. Yeah,
she's literally not attractive. Rihanna
the singer. Yeah, she's not attractive.
So why is he saying that she's attractive? Greasy.
Why is he saying that she's attractive?
Grezy. So why is he saying that she's attractive? Mhm.
That's weird, isn't it? Yeah. I know.
Why? Why is he saying Rian is
attractive? Steven Howard,
let me see. Okay, let's see. Rihanna,
I don't think she's anything special.
I'm looking on her now
again. I don't see what's so special.
Why is he saying that she's attractive?
Does anyone know?
Why is he saying that Rihanna is attractive? Steven Howard
Well, mate, I'm watching this nonslegs
and I'm [ __ ] laughing at him. So,
yeah, bro, keep keep doing your content,
bro, because I've been pissing myself laughing.
I laugh at you people making a fool of
yourselves, man. So, I mean, yeah, keep
I quote, laughing at me, bro, cuz I'm
laughing just right back at you.
1100. You're showing off £1,100.
[ __ ] me, bro. That's embarrassing.
That is [ __ ] embarrassing, bro.
Very, very embarrassing.
disguise actually. Oh my god. Jesus Christ.
Greavvesy. Why is he saying that? Um
why is he saying that Rihanna is
attractive? Where's it?
Uh, nonslegs was saying that how can I
say that Rihanna is not attractive
on his live stream. Dusty, I don't find Rihanna attractive.
Why is he saying that she's attractive?
Dusty. Rihanna of all people.
Why Rihanna of all people? Dusty.
Yeah, Rihanna. I don't find Rihanna attractive.
Why? Why is he Why is he saying that? Dusty.
Greasy. Dusty. Anyone know why he's saying that?
Anyone? No. You just going to leave me hanging? Anyone know?
Yeah. Why is he saying is attractive? Grezy.
She says that I can't deny she's
attractive. He just said it now. How can
you say Rihanna is not attractive?
Can someone answer me? Like,
can someone bloody answer me?
Do I uh even
No, I don't find it attractive. No.
So, why is he saying if I don't find
Rihanna attractive, um, I'm uh I'm gay.
But no, bro. This whole money thing,
bro, I'm laughing at it because I've
already beat him at the money game. I
showed 5.7 grand and he had nothing to
show. No one had anything to show over
that summer. So, I don't need to
withdraw money. I don't need to show
anyone money. And I know that, bro.
That's the truth. So, I laugh at it,
bro. It's actually been good content.
You haven't shown five grand of your own
money, mate. You've been beating at the
money game already.
You can keep pretending that you
haven't, but that's on you, man.
We already know, mate, that these people
got beaten at the money game
multiple multiple multiple times. Listen,
I'm not doing a video, bro. I'm going to
let him keep making a fool of himself.
It's It's good content.
It's good content, bro. I mean, look at
him, bro. Look Look at him. Yeah, he's
[ __ ] No, I'm not showing no money.
I've already shown money and that never
made a difference. I'm never showing
money again. I literally said this about
a year and a half ago. I'm never ever
showing money again.
I will never show anyone any money ever
on this community
because they've already been shown money
and every time you show them money, they
run away. Think about it, Stephen
Howard. Yeah. When was it? Not last last
year. The year before that. All that
time I was showing money before I put it
in the bank, did any of these people
show me any money? They never showed me
any money. So, we know that it's a waste
of time. We're not going to go to the
bank and [ __ ] withdraw a load of
[ __ ] money just to go through the
same thing again. We learned our lesson
two years ago that when you show them
money, they all run away.
And they had multiple chances.
Multiple multiple multiple chances to
show me money, bro. That the degree they
had multiple chances, lad.
They had multiple multiple multiple
chances to show money and they never
they never. So, bro, I'm not showing
them no money,
bro. It's not about that, Grezy. I'm
just not showing them money, period.
I'm not showing them money, period. Until
they beat my top, until they beat what I
showed and they count it out, then I got
to show them nothing. Simple as that. Which is which is
how much is it? Uh
[ __ ] it's like 11,000 and something.
So until someone shows me that money in
cash and they count it out, I'm I'm I'm
excluded from the game. Simple as that.
You they got shown money multiple
multiple times and they all ran away
every single time. I'm not showing no
money. I don't need to prove myself to
anyone, bro. If people don't think I've
got money, then don't think I've got
money. Even better for me.
I will never show money ever again.
They got shown money multiple times,
bro. Multiple times. Two grand, three five grand, four grand.
And they all ran away. They never had
anything to show me. So,
yeah, man. That's it. I'm done.
Oh, 11 £1,100, bro.
It was £1,100. Steven Howard
That's not That's not over 10 grand what
you should be showing.
That's not That's literally not 10 grand
what you should be showing. These people
got beaten at the money game multiple
times for the longest time possible,
bro. It's not on me to show anything.
It's not on me to show nothing. I'm not
showing no money, bro. So, that's it.
You can say I'm skin. Okay, whatever.
Simple. I'm not showing no money.
We've been there, done it. We've been
there, done it, won a t-shirt multiple
times with these people.
So, yeah, man.
Yeah. I'm not playing this stupid
autistic money game again.
Yep. I showed [ __ ]
money, bro. Multiple multiple times.
Isn't that right, Steven Howard?
Never ever showing money again, Dad.
Never ever ever ever ever
showing money again.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
But it was good content, bro. I like
that. It was funny laughing.
That was good content.
Good content, bro. Yeah.
Why am I going to go to Why am I going
to go to the bank Greavesy and take out £1,500
when he hasn't shown me over 10 grand of
his own money? That's not the way the
money game works.
which I'm sure you know that's the way
you know the way the game works. That's
not what that's not the way the money
game works. You got shown three grand, 2.5 grand,
1,800, 5.7 grand over the space of a
year period. And no one doubled it.
Literally nobody doubled it when I had
that money. So, why am I going to go out
and withdraw £1,500 when you still
haven't beaten me? That's ridiculous,
bro. That's That's so stupid.
If you're going to play the game, at
least beat the person first.
You understand, bro? Like, that's it. Yeah.
It doesn't matter whose money it was.
You haven't beat me at the money game. I
have not been beaten at the money game.
I literally have not been beaten, bro.
Until someone shows cash, which is
Well, let's just say it's 1140,
1100. And no, it's I don't even know how
how we do that. Basically 10 grand.
Until someone shows 10 grand cash now
talking and counting it, then they ain't
beat me. Simple as that. It is as simple
No, it doesn't count. It needs to be
cash. It needs to be £10,000 in cash.
Yeah, it needs to be £10,000 in cash.
that is embarrassing, bro. Having £1,100
to your name, that is that is embarrassing.
£1,100 to your [ __ ] name.
backy skint and a [ __ ] skin flinch.
Skint and a [ __ ] skin flinch.
So Dusty, why was he saying um
Rihanna um Rihanna is attractive
Dusty? And no, it has to be cash. Dusty,
it can't be a check. It has to be It has
to be It can't be um a check. It has to
be cash. So why was he saying that? Um,
she uh she's attractive.
I never really found her that attractive
to be honest.
Does anyone know why he was saying that
Rihanna is attractive? I didn't find her
all that attractive. Hello, anyone?
And now you're making excuses. We can
just go around in circles, bro.
We're going around in circles with this
autistic money game [ __ ] again. Why
would anyone want 10K in cash? It's the
same argument, bro. We're moving on from this.
Yeah, we're moving on from this anyways, lad.
Either you show 10 grand in cash or [ __ ]
off. End the story.
It's just the same argument.
This is exactly the same argument.
You understand what I mean, Grezy? It's
the same argument, isn't it? Well, if
you don't have 10 grand, then you don't
have 10 grand. Okay, move on.
that's cool, man.
Yeah, that's that's nice for you, man.
So, you got 1.5,000
in your bank of 3K and savings. Interesting.
That's very interesting.
That's very interesting. Very interesting indeed.
You right, Joseph Fur.
No, it has to be Cash.
It has to be Cash. Joseph Fra. Oh,
sorry. Joseph [ __ ] I made I made a
new name for you. Joseph [ __ ]
Hope you like it. I was bothered using
the same [ __ ] Ferrar. We're going to
call you Joseph [ __ ] now. Your
boyfriend was just live showing, 1100 pound.
Oh my god. It's like banging your head
against the [ __ ] wall. You got 1100
pound to your name. You're [ __ ]
skinted in a [ __ ] skin, Flint, son.
No, you can't. You can't see anything.
You're not allowed to see anything, Joe. No,
no, you're not allowed, lads. Sorry.
Sorry, Joseph Ferra.
Sorry, Mr. Ferra.
Sorry, Mr. [ __ ]
Did you like that, Mr. [ __ ] Yeah.
I'm not going to Harriut.
I'm not coming to Harriate,
mate. You can come and see me. Yeah. You
You Do you know what makes me laugh?
Yeah. Every comment about me. Every
every comment the other day was about
me. And I'm thinking, bro, you know
where I live. You know, like that's is
mad how you're commenting every day, but
you know where someone lives. You ain't
tried to come to London once. You won't
meet me in Nottingham. Bro, you're a [ __ ] house.
You're a [ __ ] house. I told you I'll
meet you in Nottingham. It's as simple
as that. I will meet you in Nottingham.
And that's it. And I'll [ __ ] do you
in, you [ __ ]
Yeah. I [ __ ] have you. I love you,
you dirty [ __ ] Yeah.
Oh, you're never going to my mom's door,
bro. You wouldn't come to my door if I
live by myself. For [ __ ] sake. You're
really You're Bro, you're really going
to use that excuse, Joe. You're really
really going to use that excuse that I
live with my mom. Oh, bro. Come on. Come
on, bro. How long did I live by myself?
How long did I live by myself? Don't
even use that excuse. Just say that
you're you're never coming to London.
Just say you're never coming to London.
That's it. Don't try and say that you're
not coming to someone's mom's door. I
lived by myself for [ __ ] years and
you still never come then you little [ __ ]
You never come. Even when I lived by
myself. When I lived by myself, you didn't come.
How many times I lived by myself? You
didn't come. So, you know, at the end of
the day, bro, it's uh Yeah. You You're
never meeting anyone, bro. You won't
come to Nottingham. Yeah. You're not
going to come to Nottingham. I said I'll
meet you in Nottingham. Yeah,
I [ __ ] and I'll take I'll spank your
ass, bro. I will pull your trousers down
and spank your ass. Yeah, trust me. I
I'll spank your ass, bro. Yeah. And I'll
laugh in your face.
Yeah. That's why you won't meet me.
That's why you won't [ __ ] meet me.
Yeah. That's why you won't meet me, lad.
You're a [ __ ]
Why don't you meet me in Bristol,
Joseph [ __ ] Why Why don't you meet me in Bristol?
Come and meet me in Bristol.
No. No. Let
Why do you come and meet me in Bristol?
A Bristol meet up. Is that right? Yeah.
Why don't you come and meet him in Bristol?
He robbed me. No one's ever robbed me
and no one's ever laughed at me. I think
you'll find that I took the last rent
money and I never gave them their money
back. So, no one's ever robbed me. Thank
you very much. I think you'll find that
I robbed them out of the last bit of rent money.
So, yeah, get your facts right, mate.
Um, and you didn't know who I live with
either, bro. So, shut the [ __ ] up.
When am I not When am I um in
Nottingham? You'll just have to wait, Joe.
You'll just have to wait for a community
post or a video of me giving notice.
You'll just have to wait, Grezy.
They robbed my Yeah. an almost empty
bottle of Savage. Yeah, they did. But I
had 300 pound out of them.
So I mean I had
no hold on. How much of money did I
have? Yeah. I had like £300 400 out of
them. The last rent. Yeah. And the
bottle was almost finished. Yeah. They
done it when I was out. You [ __ ]
[ __ ] They didn't do it in front of
me. They done it when I was out. Okay.
Yeah. So what? And I had 40 pound out of
them. So what?
They didn't they didn't gang up on me
and rob me, you [ __ ] [ __ ] I was
out the house. I come back and it was
missing. Yeah. Okay. What was I supposed to do?
And I got £400 out of them anyways.
I got the last rent out of them before
telling them. So yeah,
I would have paid them back if they
didn't steal the after shave. I would
have paid them back. But yeah, so I got
the last laugh, but I just had to put
him in his place cuz technically he
stole my Yeah, he stole the after shave.
Yeah, when I was out the house
cuz he did. So what? H
the after shave is worth £100. I got
£400 out of them. So what?
Listen, why won't you come to Nottingham?
And when they were trying to get the£50,
didn't you understand what they were
trying to get the50 for? You [ __ ] He
was asking me for £50 so he could keep
it. I wasn't born yesterday. I'm not
stupid. Why do you think that he was
asking me to lend him money?
So he could use that money to give back
to the person that
um says I owe them money or just keep it for themselves.
It's so obvious. Oh yeah,
I'm not stupid.
far from stupid lad.
And I'll tell you what, Joe, I've had more boobies.
I've had more boobies than you will ever
have. You've got a fat ugly misses.
Okay, let me see if he's shown 10 grand cash, right?
Let me see. Showing money, has he?
Nice. That's not 10 grand cash. Next.
See you later.
Yeah, the only tits I've seen is Elanes.
Good one, bro. Good one. Yeah, nice
money, bro. But that's not 10 grand. So,
we'll move on. Like I said, bro, you
need to understand how the money game
works. I'm sick of explaining this over
and over and over again.
You know, someone shows money, you double
You double the money.
Five grand. Show 10 grand. Yeah, we'll
show cash. When you show me my £10,000,
I'll show cash. Moving on. Simple. You
show me £10,000 in cash and come back to me.
See you later. Yeah.
Joseph Ferrar's a lavong.
Bro, you made it too obvious, man. You
could have actually been a good troll,
you know. Joe, you actually could have
been like a good troll. But you gave you
gave yourself away too easy.
No, no, no. It's not him done because
I've already shown thousands more than
what he's shown. And you still talk
[ __ ] It's not happening again. I'm not
playing your stupid silly little games.
I'm not playing your stupid silly little
games. You all got owned a couple of
summers ago when you got shown thousands
and thousands and thousands and you all
run off. So yeah, I'm not playing your
silly games again. You've already been
done multiple times. But what what you
people when you get done, you come back
for more and pretend that you've won.
It's a waste of time. You people are
literally a waste of everyone's time.
It's literally a waste of everyone's
time because when you get shown money,
you run away and then you come back and
start all over again. Like you ain't
just lost for the millionth time. You're
point it's pointless. You're actually
pointless. It's literally pointless.
Okay. Yeah. I'm skin, bro. I'm skin.
Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Thank you, bro. I'm
skin. If If you calling me skin gets me
out of playing your stupid little silly
games. Yes. I'm skin. Very skinn. I'm
I'm starving, bro. I'm starving.
I'm starving, lad. Fair. I'm starving, bro.
Did anyone give me £10? Yeah, I'm skinn,
bro. Yeah, very skinned. Are you happy
now? Did that Does that give you an erection?
No. Joe, you gave yourself away too easy.
Yeah. See you later. Go get a life.
No. No. No. No. No, I'm completely
skinned. Can someone give me£10? I'm
really I'm I'm starving, bro. I'm I'm
I'm starving. I'm really starving. Can
someone give me some money?
Come on, Joe. Stop being stupid. You all
got You all got beat in the money game
literally two years ago. You got beat.
You got beaten badly and now you're
you're coming back for more when you've lost.
Only you would think that you've won.
Only you would literally think that
you've won. Why are you asking people to
show you money when you've already been beat?
That's stupid as [ __ ]
Do you know why people This is why
people call it an autistic community.
You see? Well, Monty just copies people.
He's a little copycat. But, you know,
that's why people call it a disabled community.
You get beaten and then you come back for more.
What the What the [ __ ] Oh gosh.
You didn't prove me wrong on anything, lad.
You didn't prove me wrong on anything.
Uh, it's just an autistic thing people
do on here.
Basically, what it is is people are
skinned and then they ask you to show
money because they ain't got no money.
It makes them feel better about
themselves being skinned. It's very very very disabled.
It's very very disabled. I'll be honest.
I've got a couple of,000 and that's it.
I'm not showing anyone nothing. Believe
it. Don't believe it. That's on you.
That's uh that's on you, lad.
Yeah, I pretend I'm something that I'm
not. Really? What? What do What am I pretending?
What What am I pretending? Huh?
What? What am I pretending?
This will be interesting.
Stay the hell away from us, Grezy. No, I'll continue.
Do you remember Griezy? No, I'll continue.
Okay. What? What? I mean, what
disabilities do I have?
Okay. I've got disabilities. What
disabilities are that?
Well, what disabilities?
Yeah. I'm agrophobic.
Yeah, bro. I'm agoprophobic. I'm I'm agriphobic.
Yeah, I'm agrophobic.
How do you know I'm agrophobic, bro?
Yeah, I'm I'm agriphobic.
Yeah, I'm very agobic. I've got anger
issues. Does that count?
I mean, I've got anger issues if that counts.
I mean, I've got anger issues.
Does that Does that count as a disability?
No, I'm not autistic.
If I was autistic, I wouldn't have been
with normal women. I wouldn't have
normal friends. Yeah. Look at Okay.
Okay. I I don't even want to bring this
[ __ ] into this, bro. But yeah,
right. Listen. Right. Look at N legs and
then look at me.
Yeah. No, no, no. I'm not even because
we're talking about autism. Look at Nles
legs who has to go for disabled people.
Can't function in normal environments.
Then look at me,
bro. I don't have autism.
Well, I don't know what it is from
something else, but
I woke up today and I wanted to [ __ ] strangle someone
cuz of the roulette last night. Grievy.
Because of the roulette last night.
No, you're not blocked, Joseph. We can
see your little comments.
We asked I asked you a question. You
said I pretend I'm something I'm not.
What am I pretending?
What am I pretending, bro? What? What am
I pretending that I'm that I'm not?
You make excuses for women.
I haven't seen it. We I haven't seen any
of your new messages, but you make
excuses for women.
You and Ricky Millington make excuses for women.
Oh, he makes excuses for women. Joe
Yeah, that's nice. Bri, we've seen it
already. UK silent.
Yeah, we've seen it already.
Well, yeah, we've everyone here has seen
it. £1,100. Yeah. And guess what? I've
got more than £1,100,
bro. How's that one?
I've got more than £,100y, lad.
No, just tell us what it is.
Tell us what it is.
[ __ ] £1,100. What the [ __ ] bro?
You showing £,100 thinking that's any
money? [ __ ] hell. It gets worse and
worse and worse. But do you know what?
It's not all about just money. It's
about life experience. Like he's got no
life experience. He's 31. He lives in a
bedsit. Ain't traveled anywhere. Ain't
been to any nice restaurants. Ain't been
to any nice venues.
What a waste of [ __ ] life.
What a waste of life, boss.
What a waste of Why don't you come in
the hangouts and have a chat, Joe?
Why don't you just come in the chat? Uh
the the um the the the hangouts and have
a little chat.
What about that? Have a little chat. I'm
up for a little chat.
I'm up for a little chat, Joe.
I'm up for a little chat.
Is it okay if uh Joe joins the hangouts? Squeezy
for a little chat?
What? talking to someone's. Well, mate,
I'm sure if you've got a channel
dedicated to another man, I'm sure you
can come on the Hangouts and have a
little chat like Triple H does, like
Lord Jay does, like Virgin Boy does,
like Bomb has,
like Jay Willow has,
you know? Okay. like them little characters have,
you know, like them little characters have.
Why can't you do the same? Huh?
Okay, we're not putting any voices on,
so why don't you come on?
No, no, no. Why don't you come on? Why
don't you come on the Hangouts?
Grezy, would you say Nons is autistic? Yeah,
he's proper autistic in it. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, of course he is. He's proper autistic.
Yeah, he is, bro.
He's the proper smacker, that one.
Money man doxed his new address.
So what is he back in Plymouth?
He's back He's back in uh Plymouth,
isn't he? Grezy. Yeah.
This [ __ ] madness.
Nons is a really really really bad s.
Joseph Ferrar. Like he's a proper proper bad s.
Proper proper bad s. Yeah.
So, Greavvesy, why was he saying that
I'm weird because I don't find Rihanna
attractive? You didn't answer me.
You never answered.
He said it on the live stream just now.
He said, "I can't deny that Rihanna is attractive.
Maybe I just don't like black women.
Maybe I don't find black women attractive.
You know, Greavvesy,
what do you think of that? Greavvesy.
UK asylum. Why is he saying that about Rihanna?
It's weird because I don't find her attractive.
Why? Why is he saying that? Can anyone answer? Anyone?
I'm going to have to stop blocking
people now if they don't answer.
I've been waiting now for ages and no
one's answering me.
I'm trying to get to the bottom of it.
Griezy, don't make me time you out for 5 minutes.
You're on your last legs.
Don't make me time you out.
Can you answer me? UK signing. Why is he saying that?
Why is he saying if I don't find Rihanna
attractive that I'm gay? No, I'm weird.
Sorry. He's saying that it's weird and stuff.
I want answers.
No one answers. What's the point? Yeah.
Yeah, but Yeah, but Nleg says it's weird
that I said that she's not attractive.
Why? Why is he saying that?
It's not her name or anything, is it, Greasy?
It's not because she's famous, is it?
What the [ __ ]
What the Who the [ __ ] is that?
I don't know who the [ __ ] that is, mate. [ __ ] knows.
But is anyone going to answer me or
what? Bro, you're leaving me [ __ ] hanging.
Dusty, why is he saying it's weird that
I don't find Rihanna attractive?
No, I don't know who the [ __ ] she is.
But can anyone answer me this? Cuz it's
a bit weird.
No, that definitely wasn't one of my
chicks, bro. O, Steven Howard, can you
tell me why?
He says that if I don't find Rihanna
attractive, I'm weird.
Yeah. Why is he saying it though? Steven Howard.
>> Yeah. Why is he saying it, do you think?
Why is no one answering?
No, I just want to know like
why he's saying it. Is it because the
person's name's Rihanna?
Is it cuz her name's Rihanna?
Or is it because he actually thinks that
she looks good?
Or is it because her name's Rihanna?
That's the bit we're trying to
understand. UK asylum. You get it?
That's the point we're trying to understand, mate. Hey,
that's the bit I'm trying to actually understand.
I think it's just to fit in.
I just think it's to fit in.
Yeah, I've had a good day.
Yeah, I've just been chilling and stuff.
I don't know. It's Chinese. Greavvesy,
>> I had to try these today. Greavvesy.
Yeah, I had a I had a Chinese today.
Any opinion on that?
No. Me and Greaves is on a diet. We're
not having nuggets. No.
Any opinion on that?
Oh, that KSI does Britain's Got Talent
now, ain't it, Greavvesy?
He's a judge on uh Britain's Got Talent, ain't he?
Yeah, I see that.
Yeah, I've seen that on. I've seen that.
you know nonslegs don't know don't know
who KSI is.
I said, "Have you been living under a
rock? You [ __ ] virgin. Meow.
You [ __ ] burning [ __ ]
It's been at the cinema. Yeah. Oh, bless. Poor [ __ ]
Is it greasy?
Greasy, you poor [ __ ]
No takeaways um tomorrow, Grezy. No takeaways, lad.
I am watching these cat I'm watching
these cat memes on Instagrams. Have you seen him?
I'm going to have to send you one.
They're pretty cool.
I'm going to send you it.
These cat memes.
Looks like the virgin [ __ ]
The virgin [ __ ]
I'm going to send it to you.
How do I send it to you, Grevy? One sec.
All right, Greavves. Go on it. I sent
it. I sent it. Greavvesy, go on
Instagram. Quick, quick, quick.
It looks like the virgin [ __ ]
Looks like the virgin [ __ ]
Looks like the virgin [ __ ] Rezy, go on Instagram.
O Dusty, do you remember that account?
Looks like the virgin [ __ ]
You remember that?
Them [ __ ] were laughing at us, mocking us.
No, it looks like your mom.
Who does it remind you of? Greavvesy.
See you later.
Who does it remind you of?
Oh, there's a there's a rock one.
There's a rock one.
Have you seen the rock one?
Oh, UK asylum. It looks like the virgin [ __ ]
Looks like the virgin [ __ ]
You know what I mean by that? UK asylum.
Just looks like the virgin [ __ ]
Have you seen the rock meme,
Grezy? Where it's like,
did did you see it?
Shut up, [ __ ]
Did you see it?
I don't know what it's called, but I see
it. Somebody was sending me. Someone
sent it earlier.
Thank you, K. One second.
Oh, here it is.
Grievy, I sent it to you. All right, I
sent it to you, Greavves. I sent it.
Go Power Ranger.
Go Power W Ranger. I'll send it to you
on Instagram. Reeves. Oh, bless.
All right. Go on it, Grezy. I sent it to
you on Instagram. I want you to go on it
right now if you don't mind.
Right now if you don't mind,
do you know who that is? UK silent the rock.
You might not know who he who he is, right?
I like that. That's pretty cool. Woo! Oh! Woo!
He's he's an overall [ __ ] Mom
looks like the virgin [ __ ] That cat,
you know. Huh?
I said that cat looks like the virgin [ __ ]
Poor [ __ ] No, no, wait. without [ __ ]
Oh boy. My little nest.
I love it. I love it, mate. Did you see
it? What I sent you, Boozy? Trump. Who's Trump?
I don't know who that is.
I don't even know who that is. No.
Trump. Who's that?
I hear that all the time. That name. I
don't know who that is.
Is this some sort of like band or some [ __ ]
Trump. Who's that?
Who? What is that groovy? I hear that
everywhere. Is it some kind of like band or something?
Who is it? What? What is it? Oh,
I've never heard of him.
No, I've never heard of him.
Oh, really? I didn't know. I thought I
thought the last that I knew the
president was Obama.
There's a new president now. I didn't know that.
I thought it was I thought it was still Obama.
Ah, that's why we hear about this guy so much.
I thought I thought Obama was the president. President of Oh, yeah.
That's why people keep talking about him. Ah.
Never seen this guy in my life.
Never seen this guy in my whole life, bro. No,
I thought it was still Obama.
I want to do like a little quiz night
on YouTube where we do like a quiz and
everyone answers questions.
I got some questions right on the chase today. Grievy,
I got some questions right on the chase.
I'm good at questions.
Yeah, I'm good at questions.
I'm good at geography. Grezy,
I don't know who that Trump is. I've
never heard of that Trump. Oh, interesting.
We should do a little quiz night. Would
you be up for that, Grezy? Quiz night.
So, what did you think of my Reddit
thing earlier? I wasn't trolling, was I, Grezy?
I wasn't trolling on Reddit, was I, Grezy?
I'm I'm good. I'm I'm good at geography,
Grezy. I'm very good at geography.
What continent, right, is is mo has got
the most flags with a cross.
I got this right earlier on the chase.
I got a couple of Minecraft run ones
right as well.
Do you know what continent? Nope.
Come on. Have a think, bro. It's not
that [ __ ] hard.
It's not Africa.
I knew it.
Yeah, sure. Yeah. Yep.
Yep. It is Europe. Pancake day.
Pancake day, isn't it?
I don't know why I just said that. It's
got to be pancake day.
I don't know. I love pancakes. Pancake day.
Was I right?
I sure can, Captain. Yep.
But we we're going to go on a new
channel soon. Uh Greavvesy, Stephen
Howard, we're going to go on a new
channel soon. Yeah, me and Greavves
talked about this.
We're going to go on a new channel soon
where it's just um where it's just the
brothers. So, we're going to be doing
that soon. Yeah.
What community is it so far, Grezy? What
community is it so far?
Why is it so far just normal? Is it?
Well, did I get it right? The panc Did I
get it right? pancake there.
I got it right. Right.
This is a copycat community. Yeah.
You know, I said to this woman earlier
who I've been speaking to about [ __ ] and stuff,
I said, "Can you come and suck my dick
and tell me I'm the best in the world
and that you love me?"
She said, "That's a bit extreme. Love
you two for four." Haha. X. I would
never say that unless I was actually in
love with you. How's your day been?
That's not very nice.
I want cuddles and to be told I'm the
best in the world. Greezy,
I want to be told I'm the best in the world.
I want to be satisfied and be told and
and I want them to apologize on behalf
of all women that have done me wrong.
Greasy. No, I'm not a narcissist. I just
want to be told I'm the best.
I'm the freaking best. Greasy.
I want to be told I'm the freaking best.
these these women uh on Reddit earlier,
Dusty, they said stay the hell away from us.
I said I only wanted women for one
thing, Dusty. And I was like, stay the
hell away from us. Me and Greasy was
laughing at it.
You really are unhinged. Yeah.
No, I'm not nar I'm not a narcissist.
Why? Cuz I want to be told I'm the best.
I just want to be told I'm the best.
Stay away from us.
Yeah, but I don't want to stay away. Grievy,
What do you think of that, Greavvesy?
Maybe I don't want to stay away.
No, I want to be told I'm the freaking best.
Yeah, yeah, I know, Greavves. Yeah, I
know. I know. I just got your Instagram.
I just want to be I just said to this
woman earlier on Instagram, "Can you
keep me warm for the winter?"
She said, "You got a breeding kink or something."
She said, "I'm crazy."
She told me that I was crazy. I said, "Nope, I'm lovely.
I'm going to put a crown on my head as
well, Grezy. I'm the king."
How do you feel about that, Grezy? I'm the king. Yep.
I want to be treated like a king.
How do How do you feel about that, Grevy?
That's lovely, Grezy.
You think when I c when I'm offline, I
laugh about the stuff I say and I don't mean it. Grezy,
nah, I'm serious about everything I say,
bro. I'm not a troll. I'm actually not a
troll, bro. Like, you might think I'm a
trolling, but I'm actually not.
Yeah, but Greavvesy, I'm not trolling.
I'm really not trolling.
I said to this woman in California, I
said, "I want you to come to London and
suck my dick and tell me I'm the best
man in the world.