Yummy.
Absolutely [ __ ] yummy. Absolutely delicious.
That was good. Listen,
just like a nice sav chip, some ribs,
some beef jag.
That was yummy. Oh gosh, I'm bit tired now though. Gosh,
nice savoy, nice chips, nice ribs, bit
of beef tain with spice. Oh gosh,
I'm stuffed, man.
Now I'm having a lovely cup of
this thing up. Yeah, from tomorrow I'm
going to come off of YouTube for seven
days and then I'm going to come back and
see who's been on there. And if I see
you people on there, I'm going to go [ __ ] mad
because I don't know why all of these
rich people with better lives are on YouTube 24/7.
They'll have a lot to bloody answer to,
mate. When I [ __ ] come back,
bro, I'll be back tomorrow. Did I take
eight days off of YouTube?
What was it last week? Uh uh uh. One
second. One second. One second. One
Did I already prove that I can take over
a week off of YouTube, but you people
can't take a day off of YouTube?
Am I right or am I right?
Let's see who can stay off YouTube the longest
starting from tomorrow. Yeah. Let's see.
Let's see who can stay off the longest.
Let's see if you people actually have
got a life.
Are you straight on YouTube?
Yeah, we will see. We [ __ ] will see,
mate. We [ __ ] will.
We [ __ ] will see, mate. Yeah, we
[ __ ] well will.
Oh [ __ ] bro. That was lush.
Them chips were yummy.
I was just watching Britain's Got Talent.
I was watching Britain's Got Talent.
What the [ __ ] bro?
That KSI is the permanent judge now. Is he?
Is he a permanent Is he a permanent judge
on that uh on Britain's Got Talent? I
haven't really watched that, but it was
on. So, I thought Oh [ __ ]
Tim, stop embarrassing yourself.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Imagine
getting h happy over 800 quid. [ __ ] hell.
Tiffy, stop embarrassing yourself.
[ __ ] hell. Yeah, I lost 20 pound and
I was depressed for about 7 hours. I'm
still kind of depressed over it.
Yeah, I lost 20 pound on the fob tease,
bro. And it ruined my whole day. I
didn't manage to do any food shopping,
any football bets. It made me depressed. Yeah.
Yeah, PJ the virgin. Yeah, calling me a
virgin even though I prove I've had sex.
That's lovely, bro.
Yeah, I think I'm going to come off this
community, Bob Bills.
I've got a new channel, lad,
and about five or six people only are
going to know about it. I'll be off this
community soon, brother.
Very very weird. Repeating gay. Yeah, bro.
I'll be off here soon, lad.
Too disabled for me, bro. Yep. Yeah. [ __ ] hell.
You'll rob him. You won't get anything
cuz you don't have nothing.
Yeah. They've got nothing in their life,
bro. Nothing. They're on here all day,
every day, from the time they wake up to
the time they go to bed. They're just
jealous gay people and nothing in life.
What they do is so weird. If they
weren't jealous of people, they wouldn't
talk about people. Their life wouldn't
revolve around other people if they
weren't jealous. Think about it, bro.
If their if their lives were better than
yours, they wouldn't do what they do.
They wouldn't talk about people the way
they do. You get it? Yeah,
the jealous losers
basically. Yeah, bro.
Why is he talking about [ __ ] robbing
nonslegs? What the [ __ ] What is Timmy on about?
Yeah, they haven't got a life, bro. The
same with that Jo. I Bro, listen. I woke
up. Yeah, I woke up uh today and my
phone died. My phone's always dead when
I wake up for some reason. I went
downstairs. I made a tea. Yeah. I come
back up. I turn my phone on, bro. I went
on L J's. It popped up. I don't know why
it popped up. And Jo was making comments
about me. Every comment was about me.
I'm thinking, geez, bro. Come out the closet already.
This guy is a gay, bro. Proper proper
gay. Every comment was about me, bro.
They say they do it for reaction, but
that doesn't make sense because they
spend more time talking about you than
you spend on them. Don't forget, you're
you're giving your opinion on what they're doing.
They're the ones talking about me.
They're the ones obsessing over me and
I'm giving my opinion on it that they're gay.
How can they do stuff for reaction when
they react when they when they spend
more time on you than you do on them? It
doesn't even make sense. that.
Why is Timmy keep saying he's he's he's
going to rob nonslegs? He doesn't have anything.
He showed his daddy's life savings like
four years ago, bro, and kept showing
the same video.
He's talking about [ __ ] robbing someone,
but he doesn't have anything to rob.
Yeah. And the thing is, I do, you know,
the thing is, yeah, unlucky, you know,
you're never going to win with them
either. Think about it, bro. Yeah.
Non legs is showing £1,100. I showed £5.7,000.
And during that whole period of time of
me showing that money, not one of these
people showed me anything. And then
they'll come back on this community,
bro, with um less amounts of money
thinking that they've won. That's what
they do, bro. Every time. It doesn't
matter what the amount of money is.
They'll call you a virgin even though
you've proved you've had sex multiple
times. Um you can't win with them, bro.
You literally cannot win with them. Even
when they're wrong, they'll just come
back and act like they've beat you. You
You can't win with them, bro.
You cannot win with them. They've got
deep rooted jealousy problems and they're closeted.
They're [ __ ] weird, bro. Proper
weird. They're gay. Yeah, they're proper
24/7. They do this as well, bro. 24/7.
You wouldn't even do this to a woman you
was in love with if you was in love with
a woman. So, see, just just see it like
that, bro. See it like that.
Just put it that way, bro, for one
second and you'll see how weird it is.
That is strange. Yeah, it is very
But it is a disabled community. So,
what's Timmy saying now? Let me see.
I haven't done any more Lego.
I love how Timmy doesn't bring up the
£5.7,000 that was shown.
You don't find that funny? Unlucky.
No, it's funny how he doesn't bring up that.
I'm watching his live stream right now.
Isn't it funny how he doesn't bring up that
Yeah, he's going on about He's going on
about uh he's going on about nonsense basically.
That's funny, bro. That's funny.
Yeah, you just can't win with these
people, bro. You really, really, really
can't win with these people.
He's got an opinion on a Manta. Yeah,
I'm better looking than him. Better
looking than launch legs. Still calling
people a virgin even though they've
proven that they've had sex. You just
can't win with these people. It make it
makes you really think here what is the
point of being on a community, right,
where you can't win with people.
It really it does it does make you
wonder, is it like you don't make any
money from this, right? There's only about
five or six people, give or take, that
you talk to. I mean, it really like
there's lally just like no point in it, is there?
calling people mont that's better
looking than you. Calling people virgin
that's proved they've had sex. You just
can't win with these people.
Really really can't win with them, can you?
Can't win with them, lad. Can't with win
with disabled people. Yep.
I going to lie. I kind of lost kind of
lost some brain cells today, bro.
Hopefully I get him back tomorrow.
Lovely. We win today and all that much
sweet PJ is absolutely broke as a joke.
See, it's just the same stuff with these people, bro.
It's the same stuff with these people.
They don't know how much money people
have. They don't know anyone. That's
that's also the disabled part of it.
also very very very disabled as well.
How they talk about people all day every
day that they don't know but then they
say they've got a life.
Then these people say they've got a life.
They say they've got a life, bro, but
how can they possibly? Yeah, man.
I give up, bro. I give up.
I give up with these disabled people. D lad. Yeah,
I've already ate. I had Chinese.
I was just saying with these people,
Bob, you can't win with them.
the money game, the women game, the
better looking game. You just can't win
with these people, can you?
I Chinese sub chips. I've already ate
like 15 minutes ago. Yeah,
you can't win with these people, lad, can you?
You really, really, really can't.
YouTube should pay me a monthly income
dealing with these retards. Yeah.
Very, very strange, isn't it, bro?
I think I'm definitely going to come off
this community, bro. 100%. Definitely. Definitely.
I'm definitely going to come off this
community, I reckon, bro. Yeah,
I'm definitely coming off here, lad.
Off here for eight days over there. I'm
definitely coming off here, bro.
I wouldn't have went live today if I
didn't lose 20 pound gambling. Yeah. Ah,
where's Karen, man? Yeah, these people.
I just I played 20 pound on roulette
today. The the FBI's roulette. The FBI roulette, lad.
Yeah, the FBOT roulette. Yeah.
Yeah. Gave me mood swings all day, bro.
Ruin my day.
No, no, no. Yeah, bro.
I could play some roulette now. Nah.
Well, I don't see the actual point of
this community, bro. We should have a
talk about this community.
Bunch of middle-aged people sat on here.
24/7 talking about people that they
don't know every day. What life have
they got, bro?
What life have these people really got?
Come on, think about it, Steven Howard.
What life have these people actually got
sat on YouTube every day?
Yeah, I just had a big Chinese and some
chips. I scoff them chips, bro.
Fancy some more Coke, but I don't think
it's cold yet.
Some nice coke. Yeah, bro.
>> Look. See? Okay.
>> It's lovely, bro. Oh, man. It's lovely
knowing that you can show your face,
but these people can't show their face.
I love it. You love it.
Yeah. It's lovely, man.
It's weird, you know, cuz most most people
Yeah. Hey, bro. It's funny because, you
know, most people on different
communities, they show their faces.
These people don't show their faces.
Yeah. These most people show their faces.
These people can't show their faces on
this community. I wonder why Steven Howard.
I wonder why.
Yeah, bro. Cuz they're fat and ugly. Yep. What's that?
Because they're fat and ugly. Yeah.
Yeah, my football bat would have lost
today if I'd done a football bet, bro.
It would have lost. Yeah.
Yeah, it would have lost, lad.
Lucky I didn't do it in it, bro. Lucky I
didn't do it.
We need to get a haircut, bro.
Look at my cheekbones, bro. They're so sexy. Look.
Look at that.
Look at that, bro.
That's lush, bro.
So, Stephen Howard, why do these people
not show their faces on here, man?
Why don't these people show their faces
on here, bro? I bet they don't look
normal like me. Nah,
they can't show their faces.
I wonder why, bro. I wonder why.
Cuz that [ __ ] is stinking. Yeah, bro.
No Joseph Ferrar today bastard. Sad [ __ ] So, did you So, like
did you know he was um
How did you know he was a Lavong?
Um, Steven Howard
We didn't all get [ __ ] for showing
faces, bro. I'm still here.
I've got no long uh Yeah, Joseph [ __ ]
No, I'm not a [ __ ] for showing my face.
I haven't lost kids or I haven't had
kids and lost them or anything, bro. I'm
still here. These people in this
community don't show their faces cuz
they're ugly, bro.
That's why they call other people mers and
because they're the monsters themselves.
Cuz every single person that's been
docked before, bro. Yeah. That shown
their face, they've always been ugly. So
it's not been a case of where they
haven't shown their face, they got they
got docked and they wasn't ugly. They've
always been ugly, these people, bro.
[ __ ] stinking ugly, bro.
They're just fat, ugly old men.
That's what they are. With no life.
Absolutely no life. You should have went
on L You should have went on L's
earlier, Steven Howard.
I was on it earlier, like 25 minutes
after I woke up. I made a tea. Went on
it, bro. [ __ ] hell. The lot was in
there. The same people that should be at
work. The same people that should have
lives. You get me, bro?
with all of these people. They're just self projectors.
They're just self-reflectors on this community, bro.
That's why no one really comes on it anymore
to be fair.
>> Yeah. How did you know he was a lovey
bong anyways? is Steven Alward.
What gave it away for you? It was when
he started talking about the girlfriend
[ __ ] When he said, "How can someone
with a girlfriend be a virgin?" Straight
away he's a he's he's a he's a non-leg lover.
Yep. Straight away. I knew it, bro.
Straight away when he started defending
that uh when I was calling Thingy a
virgin. Straight away, bro. Anyone that does that,
it equals bias list and then it just
shows what they are.
I knew it straight away, bro, when he
was talking about like him having a
girlfriend and that.
Yeah, I knew it straight away, bro. It
took you It took you a little while to
cut it on, but I knew straight away.
Straight away, bro. Yeah. Yeah, bro. Come on.
Yeah, I knew when he started saying,
"Oh, how can he be a virgin? He's got a
girlfriend." M. But then he'd let me let
he'd let him call me a virgin. I knew it
straight away, bro. It's too obvious.
It's too obvious, bro.
He's a lavry mong. He's not meeting
anyone. He will never meet anyone. Ah. Yeah, bro.
I was in a B mood today, bro. I still am
kind of pissed off.
I don't even have 9p.
Yeah. Okay, bro. You keep telling yourself that.
Let me ask you this question. Yeah. How
do you know how much money people have?
I don't even have 9p.
Where are you getting your information from, bro?
Very random, isn't it?
Skint loaner with no money. How do you
know I've got no money, bro?
I could be a millionaire. You don't know.
9p. So, I've got exactly
not even 9p. Are you sure you're not
talking about yourself, bro? That's
very, very specific.
Very, very specific. Sorry.
Uh, yeah. When you prove me wrong, when
you people start proving stuff, I'll
prove you wrong. Yeah. Yeah. When you
One second. I'll put the link up.
Yeah, man. I'll happily prove you wrong.
Yeah. Yeah. I happily prove you wrong,
bro. Yeah. Yeah. Come come in. Show us
your face, what you look like, and I'll
go to the bank ATM. I'll go to the ATM right now.
I got two bank accounts. Yeah, bro.
Let's Let's Let's do it 100%. Let's do
it. I'm all for it, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, man. Come in and show your face
and prove you're not fat and ugly. And
I'm speculating and then I'll I'll show you money yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, man. 100%. So, you want me
to show you you want me to show you 20? Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Come in the hangouts
and show us what you look like
and I'll show you any amount of money you want.
I'll show you £500 if you want. That's
the maximum you can get from the bank.
Yeah. Yeah, man. Come on. Show us your
face and I'll show you and I'll show you
500 pound and I'll show you more
tomorrow. That's a good deal, isn't it?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's a good deal.
Yeah, that's a good deal, man. The
link's there, bro. Are you going to join or what?
And this is what these people do in this
community, Stephen Howard. Show money.
Show money. Show money. Cuz they ain't got money.
Why do you think? Yeah. They want people
to show their money because these people
don't have money. That's why they always
ask people to show them money because
they ain't got none. They want to see
what they what they don't have look
like. You get it, bro?
Yeah. I can't show I can't I've already
shown many. I've I've shown many many
things. I've shown you £2,000, £3,000,
£5,000, and you always run away. So,
there's no point. And this is why people
don't come on this community anymore.
Steven Howard, this is why there's no
point with these people. That's why I
rarely go live because of these people,
bro. It's pointless. This is why Monty
man don't go live much anymore. Seaside
Martin left. This is why people don't
bother with it anymore with these little
self-projecting repeaters, bro. Cuz you
can't win with them. You can't win with these losers.
You can't win with autism. When you
realize you can't win with autism, it's
pointless, bro. You can't win with these autistic people, you know?
That's why I don't really come on
anymore, lad. That's why you was
emailing me the other day. I can't
That's why I don't really come on,
you know. I come on today cuz I lost [ __ ]
muddy, bro. And I was pissed off. That's
the only reason. Whenever I do that, I
come straight onto YouTube, bro. Don't
know why I always have, but bro, like,
you can't win. You literally cannot win
with them, bro. You cannot win with them.
You show more money than them, they
still think they've won. You show more
women than them, they still think
they've won. You show you're better
looking than them, they still think
they've won. You can't win with them,
bro. You literally cannot win with them.
You can absolutely not win with them.
I asked Timmy a question earlier, right?
I said this and he didn't answer me. I
said to Timmy, right, if Nonss really
had money, what how comes when I was showing £5.7,000,
he didn't show me a damn thing? How
comes Red Star didn't show me a damn
thing? How comes you didn't show me a
damn thing? How comes large a didn't
show me? And they can't answer it. They
cannot answer it cuz they know that I'm right, bro.
They want you to show money and then
when you show them money, they run away
and make up other excuses. They do it
all the time, bro. That's why I don't
show them money. I let them keep
thinking I'm skinn because they don't
know anything that I've got. They don't
know how much money I have. They don't
know nothing. So, I let them keep like
saying these things, bro. Cuz deep down
they're just talking about themselves.
Dreaming about what?
Dreaming about what, bro? Yeah,
disabled community, bro. Disabled community.
It's all I can say, lad.
Was I dreaming? No. No. I had it in I
had it in cash. I don't need to dream
about having having 5K. And this is what
I mean with you people in this
community. You're backwards as [ __ ]
And the more you argue with backwards
people, Stephen Howard, the more you
become one of them, you become like them. Sorry.
You just start becoming like these
people. The more you interact with them,
the more you watch them, the more you
engage with them, you become like them.
You understand, bro?
Why do you think Kieran doesn't really
come on here?
Because it's disabled. They hurt It
hurts my brain, bro. My brain. My poor
Yeah. Disabled community, bro. You can
be better looking than them. You can
show more money than them. You can show
more women than them. And they still
talk [ __ ] They still think they've beaten you.
Look, Red Star talk talking about me
again. It's so gay,
bro. They're so gay and jealous. I've
never known so many people that are
older than me and jealous of me in my
life, bro. I swear to God, I've never
known people, bro. Yeah, even with
people that are that actually know
people in real life. Sorry, bro. [ __ ]
To be jealous of someone every day on
YouTube for years. But again in it's
normal to these people, bro, because
these people are disabled.
They're fat. They're ugly. They take the
piss out of themselves. They bring
themselves down. So to these people, it
is normal to them because they're disabled.
They are disabled. Do you get me?
I've already answered this question.
You're asking a genuine question. I've
already answered this question and we're
not going back and forth, back and
forth, back and forth.
You ask questions that have already been
answered. This is part of their
disabilities as well, Steven Howard. Um,
they ask questions that have already
been answered. They're disabled, bro.
This is why no one [ __ ] with this
community anymore, bro. That's why no
one goes on it, cuz it's just boring.
It's autistic. It's repeating. It's low
life. No one goes on it really much anymore, bro. You know,
they ask questions, you answer the
question, then they ask you the same
question. They're they're they're autistic.
[ __ ] madness, bro.
I'm going to have to come off soon.
Anyways, bro, my head's hurting through
these disabled people.
Yeah, these disabled people, lad.
And then you say, you know, what what
are people jealous of? And then people
answer you it. People answer you and
then you ask them the same question
over and over and over and over again. I
mean, I put the link I mean, I put the
link up earlier and no one joined. No
one show what they look like. You big
yourselves up on this community. Yeah.
You big yourselves up. Yeah. You talk
[ __ ] about every Tom, Dick, and Harry,
bro. But you can't show yourselves. I
wonder why that is, bro. I wonder why that is.
I wonder why that is, bro. Cuz you're
all fat and stinking and [ __ ] ugly.
Excuse my French. Coming on here bigging
yourself up, trying to put people that
are better looking than you down. Get a
[ __ ] grip, bro, and get a life. It's 2026.
Get off of here and get yourselves a [ __ ] life.
Jesus Christ, do a world of good.
the world of [ __ ] good, bro.
It actually would do you the world of
good. How you can sit on this community
for years stalking men, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] How you can even sit there and
and try to deny the fact that you are a homosexual
that's clearly jealous of something in
life. You're [ __ ] mad. Absolutely
[ __ ] mad. You really, really are.
Yeah. Why am I on it? Because I like
talking to Steven Howard. I like talking
to Greavvesy. I like talking to Kieran.
Why are you people on here 24/7 all day,
every day, and can't take a day off of YouTube?
I answered your question, so answer
mine. How comes you people are on here
from the time you wake up to the time
you go to bed, not being able to take a
day off of YouTube?
That's the question I would love to know
because don't forget, you are
good-looking. You've got all this money.
You've got this life. Everyone else is
skin. Everyone else is ugly. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. So, why are you on it all day
every day from the time you wake up to
the time you go to bed?
All this money, this perfect life that
you've got. Come on, bro. Let's be so
real right now. You know,
[ __ ] madness. It really, really,
really, really is madness,
you know. Really is.
Really is a madness.
If you weren't jealous of people, you
would be talking about people every day
for years on YouTube. You wouldn't be
stalking people every day for years on
YouTube. You can say that you do it for
a reaction all you want, but bro, we
know it's more than that. We know it's
more than that with you people. You can
say how you do it for reaction even
though you're the ones reacting every
day. You're the ones wasting your life
every day. So you can say that all you
want, bro. But it doesn't really wash
really anymore, does it? Come on.
If you're not jealous, if you're if
you're generally generally not jealous,
then why do you do what you do every day?
Why do you do what you do all day every
day? Then if there's nothing to be
jealous of, then that's good then, isn't
it? So why would you even waste your
time stalking men? Have channels
dedicated to men. Go on.
No. Yeah, but no, but you ain't got a
life, bro. Bro, bro, bro, what? People
that are younger than you, better
looking than you, bro. You need to look
in the mirror. Someone like me who's
younger, better looking, should make you
feel like [ __ ] You're middle-aged,
you're [ __ ] ugly. Looking at someone
like me, younger and better looking
shouldn't make you feel less of a loser.
You're still a loser. The biggest loser.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
You you you people here can't be any
more losers if you tried. You don't I
would be very surprised if you people
left your house,
you know. I would be very very surprised
if you people left your houses. You are
the ultimate losers. The you are rejects
of society. Like do you know what's so
mad, right? Do you know what's so mad?
Yeah. Do you know what's so mad, right?
Is you people don't even fit into
society. That's how bad it is. Like you
know people outside that are drags
outside. Yeah. You literally are
rejected by society. That's why you're
on here all day every day from the time
you wake up to the time you go to bed.
Literally, bro. Lar uh I have had a
girlfriend. Uh again, again, autism.
This is where the autism's um this is
where the autism comes into it. Again,
um I have had a girlfriend and I've been
shown with women. Again,
self-projecting. So, they say something,
you answer it, and I'll explain it to
you again. I have had a girlfriend, and
I've been with more women than you. And
that has been f and that has been proven
on YouTube. That has literally been
proving on YouTube. I've had one night
stands. I've had a girlfriend. I've been
with more women than you on camera.
We've never seen you with a woman. We've
never seen you in a relationship. This
is self-p projection. This is the whole
thing I'm talking about, right? You are
not in a relationship. You don't have a
girlfriend. You don't get dates. You're
self-reflecting. This this little
tactic, what they're trying to do,
Steven Albert, is they're trying to
bring you on their level. fat old ugly
virgins. This exactly now what they're
doing right now, bro. What they're doing
now. Yeah. Is they're trying to bring
you down to their ugly loser virgin
level. Yeah. These people don't have a
girlfriend. These people have never been
with a woman. Why are they trying to
talk about me?
They've literally never been with any
kind of woman. They don't have a woman.
Never had a date. Never had a woman. Why
are they trying to talk about me? Again,
you're younger than them. you're better
looking than them. This is where the
jealousy comes from with these people.
They don't have a girlfriend. They've
never had a girlfriend. They've never
had sex for [ __ ] sake. Let alone a
girlfriend. These people, right, can sit
there and try and lie about their lives
yet. They can try and sit there and say,
"Oh, you don't know what we have." No,
no, no, no, no, no, no. But they're on YouTube 247.
There is evidence of them on here 24/7.
What could they possibly have?
Come on, bro. It's just It is what it
is, isn't it? Yeah.
You're telling people that they don't
have a girlfriend. Even when they shown
they have, you still tell them they have
haven't had a girlfriend. Just like when
you tell people that they've got no
money, they show you more money. You
still You still tell them their skin.
Again, cannot win with you losers.
Cannot win. This is what I'm saying. You know,
it's the truth though, is it? It is the
truth. It is the truth. Come on. It is You know,
you're [ __ ] Yeah.
When was the last time you had a date?
When was the last time you got into a relationship?
Let's see what you people look like.
See, they're good at trying to project
their life onto other people, but they
never ever share anything about them.
Have you noticed it? Have you noticed that?
You get me, bro? You get what I'm saying?
Don't know who that is.
Yeah, it's the truth about you people.
I'm glad you find it amusing, bro. I'm
glad you find it amusing.
That's all right, bro. Hello.
>> Weirdo. Yeah. I'm glad you find it
amusing because it's the truth. The truth hurts.
Yeah. The truth hurts. I'm glad you find
it amusing, but I find it amusing. I You
know what? Sometimes it is sad, but
sometimes I find it amusing how a bunch
of middle-aged men can sit on YouTube
all day, every day talking about people
they don't know.
I find that amusing sometimes as well as
sad. It's proper proper sad, but
sometimes it is. Yeah.
You know, look at me, bro. I'm younger
than you. I'm better looking than you.
I've got more family than you. I live in
a better place than you. How could my
life make you feel better about yours?
What have you got, bro? What have you got?
Like what have you got, bro? Come on.
Tell us what you've got. Show us what
you've got. Why don't you show us what you've got? You know,
you say that people are skinn. You don't
know how much money people have. I could
be a millionaire.
I could be a billionaire. You don't
know. You don't know what people have.
You don't know what people don't have.
And even when you get proven wrong, you
still come on here and think you're
right. So, what the [ __ ]
again autistic community.
So what you're trying to say is that I'm
um So what you're trying to say is I'm
speculating. Is that what you're trying to say?
Is that what you're trying to say? Yeah.
So why don't you prove me wrong then?
Why don't you come on the Why don't you
click the link and show us what you've got then? Simple.
Yeah, you don't know what anyone has.
So weird. It is a proper
proper um autistic community.
Yeah, it really is.
Yeah. So, why don't you show us what you
look like, bro? Show us what you got. Yeah.
Someone that's younger and better
looking than you, that's got more than
you makes you feel better. Make it make sense, lad.
Make it make sense. This is such a
disabled community, isn't it?
such a disabled disabled community.
Wait, you actually you actually watch
people, right? And you compare you
compare it to your life.
That's a bit weird, bro. I can't I can't
say I've ever done that. So that's what
you generally like
when you watch people. That's what you
generally think. Your It makes you feel
better about your life. [ __ ] hell, bro.
That is very strange. Very strange. Very
But yet you people are sat on YouTube
all day every day. Yeah. Mad.
Yeah. So what lives have you got then?
Sat on YouTube 24/7.
So what lives have you got then sat on
YouTube 24/7 then? Yeah.
So, what lives have you got? Huh? Yeah.
Yeah. Really, bro? I think you just if
that makes you feel better, if you
convincing yourself that your life is
better than mine, bro, keep keep doing
that. Keep doing that. Yeah,
you keep doing that, bro.
You keep If that makes you feel better
about, you know, you convincing yourself
that you've got a better life than me, then yeah. Yeah.
yet are sat on YouTube 24/7. Uhhuh.
Oh my god, Timmy's hurting my brain,
bro. I'm watching Timmy. He's giving me a headache.
Oh, he's giving me a headache. Steven Howard, bro.
He's giving me a [ __ ] Oh, bro.
I've heard the word skin about 5,000
times today, bro.
Oh my god. I've heard that word about a
thousand times, 5,000 times today, bro.
Oh my goodness.
some madness. madness.
This thingy live on uh suck. Yeah.
Don't think Kieran's coming on here today. [ __ ] hell.
Jesus Christ. What, bro? I mean,
what the [ __ ] bro? I mean, I'm better
looking than you people. We've already
seen what half of you people of this
community look like. But nice try though
because do you know what's always going
to be the funniest thing? I can show my
face and you people can't.
And that's what I'll always have um on
you people. And all of you people that
have already shown your faces are
[ __ ] ugly as [ __ ] So um yeah, keep
projecting your ugliness onto other
people, bro. Because at the end of the
day, I will still be showing my face.
I'm not scared to show my face unlike
you people. So yeah, I mean that's it.
That is completely it.
Yeah, bro. You can say Jesus Christ all
you want, but Jesus Christ, you can't
even show your [ __ ] face.
Yeah, my god. I'm better looking than
you. I've been with more women than you.
I'm not fat and ugly like you, bro. I
know. Keep saying my god. Whilst you're
scared to join the hangouts. Whilst you
won't show what you look like.
Yeah, I know. Look at my hair, bro.
Yeah. Yeah, I've got hair unlike you.
You don't have hair. Yeah, look at my
hair, bro. I got a full head of hair.
Yeah, bro. You don't see me hiding.
You don't see me hiding like you. Yeah.
Look at my hair, bro. It's lovely, isn't
it? Smells nice as well.
Yeah. You ain't got hair. You're a
baldy. You're locks.
Nah. If I was as ugly like you people,
I'd hide. And that's why you people
That's why you people hide. Cuz you're
really fat and ugly.
Yeah. That's why you do the hide and
seek. Cuz of your ugly looks that you
try to project onto other people.
Yeah, bro. You tried You hide because
you people are so ugly you wouldn't dare
show your faces. That's why you tried to
bring other people down because of your
ugly looks. Ugly looks. Ugly looks. Just like bomb. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. You people could never ever
ever make me unsear, bro. Never.
Never. Ever. Ever. Yeah.
Just say my beard though. To be fair. My
beard's getting long, bro. >> Yeah.
You still there, Steven Howard?
You still there, bro?
What these people?
Yeah. So, you're not going to show us
your face now?
Come on, bro. Yeah.
These people will never show their faces.
I wonder why.
Well, hopefully this coke is cold now.
You can get doxed, huh?
Nah, you people don't show your faces
cuz you're [ __ ] ugly, bro. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on, bro. Come on.
You people have been on this community
for [ __ ] years, lads. You've been on
this community for years, man. If I join
a new community, I'd show my face 100%.
I'll show my face
100%. I'd show my face, bro, if I was
slagging people off every day. I mean,
I've got nothing to hide.
I got nothing to hide, bro. Yeah.
Okay with you, [ __ ]
Is that okay with you, honey?
Make it so.
Is that okay with you? Huh? Yeah.
Stop breathing like a baby
was whining like a baby.
Yeah, I'm going to be on after today for a while. >> Yeah.
No, I'm just not doing the Lego, bro.
No, I'm just not doing it.
I bought it for the figures. I won't be
bothered to do it, bro.
To be fair.
Haven't brushed my tooth today. At least
a bustling before I go to bed. No,
I [ __ ] off.
This can't be ours.
What's that? It
Got myself some porn.
didn't want to feel left out. UK asylum in it.
The fear of being left out.
You've got problems.
remember that I like I'm okay.
I'm not okay. No.
All right. I'm okay.
You saw him. I'm okay.
I found the two Scottish lads. UK asylum.
Yeah, I found the Scottish lads.
You want to [ __ ] with them, bud?
You don't want to [ __ ] with them.
Zachary and Marvel,
mate, they used to burn the [ __ ] out of him, brother. Yep.
Not a single penny shown by the elephant
trunk hunts back. No more money for the
fight family since the money got
stopped. Well done, lads.
If only they knew. UK asylum. If only
If only they knew, lad.
Yeah. No one cares.
Yeah, you should also show um
who's that who's that Nikki the
Destroyer. You should also show Nikki
the Destroyer what you people have done
for years as well.
If only you knew how much money people had.
Who the [ __ ] is that Nikki?
Who the [ __ ] is this? Nikki the destroyer.
Who are you?
How did you How did you find my channel?
Where where are you from?
Yeah, this community is very very weird.
I suggest you don't stay on this
community. It's very very disabled and autistic.
Yeah, it's an autistic community.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Yeah, this is a disabled community, lad. Yeah.
Well, you people in this community,
yeah, you're nasty little virgins.
That's what you are. Just nasty, nasty little virgins.
Go out. You know that is
Adam's my friend. Yeah,
someone on Reddit said, "Don't don't
gamble if you're going to whine like a baby."
I'm eating popcorn.
I'm having some lovely popcorn. M
comfort eating again. I don't comfort
eat. I'm not the one who's overweight,
but thank you M.
Nice popcorn and coke.
And I'll be having some more popcorn
next week when I go to the cinema. Yep.
Don't gamble if you're going to whine
like a baby. That's funny. That's what
someone on Reddit said. I am a baby.
Uh, I am a baby.
Um, I changed my mind
because I changed my mind. Yeah.
Why do people call people skin every day
and talk [ __ ] about other people, but
you're the one you are the ones that are
on YouTube 24/7 stalking men?
See, I answer your questions, but you
never answer my questions.
That's not really fair, is it? Nah.
You ask me questions, but you never
answer my ones. Unfair. Yeah, right. Listen,
please listen to me. Yeah, I'm going to
say this to you.
You fat people are not going to project
your weight onto me. It's not going to
work. You're not going to make me feel
insecure. You're not going to make me
feel ugly. You're not going to stop me
showing your show my face. Like, bro,
you people are obese. You're you're fat and ugly.
Yeah, you're not going to make me feel
the way you do, bro. I promise you. You
people are fat, ugly, fat [ __ ] You can
you can keep trying to talk about me,
someone younger and better looking than
you. Whatever, bro. It's not going to
work. You should know it's not going to
work, bro. I still show my face.
Something you people can never do. Yeah, man.
You people are actually obese.
Like, you know, it doesn't take much
here to be overweight, is it? It doesn't
take much to be overweight. But you
people are actual fat and obese. You
people in this community,
that's why you don't show yourself.
You're embarrassed with the way that you
look. So, you you self-reflect on other people.
Weird place, bro. Weird place.
Very very weird weird place. Mad.
Yeah. You people never show yourselves, do you?
It was roulette, bro.
It put me off my appetite all day, but I
did eat in the end. I still feel pissed
off over it though, bro. It's annoying.
Why should you show yourselves? Because
you talk about other people every day.
I fire stick. These people are obsessed
with me all day again today, lad. All day.
All day again, bro.
I think they're I think they're closeted
gays, lad. I think they're closeted gays. Close
it in guys, bro. Yeah.
So, yeah. Um, but I ate in the end anyways.
Loads of people obsessed with me, bro.
So weird this community, man. So weird.
It's a weird community. Fire stick.
If they weren't jealous of people, they
wouldn't talk about people or they the
way they talk about people.
All of the community is just so freakified.
You know what I mean?
That's just a weird
Yeah, he does it all day every day, bro. He's obsessed.
Yeah, he does it all day every day, lad.
I was I woke up today, bro. My phone
died. I went downstairs, made a tea. I
came back upstairs 20 25 minutes later.
I went on LJ's live stream cuz it popped
up, bro. And this Joseph Ferrar. Every
comment was about me.
Every comment was about me, bro.
They're gay, bro. Just come out the closet.
They're gay in it. Proper gay.
Proper gay and jealous.
Yeah. They got to be gay and jealous, bro.
Yeah, that's the one, bro. He was on
about me all day earlier. But what makes
me laugh, bro, is that like they will
comment this [ __ ] Yeah. Every comment's
about me, bro.
Every comment's about me.
Every comment's about me, but he won't
come on my He won't come on my door and
do anything about it.
You can be on YouTube all obsessed with
all your comments, but you won't come
and sort anyone out. You won't meet
anyone. It's embarrassing, bro. Really, really embarrassing.
Oi, Piggy, mate, you're calling yourself
Piggy, cuz you're the one that's fat and not me.
Stop self-reflecting your fatness onto
other people, bro. None of you obsessed
people in this community are in any kind
of shape. Any of you, you're not in any
sh You're not in shape at all.
Why are you projecting your fatness now,
bro? It's mad.
You people really are sad little bully victims.
You know, you people that do this [ __ ]
you really are bully victims. It's not
even funny, bro. It's quite sad. No,
>> I don't have Discord.
Um, why are you calling people?
I already answered them. Why are you
calling people piggy when you're the one
that's fat and not me?
You're calling me piggy when I'm
literally not even fat and you are and
you're calling me piggy. You people
really are serial self projectors.
You must do not do you have a degree in self projecting?
I swear everything you say is literally
about yourselves. I can't think of one
thing that you people say that ain't
about you. Skin you. Ugly you. No
friends, you. Fat you. Brother,
everything you say is literally about
yourselves. I swear I can't think of one
thing that you you people talk you
people call people that ain't about yourselves.
You are [ __ ] fat and ugly. What the Oh, [ __ ]
[ __ ] talking about people when you
people are [ __ ] obese.
Why don't you come on camera and show yourself?
Exactly. That's what I thought.
You never You'll never come on here and
show what you look like
cuz you're [ __ ] ugly as [ __ ] Ugly as
[ __ ] Fat as [ __ ] It's the truth
though, is it? It is the truth. It is
definitely the truth.
Definitely definitely definitely
definitely the truth. That's why you
don't show yourselves.
That's exactly why you don't show
yourselves. That's also why you'll never
meet anyone either.
So yeah, you're ashamed of the ways you look.
The way you look.
Today someone gets docked and then
they're ugly, then I'll be like, "Yeah,
okay." Nah, it will never happen. Never
Everyone on here that's been doxed has
always been ugly.
Always, mate. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. Firstly, I'm not pinging on
the pounds. I do live with my mom. I've
already got a woman and I've got savings
and you never stopped any of my sublet
money. But you keep telling yourself
that. You keep telling yourself that. I
had sublet money for four years. lived a
life that you will never be able to.
I've lived more of a life in three, four
years than you have. I've still got more
money than you. I've got a woman unlike
you. And yeah, I do live with my mom.
You probably don't even have a mom.
Unlike you people, [ __ ] middle-aged,
fat, ugly skinn, ain't got no life,
don't even leave the house. That's wonderful, bro.
At home, no women, no money, wrinkly as
[ __ ] Look at you people. Look at
yourselves before trying to talk about me. Bro,
you never got anyone's sublet money
stopped. But you keep telling yourself
that. If it makes you feel better about
the fact that I got more money than you,
you keep telling yourself that, bro. I
love it. If it if it makes you feel
better, that's good.
You never got none of my sublet money
stopped. And I've still got more money
than you. I've still got more money than
Women also hate you as well. You've
never even been with a woman. You ugly
virgin. Where's your girlfriend?
You see, you come to realize with the
people in this community, bro. It's self-projected.
Middle-aged, very ugly, no life.
Everything is about yourselves, which is
why you're on this rejected community.
You don't leave the house.
You've got nothing going for yourselves.
That's why you try to pick on other
people that are better than you. It's
not because people have said stuff about
people's kids. It's not because it's
simply because we're better than you in
every way and you hate people that are
better than you. That's why you do this
every day on YouTube. That's why you
people come on here and you do this.
You're fat. You're ugly. You're single.
You got no misses. And you try to bring
it on. You bring your lives onto other
people. That's what you people do.
No misses, no girlfriend, no sex life,
no money, never had no money. We learned
that years ago. You try to bring your
fat, rejected lives onto other people.
That's what you do.
Am I lying, bro? No, I'm not a troll.
Why? How am I a troll? UK asylum.
A troll. Why am I a troll, bro? Why? Why?
Never trolled in my life, lads. Never
trolled in my life.
Why am I Why am I trolling, bro?
What am I trolling about?
Yeah, look, you can't say anything back
because you know I'm right, bro. You
know I'm right.
I've already got a woman, you [ __ ]
You ain't got no woman. You ain't got no money. Bro,
I've got money right now. I could
embarrass you right now. needs that.
But I'm definitely coming off this
community after today for a little bit, bro. 100% disabled.
And here we're dealing with another disabled [ __ ]
Another disabled [ __ ]
You're saying that people are piling on
the pounds, but you people are already
fat and ugly.
Fat and ugly as [ __ ] That's why you
tried to bounce off of people's lives
that are better than you to make you
feel better about yourselves.
Isn't Isn't it right, Unlucky?
Isn't it right? Fat, ugly, no money, no
misses. It's the truth, isn't it? That's
why you don't say nothing it because you
know I'm right. Cuz you know that you're
ugly womenless, low life, no life, no
family. You know I'm right about you
ugly people. You know I'm right. That's
why you shut up cuz you know I hit the
nail on the head cuz you know I'm right
about you people. You got no woman. You
got no girlfriend. I You got nothing
going for yourselves. You've never been
with a woman. Yeah, man.
You've never been with a woman cuz
you're too ugly to get one. That's
another bit of yourself projecting.
Anyways, I'll let uh Timmy on. One
second, Timmy. Join again. I'll let you
on, bro. One sec. Yeah.
See, Timmy's weird because he's he's
slating nonslegs, but at the same time,
he's like licking his ass at the same time.
He He It's weird cuz he's kind of
licking his ass at the same time.
Anyway, join Timmy. Sorry, I'll let you
on. Come on. >> Yeah. >> Timmy. >> What?
>> Jimmy, I've shown 5.7 grand. I say I'll show you right
show me the these five [ __ ] you know
imaginary properties you own and I'll
show you more than 40 quid under the TV
I watched your live I watched your live stream earlier
>> PJ know you listen to me fella can we
have a serious chat talk
>> yeah I'm having a serious chat with you
I I watched your live stream earlier
>> on your streams PJ
>> and you said that you was going to rob
you said you're going to rob nonsense.
He doesn't have anything to rob.
>> I talked to you about this [ __ ] 4
hours ago. You wouldn't hear me out,
>> you know. >> Yeah.
>> Serious. I'll do it.
>> You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] Timmy. Shut up, man.
>> Well, do you want to prove it to the
test? If you
>> Yeah, I do want to prove I want to prove
it to the test. Yeah.
>> If your mother puts me up for the night,
we'll do it tonight.
You think I'm taking a piss? That's scary thing.
>> Is this guy being for real? Yeah, she
Yeah, we'll put you up.
>> Real talk. >> Yeah.
>> Honestly, I don't want to get to London,
get stranded in case the
>> Yeah, 100%. Okay, put put your money
where your mouth is.
>> Come then.
>> I just have.
>> Okay, come to London then. Well, PJ,
do you realize you got to take me to
Sean? I've got to go to the social club.
I've got to intimidate the details.
>> Why do why do you want to beat him up?
>> Cuz he called me a nons he's got to pay.
>> So, what you going to do? Beat him up. >> Yes. >> Really?
>> No. I'm sure this ain't like no Welsh
days. I'm sick of these [ __ ] little
[ __ ] mate. I want to put them in
their [ __ ] [ __ ] how it is. But you
need a beating as well because let me
explain why you need a beating because
you've got to take responsibility too,
Peter. So I'm going have to beat the
both of you up.
>> Yeah, but you didn't beat me last time.
>> Peter, you know I could [ __ ]
>> You could have beat me up, Timmy.
>> You couldn't even kick me.
>> Peter, your anger is pathetic to my
anger. Trust me.
>> No, Timmy. I'm very psychotic.
>> Seriously, Peter, it is. You are I'm psychotic.
>> Think you'd understand my anger?
No, no, Pete. This is no game. Be generally serious.
>> Timmy, I'm Timmy, I'm very psychotic.
>> I am willing to w Sean his 15 grand with
my face on camera.
>> Well, you'll be very lucky cuz you don't
have 15 grand.
>> What will happen is I'll go to his
social club and I will grab him by his head. Right.
>> Well, he doesn't have 15 grand. So, good
luck with that.
>> No, he has.
>> No, he doesn't.
>> Yes, he doesn't. He show
>> Well, get it then. If he's if he's got
50 grand, get it then.
>> True, Peter. Peter, he's showing off his
wealth and I'm going to rob it.
>> Okay, go on then.
>> Well, how could you take to your social club?
>> Well, you can find it yourself, can't you?
>> No, I can't because I'm thick.
>> Yes, you can, Timmy.
>> I know where about where it is, but I
want you to show how passionate you are
about this geyser to take me to him.
>> August the 26th.
>> No, no, no, no. Peter, if you that much
hate him that much.
>> Yeah, but he I I know his birthday's his
birthday is August the 26th.
>> Yeah, everyone knows that. Who cares?
>> No, that's his birthday.
>> Well, same day is mine. >> Yeah.
>> He's got the same day birthday as mine. >> Yeah. >> Seriously? >> Uh-huh. >> Really?
>> Yeah. He needs robbing now.
>> He needs to go and rob him.
>> No, he won't go and rob him. Not
tonight, PJ. I'm going to go and get
some beer, stay at the hangouts, and
I'll be back. See, he thinks I'm
bluffing. Go find Metropolon, please.
You [ __ ] bacon. Like, I give a [ __ ]
I unlucky. Yeah. At least I'm not like
you people, bro. Already p already piled
on the weight. Middle age, no woman, no
money. I could be like you people in it,
bro. I could be like you and the lovely bongs.
And you know what I love that there's no
hope for you.
You can't even change even if you wanted
to cuz you're too old. You're too old.
You're too damn bad now. It's over. And
that's the difference between me and you
love remongs is you're too old to change
it. You're finished.
You're you're you're you're the way you
are now for life
and there's nothing you can do about it.
And I've and it gives me a [ __ ] boner.
It gives me a big [ __ ] boner, right?
Well, you're worse than the slug. You're
worse than the slug. It gives me a boner
knowing that you're too old to change
your shitty lives. It gives me a big
[ __ ] boner. That's what it does.
Gives me a boner.
All right. If this Timmy doesn't stop,
I'm going to get LT on Timmy, Mr. Bean.
I'm going to get LT on Timmy.
Yeah, I'll get LT on him.
LT, a mad man.
Yeah, I'll get LT on Timmy.
LC a mad man.
Remember Mr. Bean? He's a mad man. Is he
So anyways, I lucky you. How comes
you've never had a woman?
How come you're still a virgin?
Yeah. Right, mate. Yeah, cool. [ __ ]
mate. Who should Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I don't want kids. I hate
So, even if you do have kids, which you
don't, I don't want little [ __ ]
shitty kids. And I guarantee you, mate,
at 28, I've been with more women than you.
More women than you will ever have.
More women than you'll ever have. Sunshine.
more women than you will ever get ever. Yeah.
You never stopped anyone's sublet money, de lad.
You didn't stop anyone's anything. Who's this? >> Yo,
>> who's this?
>> I was talking to you in the chat
earlier. I spoke to you before you got
the with me cuz I was round with you on
Monty's. Do you remember ages ago? My
name was Hugh.
>> Yeah, we're just we're just letting go,
bro. I know exactly who you are. I don't
care about that, bro.
>> I said, um, Nate, I just [ __ ]
laughing. I can't believe that that
[ __ ] fat [ __ ] [ __ ] just come on
here flexing [ __ ] 30 quid. Bro, why
you why you under Why you under a new
You was um that Q in it. Why are you
under a new name? >> Yeah.
>> Uh I couldn't get on my other email.
>> Yeah, the gambling [ __ ] bro. What's
What's up, man?
>> Did you gamble today?
>> No, not today. I can't I come up here to
say I can't believe that that [ __ ]
Timmy just come up here flexing 30 quid,
>> bro. I mean, he's a [ __ ] What do you expect, bro?
>> He said he's going to punch already and
that's what he reckons,
>> bro. You know, I've met this guy two
times, bro. He wouldn't hurt a fly. >> Yeah,
>> he's a [ __ ] isn't it, bro?
>> Yeah, Timmy. Oh, Timmy. Yeah, Timmy's a [ __ ]
>> Yeah. So, wait, wait, hold on a minute.
You was the one you was talking about
the gambling and that, isn't it?
>> Yeah, I was messing you about the
gambling the other day,
>> bro. It's [ __ ] bad, isn't it, bro?
>> Don't seriously don't. When I walk out
that [ __ ] betting shop, oh my god,
you don't realize how I feel. I feel like
>> You don't even have to be This is what
people don't understand, bro. You don't
even have to be addicted. Like you could
just lose money. Yeah. That you that you
that you're willing to lose and you can
still drive you mad.
>> What makes me angry and I agree with you
when you say it as well is when people
say it's a fun it's a fun form of
entertainment. No, it ain't. No, it
ain't. No, it ain't.
>> It isn't, bro.
>> It isn't. It isn't. Like you feel like
even 20, you feel like smashing the face
up, isn't it?
>> Yeah. It's horrible, bro.
>> That bar, is it? Oh, it's horrible. Whe
whether whether it's the spun that spins
around or the one that goes up and down
is [ __ ] vile.
>> At least you got that 490 to 850 the
other day. I can't remember the last
time I [ __ ] won.
>> I I haven't won big for 10 years. I
ain't won anything big since 2016. >> 2016.
>> Yeah. Before all this spin bar [ __ ] you
know, when it was just 100 pound spins
and it went Do you ever play online?
>> No, I don't.
Oh, that's why ain't it?
>> That's meant to be just as bad.
>> Yeah, but don't you go casino, isn't that? >> No,
I went to Birmingham the other day and I
went in that casino there. I can't
remember what it was called. The one there.
>> Yeah, I didn't gamble though. I just had a look.
>> What did you do there?
>> Just went up there with my pal. Never
been there before. [ __ ] it's a [ __ ] hole.
>> What did you What did you Did you go for
like a night out? I went I went to um I
went from London Houston to Birmingham
New Street and then uh
>> that's where that's where I've been.
Yeah, that's where I used to stay up
there. I stayed up there in some like
[ __ ] disgusting hotel. It's £42. It
was called Ibiz Budget. It's [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
>> What did you What I'm saying is what did
you go there just for leisure? Just for leisure? Yeah.
>> Yeah, just for a night out, but it's
[ __ ] horrible. Have you been there?
>> You got you go by yourself?
>> No, I went with my mate. Have you been there?
>> Yeah, of course I have, bro. I've been
Birmingham loads of times.
>> Yeah. Do you think
>> I met I met Monty? Did I met Monty a few
months ago, you remember?
>> I see the videos and that. Yeah. I
didn't know you was there.
>> Yeah, I've been Birmingham loads of
times, bro. About six times. >> Yeah.
>> PJ. PJ, that's what I come here to say. Yeah.
>> Yeah, bro.
>> I found a guy who [ __ ] keeps making
videos about you. Yeah. He's like
[ __ ] fat, disgusting, ugly [ __ ]
Yeah. And his girlfriend shout stuff out
in the background. I thought he was
American, but you said the other day
he's not. Who is that?
>> Oh, that Jamie Thompson. Yeah. Yeah.
He's a [ __ ] bro. He's been doing it
for years, bro. He's just like nons.
>> Yeah, I don't know what nons legs is,
but that guy I'm on about, he's proper
fat, disgusting [ __ ] bro.
>> Yeah, he's ugly as [ __ ] bro. Wait, hold
on a minute, bro. So, what wait, what
what day did you go Birmingham again? >> Uh, Wednesday.
>> Oh, and you come back on a Thursday. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Nice, bro. Uh, so where did you go? Like Broad Street?
No, I went uh from London Houston to
>> No, no, no. But when you was in when you
when you went to the clubs, did you go
broad street like in Birmingham? Like
the strip in it?
>> No. We was in that Chinatown bit where
there's like be restaurants and that. >> Okay.
>> Then I got in a cab to some place where
there was a few clubs. I don't know. It
was just a [ __ ] [ __ ] hole.
>> So you just starting to go like
different places now like when you're
born and that? Yeah.
>> Yeah. I've never been
>> That's what I used to do. I've never
I've never been Liverpool or Manchester either.
>> I've been to both of them, bro.
>> That's what I'm saying. That's what I
used to do, bro. Like when I used to get
born, I used to just like get a train
somewhere, book a hotel, go on a night
out, come back the next day, bro. >> Yeah,
>> I won't be going Birmingham again. That
was [ __ ] horrible [ __ ] That boring
Did you go in that boring shopping center?
>> It's massive, isn't it? It's massive.
>> There's There's bare nice birds in
there, but it's too busy in there, man.
>> Yeah. Did did you uh did you talk to Did
you try to like get any birds and that?
>> Uh if I'm honest with you, I was a bit
pissed. So, I was just [ __ ] falling over
the place and that just make myself like a div.
>> Yeah, you should go to um next time you
should go to like Cardiff, bro. Go to
Cardiff um and Newcastle.
>> I've never been I've never been to Wales
either. I've never been Newcastle
>> Yeah, they're good spots, bro. Good
spots. That's a good That's a good deal
on a hotel, though, to be fair, bro. 42.
I was I was I was shocked. Normally it's
cheaper on a Sunday, isn't it? >> Hotel. >> Yeah.
>> I don't know. I just put cheap
Birmingham hotels and it can't this business.
>> When I was in Liverpool, when I was in
Liverpool, it was £26, but that was a
Monday. That was in January, but that
was a Monday.
>> Yeah. What hotel was that?
>> Uh, was it Travel Lodge?
>> Travel Lodge is all right. This one I
was in was horrible.
>> I've never stayed in Premier In, you
know. Never. I've never stayed there. Have you?
>> I have. Yeah, I have. They're all right.
Yeah, I've never stayed in a Premier. I
can't say I have, bro. Of all the hotels
I have, I've never. But you know,
Saturday is always expensive, isn't it?
>> Yeah, Saturday is. What did you lose a
score on, PJ earlier on, Broulette?
>> Just the Just the Bet, bro. Yeah. Um, bet Fred.
>> Oh, not online?
>> Nah, I lost 100 pound online two days ago, bro.
>> Yeah, I heard you saying what? You lost
a score earlier. I bet you was well
pissed in it.
>> Yeah, I withdrew. I I will draw £30,
bro. I was going to put 20 Yeah. on a
roulette and then £10 on a football, but
bro, I was so agitated. I just went
home, bro. I was I was supposed to do
like food shopping and other stuff, but
like I get so mad, bro. I can't even
like stand stand still, bro. It's weird.
>> Ruin It ruins your day. It's horrible.
>> It's so [ __ ] annoy. But you know,
when I used to go out in central Yeah.
When I used to lose, I used to get like
it. where I was drinking. I assume I
just calm down um after a while cuz
you're drinking isn't it? So it helps
you in it.
>> Yeah. I've heard all your videos over
the years. I've heard you go [ __ ]
mental loads of times.
>> Well, that's why I try to avoid it now
to be fair.
>> I seriously I've heard I've heard you
going like [ __ ] crazy on your old channel.
>> What's the worst you see? What's the
worst you seeing? Probably the [ __ ]
um the one when you're going about the casino, bro.
>> Oh, the man. Yeah, bro. Do you know I
was in a I was in a casino with a bird.
Yeah, bro. One time, bro. I wanted I
wanted to chuck glass on someone's head,
bro. Like, I swear down I did, bro.
>> It's not funny really cuz it is like
mental distress. But, um like I can't
lie, some of the some of the times I've
heard you going mad, it was some
>> You know, the thing is, yeah, you know,
some of like my friends and that, bro,
they'll lose and it don't seem to bother
them. Obviously, they're holding it in.
Obvious obviously I know they're holding
it in, but how the [ __ ] are they doing it, bro?
>> PJ, does anyone ever say to you, "Oh,
you win some, you lose some." Oh, I hate
that. I hate it when people say that.
>> Well, of course they do, bro. Do you
know what's annoying as well? Let me
tell you what what I think is annoying
as well. Yeah. It's It's like you don't
even win anymore. Oh, it's not like you
It's you don't even get you don't even
win to then get greedy to lose because
then you can just slap yourself in the
face. Like you actually don't even win.
You actually don't even win anymore.
>> Not with this. Um, not with this spin
bar thing. You don't know. Definitely.
>> Like say, say we won today. Yeah. And
then we lost some tomorrow. We'd be
like, okay, well, you win, you lose. But
where you keep losing and you and you're
not even winning to get greedy anymore,
that's also a part of it, I think. >> Yeah,
>> cuz you're just losing. You're not ever winning.
>> I know. It's [ __ ] absolutely.
>> And have you noticed the [ __ ] odds on
the football has gotten worse as well.
Have you know I don't know if you bet on
football, but I don't I don't even um I
don't even bet on football to be honest.
What? Is it got [ __ ]
>> It's got [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] few weeks
ago I put 20 on a five both teams to
score. It come in. I only got 224 back. >> Yeah.
>> And that was five teams. That was five
teams. And also I put I was going to put
150 on two teams today, bro. But do you
know what the return was yesterday? Oh,
yeah. Today five uh £340 from 150. They
used to give back like 480 520 back.
What was what was the return if it come in?
>> 330. 340. It's [ __ ] That's what I'm
saying. Two teams. But it used to be
about 500, like 480 to about 520.
>> Someone's saying in the chat, PJ was
crying to his mom when he lost. What?
>> They're talking [ __ ] bro.
>> Yeah. No, I know you're saying it's all
[ __ ] prices, [ __ ] [ __ ] odds.
>> They're giving [ __ ] odds as well, M. And
and I think now the only way you can
really win is football, bro. To be fair,
>> I can't even lie. Yeah. All the times
I've lost big amounts over the years in
like all the bookies, Admiral Casinos
and that, I've been I've been proper
horrible to the staff as I'm leaving, I
felt bad after. It's not even their
fault. I've been really to them before.
>> I felt like just [ __ ] doing that Coke
thing today, bro. Just throwing a can of
Coke back like you know when you tip it
Yeah. and it fizzes up and then just
bang it on the machine, bro. And it'll
go everywhere. I was getting
>> Why did you not go and get your Why did
you not go and get your dinner? What?
You felt just [ __ ] so pissed off.
Yeah, just annoyed, bro. I didn't eat
until late today. I didn't eat until
like 8:00 today, bro. I didn't eat earlier either.
>> Kills your when you when you when you're
losing, mate. Just makes you want to lose.
>> It's so annoying, bro. It is so >> Whole
What channel is Nons? I always hear you
say nons. What channel is that?
>> You've seen it. No,
>> I don't know. Is that I've got I've seen
the Red Star. So, who's that one?
>> Wrong and central.
>> Yeah. And who's non legs? You always say
about non legs. What one's that?
>> Another one that's obsessed with me,
bro. Like this Jo.
>> Who's the one who
>> You've seen that, isn't it? You've seen
that Jo is in it.
>> I've seen big [ __ ] fat disgusting
[ __ ] and his girlfriend shouts out in
the background, but I don't know. He
talks about you all the time.
>> Yeah, I've got I've got quite a few
people obsessed with me on here, bro.
Who's a disgusting fat middle-aged guy
and his girlfriend shouts in the background?
>> Jamie Thompson.
>> Yeah, I think that's him. I've seen him
do be videos about you.
>> They're Bro, they're gay on here, bro.
They're proper gay in it.
>> I'm trying to see an account. I can't
find his channel. Jamie Thompson. I
don't think I've got that one.
>> Yeah, there's there's Wrong and Central,
Jamie Thompson, Joe F. There's a few of them, bro.
>> There's one here. Incel. He's in this one.
What channel is it? Don't
>> know. It's It's the one who It's the one
when your videos when your streams end,
he it's got like a bot posting them straight away.
>> Yeah, that's that Jamie Thompson as
well. That's his other channel.
>> Oh, he was saying it weren't him the other day.
>> It is him.
>> He was saying it definitely ain't him.
And you keep saying it's him and it's
not him. That's what he said.
>> It is him, bro. 100%.
>> So, you don't you don't talk to Monty anymore, huh?
I ain't spoken to him for ages. Months.
He don't really come up on it much, does he?
>> He was on the other day. But yeah,
>> but not not really, bro. Not really.
>> Nope. He has to. He went he went to
court over the riot [ __ ] and that is it.
>> Yeah, he got he's got tag or something.
>> Have you Have you ever been caught in
that? Have you been caught?
>> Yeah, loads of times.
>> Yeah, it's been [ __ ] now.
How long you got How long you got going
on tag for?
>> He said two years.
>> Funniest I think one of the funniest
videos I've seen of you is you walking
down the road is an old one and that
[ __ ] It's just the way you say it.
You're like [ __ ] hell, this guy's
dead, man. Like literally two seconds
later he gets hit by a car.
>> Well, I still I still remember that,
bro. That's weird.
>> I think No. Well, the police gave us an
update. He was he was uh in a coma and I
just assume he died to be fair.
>> It makes me laugh what you said to the
man as well. He said something to you. I
can't I can't make out what he says. And
you go what? You go shut up, bro. You
just killed someone, bro,
>> bro. [ __ ] You know what's so mad is
Yeah. When he landed Yeah. I still
remember the smell to this day, bro, of
that blood. It's It smell like raw beef.
>> Oh, was it bear was there bare blood?
>> It was bare blood, bro. Bare blood.
You thought he was running? You know, I
was walking on I was walking on the
pavement today. Yeah. Some guy with a
motor uh motorbike come beside me. I
said, "Bro, you almost [ __ ] run me
over. The fuck?"
>> Probably phone snatching.
>> Yeah, but obviously I keep my [ __ ]
phone in the in my pocket and I'm aware
that now. It's happened to me once and
it I'm wary, bro. I'm wary now.
>> You need to be careful that you, bro.
It's a real thing.
>> Yeah, I know. It happens up there all the time.
happened to me in Liverpool Street.
It was bad, bro.
>> I think I No, where did I go the other
day? I had to go somewhere. I went to
Victoria and then I changed to Victoria
to go to Houston. Oh, yeah. When PJ,
when you went Birmingham. Yeah. How long
did it take you from Houston to
Birmingham New Street? There's one train
>> Sometimes. Sometimes it was 1 hour and
20. Sometimes it was 2 hours. If I got
the faster train, it was 1 hour and 20.
>> It took me like It took me like 2 hours
to get there and then the one I got back
was like hour and a half. It go more Uh
what the first the first one the first
one was a long train. The second one was
a faster train. Yeah.
>> When I bought the ticket it was double
the price for that fast one.
>> Yeah. That's why
you know that long one they weren't
serving um snacks on it in it. I
remember they don't serve snacks on it
in it. Nah.
>> Yeah. That one has snacks right at the end.
>> Was it rammed?
>> Yeah. Proper.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Rammed, bro. Rambo. Yeah, man.
>> I didn't get I didn't get a seat for the
first like 45 minutes. when uh when we
got to Milton Kings, loads of people got
off and I got to say then
>> Yeah, that's where it stops and it Yeah,
Milton Kes is like halfway. >> Yeah.
>> Now, do you reckon you could have done
it by yourself?
>> Yeah, I'd go exploring by myself.
>> Yeah, that's good then, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Just do So, what do you want to do
next? Liverpool. Yeah.
>> I don't know. Have you been there?
>> Yeah, man. Two years ago. Three years
>> It is a [ __ ] hole to be fair, bro. But
it's a good good night out.
Go Sheffield. Sheffield's good.
>> Yeah, I ain't been there either.
>> Yeah, I'm in Manchester, bro, like 10 times.
>> What's that like?
>> It's all right. Yeah, it's all right, bro.
Better like better clubbing scene up
there. Um it's it's easier to get around
that places though cuz know London is
like too big in that, isn't it? Yeah,
>> but like um when did you last go for a
drink in London? >> Uh
I went like 3 weeks ago. I went to that
Waxies, you know, Waxies O' Connor.
>> No, I don't I don't actually know that.
>> [ __ ] uh next to O'Neal, bro. In Water
Street. Water Street. O'Neals. You know,
there's like a little pub called Wax. I've
>> been I've been to an O'Neal in Chinatown.
>> Yeah, that's the one. Yeah. Yeah. It's
in Chinatown. It's called Water Street. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I've been to that. I've been to
that O'Neal's in
>> Yeah, but next Yeah. So, next to there
is is a Waxies.
>> Yeah. I >> No.
>> Yeah. That's just Waxies.
>> That That O'Neal is in Chinatown. That's actually
>> It's sick, bro. I've been there like a
million times, bro.
>> I drink Guinness when I'm in there.
>> When did you last go there?
>> About 6 months ago. I lost about 600
quid opposite on the corner in that
[ __ ] arcade thing
>> with your skin after that.
>> No, I still had a bit.
>> Yeah, that O'Neal is lit, bro. I
>> ain't going to lie. I lost most of what
I had. Left me about a one or something.
>> Yeah, it is what it is, isn't it?
>> Yeah, it's hard to even, as you know,
it's once it gets you, it's hard to even
walk out without. It's [ __ ] disgusting.
Yeah. I remember I got I got a [ __ ]
from some woman from the O'Neal. She was
American in it. I took her around the
alleyway in it.
>> Is it?
>> Yeah, bro. She's like, "Oh, I want you.
I want you." But I was mad.
>> Is that Is that the one? Is that the one
who you give her extra money and then
she started going mad? which who
>> you to I heard you say on the video
before you [ __ ] you was getting a
blowing and then you give her extra
money to finish in her mouth and she
started going mad cuz she
>> No, that wasn't No, that wasn't that was
an escort, bro. This wasn't an escort.
>> Oh, I thought this one was an escort.
>> No, no, it was it was it was an American
from the O'Neal, isn't it? You know,
there's loads of Americans that go
there, isn't it?
>> I don't know. I've never
>> You must You must have seen You must
have seen it if you've been there, is
it? Cuz there's loads of people that go
there, isn't it? Yeah, it does get busy.
I've only been there three or four
times, but I've never spoke to anyone
American in there.
>> Yeah, you if you go on a Thursday, it's
is rammed, bro. Thursdays are the day
there, bro. If you ever I like going out
Thursdays, bro. I don't really like
Saturdays to be fair.
>> Saturdays are [ __ ] Too busy.
>> Thursdays are the one, bro. I like
Thursdays to be fair.
>> I see a video the other day. Yeah. when
I was scrolling through of you in some
[ __ ] in some brasses like [ __ ] old
flat all rubbish on the floor in that
and you was making me laugh, bro.
>> Bro, yeah, I used to I used to go to
that own it was twice a week. Like twice
a week, bro. I swear to God.
>> Who was whose flat was that you was in?
Like some prostitute's flat and it was
all messy and that
>> Oh, just someone um that lives in Shepherd's Bush.
>> It was making me laugh what you were
saying. And where the [ __ ] was she?
Oh, she went to she went like I was in
bed with her and that in it and then she
was like, "Oh, um, yeah, this guy keeps
calling me and that." I said, "Oh, go go
go with him. Go with him." So then I
could like rob the money. I robbed her
and that in it.
>> Did you even bang her?
>> Obviously, bro,
>> I don't know.
>> Like about four like four times. About
four times, bro.
>> What? And she left the cash there when
she went out.
>> Yeah, cuz she's not going to think. She
didn't think anything. I just took it
and it [ __ ] off with it.
>> Have you ever did you know
>> some It was some Somalian is it?
>> Yeah, some of them are hot.
>> Yeah, she was all right. But like it was
Yeah, we was banging, bro. We banged. We
banged a few times, bro.
>> We bang them right away, bro.
>> I see some other uh video PJ. Yeah, I
don't know if it was you or someone else
who posted it, you know, of you talking
to you. You You did make me laugh. It's
you talking to some girl. Yeah. on the screenshot. >> Uhhuh.
>> And and you're chatting away and you
know the one who said, "Why am I going
to be nice to you when you said horrible
things about me and my daughter?" You
know that one.
>> Which one? No.
>> There's screenshots of you talking to
some bird and you're chatting away.
Yeah. And like you're just like talking
normal and that and then you just you
just randomly put a come in here and it
probably make me laugh.
>> What was it? Snapchat. No WhatsApp.
>> Oh, [ __ ] knows, bro. I can't There's
been so many.
>> I don't know why you just randomly out
of the blue put she was annoying you
before a little bit and then you just
put you're a [ __ ] in it to this bird. It
just proper made me laugh for what she
was saying back to you.
>> [ __ ] knows. It's been bear. Bro, do do
you do rate do rate in Fortnite out on that?
>> Never been there. Have you been there?
>> Yeah, but not not Fortnite out.
I got a friend that lives there in it.
He's always like, "Oh, we should go on a
night out and that." But yeah, I have
been there, bro. It's mad story, bro.
Mad story. I met this woman. Yeah. I
couldn't [ __ ] I tried to order an
Uber cuz it was like in the village and
there was no signal in it. So, I had to
knock on people's door like 7:00 in the
morning to ask where the train station
is cuz there was no signals and there's
no Uber cuz it's a dead area, isn't it?
>> Yeah. You won't even be able to get an
Uber around there.
>> That's what I mean. So I had to knock on
people's doors saying like where's the
train station when like [ __ ] it was mad, bro.
>> Why didn't you just go in the shop and ask where
>> there was no shop? Cuz there was no
shops. That's what I'm saying.
>> It was just houses. Like it was 7:00 in
the morning. She was I met her on a
dating app. She was scaring the [ __ ] out
of me, bro. >> Why?
>> Because she was just acting weird, bro.
She's like, "Oh, you're my everything."
And that like she was bro spooky.
>> No way.
>> It was spooky, bro. It was spooky.
Did you tell did you did you tell her
you was going or did you just [ __ ] off?
>> No, I just [ __ ] off, bro. Wait till she
>> I knew you was going to say that. I knew
>> No, [ __ ] that, bro. No, she was scary.
She was scary, bro. But uh
>> I can see you now. I can see you now. I
bet as soon as you left her hand walking
up the road for the station. I think you
blocking her in it.
>> Yeah. No, I don't think I did block her.
I don't think I did. No.
>> What was she saying to you?
>> I don't think she did mess with me, but
I I don't I didn't block her. I remember
I didn't block her. No, bro. She was
just being [ __ ] weird, man.
>> Saying what?
>> Like just like cuz she was like, "Oh."
She's like, "Oh, I've got dyslexia and
everything. You're my everything. I love
you." And that in it.
>> Did Did you know her really well?
>> No, I just met her.
>> That's what I'm saying, bro. No, it was
like it was like um it it was a dating
app in it. And [ __ ] I I traveled to
her at like [ __ ]
>> God knows what time at 9:00 at night, in
it. So I had to like stay the night in
it because the train stop running on that.
>> Was she asleep when you left? >> Huh?
>> Did she Was she asleep when you left? >> Yeah.
>> Well, you stayed awake all night and
left when she fell asleep.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I was on YouTube.
>> Oh, that's [ __ ] dope.
>> Did you even do it?
>> Weirdo, bro.
>> Did you bang her?
>> Nah. Didn't do nothing at all, bro.
[ __ ] that. She sounds crazy. She'll end
up getting you nicked.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Didn't do anything at all at all.
>> You What did she say to you? She's like
in love with you and that. >> Yeah.
>> And she just met me in it.
>> What did you What did you say back to
her? Did you even reply? I have just
smiled and nodded my head.
>> Yeah. Literally just doing that. Yeah.
Smiled in my head. Bro, what else can
you do in it?
>> It's [ __ ] freaky. All right. Have you
seen that guy that's come on here
before? You sound like him. That Kieran, is it?
>> Kieran? No, I don't know who that is.
>> That guy. You You ain't seen that account. Kieran.
>> No, I ain't.
>> Oh, he just comes on here sometimes in it.
>> I heard some I heard some black boy on
your stream the other day talking [ __ ]
about employment. Well, I don't know who that was.
>> Who? London Taylor.
>> I don't know. He sounded black and he
was talking he was talking about talking
[ __ ] about employment or something.
>> Yeah, it would have been him, bro. It
would have been him.
>> LT or something, is it?
>> Yeah, that's Yeah, him. Yeah.
>> Yeah, he's a strange fellow. Him, bro.
He's a strange fellow.
>> Yeah, he was chatting their [ __ ] about
employment regulations and all weird [ __ ]
>> Oh, you follow football in it?
>> Yeah. What
>> What team are you again? Chelton. >> Who? >> Chelton.
>> No, you're not.
>> I'm joking. Mil.
>> Oh, yeah. Do Bro, I watched that the
rivalry of West Ham and Milwood. It used
to be [ __ ] mad back in the day, bro. >> Yeah,
>> it did it, bro. >> Bushwhackers.
>> [ __ ] that, bro. It's mad, is it? Over
over football, huh?
Yeah, proper. Are you going out tomorrow? >> Huh?
>> What are you doing tomorrow?
>> I don't know, bro. Are you?
>> Same. Don't know yet.
>> What are you going out drinking uh next week?
>> Maybe. I bet you don't drink. I don't
even drink that much anymore, you know, bro.
>> Don't you?
>> Nah, I used to drink like [ __ ] white
rum all the time. White Captain Morgans.
I don't know how the [ __ ] I used used to
do it when I was 23, 24, 25. Bro, >> yeah,
>> when I do drink now, I just stick to
Guinness or I try to just stick to Guinness.
>> Are you going to go back to the bookies
tomorrow and try and win that 20 back? [ __ ] that.
>> Nah, bro. I'm not like that, bro. I'm
not I'm not like I don't do, you know,
like Timmy. Yeah. He does it like every
day. I'm not like that like every day,
bro. But if if I I just do it randomly.
You know what I mean?
>> Timmy Timmy's bad. Really? That's I
think that's how I found you years ago
through Timmy. Timmy's bad gambler.
Really bad gambler.
>> Like and I if I lose I won't keep doing
it until I lose all my money. Like you
know some of these people and that but
it's just bad when I do do it. Do you
know what I mean?
>> Yeah. But do you
>> you going you going gambling tomorrow?
>> No. [ __ ] that. No way.
>> No. Definitely not. Why don't you buy
yourself online? Online is [ __ ] brutal.
Why don't I ban myself from online?
>> Yeah, why don't you ban yourself online
gambling? I have,
>> bro. I ban myself from Lad Brooks. Yeah,
but there's this site that I'm on and it
doesn't let you close the account. Like,
I've tried millions of times deposit
limit. They won't close it down, bro.
So, I think I'm just going to have to
have someone change the password, so I
can't access it if you get me.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's a good idea.
>> Because they won't close it. They will
not close it, bro. >> Why?
>> I don't know, bro. It's It's a site
that's not UK regulated yet. You know
what I mean? Them sites. Yeah.
>> And they will not close it down, bro.
>> And you know how you know it's so fixed?
They gave me 43 spins. Yeah. I got
[ __ ] £4 to 57 that I lost it trying
to complete the wagon. Cuz you need to
complete the wagon, in it. What's the
chances, bro? What's the chances? But
then when you put your money in, you
can't even double it.
>> All them all them promotions and all
that [ __ ] When I was online years ago,
I used to just decline all them because
of all the wagering and that. It's not
even worth doing it. No, but what it was
is they gave me it without depositing.
So, I thought, "Fuck it. I've got
nothing to do. I'm not going to put any more money."
>> I've had that. No deposit required, free
spins, and all that does is make me want
to deposit my own money and then smash
my phone up. So, I don't bother doing it.
>> Literally, it does, bro. Yeah, I know
exactly what you mean. It makes you want
to deposit your own money, bro. Is it?
>> And sometimes I've noticed as well with
the free spins they give you, you win
off of them. >> Yeah.
>> And then as soon as you deposit with
your car, you'll start with like 20, 30
quid and then it just [ __ ] goes.
Yeah. You lose when it's raw money,
which is like your money. No depositing
uh no um requirements. You lose. Think
about it, bro. £4 to 57 on roulette.
What's the chances, bro? Come on.
>> Yeah. Well, then I bet they took it all off you.
>> It took it all off me trying to [ __ ]
completely wager in. >> Yeah,
>> but think about it. I can put 100 right
right now, 150 in it right now. I'm not
doubling my money. I can tell you right
now, I'm not doubling my money.
>> It's um it's all just rigged. Big as [ __ ]
>> It is. I used to have some nice hits in
the casino, but that's that's about it, bro. >> Yeah.
>> You used to like the casino videos.
>> Yeah, I remember them years ago. It was
when you was on the iixxx account.
>> Yeah, I won four grand before from 150.
>> I remember I remember you doing one. You
was going burger and lobster. That's why
I said yesterday. It's world dear in
there, isn't it?
>> Yeah. You've been there, isn't it?
>> Yeah. It's quite expensive, isn't it?
How much did it cost you? I can't even
how much it cost. I know it was it was expensive. Yeah.
>> Me and two of my mates come to about 300 quid. >> Really? >> Yeah.
>> Well, for the three of you,
>> Timmy wants to link. >> Yeah.
That is expensive to be fair, bro. What the [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> You know where you should go, bro? You
should go to that steak and club.
>> Where? Steak and Co.
>> I haven't been there. That's deer as well, apparently.
>> Yeah. You know, you know what it is, it?
>> Yeah. I've not been there. It's meant to
be world deer, though.
>> It's nice, bro. Yeah, it's deer. But
it's nice. The chips there, bro.
>> Did you Who went? How many of you went? Just you?
>> No, I just went with my me and my mom,
bro. This was
>> that. How much was that? I bet that was
>> It was about 120.
>> Yeah. But you just cook your own like
you just cook your own own steak. But
the chips, bro, are another level, bro.
>> Yeah, they're nice, bro.
>> What did you eat today?
>> I haven't. Yeah, I'm literally That's
mad. I'm literally looking on Just Eat
now. It's all [ __ ]
>> I used to I used to use Just Eat, bro.
But you know what happened? They kept like
>> not delivering it to the address when
they were supposed to. They kept like
going to some random place, bro. So, I
had to change like the um delivery service.
>> My Uber my Uber Eats account my Uber
account got banned because I just kept
getting refunds all the time.
>> How you doing, PJ?
>> Yeah, I get you, bro. Yeah, good man.
>> Do you want to rob Sean?
>> Not really, bro.
>> Myself, but I want to see how passionate you are.
>> This guy's got really bad issues, by the way.
>> No, I got bad issues, bro. N so I want
to bo him.
Timmy, I thought you be honest by stick.
Do you lose brain cells watching this
community sometimes? I do.
>> [ __ ] Timmy. Timmy, I thought
>> Timmy, I thought you was going to punch
his head in,
>> bro. Take me, Tim. And I will. Why
should I have to do all the work?
>> Cuz you keep bringing it up.
>> Yeah. Somebody wants more than me. I
just want the money. PJ, I don't give a [ __ ] about
>> Yeah, PJ, he's got 15 grand in it. >> No.
>> Yeah, bro. Come on, Peter.
>> He hasn't got 15 grand. He hasn't got 15 grand, bro.
>> 10 cuz I've got to get my hands.
>> He hasn't got 15 grand.
>> Five grand. You get five grand for [ __ ]
all and you keep your hands clean to
take me to really.
>> Oh, this guy. Timmyy's a [ __ ] idiot,
bro. You're an idiot.
>> Timmy. Timmy. How do you know he's got
15 grand? Timmy, how do you know he's
got on camera that many times? He's a
>> You don't have 15 grand, bro.
>> The reason why I want to rob him is
because I don't like people who show off.
But I hate showoffs.
>> Oh, Timmy, Timmy, Timmy. If the guy had
15 grand, he wouldn't be in a [ __ ]
bed sit wearing charity shop clothes.
Come on. Make it make sense.
>> He's got money in that [ __ ] fairy box.
>> Okay, bro. Yeah. Okay.
>> Yeah, you're fant.
>> What's What's the What's the most money
you've ever had, Fire Stick? Uh, not
that much to be fair. About eight grand.
>> Fair play.
>> Yeah, I think the most I've ever had is
about nine. What? What? How did you get
that? Did you win it?
>> Yeah, I did actually. I won it I won it
over about two days.
>> What was it online?
>> No. Bookies. That was before the two
pound spin bar. That was when it was
that was when it went not when it you
know when it went to 50 a spin and you
had to load money over the counter for £100 spin. >> Yeah.
>> That was around then. I will rob Sean if
you admit you're a virgin.
>> Oh, bye-bye to me. See, this is why I
can't have him on here, bro. You can't
You can't talk normal with these people, bro.
>> What? They always talk about sex.
>> He's just They just talk [ __ ] in it, bro.
>> Did you kick him?
>> Yeah, he's a [ __ ] bro.
>> He reckons He reckons the 15 grand is
definitely there inside of the wooden box, apparently.
>> Man, he's a [ __ ] [ __ ] But yeah,
I've had I've had nine grand, so we've
had about the same, bro. Yeah.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Did you Did you What did you do? Did you
gamble it all back or
>> I spent I spent about three grand and
five went back was my biggest loss.
>> Did you like um Did you go on holiday or that?
>> Uh no, just bought loads of trainers and
clothes and [ __ ] I won all of that.
>> That's what I used to do, bro.
>> I won all of it over off of about 500.
So, I still ended up up.
It's not It's not worth it. It makes me
mentally feel it's [ __ ] horrible.
>> I thought I was the only one, bro. Seriously.
>> Makes me feel sick in that.
>> It makes you feel like I do. It just
sounds bad to like say it, but you ever
come out the book each year and just
feel like just punching someone in the face, bro.
>> I feel like [ __ ] throwing myself in
front of a bus. No. Have you like I felt
like just uppercut?
>> Yeah, I've had that. That's what I said
to you. I've been proper horrible.
Proper horrible. I made the woman in He
said let He said let him back in. He
won't let him back in. He what? I don't
know what he's on about. He said let him back in.
>> It dep It depends. Yeah. No, he's he's
not even trying to come back in, bro.
You know these these people that call me
a virgin, you know, like this is what I
was saying to you earlier. You can't win
with them in it.
>> Yeah. I don't know. They are like
probably I know like
>> just like Timmy and all of them. You
can't you can't win with these people,
bro. How's it going? Okay, let's not
talk about your sexuality. It's talk about the >> you
>> Timmy, why you're never going to do
anything to anyone. Why are you [ __ ]
>> He's [ __ ] screwed. He's [ __ ]
himself over showing up.
>> So, Timmy, how
>> Yeah, when I when I when I used when I
used to win Fire Stick, I used to just I
bought like a load of like clothes from
Reese, bought trainers. Yeah. Similar to
you, to be honest.
>> Yeah, that's what Timmy, how do you know
the money's there, Timmy?
He's shown it off that many times. It's
been downloaded everywhere.
>> [ __ ] hell.
>> Have you seen the PJ? Have you seen the money
by the DWP? What I haven't declared,
>> but um are you you going to you going to
go on holiday this year or no, bro?
>> I'm not sure yet this PJ cuz you're too weak. And
>> did you go last year or now?
>> Yeah, I did. Just
>> did you like it?
>> Take that.
>> Yeah, it was all right.
>> Any birds.
>> Timmy, stop it, man. He's a [ __ ] He's
This guy's a [ __ ] bro.
I don't know how people laugh at this [ __ ] bro.
>> I laugh at you. I love it when you slack
me off. I actually get hard on.
>> So, Fireick, how come you come off
YouTube for a while? I didn't see you
for a while. Bro, you just you just get
sick of watching it.
>> Um, no. I was I was still on here. Just
I was just watching. Just never
commenting on it.
>> Yeah, man.
>> The reason The reason you The reason you
had the Y with me before the reason you
had the up with me before is I said that
um I said that you told me that you
[ __ ] two girls that night. You was
with Monty. I only said it winding him up.
>> Listen to me.
>> Yeah, I don't. It doesn't matter
anyways, bro. True [ __ ] game of being a virgin.
>> But Timmy, you actually are a virgin,
>> bro. You don't you know like I done like
a video of me getting my like my dick
sucked in it. I don't know if you ever
saw that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'll see
that one. I did see that one to be fair.
>> And this guy is still calling me a
virgin. Like you can't win with them, bro.
>> Sorry, bro. You might be laughing,
>> bro. Look at this bro. This is
embarrassing, is it?
Timmy. Timmy. Timmy, do you Timmy, do
you actually think he's a virgin? Be
honest. Do you think he's a virgin? Jokes aside. >> Peter,
>> No. Go on. Answer the answer the
question. Timmy. Timmy, do you really
think he's a virgin? Jokes aside. Be
honest now. Do you think he's a virgin?
>> I do think he's a virgin. Yeah. Oh, for
[ __ ] sake. Oh my god. You can't You
can't You can't win, bro. You can't You
can't win with him, bro.
You can't you can't win with them.
>> Um, did you Fire Stick, have you been
watching that Britain's Got Talent?
>> I was watching it about an hour and a
half, two hours ago. It was [ __ ]
>> Yeah. How come that KSI is a judge now, isn't it?
>> Yeah. He's the one who was boxing, is
it? With Logan Paul and that.
>> Yeah, that's weird. He's a judge now, bro.
>> Yeah. I was like, what the [ __ ]
Why is he left? I I didn't I didn't I
didn't kick him. He He left, bro.
>> Why is he in such a good mood? He must
have won money.
>> Yeah, bro. Maybe. Maybe.
>> I think he was gambling earlier because
I'm sub to him and I see the video he put up.
>> We We should meet up for a pint, man.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, definitely.
>> I don't know when I'm going to I might I
might go out next week or the week
after, bro. I don't know.
Who knows, bro? Who knows?
>> I think when he says that about you
being a virgin, I think he just says you
I think I think he's just trying to wind you up.
>> Yeah, but it's just silly though. Look, really, bro.
>> It's just me trying it.
>> To be fair, I did see a video of you.
It's all dark and you're videoing and
you're chatting away to the girl and you
said you mentioned something about we
[ __ ] last night and she said, "Yeah."
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying, bro. And
they they still call you a virgin. That makes sense.
>> Send that video to Timmy, isn't it?
>> I'm sure he's seen it.
>> Well, then he still keeps saying the same thing.
>> What one are you talking about? The one
from New Zealand.
>> I don't know. It's all dark and you're
chatting away to her.
>> What? In like a silly voice.
>> Uh, no, not really. You just like um you
you say something along you basically
you say something to prove that you
[ __ ] her last night and she agreed.
>> Yeah, but what if Timmy hears that? They
still say you're lying. >> Yeah,
>> he's Bro, you're I don't think you
understand. Timmy's got really bad disabilities.
>> He's Is he got a bird? >> Nah.
>> When did When did you last have a bird? >> Uh
about two years ago.
>> Yeah. You don't really care, is it?
>> No, I don't. as you know as you get
older you don't really care as much as
when I don't really care bro
>> I like my freedom I like to do what I
want when I want whenever I want
>> and I feel like your sex drive gets a
bit like it goes that the more you get
older the more you just like and it
>> you hate you you hate most women though in it
>> no I don't know do you know what I hate
bro I just hate the fact that they they
can do mad [ __ ] yeah and lead people on
and no one really calls them out for it Yeah.
>> And I hate white I hate white knights
more than anything, bro. What's your
opinion on them? Do you like them?
>> What some [ __ ] What the [ __ ] that?
They know what that is.
>> Like simps that like defend women to try
to look good.
>> Oh, they're just creeps when they do that.
>> You see it on nights out. Like I'm maybe
you have I don't know, but they do it.
Don't know if you've seen it, but they
do it on nights out as well. Like they
do [ __ ] If I've been out over the years
and start arguing with Sunburn, a bloke
always gets involved, but all he's
trying to do is [ __ ] her anyway.
>> Yeah. And and and and it's weird because
they don't like these like simps, but
then they still defend these women, it's
weird. I don't get people like that,
bro. Cuz my argument is this. Yeah. It's
like the women are not innocent. So,
when you have people defending them the
way they do, it's just weird to me.
>> Just reading your chat, you get some
weird [ __ ] wrote in your chat.
>> Yeah. So what what you've argued with
like a bird before and then a man's got involved. Yeah.
>> No, it was years and years and years
ago, probably [ __ ] seven, eight year
ago. And um
>> was in a club.
>> Yeah. The smoking area. She knocked the
drink all over me. I was pissed up and I
started screaming and shouting that. And
then this bloke was like, "Oh yeah,
don't talk to
>> Did you see that train? Did you see the
train video of me? You saw that in it?
You definitely saw that?"
>> Yeah, I see it. Yeah.
>> And you see that guy and then he got his
he got his head crushed in the door,
bro. Is that Is that what happened?
>> When he walked out, you know the
Elizabeth line, you know the doors as he
it's a time. So when he got to the door
>> on the Elizabeth line, you have the
train door and then you have another one
to the platform.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So when he walked when he
went to come off the door, it it shut in
his in his he crushed his head.
>> Oh. What? Just what? Just after you was
around with him.
>> Yeah. Yeah. That's what I'm saying. You
deserved it, bro. Is it
>> bro? That's so violating for him. That's
so violent. You should have just g
>> Well, he shouldn't he shouldn't be
defending women just for the sake of it
then, should he, bro?
>> Were you laughing when his head got shut
in the door? >> Obviously.
>> Is he his fault, bro? No one asked him
to start like [ __ ] sing, isn't it?
>> Where was that white chapel?
>> No, it was um it was going towards like
I think it was like Ilford. >> Yeah.
>> You know, Ilford, is it? Yeah, that's
Essex, ain't it?
>> Basically. Yeah, basically.
>> You're Lewis, is it? I've never been there, bro.
>> It's a [ __ ] hole.
>> I swear I've never ever ever been there,
bro. That's like one of the places I've never been.
>> I've heard about it. You So, you're like
near Catford, isn't it?
>> Not far. Do you know Peekom?
>> Yeah, I know Peekom. Yeah.
>> Do you think Peekom's a [ __ ] hole? Never
been. That's what I'm saying. I've never
been. I don't think I've been high.
>> It's like, you know, Cuden. I've never
I've been through it. Like, you know,
like in the summer I go to Brighton on a
train, you go through Cuden, but I've
never been like outside it.
>> I've stayed there in a hotel a little while ago.
>> It was [ __ ] was it?
>> I just went there for something to do.
Yeah, it's proper bad. It's always got
about on YouTube.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] that. I've heard about
Cordon, bro. I've heard, you know,
Brixton ain't even bad anymore. It used
to be bad. Like, you know, like 10 10 12
years ago, it used to be bad. It ain't
even banned anymore.
>> Well, Brixton.
>> Yeah, I went when I was 15. I've been
since, but when I first went when I was
15, it was proper like bad, bro. Bad.
But now it's not as it's it's all right now. It
>> I've never been there.
>> Well, Brixton. >> Yeah. >> Really?
>> Yeah. I've never actually been there.
>> Yeah. It's uh It's all right, bro.
Yo, PJ, do do you know that um do you
know who Darth Viper is?
>> Who that weirdo in it?
>> Yeah, Darth V.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That E juicer is in
it. That weird guy, bro. Yeah.
>> I don't know. Do you think he's a weirdo?
>> Yeah, bro.
>> I was watching some of his videos the
other day, bro. He's [ __ ] weirdo.
He's with some some bird dressed as a
bloke and that being all like [ __ ] weird.
>> Who do you think's the weirdest [ __ ] on here?
Uh, what the worst?
>> You watch L in it.
>> Oh, I hate that [ __ ]
>> Is it? I hate I hate him, bro. I hate him.
>> You know, he's never done. He's never
done that wrong personally. I tell you
what it is. Yeah. It's It's the way he
looks. He's just a big fat [ __ ] Like,
you know, the tree trunk legs when he
puts his feet when he puts his feet on
there. Do you agree with me though? He's
just a big massive beast.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
But I don't even know if you got
>> You're you're 32 in it. You said
>> no 30.
>> Oh, okay. Oh, well. Yeah. Around about
the same age as me.
>> That lord that Lord Jod, you seen the
size of his legs? He's [ __ ] disgusting.
>> He's a fat ugly bastard, bro.
>> And I can't stand his accent. I can't
understand the words.
>> You know, you know when I You know, when
I first uh discovered him, bro, I
couldn't even understand him, bro. I
needed subtitles. It took me a while. I
can't I can't understand him. He's just
That's all I can understand.
>> It's a dirty Northern Irish accent. It's
dirty, bro. Is it?
>> Northern Northern Ireland says horrible.
>> And and and the Brummy accent is
horrible as well, isn't it?
>> When I was there the other day, for the
first [ __ ] three or four hours,
everyone I spoke to spoke like they come
from London. Then I started doing the
Brummy accent. But yeah, Brumy's
horrible. Sounds like they're crying. >> It
on Sunday. I know. really horrible.
I don't I don't like the accent. Bry's I
think Scout is horrible as well.
>> Yeah, it is.
>> But yeah, Brmy. No, Bra like Timmy's
accent is bad.
>> You know you know you know Ali Law is retired. >> What?
>> Ali Law is retired. You know that.
>> What? What's that? I don't know who that is.
>> Ali Law that that ginger guy that used
to climb up the bridges and [ __ ]
>> Oh, him.
>> Yeah. You know he's retired in it.
>> Has he?
>> You know who it is, didn't it?
>> No, I don't.
>> Oh, he used to just like climb climb
bridges and [ __ ] like um
>> Yeah, I know. You mean
>> he done all the climbed all the big I
know roughly who he is, but I don't know
that much about him.
>> Yeah. Yeah, you've heard of him. Yeah.
Yeah. The bridges are there. He's retired, man.
>> Is he the one who climbed the shard or not?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
So, but how did you like did you
discover his channel?
>> No, I don't know who that is. All I know
is that Giza climbed the big buildings
now. I don't know who his name is. So, I
just ain't got a clue.
>> Where did you hear about it?
>> I see a thing on YouTube about a giza
climbing the shard. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. That was it, bro. That was it.
>> Someone said, "This is the most autistic
conversation I've ever heard."
>> Yeah. It's funny, bro.
Who the [ __ ] Ali Law?
>> Yeah, that that guy, bro. That that that
done the the the big brother and that is it.
>> No, you're making it up, bro. That's why you're laughing.
>> No, bro. I swear to God, he's got a YouTube channel. >> Bro,
>> I thought you was on a wind up.
>> No, 100%. No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. He He's retired, but he doesn't make videos anymore.
>> Oh, [ __ ]
>> Yeah. He He done that. The thing you're
talking about is him. Yeah.
>> Hey, what made you say that anyway? That was random.
>> Because um he used to put up some good
content in it. >> Yeah.
>> But he stopped doing it.
So you only you only watch like this
community, isn't it?
>> Oh, yeah. He was asking me um
who's the most [ __ ] Uh
well, the worst liar I think is Fat Dan. Uh-huh.
>> for talking [ __ ] He's fat Dan.
Apparently, he's dead.
>> Yeah, that's [ __ ] isn't it? That's
what the great guy said that, is it?
>> Yeah, I reckon he's [ __ ] The worst
one for [ __ ] is Fat Dan. Uh, who's most [ __ ]
>> Oh, I don't know. Maybe Rise.
>> Yeah, he's a [ __ ] [ __ ] in it, bro. Proper [ __ ]
>> He's a proper weirdo,
>> you know. You know, yeah, he he's he's
an idiot, man. He just copied things
that I say.
>> I only ever spoke to him like three times.
>> He just copy things that I say, bro.
>> He used to I can't lie. He did use he
did used to make me laugh. I can't lie.
>> Yeah, he's funny. But
he's a bit of a copycat in it.
>> Well, he used to copy you, does he?
>> Like what I say about this community,
about how a lot of these people ain't
got a life for that. He he he copies.
>> You know what I mean?
>> PJ, do you know do you know who Johnny Sins is?
>> Yeah. Porn star, bro.
>> Yeah. Do you watch any of his videos?
>> I don't watch. No, I don't watch any
stuff like that, bro. Because the thing
is, yeah, it looks too fake. So, I can't
get up on it.
>> Finally, someone who's talking sense.
They're so crap and unrealistic. The
room is all bright. They're always in
some like fancy apartment with big glass
window. It's just so fake. Not. And even
if you type in amateur homemade, it
still brings up Johnny Sins, isn't it?
>> Yeah, bro. I watch You're going to laugh
at this, but I watch porn from Vintage.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I've heard you say you watch
Vintage cuz it's more realistic.
>> Yeah, bro. Proper proper. I do. My
friend said to me like, "What? You watch
porn from the 70s? That's weird."
I was dead when he said that. But the
weirdest thing about it is do you know
the people you're watching are like in
their 70s now or they're dead. That's
the only weird thing.
>> So you do actually kind of think like
about that like when you're kind of you
know watching it.
>> Do you go on chatter bait?
>> I went on it yesterday bro and oh like
you know how like I'm into [ __ ] and
that. Yeah. I was watching some women
give some nice [ __ ] bro.
>> I've never been on there.
>> Yeah I went on it yesterday. [ __ ]
greasy told me about it.
You know that Greavvesy in your chat? Is
that the original one like from years
and years ago used to be like on on
Seaside Mark's chat? >> Yeah.
>> Is it the proper one or is it a fake Grey?
>> Yeah. No, it's a it's a proper one.
>> Oh, yeah. Grezy, if it's the original
one, Grezy, do you remember that video
of Seaside Mark and he says, uh, I'm
going live. I'm going live on
Chatterbait in a minute. So, if anyone
wants to join, anyone wants to join and
wank off with me, I'm going to be on
Chatterbait. Do you remember that, Grezy?
>> You You know that Mark? Yeah. You don't
understand that. I think he I think he
was a troll. You know, bro,
>> the first person I found about 12 years
ago was Timmy and then I found Mark.
Then I found you.
>> I found Tim because when I used to play
the FBI, I was like, "Oh, let me go on
YouTube and watch FBI videos."
>> I typed in I typed in FBI roulette
roulette and then that's how I found
Timmy. There used to be an account
called Jono and then he used to do um
roulette videos but he deleted his
account. Some [ __ ] like that.
Butimmy's one when I first found him was Fruit Madwell.
>> Yeah. He remember Do you remember that
video where he was with um Tiger and
Charlie and they were gambling on the roulette?
>> Yeah. And um
>> yeah Charlie's unworthy clock isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> He's all right. He's actually a cool guy.
>> And then yeah I've seen that video.
That's the that's the that's the first
ever one I see. And then Timmyy's
saying, "I want to get to 1,600." And
they're saying, "He's saying, you got
1,600 now." And Timmy's just going mental.
>> Yeah. Yeah. He'll never he'll never
he'll never change, man.
>> Have you seen the one of like Timmy is
like so going crazy, hysterical cuz he
won them. I think it's like£25 jackpot
on the fruit machine and he's singing,
dancing. Rip it, baby. Rip it. That's
what he keeps shouting.
>> No, I don't think I've seen that one. No. >> No.
So you remember like you remember Money
Mike and that is it?
>> Yeah, that's Timmy's mate, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> But like listen, do you think Cai Mark
was a troll?
>> Um what what faked all that [ __ ]
>> Like a lot of stuff like No, like you
think he was just winding people up with his videos?
>> I don't really know, but I can't lie.
Yeah, probably Greavves probably agree
with me. Yeah, that man [ __ ] provided
me with years and years of
entertainment. Yeah, he was some of the
[ __ ] videos were
>> you know the only thing is bro. Yeah, I
watched him but I stopped watching him
for ages because it was just the same
[ __ ] I stopped for ages watching him.
>> Greavves will probably agree and you'll
probably agree. He like back when he
lived in like one of not when he was
>> Yeah, that's when he done the best videos
and then when he went to um when he went
to like Sherborn the videos got a bit
[ __ ] and then when he went to
>> where is he now? Um,
can't remember what it's called. >> No,
>> I know what you're talking about, but I
forget. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Basically, the video just got more
boring and boring.
>> But the thing is, bro, the thing is
Yeah. Do Do you remember that video when
he drove all the way to Kent to try to
get with this woman? I think I'm the
only one that remembers it. Like, I'm
talking I'm talking like maybe seven,
eight years ago.
>> Have Have you Have you or Greezy, have
you seen the one where he drives like 2
hours away to buy to buy tomato flavored sausages?
No, I don't think I saw that one. No, I
stopped watching him though like for a
long time because it was just repetitive in it.
>> Yeah. Did you see the one Did you see
the one where he put his bed in the bathroom?
>> No, I seen the one where he's playing
with [ __ ] Um,
>> I've seen that one.
>> I just think I think he was just like
whining people up, but like do you know
do you think I'm a troll? People think
I'm a troll, bro, but I'm not.
that um that one where he's going
through [ __ ] is when he's on newspaper
and he said he's looking for golden nugget.
>> Yeah, but people think I'm a troll, bro,
but I'm actually not. Do you think I am?
>> What a troll. >> Yeah.
>> Uh no, I'd probably say you're not
because you talk about your life and real things.
>> Yeah. People like Rezy and [ __ ] they
think I'm trolling, but I'm actually
being serious, bro. >> Yeah. Mark,
>> he did used to Do you know what I didn't
understand about people? Yeah. That used
to hate on Do you remember years ago?
Yeah. When you used to get a lot a lot a
lot of hate like for being on benefits
and that. Do you remember that?
>> Yeah. Cuz people say you're scumbag and that.
>> But the thing I don't get it Yeah. is
they're still watching him. Yeah. They
don't have to watch him. A Yeah. And B.
Yeah. If he's not [ __ ] over the
system, then someone else is going to do
it. Think about it, bro. The thing that
makes me laugh about Mark is he gives
you all the bigger on there. Yeah. Oh,
I'll do this and I'll do that. But so
many times when he's been started on, he
[ __ ] shits himself every time.
>> Oh, dude. I remember when he got
battered. I remember when he got battered. Remember?
>> And he was what? He was crying
afterwards when he got home.
>> Yeah. He got battered. I remember that.
>> Someone rung the pub. I think someone
rung the pub and said he was a nons.
>> They battered him in it. Yeah. But the
benefit thing I never understood, bro,
because like there's always going to be
someone [ __ ] the system over, bro.
>> I don't know. I don't know where Mark
was getting all that dough from. I don't
know whether he had some money and it
run out. I don't know. But he was
>> he probably got he probably got
backdated money or something, bro.
>> But PJ, he was buying a PS5 brand new
for like 600 quid and then he'll go and
sell it to CX for [ __ ] 220, 240, but
he do it he do it again
>> cuz he used to cuz he used to gamble all
his money, bro. Yeah, he he says he
ain't been in the bookie since October 2022.
>> No, I remember I remember he used to go
do remember you know you know he used to
make me laugh about when he was playing
the move out on the machine and he said
it looks for what you ain't got
>> still to this day that makes me laugh.
>> He was still he's he was still gambling
the last few years was he definitely in it.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Like look at that.
>> Definitely bro
>> like look at that look at that electric
bike. He got that for like 1,600 and
then sold it. How much did you get for
that Grezy? It weren't a lot.
>> You knew and Greasy probably know more
than me because like I said, I stopped
watching them for a long time, bro.
>> I've known who Greasy is for years.
Greasy, do you remember when Mark was
live with them two old [ __ ] birds
that old tart and they're outside in the
tent and then she goes, "Hello, Grezy."
You was in you was in the same live
stream. Do you remember that, Grezy?
Yeah, I definitely don't remember that.
Mc Greavves probably does.
You remember when he met with Tiger and Timmy Eldridge?
>> Yeah, I've seen that. That video's got
bare views on it, isn't it?
>> Yeah, bro. Definitely.
>> Timmy Timmy won that day and he's got
money, isn't it? And he's like clapping
and dancing and making that noise that
he makes. So what what what um this is
how we do what year did you discover mera?
>> Uh I found Timmy for Timmy and Mark
found around the same time. I found you about
five six year ago.
>> Wow. Yeah. Long quite a while ago then
>> I was I was literally when I was in
Birmingham I was I was I was showing my
power YouTube short of you and I must
have you know when you swipe down swipe
back up so it plays again. I must must
have shown it to him about [ __ ] 20
times. We both in that hotel. We both
wetting ourselves laughing and my mate
said to me, "Who the fuck?" I said, "Oh,
s on YouTube." My mate don't know about
this community. So, if you try and
explain it to people, you can't really
explain it, can you? You got to be in it to know.
>> It's so disabled, bro. I wouldn't even try, bro. >> Yeah.
>> But no, it was for you. Oh, another I
must have must have watched it 10 times.
What? You was so funny what you were
saying. So, how much how much all in all
do you reckon you spent on like that Birmingham trip?
>> Like with the train and everything.
>> I worked it out when I got back. I spent
about 300 quid.
>> Well, it's not too bad though. >> No,
to be fair, you know, with the trains,
it's like if you get a rail card, it's
not even that expensive. But when you go
in Manchester, it's always the same
price. Whereas Birmingham, like it's
it's a lot lot cheaper for some reason.
I don't know why, but yeah.
>> Yeah. I was shocked. The hotel was only
42 quid. Where did you stay up there?
Uh I last time I was with uh Monty um I
just stayed at his but before then I
stayed at uh the it's called a block
hotel but the only thing is there's no
windows so it was [ __ ] hot as [ __ ] bro.
>> Oh that's like premier some of the
premier ends I've stayed in though you
can't open the windows well hot.
>> Yeah I've stayed in a block hotel. Uh
where is yeah I think I've stayed in block and
>> I first went there when I was n I first
went there when I was 19 but I I went
for Marley Bone. You can also go for
Marley Bone. I don't know if you knew
that, but you can also go for Marley Bone.
>> I thought you can only go from London to Houston.
>> Nah, Marley Bone and Houston cuz
>> when I was walking to get on the train
from Houston to Birmingham. Yeah. On the
left hand side there was all two ticket
people on the [ __ ] gate thing. That
was for the faster train and then the
slow one was 12 minutes after. I did try
and sneak through but I started arguing
with her and she was like, "Get the BTP,
get the transport, please." I mean, in
the end, I just went on a slow one.
Mad. Mad. Yeah. No, there's two ways of
getting there. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I didn't know you go from there.
Mar isn't it?
>> Watch when you go to King's Crossbow.
That is that that's that train station
is huge, bro. It's big.
>> Yeah, I've been there loads of times.
>> Yeah. But have you been to the bit where
like there there's two parts of it? Uh
>> there's there's there's there's like the
Euro store bit and then there's
escalated when you go up to go to
Nottingham and then there's a second bit
where you go like Newcastle and leads
and that is
>> I didn't know there I didn't know there
was a second bit there.
>> Yeah, there's two there's two parts to it.
>> Oh yeah. Have you been to that station?
Yeah. [ __ ] I think it might be Canary
Wolf and you have to go through like a
shopping center to get to the Elizabeth line.
>> Uh no, I don't think so.
>> [ __ ] well confusing.
Why did you Why did you go King's Cross?
Was you on the US or something?
>> No, I can't even remember. I was
>> Yeah. So, you Nottingham and Sheffield
like just up the escalator, but then
there's a second part of it and it's
>> when you're on the when you're on the
trains. Yeah. Especially when you're on
the underground. Yeah. Do you ever think
like do you ever walk you ever just walk
every no matter what bit you go on the
people stink of bo?
>> Yeah. Yeah. They stink, bro. Have you
ever, bro, have you ever come back out
on a train? Yeah. And you you get into
like an argument with someone like on a
r? I have, bro.
>> Uh yeah, I heard I heard you ran with a
bus driver once.
>> Yeah, it was funny, bro.
You should go you should go if you
really want to go to like a really
rundown shitty place, bro, you should go
to Middles, bro. I've been there. It's a
[ __ ] hole. Go there, bro. Check it out in it.
>> How bad? really bad.
>> What life?
>> Really [ __ ] bad. It's a [ __ ] hole, bro.
>> How How long was you there before you
realized it was a [ __ ] hole?
>> [ __ ] two minutes, bro.
>> Obviously. Yeah. Yeah. I was staying
there just and then I was going on a
night out in Newcastle and that in it.
>> Was it really really bad?
>> Yeah, it was bad. Bro,
>> I'm just googling it now.
Have you ever been to slow?
That's a [ __ ] bro.
>> I've seen on the telly. That is a [ __ ]
hole. A proper proper [ __ ] hole, bro. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, I've been there. It's a [ __ ] hole.
Do you remember? Do you remember that Fraser lad? >> Who? >> Fraser.
>> No. Who the [ __ ] that?
>> Some guy. He used to used to come here.
You remember him? We used Freze. We used
to call him Phys. Or was he in this community? >> Mhm.
>> His name was Ross. His first name was
Ross in it.
>> No, I don't I don't know who it is.
>> Yeah. Have you ever spoke to that Darth Viper?
>> No, he's he's come on here texting and
that and just chat [ __ ] but yeah, he's
just a [ __ ]
>> He's a proper He's PJ. He's a proper
weirdo. He is.
>> He is, bro.
Proper on it. Proper. Proper.
>> Uh, you asked me who the biggest weirdo
on there was. Yeah, like I'd say it's
Rise and [ __ ] you know that Faith.
>> Oh yeah, he's in prison, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Did you see him on that [ __ ]
burnt that thing? [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Did you think Monty M's going to
go to prison?
>> Uh, no. Because he told me that he's
never had community service. He's never
had a suspended sentence. He's never had
tag. He's never had [ __ ] all. So I said, "No."
>> In prison, is it?
>> Yeah. only once.
>> [ __ ] that. But it was just scary.
>> Yeah, it was horrible. 80 years it was
when I was 18. Belmont.
>> How long How long How long did you spend there?
>> Uh 6 weeks.
>> Oh, I bet it dragged on in it.
>> It was 12 years ago when it's [ __ ]
>> [ __ ] that, bro. You know, do you know
the bit that kind of scares me? Yeah.
Like, so like, did they remind you? >> No.
>> Yeah. show. You know the thing that
scares me is like you know from the
court Yeah. when they when they drive
you like to the prison it's eight it's
like an hour away isn't it?
>> Um it depends. It depends what court you
depends what court you was at
>> but how long did it take how long did it take you?
>> About half hour was a Brmley magistrates.
>> Oh what what magistrates? >> Brmley.
>> Okay. Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Took about half hour. I got three marks.
>> I done about five. I done about five and a half.
>> What did you do?
>> Um I was on a driving ban
>> and then I smashed up I smashed up my
mother's car and I got nicked driving whilst disqualified
driving drink driving whilst disqualified.
>> That's quite steep though, is it? Like
normally you don't go prison, is it?
>> Um they was going to um it was they did
arrest me for dangerous driving at first
but then they dropped it.
They shouldn't. You should. That's quite
like steep though, putting you in prison
for that, isn't it? Oh,
>> I should have plead guilty. I pleaded
not guilty and went to trial and got
found guilty. If I had pleaded guilty, I
probably would have got much less penalty.
>> Yeah, probably. Yeah. Yeah. cuz I got I
I when I when I crashed the car, I broke
my leg and then they come there and my
leg they had to take me to the hospital
before to the before the police station
>> and then I was in the hospital for hours
and hours and hours and then uh by the
time I got to the police station I
refused to blow and I should have blown
I'd probably been under.
>> Yeah. Yeah. That's the thing is it but
you know you know it's in America it's
so [ __ ] bro because they don't do the
blowing. They do like these tests, isn't it?
>> What tests?
>> They do these tests where they make you
like count and and and and like they be
like, "Oh, how many fingers am I showing
up?" And they don't do like a a blow
test like they do here.
>> It's weird.
>> They make them walk up and down there, is it?
>> Yeah. They do some mad [ __ ] bro. They
do some mad [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah.
>> Whereas here, you just blowing it.
>> So PJ, have you been watching Bear
Vintage Porn lately or not?
>> Nah, not Bear, bro. I watched it the
other day, bro.
>> You said on you said on stream the other
week you you've not even been watching porn.
>> I watched it a couple of days ago. I
don't watch it that much, bro. >> Yeah,
>> you watch it in it. You watch porn in it >> sometimes.
>> Yeah, but you have to use a VPN now. Is it?
>> Yeah, because [ __ ] if I'm if I'm
indoors Oh, you made me laugh saying that. >> Yeah.
>> If I'm indoors connected to Wi-Fi, it's
all right. If I'm out somewhere or
whatever, I'm on a mobile data, then
yeah, I have to connect to a VPN. But I
used to have to do that anyway because I
I haven't got adult websites turned on and
you have to send them a picture of ID.
But even now, if you're from the UK in
it, you have to verify your age and like crap.
>> Yeah, that's why I just use a VPN, is it?
>> Yeah. Where do you normally pick? Belgium.
>> It's just just No, any anywhere, bro.
It's not Belgium. I don't know where, but anywhere.
Some of them pick them by themselves.
>> Yeah, I think it's like Argentina or some [ __ ]
>> That made me laugh when you said about VPN.
>> So, what what kind of porn are you watching then?
>> [ __ ] just homemade amateur.
>> So, no vintage?
>> No, I've never I've seen it here, but
I've never watched it. All like hairy
and fat and disgusting.
>> I like like a nice story vintage. Like
>> it sounds so weird, bro. I know it does.
It does sound so weird, is it? But yeah,
>> I know what you mean, though. But it's
more realistic than like Johnny Sins and
Elbrook, for example.
>> Yeah. Where
you watching with this woman and she was
like [ __ ] in the cinema and that, but
it was like a story. It was like a
>> I've watched I've watched ones that are
not a story.
>> Yeah. Like I like them story ones, bro.
like the proper proper story. But do you
know what's so mad? Yeah. Is a lot of
them porn stars like even like not
vintage like even in today's like day
and age bro a lot of them are dead you know bro. >> What
>> a lot of them died young is it? A lot of
them did bro.
>> What like 70s porn stars?
>> No like even like even today's ones like
stuff and them as well like a lot of
them have have died quite like young you know
>> why have killed themselves. Some have
died. You know what I mean? How do you
even know that? Because I I do my
research in it, bro.
>> What? Reddit?
>> No, I just my research in it, bro. Like
you get to know porn stars and that in
it. And like I mean, you ever been on a
thing called Kora?
>> Nah, I use um X.
>> No, I'm not on about porn websites. I'm
on about just like search. I know. It's
the same as [ __ ] What's that one that
you go on Reddit? It's like that. It's called Kora.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I have actually. Yeah.
>> People [ __ ] on it.
>> Yeah. I've I've not I've not used it,
but I've I've read like people posting on it.
>> Yeah. I've seen your screen.
>> Have you been Have you been on Mom's Net?
>> No, I've heard of that though.
>> Yeah. There's one called There's one
called Mom's Net and it's
searched up over the years and it's come
up mom's net. I have searched up over
the years. It's called Mom's Net. What
have you been on that? Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And there's what? There's
one called Digi Spy.
>> No, I've not been on that one.
>> Yeah, cool. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Someone's saying that someone's saying
basically that you never got the food
earlier on after you gambled because you
gambled the food money away. That's what
they're saying in the chat.
>> Yeah, they're chatting [ __ ] Bro,
>> I ate earlier, bro.
>> What did you What? They're saying that
you gambled your food money away. I
thought you left with a tennis,
>> bro. I've got money, bro.
>> Yeah. Obviously, bro, I never I never
don't have money, bro. I'm saying these
people are idiots, bro.
>> That's what they do. They call people
skint every day, bro. Would you um would
you join the porn industry? I've been
thinking about pride, bro.
>> Probably not now. >> Really?
>> Would you?
>> Yeah, I've been thinking about it.
I've been saying I'm going to like apply
and that, but I haven't. Why not, bro? I
don't know if
>> I would even know. How do you even go
about doing that [ __ ]
>> You just applied for a website, ain't it?
>> Oh, yeah. I thought you was going to Thailand anyway.
>> Will you come with me?
>> I would like to go there. The flight's
too long, though. But I thought you was
going there soon.
>> Yeah, I might still do, bro. But we
should go together.
>> Would you be honest? Yeah. Don't even
lie. Would you [ __ ] a lady boy? >> No.
I wouldn't personally, but I'm not gay
in any way, shape, or form, but you'll
probably agree with me. Some of them you
would not know the saw something on
Instagram earlier when
>> some of them are [ __ ] one lady boy,
but you wouldn't believe. Yeah, you wouldn't know.
>> Yeah, you would not know. I don't It's
not being gay either. Just being
realistic. Some of them to look at are
actually so good-looking where they had
loads of surgery and that.
>> So, when was the last time you like you
you've you kissed a woman like two years ago? Yeah.
>> No, not two years ago. [ __ ] two two
years ago. So when was the last time then?
>> Hold on one sec.
Hold on two minutes.
Greg, do you like these little discussions?
Oh, Grezy's such a troll, man.
Do you remember Grezy? Poor [ __ ]
Greasy. Poor [ __ ]
Do you remember that account? Grezy, poor [ __ ]
Yeah, he'll be getting deprived of consensus. [ __ ]
Oh, that cat looks like the virgin
[ __ ] We look like a virgin [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I'm back now. What are you on
about, poor [ __ ] What is that? Do you
remember? Do you remember that account
that used to come on and like mock me?
Like it used to come on like different
accounts and that. Do you remember?
Don't know. It's been a lot quite a few.
Yeah, I just used to
um so um yeah, when did you last kiss someone then?
>> Uh no comment.
>> Fair enough, bro. Fair enough.
>> These these videos just get posted
everywhere, so I don't want to go into detail.
>> Yeah, fair enough. To be fair, bro. To
>> I'm a I'm a li I'm a dirty not doing
anything. I don't care.
You're a [ __ ] It
>> don't really bother me. You know that
disgusting fish tuna smell.
>> So like when you was in what what food
did you eat, bro? When you when you went
bing rub there,
>> just go and get some tell. Let me tell
you something. If you ever get a
stinker. Yeah. If you have a [ __ ] a
mackerel, just go in the [ __ ]
bathroom. Yeah. Look for Vick's vapor
rub. Just put a little bit underneath
your nose like a little around your
nostrils. Go back and smash it.
>> Works every time. Then that way you
ain't got brea
or if you can't if you can't find any
like body lotion or anything like just
to find your nose then you just got you
just got to [ __ ] don't breathe
through your nose in it. Just breathe
through your mouth otherwise you'll be sick.
>> Did you have some good food in Birmingham though?
>> Uh no [ __ ] Popeyes. It was [ __ ] disgusting.
>> Never had that. You know I know what it
is but never had it.
>> [ __ ] horrible. Don't get it.
>> I used to go to this um buffet in
Birmingham called Jimmy Spices. Lush
bro. Lush. I don't know if it's still
there, but it was in the by the Chinatown. >> Yeah.
>> All the places Chinatown looks horrible.
>> Yeah. I don't really like Birmingham,
bro. To be fair.
>> No, it's a [ __ ] hole. Are you going back there again?
>> No. No reason to. Do you know the reason
I went to I went to meet Monty? Cuz I
said I was going to. I said if my
football wins, I might. And then it won.
So, I kind of like I didn't want him to cry.
If I didn't go, he'd start crying in it.
>> PJ, you got to tell me something. Please
tell me this. Yeah.
>> What happened with the [ __ ] with in
the nightclub in Brixton, bro? Please
tell me the truth,
>> bro. I told you earlier, you know,
>> but I've heard so many different
stories. I want to hear it from you. You
never told me before.
>> Yeah, I'm sure I have, but I'll tell you again.
>> I asked I asked you before and then you
said you'd tell me later on.
>> I'll tell I'll tell you. I'll tell you.
So I was in Brixton in this nightclub
and I was getting sexually frustrated.
>> So I come out the nightclub and it
closed right in it and I'm thinking,
bro, I need to like I need to have a
wank in it. I'm getting [ __ ] horny in
it. And obviously I'm far from I'm far
from home in it.
>> So I went like in between this like wall
thing in it and I started wanking in it
and it was by like someone's motorbike.
I didn't even [ __ ] realize. And the
guy come up to me, what what are you
doing? He trying to steal my motorbike.
He's he trying to grab me and that, bro.
And his friend was like, "Leave him.
Leave him." I said, "I'm not trying." He
thought I was trying to steal his bike.
>> Did you tell him what you was doing?
>> No, I didn't tell him what I was doing,
but I just said I weren't obviously not,
but I said I weren't trying to steal your bike.
>> Imagine if you He assumed I was trying
to like break the lock or something in it.
>> Imagine Imagine Imagine if you said to
me, "I'm not stealing your bike. I'm
just wanking it."
>> Yeah. Obviously, I didn't tell him that
in it, bro. When he first come out, did
he do you see Did you have your dick in
your hand? Did he catch up?
>> No. No. No. I don't think so. I think I
think I see him coming toward me. You
know what I'm saying? So, I had to
>> Yeah, but obviously when you said to
him, "I'm not stealing your bike." He
would have automatically said to you,
"What the [ __ ] are you doing here then?"
>> Yeah. I don't have said something. But I
forget in it.
>> I bet you said you was having a piss in it.
>> Maybe. Maybe. Maybe. I can't.
>> PJ, tell me what happened. What happened
with this Escort? the one that you paid
extra to finish in her mouth and then it
all ended bad. What happened?
>> Uh so bas so basically yeah she was like
oh oh I can finish in her mouth in it.
Right. So I paid her extra in it.
>> So then she said I can't do it. And I
said oh I want I want half my money
back. I want half my money back.
>> She was like no no no. And you know how
like these brothel have got like
security in it. >> Yeah.
>> He was coming up. Yeah. And I told him
yeah get the [ __ ] out of my face. Yeah.
I want I want like half the money back.
Cuz that's what we agreed with. He was
like, "No, no, no. You got to go." I
said, "If you don't give the money back,
I'm going to do the windows." And I
swear to God, I was going to do the
windows. And I was shouting, shouting,
shouting. Bro, 10 minutes later, they
gave half the money back cuz we had a deal. >> Yeah.
>> Well, they actually paid the money back.
>> Half the money back. Half not the money,
but half the money back because
obviously I paid extra. When When you do
it in a mouth, they charge you extra in
it like they normally do, in it.
>> Yeah, they always do. Or it's called ow or without.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying. So
obviously I paid for it like in you know
what I mean?
>> Yeah. But when um
tell us when you
>> I was going to smash the windows, bro. I
was just going to do the windows in.
>> Was he trying to beat you up? >> Huh?
>> Was he trying to beat you up? The security guy?
>> No, obviously not. I said, "Yeah, I'll
go. But if you don't if you don't give
the money back, I'm going to do the
windows in." So
>> yeah. Yeah. And they they probably give
you they probably give you the money
back. They didn't want no police there in it.
Yeah, but a lot of these escorts, bro,
nowadays are so rude. You know, when I
last met Yeah. which was a few weeks
ago, they're trying to say, "Oh, yeah."
Now they're saying that they don't suck
[ __ ] dick without [ __ ] condom.
It's got worse, bro.
>> Did you get
>> It's hard to find a good escort
nowadays, bro. Like, it's hard. Like,
you do get them. There are good ones,
but there's a lot of rude ones, bro.
>> I've I've done loads and loads and loads
of brass. She's in call out call.
>> So, you know what I mean. So, you know
what I'm saying in it, bro? Some Yeah.
Some some are like really really nice is
it? You can get them really but most of
them are I swear they're [ __ ] most of them.
>> I can only there's only two like I said
I've done nice but most of them are
disgusting. Even the ones on Viva
Street. Yeah. Do you know what Viva
Street is? Isn't it?
>> Yeah. Of course I know.
>> Even on Viva Street. Yeah. If you like
even the ones that say ID verified then
they're just still different people most
of the time when they come. And also
have you ever been like going through
them all? Yeah. And then I just like
save the one, two, three, four, and I
just message a load of them, see who
answers. And then when you go to go on a
different advert with different
pictures, you press call and then cut
the phone off them. Go to save the
number and it's the same number in it
with a different ad.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Exactly,
bro. Exactly. And who you're talking to
on the phone, you're not it's not them.
So when you get there, so they're
telling you something on the phone,
right? So then when you get there,
they're saying something different. >> Yeah,
>> bro. You know about Fever Street. [ __ ]
me, bro. There I've had it so bad here
where I've actually been there and they
haven't they haven't like they've made
me go all that way and then they've not like answered.
>> I've had that before. I've had them
trying to get me to fend money before I get there.
>> I had one, bro. Yeah. I was I was trying
to get a [ __ ] um [ __ ] before, bro.
Yeah. Like without a condom and that.
And there was one escort I knew, but she
moved. I had to go all the way to
[ __ ] Harlo. I had to go all the way
to Bro, it was long, but I was like I
really fancy. I was horny that day, bro.
It was in the summer, in it. >> Yeah.
>> So, I knew like cuz I had been with her
before, but she moved from Stratford in
it. So, I went all the way past Wembley
and [ __ ] bro. Like, cuz I knew. But
like, so how many would you say you've
been with? I would say me easy 100 plus.
But I've been with so many, bro.
>> No, not that many. Me probably about 40
in my still enough. Well, I'm saying
probably to be fair, probably 40, 50,
but I don't know. I've been with so many.
>> The dearest
The most I've ever paid was 200. That
was for an hour out call. That was when
I was in a Hilton when I won loads of
money years ago.
>> Hotels are [ __ ] nice, isn't it? Rm Hilton Hotel.
>> Yeah, I won a few grand so I just went
on a mad one and the cheapest I've had
was a in Chinese 15 minutes 30 quid. She
was disgusting though.
>> Have you been with other Chinese before?
>> Uh I've done two or three.
>> They're nice. Do you know what though?
They are nice though. But they're like
the attitude is nice. They're not rude.
I've noticed that, bro. With Chinese
people, they're not rude.
>> I've never done a I've never done a
black escort. My mate did when I was
with him, but I didn't.
>> Bro, do you remember Do you remember
that Chinese one I had started licking my ass?
>> No, my my power had that before.
>> But you you bro, I went to this [ __ ]
I went to this um escort. I still got
her number, by the way. She's in
Manchester. She always says, "Oh, come
to Manchester and see me. Come to
Manchester and see me." I've gone to see
her. This is when I was living in
Stratford. I've gone to see her and that
and then she's given before she's giving
me a [ __ ] Yeah. She's she's licking
my ass. I'm thinking is she doing what
I'm I'm thinking she's doing, bro. I'm
thinking she was she licking Was she
licking the was she licking the bit in
between the guicking your [ __ ]
>> She was licking my [ __ ] She was
licking my [ __ ] Bro,
>> what did you say?
>> I didn't do anything. But do you know
the maddest thing? Yeah. I bared before.
She's lucky I barfed, bro. cuz I'm
pretty sure people would have some [ __ ]
in her mouth, bro. Like I literally
bathed before I went there.
>> Yeah, very luckily I did. But she's I
think she's like sucking my dick in that.
>> Did you have a [ __ ] after you had a
bath? Did you have a [ __ ] after you had a bath?
>> Um I don't think so.
>> Just like even [ __ ] before I had a bath.
>> Even though even when you use baby wipes
now, there's still poop particles there for everybody.
>> Yeah, true. But it would have been a lot
worse. Imagine I just had a curry, bro.
Yeah. I just had a coffee and and I did
bath. Your you bro, you know your hotel
in Birmingham did have a bath.
>> Uh, no. It was a [ __ ] It was a
disabled It was like a disability access
room for people in wheelchairs. They
give us that one. It had like a wet room
shower with seat.
>> So, what what Hilton was you staying at
when you stayed in the hill? What
location was that?
>> Uh, Tulie Street right near London Dungeons.
>> Oh, bro.
>> London. I would I would love I haven't
had a bath for ages because there's no
bath in this house. But when I used to
stay in hotels, I used to like love I
used to take advantage of them baths,
bro. I used to I used to [ __ ] have a
bath. I used to nickel like the towels and that
>> Well, the hotel ones.
>> Yeah, I take them back with me, bro.
>> I don't care what anyone says. You will
never get softer towels in a hotel towel,
>> bro. You don't, bro. We've still got
them from like a couple of years ago.
They still look brand new, bro.
>> I've done that before. I took the towels in.
>> They last years. They last They last
years as well, bro. But the one they
they last is in it, bro. 100%.
>> Yeah, they're good.
>> And they give you these little like, do
you know them little um these little
shampoos and the shower gels, you know,
like these little dark blue [ __ ]
thing? They smell so nice, bro.
>> Yeah. Do you take all that as well?
>> Hey, I take everything, bro. >> Yeah.
>> Do you take do you take this stuff as well?
>> Uh took towels before. Um I took a
pillow once. Can't remember why,
>> bro. Like I used to when I used to go
traveling. Yeah. I used to have this
like duffel bag. I got it from Amazon.
It's about10 pound. You know them duffel bags. >> Yeah.
>> And I used to just ram the towels in
them, bro. You could fit so much [ __ ] in
it. Like just take them back with me.
>> Yeah. Done, bro. Done. Job done.
>> When did you When did you stay in the hotel last? >> Uh
Jesus Christ. When was it?
>> I can't even remember, bro. Probably
when I went to Wales, maybe. That was like,
[ __ ] knows, bro. Maybe a year, year and
a bit ago.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] hell. Ages ago then.
>> Ages ago, bro. I don't really do it
anymore. I think it was Wales. cuz I
didn't I didn't in Birmingham
or maybe it was maybe it was London bro
when I was shing this burden at I used
to like stay in hotels and maybe don't
know maybe it was either there or Wales but
I stayed in more hotels out of London
than I did in London that made sense.
>> No, I couldn't hear you. It all went
quiet. I can hear you now.
>> I said I used to stay in more I've
stayed in more hotels out of London than
in London. I've only seen him a couple times.
>> Yeah. Yeah. If you're going to do it,
you might as well go. That's what that's
all that's all me and my mate done was
went up Birmingham just to explore.
>> Yeah. I've done enough. I used to do a
lot of that, bro. Edinburgh. I stayed in
a hotel in Scotland. Was nice, bro.
>> Yeah. I've not been there.
>> Yeah. Nice hotel, bro. Nice hotel. Nice
towels. Nice, bro.
>> Did you go to Did you go Glasgow?
>> No. Edinburgh. I've never been Glasgow. Yeah.
>> You ever you ever been to Southampton?
I've never been there.
>> No, I ain't.
>> You never been there? I've never been
there or Blackpool.
>> No, I've not been Blackpool. You're
right about um You're right about
middles, bro. I googled it. Is it? I
googled his middles were a nice place to
live. And it basically just says here is
a [ __ ] [ __ ] old man.
>> You've been You've been to Brighton
Beach though. It
>> Yeah, I've been the casino there. There
was when I went there about 10 years ago
was a casino. I don't know if it's still
there on the on the seafront.
>> Yeah, I've been to the same one, bro. I
think I won like
>> I lost about 500 quid in there.
>> [ __ ] hell. Did you just go straight
back home after?
>> Uh yeah, I had two more nights in the
hotel and I was just so pissed off. I
just uh just Yeah. Just drove home. Just ruin
ruined the whole thing.
>> Yeah, it does. It just ruins the whole
Just ruins the whole neighbor. Yeah,
>> I I reckon you're going to play some
online roulette soon, bro.
>> [ __ ] that.
>> You are. You are. It
>> I ain't even got no online accounts. I
was banned on that GameStop years ago
and then every time I used to try and
make a new one, he used to tell me no.
>> Tell us when you locked the escort in
the Oh, yeah.
>> I I had a man escorted.
>> Yeah. Go on.
So there was this h so this was the
second time of me using an escort right
when I was 17. Yeah. And I [ __ ] her in
it. And I came in like um like quickly
bro maybe 2 minutes a minute. 2 minutes
>> and I feel like oh I didn't get my
money's worth. It was only £110 a lot
cheaper back then. So I was like oh I
want my money back. I want I want my
money back and that in it. I lock I
locked her in until she gave my money
back. I sw Yeah. That was years ago. I
just saw that comment. Yeah. >> Time.
>> If you pay when when you pay for an
hour, have you ever had them when they
like when it's an out call to hotel and
then they try and sit there. They try
and kill about 20 minutes talking [ __ ]
>> Yeah. I had this one bro who who I was
um who I was saying, "Oh, she only does
out call." Yeah. But she wanted me to
travel to her area in a hotel. And I'm
thinking, "Oh, I'm not doing that. What the fuck?"
>> Like, she's just trying to take the
piss. Like and and what was so weird is
I've seen her like four times before.
She just turned into like a [ __ ] I
know. [ __ ] you, bro.
>> Yeah. What's that about?
>> I don't know, bro. I said if you if
you're going to charge people out call prices,
>> you need to your area is it?
>> I'm just laughing because I've got one
I've got one once and uh that's I've
never refused any of them. Yeah, even
bad ones, but this one I said, "No, [ __ ]
that." You know, when you go
>> I've done escorts I've done escorts out
of London as well. I've done it in
Manchester. I've done it in um where's
the other place? Nottingham. I've done
it in I've done it in Newcastle. I've
done it in um Sheffield. Oh, there's a
brothel in Sheffield. Oh, bro,
Sheffield's a good night out, bro.
There's like a few brothel there as well.
>> Do you find Do you find when you go to
in calls, they're well secret about the
address in it. They only give you the
postcode and that
>> you have to bring
>> and then when you get there and then
they give you the number then Oh, yeah.
Scotland as well.
>> Oh, bro. That's the baddest thing. Yeah.
When I went to Scotland. Yeah.
Literally, I went on a night out. Yeah,
bro. And I stay in the hotel. So,
everywhere shuts at like 3:00 in the
morning, in it. So, I banged I banged
this escort. She was from Albania. I
remember this. Yeah. And I just got the
first train back on, bro. It was long.
It was long. I didn't even go back to
the hotel. Went on this.
>> You went back to the hotel. I know you did.
>> I didn't, bro. I got the first train
back home. I didn't even [ __ ] cuz I
went on the night out. It was a Friday.
I I got the numbers. I got up I got some
numbers and stuff. Um bang this escort
got a train home and just text the
numbers up. I should have stayed a bit
longer though, bro. To be fair. I should
have went glass and that but I just went back home.
>> What? Then what? Then went to sleep.
>> Yeah, bro. I f I fell Bro, I fell asleep
on a [ __ ] train, bro. I was tired as
[ __ ] all that day traveling and I was tired.
>> I remember falling asleep. Yeah, I
remember falling asleep and waking up in
Newcastle, bro. It was long.
>> No way. Yeah, it's long, bro. It's long. Yeah.
>> Wait, PJ, if you're on a train. Yeah.
And you're dying for a [ __ ] Yeah. Do
you do you use the toilets on it?
>> Yeah. Damn right, bro.
>> I bet you like the flusher in it. You
know, when he goes,
>> "Yeah, but bro, I'm scared. I'm always
scared to No, no, but bro, I'm scared to
fall asleep on trains because you know
Do you know why, bro? Why do you think
I'm scared to fall to sleep on a train?"
>> I don't know.
>> In case someone nicks my phone, bro.
>> Yeah, true.
>> That's what always goes through my mind,
bro. Like if I thought that's the only
You know what I'm saying, bro? Yeah. Literally. Literally.
>> Have you not ever gone into the train
toilet before though? There's [ __ ] and piss everywhere.
>> No, not not in um not in the train ones. No.
>> Have you ever Have you ever dodged like
the ticket inspectors and that they're [ __ ] the toilet?
>> There was one before. He was a when I
come back from Birmingham, he's being a
proper [ __ ] bro.
I' had mad bus drivers. cuz me and bus
drivers don't get on.
>> Yeah, they're ignorant bus driver, bro.
A lot of the It's so ignorant, isn't it?
>> What happened with the one from on the
train from Scotland?
>> Oh, no, there was not. There wasn't It
wasn't there. It was coming back from
Birmingham. No, basically what it was is
I went on the train. Yeah. And he could
have easily just let me stay on that
train, but he kicked me off and then I
had to wait eight I think I had to wait
in commentary for like another [ __ ]
It was long. He was just being He was
just being a [ __ ] He could have easily
let me stay on that train, but he was
just being a [ __ ] >> Yeah.
You just give them fake details. You
just I just give them fake details. They
can't touch you. They can't like You
know what I mean? So, Oh, yeah. That's
what I always do.
>> You know, you know, Wait, wait, wait.
You know, when you went Birmingham, did
any ticket inspectors come? >> Yeah.
>> Well, both times. But there back in it
>> on the way there and on the way back.
>> See, do you know what's so funny though?
Yeah. Every time I've been to Wales, I
can never recall them being on on like
any of them trains, but every time I go
in Manchester, they're always there,
bro. Birmingham, they're always there.
>> I tell you where I tell you where's hard
to get through the I'm I'm I'm good at
doing it. Yeah. Like London Bridge is
easy. I can just walk through with
people. I'll just push through them. I
tell you where's hard. Liverpool Street,
that's hard. If you ain't got a ticket.
>> Yeah, I can imagine. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I can imagine. Well, like going to
like um like Clton and like Essics and
that is it.
>> Yeah. I was where was I going? I was
going to I can't remember where I was going.
>> I really can't remember where I was
going, but I didn't want to buy a
ticket. But yeah, you can't get through
there. I did. I pushed through with
somebody and they was on me straight away.
>> So, you just didn't go then or you had
to buy a ticket?
>> Yeah. No, I had to buy a ticket.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Do you ever when you do buy tickets? But
you know sometimes No, no, but bro,
sometimes have you ever had it yet when
you've got off at a station and there's
just like foot there's police and everything like
>> Yeah, loads of times.
>> Yeah. So you can't get away there
either, is it?
>> Yeah. It's just long. I've I've gone
back onto the platform and got a train
on to another stop. I've done that as well.
>> Bro, you know the train station
Maryland? Have you ever been there? The Statford Mland.
>> What? I've been Stratford station.
>> No, there's one called Mryland before
it, bro. And I swear to God, Greavvesy.
Yeah. One time I come off like Maryland
and there was like bare there was so
many inspectors and police waiting. Are
you sure you've seen that?
>> Well, you've seen that. Really? Yeah.
>> I've not been to Maryland. I've seen
>> you seen it in other stations. How Okay.
How many was there then?
>> Well, when I see it. >> Yeah.
>> Uh London Bridge Underground about 10
police officers with the where the bars are.
>> Yeah. They're waiting in it. Yeah.
They're waiting for people.
>> They had a they had a dog. One of them
was had a dog and you know letting it
sniff people. Is it they went by for
drugs? I think
>> that happens in Stratford though. You
know Stratford Westfield in the summer
they do that in it where they pull
people aside to search them and that
>> you know Stratford station you walk I
was there the other day we we we got off
there and we got to eat and Stratford
station is that the one where you come
outside and there's steps that go down
and like weird flower leaf things great big things. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I was there the other day
and I crossed over and went into the
center and then in some little food
court thing and there was some pizza
place. [ __ ] well nice.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Do you know what I mean?
>> Yeah. What What Stratford Center? Yeah.
The shop a small bit shopping center
bit. Yeah. Yeah. There's like a It's
called continents, isn't it?
>> Yeah. I don't Yeah. I don't know. It was
like two pound.
>> There's different food places. There's
>> Yeah. Different food places in there.
>> Yeah. There's like a kebab one. There's
like Yeah. Yeah. A beach one. Yeah. I
know what you're talking about, bro.
There's bare people begging when I come
out of the shopping center on the floor.
>> You went past the subway and that in it. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, I know, bro. I used to live in
Stratford for years. You like it? What?
What the [ __ ] was you doing there?
>> Uh I don't even know why we was there.
We changed there. >> Yeah.
Yeah, bro. [ __ ] hell. Yeah, I used to
I used to live there, bro, for years.
But I never go drinking around. If I
ever go drinking, it's always Tottenham.
It's always central. I never [ __ ] go
anywhere like that. You I mean did you
say Tottenham Court Road?
>> Yeah, always. Bro, Leicester Square,
Chinatown, always. Is it?
>> Have you ever been to somewhere called Sul South?
>> No, I know it. There's loads of Indians
out there. Is it?
>> Yeah. Just spare packies everywhere,
bro. Like literally, it's ridiculous.
>> I've heard of it. Yeah.
>> When you come out when you come out the
station, it doesn't say like welcome to
It says welcome to S, but it's in Arabic writing.
>> Yeah. What did you what did you go
drinking there or something? Uh
>> we was going to but it just [ __ ]
stinks of curry everywhere
and we're just full of Indians and it just Yeah.
>> Have you been Shepherd's Bush?
>> Yeah. Bushy that it's got a good
Westfield though. It's better than Stratford Westfield.
>> I've not been in the Westfield though.
>> Yeah, it's big. It's [ __ ] It's only
two floors but it's huge bro. [ __ ] hell.
>> Have you been to that South place? It's probably
>> No, I've never been there. There was one
woman I was I was I met before in
O'Neal. She was from there. She just
spit up with her boyfriend in it. Yeah.
And I met my friend in it. I p I sort of
lipod her up in it in front of this
white night in it and we started kissing
and that it was funny.
>> One of the one of the birds I see you're
in like a club and the music's playing
and you're kissing her. She's rough. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But you've seen me with other
people as well is it?
>> Did you bang that one? That rough looking one?
>> Nah. You've seen me with other ones
though, is it?
>> Uh, I see there's one of them. He was
like start tonging her. The video is
only like 10 seconds. She was fit as [ __ ]
>> Which one? The one in the pink.
>> I can't remember.
>> Probably. Yeah.
>> You're wearing a You're wearing a You're
wearing a jumper.
>> Yeah, the Ralph Lauren jumper. Like it's
like a beige one, isn't it?
>> Yeah, that bird was nice looking.
>> Yeah, bro. I think Bango, but Yeah.
She's from Brazil, isn't it? Is she from Brazil?
>> Yeah. You You've been with Bro, you've
been with a Brazilian escort. I've been
with bad escorts, isn't it?
>> Have you ever when you've been on Viva
Street, have you ever looked here and it
says like they're 23 year old, they're
from Brazil, and then when they come,
it's like some 40-year-old Romanian.
>> No, it wasn't the one I paid, mate. All
of the women I've kissed and never paid
any of them.
>> We're not all like your boyfriend, Lord
J, bro. We're not all like your boyfriend.
>> Who is this doctor?
>> Yeah, it is. I know what you mean. Yeah,
they did. They're catfishing, is it?
These escorts are catfishing.
>> Who is this Dr. Eko? He's always beefing
you, isn't it?
>> This another L ass licker.
>> What do you mean that's the one he paid?
What did you pay her for that kiss?
>> No, obviously not, bro. These What it is
with these people, bro? Yeah. Where
they're ugly and they can't pull birds,
they think everyone else is like them.
>> That's what they're like on here, bro.
That's how they think. That's how their
mind think because they can't go out and
get anything. Everyone else is the same
as them. that fit girl. Yeah. Please
don't tell me you paid her for that kiss, bro.
>> Bro, I just told you I didn't.
>> Oh, yeah. I didn't hear you.
>> Oh, no, I didn't. No, no. What I'm
saying to you is, bro, these No, no.
What I'm saying to you, bro, is that
where these people can't go out and get
it, they hate other people that can, so
they just talk [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> I mean, you should know what they're
like, bro. You've been on here like
years it, bro. Like,
>> yeah, just trollers.
>> But with the escorts and stuff. Yeah.
Um, yeah, they're catfish. Yeah. I mean
I mean like the ones you've got. Yeah,
most of them. Where have they been from?
>> Um, normally they're Romanian.
>> They're rude though. That the Romanian
ones are rude, isn't it?
>> I've only ever had one English proper
English woman. She was about 40. Black
I've never had an English one.
>> Yeah, I've only ever had one.
>> I had two when I went to Amsterdam.
>> I've done I've done loads of them
Romanian ones and they're just so blunt
and rude. All they want is your money
and they just want to [ __ ] off quick
time. It just really pisses me off. I
just want to punch her in.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Ice. Well, they used to be obviously
obviously they're all there just they're
only there for the money and they don't
give a [ __ ] about you. But at least some
of them sit and chat you and like have a
laugh with them and drink and >> Yeah.
>> But some some of them are just so blunt
and rude and horrible. One of them I
really want you to just punch your head
and really did horrible [ __ ]
>> Some of them like if they like you
enough, bro, some of them even try to
kiss you and that bro even though
they're not supposed to. Yeah, rarely.
But it has one I had one who didn't
speak any English and she g me a
laminated piece of paper with with a
price list. It said like oral without
extra 20 kissing extra 20 and you had to
I've had it where I've had to translate
like you know like Google translate on my phone.
>> No you ain't.
>> Yeah I [ __ ] have
you spoke what you spoke into the phone
then put it to her face.
>> No I just typed it. I just typed it in
>> Yeah. Did she know? Did she understand?
Well, yeah, cuz it it translated into
her language, in it.
>> Yeah, but sometimes that Google
translate, I've done that before and
then apparently it don't sound the same
as what how they actually speak or
saying, but did she know?
>> There was one there was one I used to
like um I saw twice. I don't know what
happened to her. And she was nice, bro.
She's like, "Oh, is everything okay? Did
you like the service?" She was like
really nice, bro. Like they are there,
but they're hard to She was like Italian
and Romanian, but she was so nice, bro.
>> But most of a lot of them were just
[ __ ] Yeah, a lot of them are just I
had it before in I had one before in
central London, bro, but you had to use
a condom mute. It sucked. >> Yeah.
>> You know, like Chinatown, bro. There's
bit there's places in Chinatown where
you can walk up the stairs. Like there's
there's certain places, you get what I mean?
>> Have you done it? Yeah, I know. The same
in SO as well.
>> Yeah, there's certain like Yeah. Have
you been so
>> obviously, bro?
Have I been Oh, of course, man. What the [ __ ]
Go to Amsterdam. There's some nice
escorts. I I use two.
>> I want to go. I really want to go there.
Apparently, they're more expensive, though.
>> Nah, bro. 50 to 100.
>> How long?
>> I can't I think I had half an hour.
>> Yeah, that ain't too bad.
>> Yeah. And you can actually see who
you're picking. I went a few Do you
remember when I went there?
>> Yeah, I remember when you went there. I
didn't know you on Brasses there. Yeah,
of course I did, bro.
>> How did you get there?
>> People don't, but >> Huh?
>> Did you fly there?
>> No. You >> Yeah.
>> Would you Would you would you would you
go Would you go by yourself?
>> Uh, I'd probably just go with probably
just go by P. I would go places by
myself. How did you get the Euro Star
there to Amsterdam?
>> Uh, King's Cross.
>> Yeah. To where?
>> Amsterdam. Central train station.
>> How long does that take?
>> It took about 4 and a half hours, bro.
I'm not going to lie.
>> Yeah, it took Yeah, 4 and a half hours.
>> I didn't know you could go from King's
Cross straight to Amsterdam.
>> Yeah, that's a US, bro.
>> Yeah, I didn't know all the way to Amsterdam.
>> Yeah, it goes to France about go to
France, Belgium, Amsterdam.
>> Yeah, a lot of people go there, go on
the ferry, is in it. They go like David
Deal and then they drive there. So you
you've been to Paris?
>> No, I ain't.
>> No, I haven't either.
>> Would you want to go there?
>> Did you did you go to France? So you
didn't go like in school as a child? I never
>> No, I didn't know. >> No. No, bro.
>> When are you out when are you going out approaching next?
>> [ __ ] knows, bro. I'm talking to this
bird. I'm going to be meeting her soon
in it. Someone I met a few weeks ago and
that she's cool that in it. So I
probably just meet her.
>> No, you're not going to approach me. I
thought you was quitting approaching.
>> That's what I'm saying. I have quit.
That's what I meant. And and this person
>> I said in your chat to you a couple of
months ago. I said to you [ __ ] you
should go approaching.
>> I went out, bro. I went out three weeks
ago. That was the first time in three months. Bro,
>> everything I suggest everything I
suggested to you about approaching to
get birds, you said you've already done it.
>> Yeah, that was months. But bro, listen.
I can't be bothered with it anymore,
bro. I mean, I mean, when are you going
to approach again?
>> I ain't.
>> This is long.
>> But like, do you ever see anyone in
public? Then you just do it.
>> I have a few times, but they always just
say, you know, exactly what they say.
>> I don't know what they say. I don't I
don't know your experience. I know my
experiences, bro, but I don't know your experiences.
>> Oh, yeah. I bet you've got a BU account, isn't it?
>> Nah, I don't use dating apps, bro. I
haven't for ages.
>> Boom. Yeah, you got to upgrade to the
premium one, otherwise it's [ __ ]
>> I was on [ __ ] Bro, I was on Tinder
the other day. Yeah. And I'm I'm telling
you, I swear they're bots, bro. I swear
they're bots on there.
>> Some of Some of the pictures look like
them fake American pictures, in it,
>> bro. There's one I'm speaking to
actually on on on WhatsApp. Yeah. She's
not fake, but she's she's not the best
looking to be fair.
>> Well, where's she from?
>> Uh, somewhere uh halfway halfway to
Cambridge. Halfway to Cambridge. But
she's not fat. She isn't fat.
>> What app did you meet her on? >> Tinder.
>> Well, you're both swag. >> Yeah.
>> So, wait. So, like what's what's
happened before? Like when you've
approached the public?
>> Um, just similar to you. I only do it
when I'm pissed. Um,
>> what did they what did they say? What
did they like? Tell me the things they
done and that.
>> I've got a boyfriend.
>> Yeah, but no, but like did you No, no,
but did you get their number and then
they started [ __ ] with you via text as well?
>> No, to be fair, I haven't.
>> Cuz I've got numbers and then they've
started like [ __ ] with me like via text.
>> Oh, no, bro. You don't need to tell me.
I've seen all the damn screenshots you
put up. I read every single one.
>> Yeah, that's that's why I was like,
"Fuck this, bro." Then this is too toxic.
>> I can't lie. I can't lie. That one that
girl was deep. Yeah, she look quite fit
as well and you're chatting away to her
and then she like everything's going
fine and she just [ __ ] just switches
just turns up on you.
>> Which one, bro? There's so many.
>> It's I don't know. She looks quite fit
in a picture and you're chatting away to
her and then yeah, she just everything
seemed to be going well and that and she
just turned on you. I don't know why.
>> You know the one I'm on about?
>> Nah, bro.
>> Remember that post you put up with all the
>> I heard the video. Yeah, in the video.
Yeah, I know. But I don't know which one
you're what what specific one you're talking about.
>> Oh, yeah. I've seen I've read all I've
read all of your ones.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] in it. Proper [ __ ]
>> Yeah. I don't know which one you're
talking to, bro. Cuz most of them went
like that, is it? So,
>> yeah. I can't lie. You have had a bad
luck with uh with girls you But that was
annoying you though. That was annoying
you when people was defending them, was it? >> Yeah.
You said it was annoying you or
something, couldn't it?
>> Yeah. Um, it just pisses me off when
people say, "Oh, there's plenty more
fish in the sea." Or, "We'll just go out
and try again. There'll be one."
>> Yeah. [ __ ] that, bro. You You've seen
from my experiences, it's quite hard.
>> You put You put a lot of time and effort
into that. I can see why you're [ __ ]
sick to death with it.
>> Yeah, bro. Do you know when I quit?
Yeah. You know, when I quit like 3
months ago, I was getting like mood
swings every day for like a week and a
half. It was pissing me off, bro. But
then after that, after that. Yeah.
>> Oh, bro. After that, I was fine in it. I
was like, "Okay, just move on about it."
>> Yeah. Why was you getting them mood
swings? I was listening to your streams about it.
>> Cuz it was cuz the whole dating thing
was annoying, bro.
Put yourself in my shoes, bro, if you're
getting like [ __ ] up. Do you know what
I'm saying, bro? Like,
>> how many years worth of approaching have
you actually done?
>> Years. But what you're not
understanding, bro, is like, you know, 2
and a half years ago, it was it was
easier. It was better. Like, it was
still hard, but it was better than now.
I used to get like loads of dates, and
>> it was still hard, but you'd get bits
here and there. Do you get me? >> Yeah.
>> But now you you don't seem to get [ __ ] all.
>> Why? What's
>> I don't know, bro. I don't I just think
it's it's gotten harder, is it?
You know what I mean, bro? Like
>> I just But you have you have you ever
been out drinking? Yeah.
>> And got someone's number and got a date
that way? I'm sure you haven't. It
>> uh Yeah, a few times.
>> Yeah. So like you know when you when you
when you know when you went to that
O'Neals last year, did you talk to
anyone in it? You must have.
>> Yeah. It was packed.
>> Yeah. It was always So like did you did
you get how many numbers did you get?
>> Bare girls in there. Just none. I was
pissed out. My head falling all over the
place. There was be girls in there all
like uni all like uni girls. They look about >> Yeah.
>> Between between 18 and 25.
>> I used to love that O'Neal, bro. Like I
said to you, bro, like I think I used to
get there. I used to get a lot of dates
from there as well. But
>> I always if I go there, I drink Guinness
in there. Everyone drinks Guinness in
>> There was loads of like managers and
security in it.
>> Have you not seen the bird in there? The
one with light blonde hair.
>> Which one?
>> One who works behind the bar.
I I I've seen Indian ones and that, but
>> I've seen the Indian girl as well. She's
all right looking, isn't it?
>> Yeah, there's a few right bartenders,
bro. I They used to all know, bro. It's
funny you should say that. Yeah. You
know, my friend um he went to O'Neal's
the other day. Yeah. And the bouncer,
cuz I know all the bouncers. Yeah. He
says, "Oh, where am I?" And that I said,
"Oh, give him my number." He said, "You
ain't been coming for a while and that
in it." I said, "Yeah, bro. I got my
phone stolen, so I had to change my
number." Like, they all they all know me
there, bro. The bartenders.
>> How many times have you been there?
A lot of times, bro. A lot of times. >> What?
>> More times. More times than I've banged
escorts, I'd say.
>> No way. You've been there that many times.
>> Yeah, bro. I used to go there. Like I
said, I used to go there Thursday, Saturdays.
>> [ __ ] hell. I didn't know you've been
there that many times.
>> Many, many, many. That was my go-to
place, bro. That was like That was like
the pickup place, bro.
>> All right. Yo, PJ, that's what I was
going to ask you. Yeah. Who is Do you
know the video of the geyser and he
rings up the casino and says that you're
threatening to kill the kids on that?
Yeah. Who's the gezer? Whose voice is
that? Who brings the casino?
>> Uh, Voice of Reason.
>> Who is it?
>> He's He's called Voice of Reason.
>> Is it? What? V O R. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, I've seen him on here. I don't
really know much about him, but I've
seen him on here. Is that him on there
saying all that?
>> Yeah, he's a freak, bro.
>> Is he a weirdo?
>> Proper weirdo, bro. Proper weirdo.
>> He's like He's like being world dramatic
and that he's like, "Oh, yeah. I think
you should know because he's he's a
dangerous person and he's
>> Yeah, he tries he tries to get people
banned from places, bro. Cuz he's fat
low life, isn't it?
>> Is he fat disgusting [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> I've never seen him.
>> What's What's your What's your favorite
month to go drinking in like June and it? >> Um
I do like it in the summer, but you I
don't like it when it's really hot. I
like it when it's you know when it's
been really hot and it cools down in the evening.
>> Yeah. Like like at like Aprilish, isn't
it? Early May.
>> Yeah. And then sitting in like weather
spoons in the garden. That's nice.
>> Yeah. I don't like it when it's too hot
to be fair.
>> Yeah. No, that's
>> And you know, Guinness like I like
Guinness and you like Guinness. That's
more like a winter drink. You don't
really in the summer it's a bit like too
much. You get me?
>> Yeah. I always find Guinness like a
Christmy drink. Don't know why.
>> And January and February. Yeah.
>> Yeah. When it's when it's hot when it's
really hot, you don't drink Guinness then.
>> I have Corona. Me.
>> Corona's nice with lime.
>> Yeah. In the in the summer in it. Yeah.
Yeah. Desperado was lying like that.
>> You You can't drink white rum in it. Nah,
>> I've never drunk it.
>> It's [ __ ] bro. It's really [ __ ] the
next day. Yeah. You You get these mad
hangovers. Mad hangovers.
>> I drunk. I had drunk, bro.
I um What did Tim say? PJ turned gay. What?
>> It was Timmy. You don't make sense. I
don't know what the [ __ ] he's on about.
I had drunk rum. I drunk that Ray and
nephew and I got pissed out my head on it.
>> But and you know the good thing with
Guinness you know if you drink a lot you
you don't get the hangovers. That's the
good thing about it. >> Uh
I don't really get hangovers.
>> How many how many Guinness can you drink?
>> Bro, I would say roughly bro in a whole night.
>> I'm saying six or seven, bro. You
>> That's exactly what I was going to say.
Six or seven. any more than that just
make me feel sick.
>> Yeah. Like people say like the thing is
in central London they say, "Oh, the
prices are a lot." But they don't
understand, bro, you're not really
realistically going to be drinking more
than seven Guinnesses. Whereas whereas
like with the with the spirits, they
water it down in it. Whereas the beer,
they can't really do that. So
>> yeah, they definitely they definitely
water the spirits down. I don't give a
[ __ ] what 100%, bro. Like you've been to
Simmons before, in it.
>> Yeah. And I dropped like 2530
worth of [ __ ] rum and it didn't even hit me. >> Yeah.
>> Said the other day. Wait. Um, let put
the link in for Timmy. You said he's
with a bird.
>> Yeah. Okay. I want to say, bro. Yeah.
So, they just take the take the absolute
[ __ ] piss, bro.
>> 30 of That's like 10 shots. You should have
>> What simmons did you go to? >> What?
>> What Simmons did you go to? >> London.
Yeah, but which one? There's loads in London. >> Central.
>> Oh, yeah. But like Leicester Square or Oxford Circus.
>> Oxford Circus. Have you been to that one?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> That's the one I went to. It's dear in
there, isn't it?
>> Yeah. But if you go like Thursday,
there's happy hour in it on the like
Yeah. Monday to Friday or something.
>> Oh, I've only ever been there like once.
>> Do you like it?
>> Uh, it was all right. I prefer O'Neal
was in Chinatown. >> Yeah.
>> What What day did you go to that uh
Simmons then? Saturday. Yeah.
>> I ain't got [ __ ] clue years ago.
>> Yeah. Mad.
>> Where's Tim?
>> Why do you go Why do you go drinking in
your area? Not busy enough, is it?
>> Um Yeah. It's just a [ __ ] hole.
>> I can't [ __ ] I can't go and sit in like
local pubs, you know, be just some fat
disgusting old men and
>> No, I can't. I can't. That's why I can't
>> You know, do you know the pubs? I mean,
and it stinks.
>> Yeah, I know exactly what you mean, bro.
>> Carpet stinks in there.
>> To be fair, though, you you have you've
been to Rumford.
>> Yeah, up in Romford,
>> bro. They're drinking They're drinking
over They're drinking over here, bro.
It's not even that bad. You know,
there's like good little drinking a few
spots, you know, to I've been on a night
I've been on a night out in Bason. >> Yeah. Yeah,
>> but you know, Roford, there's a few like
little places, you know,
>> Yeah, there's a couple. It's not too bad
if you just wanted like a quick drink
and a You know what I'm saying? Like
it's not, you know, it's not bad. It's
not bad at all.
There you go. The link's there. Who's not joining? >> He's
a bit of a Rford's all right, you know.
Yeah, that's where you live in it.
>> Near there. My mom moved in it, but I'm
not from there. From East London. But yeah. Uh
>> yeah, there is there's a few places
comes under Essics, isn't it?
>> It comes under more London to be fair.
It's more London, isn't it? Because it's
like it's just it's more London.
>> Essics is like what I class Essex is. I
class Essics as like Chelmsford,
Colchester, South End. That's what I
class like Essex. Do you know what I'm saying? As
>> Yeah. Have you been to Ilford?
>> Yeah, many times. Bro,
>> that's where I had a [ __ ] It's a
[ __ ] Bro, have you been to the
O'Neals in Ilford?
>> No, I ain't. That's where I had my
That's where I had my car windows tinted
there. And it was a [ __ ] hole.
>> It's a [ __ ] hole, bro. There's loads of
bookies. There's loads of like phone
shops and that.
>> There's loads of phone shops and TK Maxx
there and that. Yeah. Bitlford, bro.
>> PJ, would you PJ, would you say that you
hate all women?
>> No, not really.
>> That's what they always write about you
on the videos, isn't it?
>> Yeah. I just think most of them are [ __ ]
>> You've had a bad bad run with them, is
it? You would you say most of them were [ __ ]
>> The some of the ones that you've had.
Yeah. When I was reading them messages.
>> Why? Cuz Okay. What were they doing?
Just blatantly leading me on it.
>> Yeah. One of them was it looked like it
was going well and then [ __ ] she just
I don't know. Head [ __ ] you.
>> Oh, and do you know do you know what
annoys me, bro? Yeah. With with these
people like it could be anyone online.
Yeah. Like you were saying crawl on
Reddit. Yeah. So you meet a bird, you
try to meet them within four or five
days. People say, "Oh, oh, you're trying
to meet them too fast. Oh, oh, you're
coming on too strong. Uh oh. So then you
you speak to them for 3 weeks and then
they just [ __ ] you over anyways. Like you can't
>> I've read I've read
>> you can't do you can't do right for
doing wrong. Do you get like as a man?
Yeah. They always want to blame you.
Does that make sense?
>> Yeah. Yeah. 100%. I've read your Reddit
post as well that you've posted before
and it I agree with what you're saying
about literally you can't win because
one person will say you're being too
pushy and then you'll put an approach
video up of you like being like a bit
more quieter and a bit more shy and they
say to you show a bit more enthusiasm
and then if you do that then they say
you're being too pushy and then if you
do that then they say you're not you're
not being pushy enough.
>> It's [ __ ] ridiculous.
>> Like this woman that I'm speaking to
now. Yeah. Like I'm going to be meeting
her like [ __ ] next week and that but
I've been I've spoken to her like voice
notes. we speak every day that like
she's got like stuff going on and [ __ ]
and she's overwhelmed. But that's like a
one-off. But normally, bro, like say you
go on say you go to O'Neal yet on a
Thursday, you want to be meeting a woman
by the next week, bro. There's no reason
why you you you you can't. You know what I'm saying?
>> Unless some, you know what I'm saying?
Like unless they're in another country
or there is a valid reason. Like what's
the excuse, bro? Come on now.
>> This one you're talking to now is she bare fat.
>> Nah. No fat at all, bro.
You're a fat girl, would I? Come on.
>> You know when the Yeah. [ __ ] that. You
know when you go on the You know when
you go on the been on the dating apps? Yeah. >> Uhhuh.
>> And you know when you've been looking
through and that on plenty of fish and
that like obviously everyone that do you
ever notice the fat girls like they
never they only take a picture from like
the shoulder up.
>> Yeah. like certain like angles to make them look
>> And have you ever have you ever like you
ever been like chatting to one and they
finally do send you another picture?
Yeah. And you just can't believe how big
they are cuz in the pictures you've seen
already they don't even look big at all.
>> Yeah. Exactly, bro. I I've I've
approached people and they look and
where I've been like drunk. I haven't
remembered what they kind of look like.
So I've got them on WhatsApp. So you're
seeing their picture in it. So you you
only kind of remember them from like
their picture. So I think oh [ __ ] yeah
man. And then you meet them and they're
[ __ ] completely [ __ ] different.
>> Have you ever gone to meet a bird and
then you've not even spoke to her? You
just turned around and [ __ ] off.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I I've I've walked out on
people. I've literally like said I'm
going toilet and didn't come back.
>> I've had it happen to me as well. I've
had it, bro. There was one in O'Neal's.
Yeah. With this Canadian. Yeah.
>> I said I'm going toilet. I'm going to
come back, bro. Went back. She dipped. Bro,
>> what? Tell me what happened with the one
where you [ __ ] off. What's the story?
Oh, she was from uh Birmingham. Yeah,
funny enough. Yeah. And I didn't really like
>> like her like that. Yeah. Because she
was a bit like me. Oh, and do you know
what? It wasn't even that yet. It was
the fact that she was trying to get me
to pay for everything. She's like, "Oh,
bias this in Weber Spoons. I want you to
pay for this. I want you." And I'm not
getting anything out of it. She's
[ __ ] off back to Birmingham tomorrow.
And I'm thinking, "No, I just need to go
to that. Just [ __ ] off."
Like, because if she wasn't like that,
then I would have just stayed in it. But
it's like she isn't the best like
looking. She's trying to get me to pay
for everything. Like
>> she's just trying to She's just trying
to use you. >> Yeah.
>> What did she What was she like bare fat in it?
>> Yeah. Kind of. Yeah. Yeah.
>> And like what did she have a bit of an ugly face?
>> Yeah. But obviously if she wasn't trying
to use me in that then I probably would
have just stayed. You get Do you
understand what I'm saying?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. She's just trying to
take a piss. >> Yeah.
>> So I just [ __ ] dipped, bro. Um there
was another one. There's another one I
dipped on before. Oh yeah, there was a
Ginger one who I met in O'Neal's. Yeah.
And I went casino with her. I was like,
"Bro, I can't even I went on a date. We
went to O'Neal's." Couldn't even imagine
like kissing her, bro. She was like,
"Jinger with freckles, bro." I said,
"Oh, I'm I'm I'm going toilet." And I
just [ __ ] off. But the thing is, bro,
you know when I done this, yeah, I never
blocked them, bro. And I always like a
couple of months after. Yeah. Listen,
bro. I always said, "Oh, I done this
because of this reason." I never like
I've never just ghosted someone and left people wondering.
>> The minute you left the minute you
walked out at the casino, you blocked
her to PJ. I know you did.
>> No, I didn't. I swear to God in my mom's
life, I didn't, bro. I I've never done
it. I've never blocked them when I've
ditched them, bro. I swear to God, I never have.
>> Do they not start ringing you in that?
>> No, they just say they just they say
like two messages being like pissed off
and that and it, but then what I'm
saying to you is like after a month or
two months, I'll come back and and I'll
explain, oh, this that and the other.
But whereas these women, they won't.
They'll ghost you and block you and they
don't care, bro. That's how you know
they they got no emotion, bro. >> Yeah.
>> Cuz I feel bad to the point where I was
like, "Oh yeah, I done this because and
and I weren't even chatting [ __ ] Oh
yeah, like I was still on another person
and that I've never blocked them." Like
I I can't do that, bro. I don't know
about you, but I can't do that, bro.
>> Yeah, I'll just block.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying. I can't I
can't just block Like I can't do that,
bro. Like what what these women I can't
do that, bro.
And then when they sent when they send
you a message like why did you ditch me
and did you answer?
>> She didn't say why um with the
Birmingham one. Yeah, I did. I said oh I
said oh there's a problem at the house.
I had to go back to the house and that
in it. I did answer. So I never block I
never blunt them and blocked them ever.
>> Did you say to the other one like I
couldn't kiss you cuz you like
disgusting [ __ ] face with the
freckles on that?
>> No. I don't even think she was too too
she wasn't like really fat and really
bad, but she just wasn't like
obviously she she wasn't good in it.
Obviously, bro, like >> Yeah.
>> You know what I'm saying, bro? Yeah, I
[ __ ] But I'm sure Have you had that
like when you've been on a date and like [ __ ]
>> Yeah, of course. So, I've
just What? You just didn't kiss them?
>> What? Say that again.
>> And what? You just didn't kiss them? Um,
no. I see I'm a dirty kind. I just I
bang anything. I don't care.
>> Yeah, but obviously if they're trying to
use you that you Yeah, I get what you mean. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, I've had I've had that.
That was a big fat thing. I I had I had
that and I just [ __ ] off literally. I
paid for You ever been You ever been
Have you ever been to the Swan in
Stockwell? That's a good place.
>> No, I ain't. The one I'm on about. I
paid for a hotel in it and I said to
her, um, what did I say? Oh, I've left
something in the car or something like
that. and she was upstairs in the room
that I paid for.
>> So I just went down and I said, "I want
to check out." I said, "Some fat bird's
just gone in my room and she's refusing
to leave. So I don't feel comfortable
staying this hotel now cuz she's got in
my room so easily." And I just put the
key card thing down and left. >> Really? >> Yeah.
>> That's mad. But you've heard of this
one, isn't it? I'm sure you have.
>> What? Stockwell?
>> Yeah, bro. It's a good It's a good club,
bro. I've had people like fans there.
>> I've not been there. My mate was on
about the other day. Well, he was
talking about it. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I had a one night stand there on
my birthday, bro. I've
>> never been in there. Apparently, you get
loads of birds in there.
>> You do? You get loads of Irish Irish uh
Irish women, bro. Yeah. I've had two one
night stands there. Me.
One on my birthday and one the week before that.
>> Have you ever had a bird try and put a
finger up your ass?
>> Nah, bro. I have you ever like fingered
someone? I fingered people in their own
hills, bro. I swear I fingered in that
O'Neal. I swear to God.
>> Whereabouts was you?
>> You know the top top top floor. You know
where the like seats are? We like we sat
down kissing and that in it and I was
fingerling the [ __ ] out of her. Bro,
>> did she stink? I swear to God. >> Huh?
>> Did she stink? >> No.
>> Be honest. Don't lie. When you finger a
bird Yeah. when you as soon as you get a
chance when she ain't looking, do you
smell your finger? Be honest.
>> I I didn't, bro. I actually didn't.
>> Yes, you do. Everyone does, bro.
You're dirty, bro. I don't know what
you're trying to your finger in.
>> You just a tuna test in it before you bang her.
>> Have you done that though in clubs and that?
>> What? Sniff the [ __ ] tuna.
>> Not like fingering than that.
>> Uh, no. I I've never fed the bird in a club
>> like you know, you know.
>> How did you do that? You have got chucked out.
>> I did get chucked out.
>> Why? How did you get caught?
>> Because what what happened was Yeah. As
I was thinking, as I was fingering her,
bro, I swear to God, I'm not even making
this up. Yeah. As I was fingering her,
she kept like coming on to me. Yeah. And
like she was take she was pulling her
top up in it and like putting her tits
in my face. I I swear to God the bounces
the bouncers coming out.
>> And she kept doing it and she and I
said, "You can't do this here. Like
people are looking people are looking
and that in it." And then he he threw me
out of that. He said like, "You can't be
doing that." He just threw me out. I
said, "The [ __ ] was coming on to me." He
just threw me out.
>> [ __ ] hell. Was you going to
>> Yeah, it was on the top floor, bro. You
know the top floor where the seats are.
>> Yeah, I know exactly what you mean.
>> Yeah, I said she was I must have been
turning on with the fingering, bro. It
>> Well, so you was fingering her [ __ ] out
of her and then she kept pulling her top
up and that one in that
>> Yeah, after after a while after a while
she she kept coming on to like putting
herself on putting pulling her top up
and sticking her tick to my face and that bro.
>> [ __ ] hell. I bet you wanted to take
people I was like people was looking,
bro. People's looking, bro. I said
people it did the security just see you
or did somebody go and get him?
>> No, I think they just saw it to be fair.
>> It was bait, bro. Obviously it was bait is it?
>> What was you thinking about going and
bang her in the toilet in it?
>> Yeah. I was like, "Oh, let's like take
it somewhere else in it." And she's
like, "Oh, I can't leave my friend. I
can't leave my friend." I was like,
"What the [ __ ] Why you doing all this?"
You know what I mean?
>> Well, she's better fat.
>> No, she weren't fat at all. >> No.
>> No. I was I was suck I was sucking that
[ __ ] as well. Everyone was looking, bro.
It was a bad situation. It was mad. It was bad.
>> You sucking their tits as well. >> Yeah.
>> You're lucky you didn't get
>> And obviously people are sitting down.
People are sitting down, bro. And then
people like, it's obvious, isn't it? You
know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> But do you know, bro, do you know Yeah.
You know that O'Neals, there's always
fights and there's always people from
the army that go there. You've seen it,
bro. You must have seen it.
>> Yeah. You get soldiers in there, is it?
>> Yeah. I met a couple in it. Yeah. But
the thing is, bro, they had to stop
letting them in, in it, because they
used to always be fighting with the
Americans a lot, in it.
>> I've seen them in there in uniform.
>> But really?
>> Yeah. Honestly, in in all their army
uniform, I see them in there one time.
They weren't It was in the daytime. I
was in there having food to be fair.
>> Yeah, they Yeah, they ain't been coming
for a while.
>> Why do soldiers go there?
>> I don't know, bro. But I know I've met a
few in it. I've got him on Instagram and
that in it. I've been having a couple of
them. Yeah. Have you had the Have you
had the fish and chips in there?
>> No, I've had the burger and chips.
>> I ain't had I ain't had the burger.
What's that like? The fish and chips is well.
>> It's all right.
>> And it weren't even that dear either,
PJ. It weren't even that dear.
>> Was it nice? Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> No. What I used to do with when I used
to go there, I used to get like a the
burger with the cheese with the bacon
and the chips.
>> It was nice, bro. It was nice to be fair.
>> How much? But do you know the thing is a
lot of the a lot of the bartenders Yeah.
Um they they leave after a while. A lot
of the man they leave in it and change
and that in it.
>> Yeah. That Indian girl, she she works on
the ground floor behind the bar, isn't it?
>> Yeah, she there was one there. I can't
remember. There's there there's loads of
Indians and she was nice, bro. She was [ __ ] nice.
>> No, there was one of them. She was
proper nicel looking on the ground floor
behind the bar.
>> Probably the same one, bro. Probably the same one.
>> Do you reckon?
>> And there's there was a there was a
Welsh guy in it. He left. See, this is
what I mean. I know. I know. So I I know
them in it because the amount of times I
used to go there. >> Yeah.
>> Would you would you be a bartender there or? >> No.
>> One of the managers got banned because
he was drinking on the job.
>> Did he? >> Yeah.
>> What was he a pizzard?
>> I don't know. But he was just he was
just drinking when he you know it's
supposed to be good there. St. Patrick's
Day isn't it?
>> Yeah. It's the 17th of March, isn't it?
>> Yeah. I might I might go out saying
Patty's I don't know.
>> But um the thing what was I saying to you? Um
what I So when you went when you went
there, did you stay there till like 3:00
in the morning? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Until it closed, isn't it? Yeah.
>> That was on a Friday.
>> Yeah. Oh, nice, bro. Nice.
>> I've been there just in the week as well for food.
>> Yeah, it's nice.
That's only good O'Neals, isn't it?
There's no other good one.
It's a bit more quiet in the week just
during the day when you go for food.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Where's Where's another one?
>> There's one in King's Cross.
>> There's one in Lstone, but them ones are
[ __ ] They're just like local kind of
local ones, isn't it?
>> Have you been to them ones?
>> I've been to the one in Leighton Stone,
but not like at night and that just like
for food, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> And I've been to the Ilford one. It's
okay. I met like a couple of people from
Newcastle, but it's nothing like the the
the Chinatown one, obviously. Is it?
>> Yeah. Well, and you've seen bare
Americans in that Chinatown one.
>> Bare Americans, bro. Be If you used to
go on a Thursday, bro, it would just be
full of Americans, bro. Full of them.
>> I've not been there on a Thursday.
>> Yeah. Go on a Thursday, bro. You'll love
it. It's probably even busier than a
Saturday, but it's still It's like the
right kind of people. But Wednesdays is [ __ ] >> Yeah. Yeah, bro.
>> Did you ever kiss? Did you ever when you
met there four times? Did you ever kiss
anyone in it?
>> No, I didn't. No, I didn't to be fair. >> Yeah.
Be fair times in it.
>> What in there? Will you kiss be birds in >> Yeah. >> N
Are you B Are you barred from there now?
Cuz again when you got barred from
there, bro. Yeah. I'll never That's why
I said to the bouncer in it like when he
like I said when he was messaging me up
there saying where you been in it I said
oh yeah he said oh you can try and have
a word nah no chance because the thing
is with with that place bro yeah yeah
the management you know the actual
management and certain bounces they
never they never change so they will all
they know they know who I am
>> when was you there last [ __ ]
probably like a year ago bro you know
that video where Lord J put up with all
that cash And PJ's skin. Yeah. >> Mhm.
>> That's a lot of money. You got you got
to give him you got to give him that.
You got to give that to him. That is a
lot of dough to be fair.
>> Yeah, but I've shown more money than all
of them on here, bro.
>> Where did he get that dough that he put up?
>> Which dough? How much?
>> When he he put it on the bed and he
wrote out he wrote with the money PJ's skin.
>> I don't know, bro.
>> Have you seen that video?
>> I've seen so many videos of people doing so money.
I wonder just wonder where he got him
from. Is he got is Lord Jay? Is he rich?
>> Is he [ __ ] rich, bro?
>> I don't know about his
>> What's the most you've ever had in cash?
Not in your account, but like cash like
I mean actual cash like in front of you
>> that that like just under eight grand.
What? I said I won.
>> Oh, it was actually It was actually in
cash. Oh wow.
>> Yeah, I had it in cash. I got I had like
4,000 from Coral, but they could only
give me 2,700 and they said I could um
put the rest on a card. It takes a
couple of days. And I said, "No." Now I
went back and got the money next the
rest of it.
>> Yeah. I The most I've ever had in cash is 5.7.
>> Yeah. One in the rest on your bank.
>> Yeah. It was in 50s.
>> Yeah. I've seen
>> I bet you missed them days, is it, bro?
>> Yeah. I've seen them videos of you back then.
>> But it was good. It was good
experiences, isn't it?
>> That's when you used to go casino, is it?
>> Yeah. Pers Days, bro. Used to be the
days in them casinos. I used to win,
bro. Nine times out of 10 on a Thursday.
I don't know what it was.
>> What did you play in there? Roulette.
>> Always roulette, bro.
>> What? Live roulette?
>> Nah. No, no, no. On the machine. Well,
live. It was on the It was live on the
machine if that makes sense.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I know the one you mean. >> Um,
>> that thing. I hate that one though. It
just [ __ ] robs the [ __ ] out of you.
>> But they're dodgy, bro. Like they they
will do anything to like not pay you out
and [ __ ] in it.
>> Yeah, I know. when when you had that
madness there, you lost like 200 quid in it.
>> Yeah, I've had some mad times, bro. I
had some bad times there. But you know
the O'Neal staff, they're never going to
change in it. Nah.
>> Do you not reckon?
>> Nah. See, with Simmons with with other
places, yeah, staff always change, but
there they never seem to change.
>> PJ, how much when you went back to the
casino that time and then they wouldn't
let you have your money, how much was that?
>> Uh, a,000. And I got it in the end. I
put £30 in. I got it to a,000. But I had
to go through like hoops and that to get
it in it.
>> No, the one where you had like 200 quid
left there on in in the machine. They
wouldn't give it to you.
>> Oh, it was 500.
>> Yeah. Why did they chuck you out that time?
>> Because they said that I was banned in
that. So what they done, you know, this
is what I'm trying to say, bro. They can
actually void the ticket. >> Yeah.
>> So like say you say you put money in,
right? that you know like the money like
the credits in the machine they can
actually void that ticket.
>> Oh [ __ ]
>> so they so they actually voided it. You
get what I mean?
>> You gave the ticket to someone else
didn't you to go in and do it?
>> Yeah I gave it to this American guy.
Yeah. To see like if he could like do it
under his name but it was void and he
gave it it was it was void, bro. It was
[ __ ] He come it was void.
>> Did you Did you think that he patched it
and he was lying at first?
>> Nah no no no no, bro. They they know
what they're doing. They
>> through the machine, is it? Like cuz
they do it from a computer. It's
computer. When when you're playing
machines, you never not see someone on
the left on like a computer. >> Yeah.
>> You're that little person on a computer
and they just just voided a ticket.
>> And it was it weren't valid. It weren't
valid. When I tried, it weren't valid.
I've been in bookies before with my hood
up playing roulette and I've been
winning and then they've they've come
out to change like the dogs on the
newspaper and Sydney me and they've
turned the machine off but they've still
paid me out to be fair.
>> Yeah, they they're [ __ ] bro. They're
>> So, what are you going to do? Are you
just like going to quit gambling? >> Um,
no. Probably not.
>> At least you're honest. At least you're honest, bro.
>> No point of lying. Every time when I
lose a lot, I think that's it. That's
the last time and then I always do it
again. Horrible, horrible, horrible disease.
>> You just I just don't think you can just
win anymore. What What do you think the
best chance of winning, bro? Like, honestly,
>> no. Now, now you can't. It's I used to I
used to at least before I'd either win
big or lose quick when it was 1500. Now,
>> now it's just disgusting.
>> Don't get me wrong, bro. Don't get me
wrong. Like, there's been times where I
thought about like putting a nice chunk
of money online, like £500, and just
going for it and roulette. But we know
what happens, isn't it?
>> Yeah. I've seen your video on there and
you just lost it all.
>> You know what I'm saying, bro? Like,
well, if I if I put £500 on it now, what
do you think would happen? >> Um,
I can't say, but even if you won, this
is why there's no point of me even
gambling yet. Cuz even if I win, I would
just go back and lose it. And in the
end, I end up losing everything. There's
no point. But
>> Okay. Yeah. But here's the thing, bro. I
But do do you think if you won like a
big big amount, you could just stop?
Yeah. Like say Okay. Say you say you put
£500 on it now. Yeah. You won 30 40
grand. I would I think I would stop
until that money's finished.
>> Yeah. That that would be enough for me
to stop cuz that'd be a big chunk back
of what I've lost in my life.
>> And and then and you just do it again if
you ever if you do ever run out of
money. You get me? >> Yeah.
>> There was a there was I know a guy.
Yeah. Kind of like a friend. Yeah. He
won 17 grand from £140.
>> What? On line?
>> No. In Asperers Stratford.
>> Did he give it all back?
>> No. I think he he gave seven of it back.
But what I would have done, bro, this is
what I would have done personally. Yeah.
I would have put two grand on the
football bet and could protect the 15.
>> Yeah. Imagine if that football bet come
in. That's big money.
>> Just put two grand on the double both
teams to score. Done.
>> Is that like that's like [ __ ] seven
grand back anyways? You get me? >> Yeah.
>> And obviously kept the 15. But yeah, if
I won like 30 40 grand, I would I would
just stop until I run out of money. PJ,
that video. Oh, you ever seen him?
>> Not Not his face, but Yeah.
>> Why is he [ __ ] like Why has he got
such a problem with you?
>> Cuz they're obsessed, bro. They're weirdos.
>> Out of all the people on here. Yeah.
That like the ones who put videos about
you and that, who would you say is the
most like [ __ ] freak?
>> Red Star.
>> Red Star. Yeah.
>> And you would agree, I think, in it.
>> Red Star. Oh, he puts bare bare videos
about you in it.
>> He's gay in it, bro. You But but this is
what I understand. How they can sit online?
>> I've heard this. Yeah. Is he actually
gay or not?
>> He must be gay, bro. Think about it,
bro. Would you Would you sit on the
internet? Yeah. Stalking a man from the
time you wake up to the time you go to
bed. You wouldn't even stalk a woman
like that, would you?
>> Do you reckon? Yeah. When he sits up in
the morning in bed, do you reckon within
20 minutes he's checked your checked if you're streaming? >> 100%.
>> Mhm. You know he is, isn't it?
>> He's a proper They're obsessed, bro.
They're gay. They're jealous. They're
everything, can it?
>> You've been to You've been to Asperers
in Stratford, is it?
>> No, I've not been there. It's casino, is it?
>> Yeah. In the shopping center, bro. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I've not been there. You've been
in there. I
>> Yeah, years ago. But I I remember when I
went in uh not last time, and some
before that I went in Patty Power with
60. I won a grand, bro, on the roulette
in like 5 minutes. Was that ball back on
the old roulette?
>> No, the the ball roulette. I hit 17
twice with max on it.
>> Yeah, I've had4 9500 to one loads of times.
>> [ __ ] hell. Oh, that global that
global draws the worst, isn't it?
>> Yeah, it's a comeback, isn't it?
>> It always goes on 10 to one, is it? It's so fixed.
>> Yeah, 10 to one every time. And as you
know, it's hard. It I've even done, you
know, like when you you can put 30 worth
of chips down. M
>> even even like [ __ ] when I do a [ __ ] bet
like six quid it still always lands in
the red but you know how hard it is to
get a spin when you're doing max like 30
a go like when I do zero section and
then it [ __ ] is 10 to one or even 20
to one [ __ ]
>> and it always does it right next to the
100 to one as well.
>> It's [ __ ] bro.
>> Have you noticed the roulette spin now
is like half the size of what the old
one used to be?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I know exactly what you
Yeah. Yeah. But as soon as they put that
bar in Yeah, bro. But bro, that [ __ ]
that 20 that that 100 pound spin
roulette used to be I don't know how
they allowed that bro for so long.
>> Years ago, you know, years and years and
years and years I'm talking years ago. I
don't think there was a cap on it. Was there?
>> What? On the roulette?
>> Yeah. No, I I don't think there was even
a£100 cap. Like I'm talking years ago.
>> Yeah. I don't know about then. I've only
ever known it to be 100 pound.
>> Yeah. I think years and years ago, bro,
I think it was anything. I'm I I'm not
sure, but I think so. People was talking about it.
>> I don't ever I don't ever play slots.
Too slow, too boring. I just play roulette.
>> Yeah, I used to play that fishing
frenzy, but 99% of the time it's just roulette.
>> I can't play that fishing frenzy cuz it
just when I get the game and the
fisherman don't show up, it just makes
me want to [ __ ] kill it, bro. I I
punch them, bro. The worstest, bro. When
you used to get a two pound bonus. When
you used to get a two pound bonus and it
paid you two pound, I banged the machine
once, bro. I swear. Oh, I've done that
loads of times and chucked out and doing it.
>> Yeah. What you saying, bro? Sorry.
>> That um I one time I won a load of money
on the roulette and started playing
slots cuz I thought I didn't want to
lose it on the roulette and then I was
on that years ago. This was I was on
that fishing frenzy. Yeah. And oh mate,
one one of the games or bonus games I
got cost about 350 quid and it paid [ __ ]
all fishermanmen just didn't show up. >> Yeah.
>> Biggest win I've had off of that is 360. Mad.
>> I've had zero that eye of Horus. I've
never won anything on that ever.
>> Have you ever felt like doing yourself
in over gambling?
>> Yeah, of course I have. It's [ __ ] brutal.
>> It's mad, isn't it?
>> Yeah. It's [ __ ] horrible.
>> You know Timmy? Yeah. He lost all his
money. Yeah. One month he had to live on
off bread and water.
>> That's funny, isn't it? Well, he was
actually just eating bread and tap water.
>> Yeah, cuz he lost all his money in it.
>> Are you messing about or do you know
that for a fact?
>> No, I mean No, seriously.
>> What? What? He had bread every day.
>> Yeah, he had no money. He done his
sacking in it.
>> Well, didn't he have nothing in the
freezer and I think
>> How do you know he was just eating bread?
>> Bro, like he cuz he said it. He told him.
>> Oh, what? He actually said it. M
Well, you said I've got I've got
survival on tap water and bread till I
get paid. [ __ ] hell.
>> Yeah, but I'm sure you've had [ __ ] like
that in it. Or not as bad in maybe it
not as bad as that.
>> The years ago, like six, seven years
ago, if I lost all my money, I I
wouldn't have money to eat really. I
>> um but I think Timmy will literally
gamble everything and he'll sell every
he'll sell everything. He'll do anything.
Who who who do you reckon the worst
gambler is on here? >> Um
I don't know. I don't really know that
many on here. Probably Timmy. I know a
few that are on here.
>> And who's the second?
>> See Mark was just a [ __ ] when he
played with it.
>> Done really done really stupid crap pointless bits.
>> Yeah, bro. 100%.
>> Timmy's I think Timmy must be when you
talk about gambling it makes you want to
do it, isn't it? Yeah, I think Timmy's I
think Timmy must be a skint now because
years ago he used to do good videos 50
and 50 and 100 pound spins, but now he
does like [ __ ] crap videos and no
sound of like 20p steak. I just can't
even watch them. They're so boring. >> Yeah.
>> So, you know, you know when you turned
that 4 something to 850 the other day?
>> Yeah. I had 490.
>> That was just that was just money. That
was just money you got paid, is it? I'm guessing
>> I had uh 490 and I left with 850. I had
um I had
>> you know that when you took that when
you took that 490 out Yeah. Did you have
any money left?
>> Uh yeah.
>> Or like a lot or no?
>> No. I can't remember. It was a couple of
hundred quid. Not a lot. >> Yeah.
>> Once I' once had um once had lost next
day or whenever it was. I think I had
likeund I save like 100 just to eat and
[ __ ] 850. [ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah, that was Bet Fred. How was a [ __ ]
>> I think the most I've ever lost the most
I've ever lost online is two grand in an
hour. And the most I've ever lost in
real life is
I think 600. >> Yeah.
>> In a casino. But I don't think it's ever
been more than that. Nah.
>> Well, you've never gambled all your money?
>> Not for like seven, eight years, bro.
>> You must have one time. No, seriously, bro.
I've lost a lot of money now, but I've
always had money. So, like, no, I have
one time. Yeah. Years ago. I have years
>> You must have gone and lost a grand in
the bookies before. Everyone has your gamles.
>> No, not in the bookies. >> Never.
>> Maybe not.
>> Never, bro. But my my sister my sister's
boyfriend did before. Yeah. He was on
his lunch break, isn't it? Like from
work and he lost the grand in it.
>> Yeah. That's how I get job. And then um
he had to borrow money in it to get
>> [ __ ] hell.
>> Is that funny?
>> Are you going gambling tomorrow?
>> Nah, bro. But you're making me want to
[ __ ] do it now, bro. Talking about
it, is it?
>> [ __ ] that. Don't gamble. It's not worth it. It's
>> [ __ ] is it?
>> Yeah. It just makes you feel like [ __ ]
>> But you know the maddest thing is Yeah.
It's It's a shame the feeling don't stay
with you. Like say like you get really
depressed and that. Yeah. But then when
you have money again or you walk up,
you're like, "Oh, it's a good idea, isn't it?"
>> But then the cycle continues. You get
me? And you lose.
>> You're making me laugh, man. Cuz I'm
exactly the same.
>> Cuz it's weird because you don't It
should stay with you, but it doesn't,
bro. It doesn't.
>> Someone said someone said yesterday that
you sold your phone, your other phone,
your expensive one to go gambling. Apparently,
>> never happened on here.
The gaz who said it had a p his profile
picture was like a packet of ready sorted crisps.
>> Yeah, he's an idiot.
>> I don't know who he is. He said that you
sold your other phone and pretended the
police have got it. Nah,
>> bro. Um, what was I saying? [ __ ] um,
so like Oh, for you you've smashed
bookies up and that is it?
>> U punching machines for that.
>> What did that make you laugh earlier? I
said I wanted to do the Coke can cuz
it's a good idea, ain't it?
>> Yeah. No, that video you done that time
with the boogie was funny.
>> Well, I've actually done like the the um
the the windowing before. Well, like you
know the glass.
>> Did you get arrested for it?
>> No, I literally it was you know like
years ago. Yeah. You remember the old 50 not? >> Yeah.
>> I had like 50. Obviously, I didn't have
a lot money back then. I had less money
than than I do now. I lost 50 pound,
bro. And I had You know what I mean? I
used to do weightlifting and that in it.
So I went back with like a dumbbell bar,
bro, and I just banged it, bro. And it
and it just cracked. It didn't go
through it, but it cracked it. And you
know what's so mad is, bro, like I've
been in I've been in that betting shop
like since, but not straight after. And
I never got nicked.
>> I thrown stuff. I've never been nicked for it.
>> Well, you went all the way home and got
a dumbbell and went all the way back
there and smashed the window.
>> Just st it in. Yeah. Just like bam. And
it just cracked.
>> [ __ ] hell. Well, you never got nicked for that?
>> Nah, I've never been nic I've never been
nicked for criminal damage, funny enough.
>> Did you pick up a lot of it? I just just
never been caught. Have you?
>> I've been into criminal damage. Yeah.
Did you pick up the dumbbell and take it back home?
>> I think I I think I No, I think I
probably down a not a drain or probably
tucked in a bin or something.
>> Yeah, you picked it up after you smashed the thing.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Did the staff come out?
>> No. No, but imagine that though, bro.
Just imagine imagine that. Yeah. Imagine
that. Yeah. Like
listen, bro. People in the betting shop.
Yeah. Like betting on like the window.
>> You reckon they heard it?
>> Yeah, of course they did.
>> But you know, Money Mike Buddy Mike told
me a mad funny story before. Um >> what?
>> He said that he was in a bookies. Yeah.
>> Um Yeah.
Uh and and some guy he lost uh 60 pound
in it, bro. I think it was 60.
He came back he came back with a load of
paint in it and he started chucking it
all over the shop. Like white paint. I
swear to God, bro. Wait, PJ, have you
seen the video on YouTube of the the
geyser in the bookies and there's he
starts smashing all the machines up and
he he pushing there's there's a geyser
playing I have Horus and he pushes the
machine over and then he picks the
machine up and carries on playing if you
seen that one.
>> Uh is that the one where the woman's
like shouting like behind the thing and
>> Yeah. Please help me. Come quick. Please
>> Yeah. And he's given a location. Have
you seen the one where the guy Have you
seen the guy with the one where the guy
puts his fist through it?
>> Uh yeah. He goes he laughs goes to hits
it then he stops and he goes bang.
>> Yeah. Yeah. He like Yeah. Yeah. He like
>> He looks like he looks like a Turkish gzer. >> Yeah.
>> Have you seen the fat scaler? The woman back.
>> Yeah. That's old, bro. Yeah. That's so
>> Have you seen
>> Did you get Did you get Did you get
nicked like for criminal damage you done
to the Brookies?
>> No, I didn't. I don't even know if I
broke anything. I just threw the chair
uh through all the pens and just pushed
the machine and it fell to the side.
>> I've had it before where you where
they've called the the like I think
they've called the police like the alarm
starts going. That's them calling the
police, isn't it?
>> [ __ ] It's probably the machine with the
with the alarm going
>> sp I have spat on it in that though. I
have spat it.
>> I've done that. Um PJ, have you seen the
video of the Muslim gezer playing the
machine and he's going, "Fuck you. [ __ ] Chris."
>> Yeah, bro. It's that's old as well.
Yeah, I've seen all of them, bro.
>> What happened? He It's like he's having
an anxiety attack, isn't it?
>> Yeah. What about the Indian ger who's
standing there going put shout talking
[ __ ] in his language?
>> Yeah. And I've seen the one where he's
like, "Fuck you, Jesus." And that is it.
>> Yeah. [ __ ] you. [ __ ] Christmas. [ __ ] Jesus.
Yeah, there's been so many of them, bro.
But there's there's there's one where
have you seen the one where he's
smashing stuff up and the woman's like,
"What are you doing?"
>> Yeah, I think I have. I've seen one
where he smashes all the screens and
there's water balloons.
>> So, what will happen like say you go in
now? Yeah. And you just do all of the
machines and you'll get nicked in it.
>> Yeah. Criminal damage.
>> Yeah. But would they is it 100% they'll find you?
>> Um, yeah. Yeah, if you went and smashed
them with machines, then yeah, they'd
probably even find you.
>> But if it's one, maybe not in it.
>> Um, yeah, you got more chance of getting
away with one, I suppose.
>> Yeah, cuz I heard the guy that gone all
I heard he went prison.
>> I just some of some of the women in the
bookies with the staff is [ __ ] so
[ __ ] fat, horrible [ __ ]
Yeah, but I heard I did hear
in London Bridge. Patty Power. Oh, she's
an horrible country.
>> Which one?
>> London Bridge. Patty Power. Big fat
woman. Do you know what I mean? Big
massive fat [ __ ]
>> No, I've never been to a Patty Power in London Bridge.
>> Oh, she's a horrible [ __ ]
>> Well, you used to go there a lot. Yeah.
>> Oh, I've been there a few times.
>> Have you been to that? Have you been to
the Bford in Chinatown next to Hills? I
used to go all the time, bro. Yeah.
>> It's like little I've been Is that the
one with like a little weird basement? >> Yeah. >> Yeah,
>> bro. You go there, you gamble, then you
go to the O'Neals. Is it?
>> I won. Yeah, I won in that one to be fair.
>> Yeah, I met some guy there before, in
it. Yeah. And uh literally we was
gambling a little bit and then we just
went to the O'Neals after. I had a pint.
>> What? That the one you're on about? It's
a few doors down and it's like a little weird basement.
>> It's literally next Yeah, it's literally
next door to It's next door to it.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I've been in there. Well,
you was with this guy. Was he gay?
>> No, no, no, no. I met him in there in
it. We was gambling in it and then we
just started talking as you do and then
we just went for a pint in it. Let's start.
>> Was he gay or was he straight?
>> No, he was straight, bro. He's got a
misses, isn't it?
>> Was he weirdo or was he all right?
>> No, he was all right, but he's a proper
proper proper addict, bro.
>> What? A sniffhead or gambling?
>> No, a gambling addict, bro. >> Yeah,
>> he was from Chester. You know Chester? Yeah.
Did you win or lose?
>> Uh, probably lost. >> Yeah,
>> I would have remembered if I won. You
know what I mean? You you kind of
remember when you win. You know what I'm saying?
>> The sign outside says bet Fred and has
in Chinese writing as well.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. China sounds good, bro. It
>> Yeah. I always lose money there though.
>> Yeah. [ __ ] in it. And there's, you know,
opposite O'Neal, there's like a little
arcade in it.
>> Yeah, that's the one I lost in.
>> Yeah, I lost the [ __ ] um I lost
fishing frenzy, bro. I lost some fishing frenzy there.
>> You know that one on the corner, you
know, stop and step done a video in
there, is it?
>> Yeah, I think I see that. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> What do you think of that stop and step?
I think he's a [ __ ] bullshitter.
>> I was just going to say to you, do you
reckon he's full of [ __ ] Because
>> he's got to be. How is someone always
winning like that, bro?
>> Yeah. How is he always He always always
gets out the [ __ ] every time.
>> Yeah, he's a bullshitter, bro. He's gone
to Blackpool, isn't it?
>> Yeah, he's been Blackpool. He's been all
over. I've been following him for years.
Where the [ __ ] does all the money come from?
>> Yeah, exactly. Exactly.
>> Like, do you do you remember Hyperlinks?
He's finally run out of money.
>> I was watching I was watching him. He's
actually all right, bro. I like him. I
was watching him the other day.
>> Yeah, he's out of money now, isn't he?
>> Is he? >> Yeah.
How do you know?
>> Cuz he said
>> on a video. So he's he's skinned. >> Yeah.
>> But to be fair, he's stupid. Do you know
why he's stupid, bro? Cuz he had money.
He could have invested like all that
money you wasted gambling to be fair.
Yeah. He could have done so much with it, bro.
>> Do you know Rock and Roller?
>> Yeah, he does. He He streams on kick
now, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Do you reckon they're fake them?
>> He's fake, bro. He's fake, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Yeah, he's definitely fake.
>> He's definitely definitely definitely [ __ ] fake.
>> The only one I don't think the only one
because look at it. How are they hitting
all the You You try to do what they do.
You try to replicate what they do, bro.
Yeah. You won't hit no numbers. You
>> It's never ever ever happening. No way.
>> But do you reckon Hyperlinks uses fake
money? I don't think so.
>> No, I think he was real to be fair.
>> Um, who was it? What about like have you
have you seen have you seen that secular slots?
>> No, I haven't. I've seen Bandit.
>> Yeah, he's fake in it.
>> Yeah, Bandit's fake definitely.
>> He's from and that Jimbo Casino and that
>> What's your opinion on OAB Gambling?
>> I haven't really watched his stuff. I
know who he is.
>> Yeah, I don't reckon he's f You know,
stop and step. Yeah.
>> Oh, I like You know who I like, bro? I I
like Seven Neighbors. He's He is a He's
a mad [ __ ] though. Yeah. Are they real?
Are they massive spins? Are they
actually real in the casino?
>> Who's seven neighbors?
>> I think so, bro. Yeah, cuz he shows
money in it.
>> Have you noticed the last probably five
or six stop and step videos? Yeah. He's
been in like He never goes bookies. He
was in the arcade. He always gets about
800 in. He always manages to get a jack.
Like he just does stuff that never happens.
>> Yeah. He's full of [ __ ] bro.
>> He must Oh, I don't know. Maybe it is
real. What's your opinion? He just
>> I think he just shows he probably just
shows just the wins it.
>> He does show losing videos sometimes,
but [ __ ] I don't know.
>> He's fake. Definitely.
>> Do you like Seven Neighbors?
>> Seven Neighbors is all right.
>> Yeah, he's all right. Is he? Yeah, he's
he lives in South Ending him. He doesn't
live too far.
>> If you go there approach him.
>> Yeah, I've been I been to South End in
years, but I used to go all the time as
a kid. that you've been there, isn't it?
>> Yeah, of course. Adventure Island.
>> There's a Grove on the corner. There's a
Grovener on the corner there.
>> I don't know. You know? >> Yeah.
Have you ever been in that adventure island there? >> No.
>> Blackpool, bro. There. It's supposed to
be good there, but it's
uh roller streams once every f he's not
fake. Do you think casinos want people want someone?
>> No, I still don't believe that rock and
roller uses real money, bro. I don't I
don't believe it.
>> The rock and roller his YouTube short
video, all of them for years. Rock and
roll is fake. >> Yeah.
>> And if it's not fake, then he's just a
[ __ ] degenerate gambler. But I'm just
not having it. I've seen him do like 20,000. The
>> only the only one that I think is real
is Hyperlinks and Seven Labs. That Seven
Labors is minted, bro. Is he?
>> Yeah. I don't know how he gets his
money, but he's got a lot of money, bro.
>> He won 80 grand, didn't he? A while ago,
>> did he? Yeah. He's lost a lot, though,
as well. Yeah.
>> I've seen him lose about 10 grand.
>> But you know what I don't understand,
bro? Yeah. Is if you've got all of this
money, bro. Like, hear me out. Yeah.
Surely you wouldn't be getting as much
as a gambling buzz. Cuz think of it,
bro. We We're not rich like me and you
and other people that gamble in it.
Like, so that's not all excitement is
winning, is it?
money. Only if you've got so much money.
Yeah. If you've got like you know Wayne,
you know Wayne Rooney. Yeah. He used to
gamble all the time, bro. Like [ __ ] Manchester casinos.
>> Literally, I couldn't agree more with
you. Yeah. I'm exactly the same. If I
had 20, 30 grand, I wouldn't even
gamble. The point of gambling is to win
money. When you've got low, what's the point?
>> Yeah. Exactly, bro. Exactly. Exactly.
>> Look how Look how much Drake loses.
What's the [ __ ] point?
>> Yeah. You know, like Wayne Rooney, he's
a sniffhead. He always used to go to the
Manchester casinos, bro. I always used
to see it. Always.
>> Well, you've seen ruin it.
>> No, like I've I've read about it in that
in it. Like
>> he loves um he loves he loves sniffing
gear and [ __ ] bra.
>> Yeah. And casinos and that. But it
doesn't make sense cuz if you got all
that money like there's no buzz to
winning more. Yeah. You get like you
know what I'm saying?
>> Yeah. What's the point?
>> Doesn't make sense, is it? Like when
I've seen that rock and roller with
likeund one time I seen about 130,000 it
said euro not pound it said euro in his
account and he still carried on playing
and lost like 40 grand of it and I think
what the [ __ ] if I had that I wouldn't
even gamble and I need to gamble.
>> I wonder how much that hyperlinks has
lost in the past four years. He has
wasted so much money bro 18 grand in Vegas but
>> he lost all that. But do you remember
when like a few years ago, bro, he used
to [ __ ] um he used to he used to
stream you remember when he you know
when he used to do like streams all the
time on YouTube?
>> Yeah, I used to like them streams. He
used to have social ones. He used to
have people around. One night they was
all drinking and sniffing.
>> Yeah. T Do you remember when Timmy went there?
>> Yeah. He stole Apparently stole money.
>> So like he used to waste so much money
on them streams. But I used to I used to
I used to like the Yeah.
>> Yeah. I used to like his streams. That's
like 2018. I used to watch him.
>> You remember Fruity Slots?
>> Yeah. Well, that's fake, isn't it?
>> Yeah, definitely. Million%.
>> Have you ever heard Have you ever heard
that apparently when uh Timmy was with
Hyperlinks, he [ __ ] stole coins?
>> Yeah, I heard that. That's been going
ages, bro. That rumor. Yeah.
>> Do you reckon Do you reckon Timmy would
steal a handful of pound coins?
>> Probably, bro.
>> Do you reckon he would? Yeah.
You think he would?
>> Um, yeah. For gambling. Yeah. That's the
place. That's the place he takes people to.
>> Yeah. I'm trying to think of any other streamers. Um
>> Jimbo. Yeah. He was a C. I didn't like that Jimbo.
>> Jimbo Slots.
>> Yeah. That Craig that Craig Slots. He
was from um Colchester. I didn't like him either.
>> I thought he streams are boring. You
reckon he uses real money?
>> I don't know. His streams was a bit boring.
>> Yeah. You know him though, ain't it?
They They all met up. Like there's
there's a lot of streamers that have all
met up and that is it.
>> Yeah. I've been watching
>> remember what's his name? Um Oh, you
know, let's give it a spin in it. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. He was from [ __ ] Sweden or some
[ __ ] is it?
>> I'm not sure. I've never really watched.
>> You know who I'm talking about though, is it? >> Yeah.
What's your opinion then on that bandit?
Do you reckon them all them all the
videos are real or fake? >> Fake.
>> They got to be, aren't they?
>> They got to be fake, bro. They've got to
be fake. He used to do like He used to
do like Ala Long like slot ones. Yeah.
>> I know. [ __ ] some of them crazy.
>> Do you remember that video Rockola done
about compulsive gambling like years
ago, but he deleted it in it?
>> No, I didn't see that.
>> Oh, he was talking about compulsive
gambling. He said that he's been in a
dark place cuz of it. Is it?
>> Is that what he said?
>> Yeah. He said it could really [ __ ] up
your life and that is it.
>> Well, then he deleted it after.
>> Yeah. After a while. After a while.
Yeah. And Yeah. You made a new channel.
It's like I used to watch Rock and
Roller, but then it's just like He used
to have like really good roulette videos
like And now there's nothing It's
nothing compared to what it was, isn't
it? Do you remember Do you remember when
you watch Did you watch his big Do you
remember Did you watch that big loss of
his before when he said keep going
[ __ ] keep going on the roulette? >> Yeah,
>> he was going mad at it. He said 3
[ __ ] four again.
>> Yeah, I've seen them all.
>> But then there's not much anymore in it.
Yeah, he made he got money from
inheritance. I think that hyperlinks in it.
>> Did he?
>> Yeah. He sounds quite posh and bit a bit
gay as well.
>> Yeah, he's from um he's from Norwich, isn't it?
>> I used to watch his fridge tour videos.
He used to have some decent [ __ ] to be fair.
>> Yeah, he was all right, bro. Yeah, he
was he was actually one of the only ones
I could stand to be fair.
>> The last video he said um Yeah,
basically he's out of dough. So,
>> how's he going to make more? He's not in it.
>> Yeah, he can't. He's [ __ ] in it.
Yeah, Rolet is the only one who plays
roulette. No, Hyperlinks plays roulette.
Seven Neighbors plays roulette.
>> They all play roulette. Who said Who said that?
>> Not all of them. Not all of them. But yeah,
>> who said that? This fake Tim Aldrid.
>> Yeah. No, Rock and Roller does. Um, Hyperlinks does.
Seven Neighbors does. I don't stop and
step don't really, does he?
>> No, not really. He just does.
>> Not really. >> Yeah.
>> His name's Darren. His name's Darren. Is it?
>> Yeah. He lives in um He said he lives in
Cormal, isn't it?
>> I thought he lives in Deon is it?
>> Does he?
>> He doesn't sound like he does though. >> Yeah.
>> He's He's got to be a millionaire. >> Yeah.
>> To be gambling that long every day, all the time.
>> I mean, the real ones I mean the real
ones only play roulette. Yeah. Yeah.
What did you say, bro?
>> I said stop and step. He must have a lot
of money, a million plus, because he's
been gambling for [ __ ] all them
years. Every day
>> you stop and step. Yeah.
>> Yeah. And he just always seems to [ __ ] win.
>> And that seven neighbors, I wouldn't be
surprised if he's a million. Yeah.
>> Why has he got bear though?
>> He's got bare money, bro. He gamble a
lot if you watch his videos. Yeah.
>> He'll go skint one day in it.
>> Yeah, of course.
>> I heard
owns a bakers. What?
>> He's quite old, isn't he? That seven
neighbors, isn't it? He's quite He's
quite old. Seven neighbors, isn't it?
>> I don't know. How old you say he is?
He's over 40.
>> Yeah, over 40. Yeah.
>> He loves I I always hate that. I don't
like that number seven, but I used I
used to hate it on that.
>> What? Seven neighbors.
>> I just hate it. Yeah. And I just hate
the number. I like eight and 11.
I normally go zero section or opposite tier.
>> Yeah. Seven neighbors.
>> Seven neighbors. What's that? 28 7 12 18
22. But [ __ ] Horrible numbers.
>> He just goes to V. He just [ __ ] off to
Vegas whenever he likes it.
>> I do like 8 or 11. And when you know
>> I like I like 5 8211 1720.
Is that what numbers you do? >> Yeah. >> Two.
>> What's your biggest What's your biggest
loss with What's your biggest loss? I
lost FK one time. Uh two grand online.
>> Mine's 5,000.
>> Mine's Do you know what though? When I
lost that two grand online. Yeah. I kind
of just felt like I was kind of in shock
more than raging. I'm sure you've had
this before. Yeah. There's been times I
I I think where you've lost and it
hasn't bothered you as much. Like might
maybe one in like five times it can
happen, isn't it?
>> When you lose so much and it's been
taking you up and down, up and down for
hours in the end, you're just laughing.
>> Yeah, I think that's what it is, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. I lost two grand online,
bro. And it was so blatantly rigged
because it'd get me to like a certain
point and then that's what it does in
the book is you know the bar roulette.
Yeah. It will give you 20 pound. Yeah.
And then he'll take the 20 to get the next spin.
>> That's what it does to keep you going.
Put more money in.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yep. Exactly.
>> That's how you get addicted. You see
that's how they tried it.
>> So many times on my last two pound
they'll get a spin and a drop next door
and you think is that coincidence?
>> Yeah. I had it today bro. Obviously my
my when I play I was doing second dozen
so my jackpot numbers was 17 and 20 bro
it went 25 two times in a row bro
>> which is next after 17
>> yeah 225 17 it
>> yeah that was the big and that was the
biggest number and it's so fixed bro
>> yeah just they're meant to be roulette
meant to be 100% random no [ __ ] way >> it's
percentage based every couple of grand
it takes probably gives a jackpot
You know, have have you played it in the
pub? The roulette?
>> Yeah. [ __ ]
>> There's There's one there's a bar
roulette, but it only pays 100. And then
there's one with wheels.
>> Yeah, they're all crap. I hate them.
>> They're [ __ ] isn't it?
>> Yeah. You can't win the [ __ ] away with
them. They're absolute [ __ ]
>> They are [ __ ] bro. To be fair. So, um, yeah.
Are you doing anything for your birthday this year?
>> Uh, got nothing planned as yet. What's
happening with you in Thailand?
>> I'm still going to go in it.
>> Yeah. When are you planning on going?
Are you going to [ __ ] Are you going to
[ __ ] their glasses there?
>> Yeah, of course, bro. My friend lives
there. I know people that live there
now. They just people live there.
>> Someone Someone I know went there. I've
never been there. Someone I know went
there and he had two Thai birds. He had
him all week like for seven days
massaging him, cooking for him, sucking
his dick, whatever he wanted. And when
he paid was paying him like he worked
out what he g him in total, it worked
out the equivalent of like 300 quid in
our money which is like [ __ ] all. >> Lovely.
>> Could you love it?
>> Would you like two ters looking after
you all week?
>> Yeah, why not?
>> Would you treat him like [ __ ]
>> Would you?
>> Yeah, I would. Would you? Would you be
really horrible to them? >> No.
>> No. Another day I
>> You've had a lot of one night stands.
You have, bro.
>> I've had a few.
>> Yeah, I've had about five, six.
>> Five or six? >> Yeah.
>> I don't think you should move to
Thailand. I think you should just go
there for like a week.
>> I don't think I would move there. My
friend did, but I
>> You were saying before you was going to move there.
>> Oh, no. I don't think I would, bro. May
maybe a month. Maybe Maybe I'd spend
like a month there. Yeah,
>> but I don't know. Would you Would you go to Australia?
>> The flight's too long, is it? Same as
it, bro. That's long, is it? Yeah.
>> I don't like flying either.
>> Does it scare you?
>> Uh, yeah, it does to be fair.
>> Well, like the whole time.
>> It's just horrible. I hate it.
>> Or do you just think it's like going to
So, how did you do Cypress then? That's
like 4 hours, isn't it?
>> Yeah, about 4 and a half hours. Um, I
just took some daipan before I left. >> Yeah,
>> I was trying to fly home.
>> Yeah, but it's it's coming back as well
cuz you also need to come back, isn't it?
>> Yeah. On like the last two days, I just
kept thinking about a flight home. I
just hate flying.
>> Yeah, my friend was like my friend my
friend my friend my friend that lives in
Thailand. Yeah. He went Spain years and
years ago and he said he'd never fly
again. He hates it. He fears it. He He
swore he'd never fly again. And now this
is his third time in Thailand. He said
because this country is so [ __ ] he'd
rather risk dying on a plane than like
staying here in it.
>> Yeah. Has he got on has he got a bird there?
>> Or is he is he single?
>> No, he he Well, he gets with like
multiple birds in it because it's so
easy there. You just jump on Tinder,
they come to you, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Does he pay them?
>> Sometimes yes, sometimes no.
>> They're cheap, isn't it? >> Yeah.
Sometimes. Yeah, sometimes. He hasn't
>> I want to go Japan.
>> Why? [ __ ] that. That's Mo.
>> It just looks like a sick like a sick
place. You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. Would you try and [ __ ] Chinese
girls? Japanese girls.
>> Yeah, of course, bro. But do you know
what? I've never I've never approached
any, you know, cuz I've never really
found them attractive. Have you?
>> No, they're not my not my cup of tea.
They're always hairy as well. Well, you
wouldn't say no to one if they offered
you, of course. Is it? >> No.
No, I wouldn't. Well, you really want
you Was you trolling me yet when you
said that? Like you actually approached
some birds and they told you they had a boyfriend?
>> No, I was being serious. Just me pissed off.
>> But what was it? In the bars and clubs
or was it sometimes on the street?
>> Normally just in the smoking area
in the street. They just said had a boyfriend.
>> Yeah, sorry. I got a boyfriend. What did you say?
>> Uh can't remember. Just laugh probably.
>> Yeah, they're full of [ __ ] in it.
>> Yeah, they say that even when they ain't got boyfriend.
>> Yeah, I would say like three times out I
I would say like three three times out
like three out of 10 do
what? Say that [ __ ]
>> I'd say no. I'd say three out of 10
actually do have a boyfriend and don't.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I agree. I
reckon because there's a lot of sing
there is still a lot of single people.
There's still a lot of single people out
there. You know what I'm saying, bro?
>> Have you ever like have you ever
approached like homeless women or like
crackhead crackhead women?
>> Nah. Ever?
>> Yes, you have. I know you have.
>> No, bro. Have you?
>> Like not not for another like you
understand like some homeless crackhead
woman just said to her like, "Oh, will
you suck me off? I'll give you a score."
>> I think I did in Manchester once.
I think I was down bad, but I was like,
I I tried the whole night, didn't get
nothing. But I think I did in Manchester
once and she said no.
>> She crackhead.
>> She was homeless. You weren't a
crackhead. She was homeless.
>> Was she disgusting? >> No.
>> She's been away for a blow in it.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Yeah.
>> Well, I've done it in real life. Yeah.
You saw the videos. I was offering like
normal people money for [ __ ] bro.
Like So, they said no. I thought that
was going to work, bro.
>> One of my one of the funniest videos
I've see of you is you go up to like
some posh [ __ ] woman who like
obviously works in like a London office.
You know the one I'm on about in it.
>> Yeah, bro. Don't
>> [ __ ] But you don't understand. You
know that same day I carried it on like
I done it even when I was drinking. I
thought it would have worked me. I I
generally thought it was going to work.
>> Would you would you have actually paid the money?
>> Yeah, I had the money on me, bro.
>> That that you know what it was. You know
what it was, bro? I tell you what it
was. Yeah. I was just trying things that
might have worked. You know what I'm
saying? Like to get out like the
situation. Like, do you get what I'm
saying, bro? Like just trying different things. >> Yeah.
>> I thought that would have worked. You
What if you thought that would have worked?
>> How much was you offering them?
>> Like free bills.
>> Yeah. Yeah. That
>> which is still a lot of money. It's
still a lot of money to to most
considering like like a lot of people
don't have money. You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. To be fair, I thought that would have worked.
I thought that definitely would have
worked, bro. And then I've done it in
like the bars and clubs as well.
>> Yo, PJ, who's that woman? Yeah. She's
like, she's a bit fat and she looks
foreign and you're like going mad at her
and filming her. You're in like looks
like you're in a park. It's grass and
that and you bought her.
>> Oh, yeah. I remember, bro. Yeah.
>> What the [ __ ] was that about?
>> Oh, being a [ __ ] in it.
>> Why was you so pissed off?
>> Oh, she was just being a [ __ ] in it.
>> Yeah. What did she do?
>> That's a long story, is it? Yeah, please tell me.
>> No seen that video.
>> I was just offering her money and that is it.
>> What? For sex,
>> something like that. Yeah.
>> But she was But it wasn't that. No, but
it wasn't that though. Do you know what
it was yet? It was a case of like, you
know, like when she went back, she
weren't going to answer my text and that
like, you know, she was a time waster as
well. It wasn't just that. It was like,
you know what I'm saying?
>> She was she was playing games as well.
One minute she was talking like fluent
English, next minute she was acting all
scared and that. Yeah, that's what I'm
saying. Yeah, it wasn't just that. Cuz
if someone says no, they say no. Is it?
>> Yeah. She was being like a head [ __ ] and
you said to her in it, you don't want
the wine. You can keep the wine in it. >> Yeah.
>> You like that?
>> Yeah. That's jokes.
>> There used to be this account that come
on and used to say, "Eat a belly, you
need to go out today. Don't let them
cing women win."
Like some account used to come in and
mock me in that, bro. I don't know what
happened to it.
When I woke up the other morning, you
were streaming. Yeah. So, I put you on
and I was in the bathroom brushing my
teeth and I could hear you in the front room. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> It makes me laugh. You was ranting about
somebody. It's the way you're [ __ ]
good at it. It's the when you get when
you get on one, I'll tell you roughly
what you said. You said, "This is what I
could hear from the bathroom." I was
pissing myself laughing. I sprayed
toothpaste everywhere. [ __ ] sake. You
was going disgusting. Fat middle-aged
tiny dick gay stinky disgusting girl. He
was going on about this abuse about
someone. It's [ __ ] making me laugh.
>> Yeah, bro. >> Who?
>> I don't know who you was on about. Who
would that have been about?
>> Probably one of these people from a channel.
>> You said fat, gay, disgusting, middle-aged. Um,
>> do you know what I don't get? Yeah.
There was this woman who I approached
there in Mford. Yeah. In like one of the
bars December. Yeah.
>> Yeah. And um he said, "Oh, hey." Yeah.
Dropped me a message. I messaged her.
She didn't even she I said, "Oh, do you
want to come out and that?" She's like,
"Oh, I have to look after my little
girl. She's a single mom." Messaged her
the other day. How's it going? What is
even the point? What's the point of
giving someone your number to say, "Drop
me a message if you're just not even
going to respond." Does it make sense? Not really.
>> So, tell me what happened again. What happened?
>> So, I approached her, right? And she was
like really, really nice. She's like,
"Oh, hey. Yeah. Uh, here's my number.
dropped me a message and that I dropped
her a message. She didn't reply. Dropped
her another message like just if someone
doesn't reply, I'll message them again
like 2 weeks later. And if they still
don't reply, just delete the number.
Messaged her two weeks later. Said, "Oh,
do you want to come for a drink?" She
says, "Oh, um, I can't I've got to look
after my girl. Sorry." So, I messaged
her the other day just like, "Oh, how's
it going?" Didn't even reply. Like, what
what's the point of giving you a number, isn't it?
>> That's what I mean. That's just head
That's girls head [ __ ]
>> because they're actually it's not it's
like they're actually saying oh how
they're telling you to message you know
what I'm saying it's not like they just
give give their number to get away from
you get me like
>> so why didn't you say to her why did you
give me your number then
>> cuz what's the point bro it
cuz you're just going to get into
pointless arguments and what am I going
to get nothing so
>> where did you approach her at
in Rford, bro.
>> Yeah. Was she
>> one of the B? Yeah. She's white and
she's a single mom as well, but
obviously that that didn't bother me, you know.
>> Wait, PJ, where was the place you was on
about before a couple of months ago? You
went there and you come out of the
station and you said you was walking
through some like council estate and it
was a proper [ __ ] hole.
>> Which place? Uh,
>> you said you got off a train, you was
walking through some council estate and
it was a proper dirty stinking [ __ ]
hole. Was it was it in London?
>> No, it was out of London. Somewhere you went. >> Um,
>> was that the Middlesbrough place?
>> Probably. Yeah.
>> Probably, bro. Yeah.
>> Saying something about going for a council state.
>> [ __ ] knows, bro. I've been to so many places.
>> What's the most disgusting one?
>> Probably um Yeah, Middlesburgh, bro.
>> Is it that bad? It's worst place I've been.
>> Slow, but at least with slow, bro, you
can get back home quicker. Whereas
Middlesbrough, you're 5 hours away from
home, in it.
>> Did you stay there in a hotel?
>> Yeah, I stayed in this No, I stayed in
this uh I've actually got a video of it,
actually. Um I stayed in this um it was
just shared accommodation, bro. Like,
you have your own room. You can use the
kitchen and everything. You know how
much it was, bro? £26 for the night.
Dirt cheap, bro. Dirt cheap.
>> Did you have to share a bedroom?
>> No, you don't have to share a bedroom.
No, no, no. There was like a balcony,
bro, and all you could see outside the
balcony was a bunch of spice heads, bro.
>> Have you ever um
Have you ever been
>> You know the funny thing is the people
there, bro. But the people in
Middlesbrough were so nice. They were
actually really friendly, funny enough.
>> Have you ever seen the on booking.com?
Have you ever seen them places in London
and you can stay there in like a dormatory?
>> Yeah, I've seen it, bro. Cuz that's
where I book all my [ __ ] I I book
from booking.com in it. So yeah. Yeah.
>> Would you stay in Do you stay in dormatories?
>> Nah. When I was when I was in Amsterdam,
I stayed in a hostel.
>> Was there other people in the room?
>> Yeah. But it was good though cuz you
meet people doing the same thing as you,
bro. It's like I feel like everyone's
just even even if you stay for just one
night, you know what I mean? Like it's
it's experience. You know what I mean?
>> Was you sharing the room with crackheads there?
>> No, they weren't crackheads. They were
just like normal people that went like
un They were just like people that went
university and people that just traveled
by themselves. The world crackers. No, no, no.
>> Weren't like a junkie's hostel? >> No.
>> No, bro. Cuz it was like this is like a
traveling place, isn't it? No, no, no, no.
>> But the only thing that was bad about
that is when I come back at like 3:00 in
the morning, you turn the light on, is
it? And then everyone wakes up. >> What?
>> You turn the light on to see where
you're going so you can get into bed, is
it? And then obviously people were
sleeping, didn't it?
>> But it only cost me €58 for three nights.
>> What? €58 each night or just for all three?
>> No, for three nights. For three nights?
>> Why was it so cheap?
>> Because there's a hostel.
>> Did you feel uncomfortable sleeping with all randoms?
>> Nah. No. It was like bunk beds, isn't it?
>> Was you on the top or bottom?
>> And I remember I met I met this woman
from Germany. She was [ __ ] eyeing me
up, bro. I swear to God.
>> Was she staying in the same hostel? >> Yeah.
>> It was I still got a guy on Instagram
from the one I met in it like years ago.
I saw him on Instagram.
>> The bird from Germany. Why didn't you
chat to her? She weren't really by.
She's like proper skinny and that is it.
>> How many How many brings did you do there?
>> Two, bro. >> Two. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, bro. Two. They were [ __ ] sexy as well.
>> Was they? >> Yeah. Proper, bro.
>> You're You're going to go this year, isn't it?
>> Yeah, probably.
How do you know that?
>> I don't know, bro. Cuz you love like me.
Oh, that's another thing I want to ask
you. Yeah. What What's your opinion on
this? Like people that say, "Oh, I don't
like escorts because I don't want to pay
for sex." I personally think Yeah. that
every everyone pays one one one way or
another. Like what's what's your opinion
on it? Why why did you do it so many times? People
>> even people with birds like with birds
and they're basically paying for their
sex as well.
But what's the reason why you've used so
many? Like for me it was just like
convenience. Like what I I do if I go
out drinking I always get an escort at
the end of the night. That always happens. >> Yeah.
>> You'd have the same with you or
>> same. Yeah. Just drunk and convenience.
>> Drunk and horny. You just after some
Guinness, you just want a nice [ __ ]
You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. Just quick, easy, done.
That sounds [ __ ] bad though, is it?
It does sound bad, is it?
>> Yeah, bro. I used to I used to love just
getting like a [ __ ] You know what I
mean? You remember that? Do you remember
that 19year-old and that she used to
just come around and suck my dick, bro?
>> Do you never [ __ ] the the escorts? Do
you never [ __ ] them? Do you only get a bloody?
>> No, I have I have started to the last
few I have. Yeah.
>> Yeah. You have to use a condom in it.
>> That's the thing. I I don't like
condoms, bro. hurt.
>> You just can't really feel that. It's
just crap with a condom in it.
>> Yeah, but what else can you do? Cuz
they're not going to let you [ __ ] them
without a condom. So, say you wanted to
[ __ ] someone without a condom. What are
you going to do if you can't find
someone? You're [ __ ] in it.
>> I've had it as well when I've been doing
them and I've like grabbed their tips
and that and they're like, "No." And
it's just [ __ ] and just ruins it. >> Really? >> Yeah.
>> They're like, "No, really?"
>> Yeah. A few times. So, what did you do,
>> man? I've been out my nut before and
just stopped and said, "I'll just get
out. [ __ ] off."
>> Yeah. Yeah. Some of them, some of them,
that's why you need to find like the
right one and Yeah, I get it. I get it.
I've had it before where they've
swallowed my com, but I've had to pay
like 150 in that.
>> Have you?
>> Yeah. And they've actually swallowed it.
>> [ __ ] I never thought they do that.
>> They most don't. Most don't. But
obviously if you if you if you offer
them the right amount of money, they
will in it.
>> Have you ever had one start strip
teasing and dancing? I've had that.
>> No, I've never had that. Have you ever
been to a strip club? I have, but I
don't see the point in it. To me, it's pointless.
>> I've never I've never been to one, but
apparently they're expensive.
>> Yeah. And And the thing is you you're
just horny, so what's the point?
>> You might as well escort in it.
>> Yeah. You you just you just blue ball
yourself. It's just pointless. You just
blue ball yourself.
>> You get what I'm saying?
>> Yeah. It's just like It's just a tease,
isn't it? It's a bit pointless. You
better just get me escort. >> Yeah.
>> If I went I've never been to one, but if
I did, I'd get bored of dancing in that
after a while.
>> So, when you when you go out drinking
Yeah. do you How How long do you stay
out for? Like 10 hours, isn't it?
Uh, normally go out about 600 7:00.
Yeah. And then Yeah. about 8 n 10 hours.
>> I've done it before, bro. And I've come
back at like 9:00 in the morning.
>> Well, you've been out all night.
>> All night, mate. All [ __ ] night. Yeah.
>> I've done it before. I went I went to
the swan. Yeah. I banged this [ __ ] in
it and I had to come back from battery in it.
>> Oh, it's long, bro. Long. [ __ ] long. Yeah.
Why was you embarrassed?
>> Cuz that's where she lived in it.
>> No. Did you [ __ ] that one?
>> Yeah, she was from New Zealand.
>> Who was the 19year-old? What one was that?
>> Oh, someone who I met like a couple
years ago through cold approaching, didn't it?
>> Did you [ __ ] that one?
>> Yeah, few times. But then after a while,
I just prefer [ __ ] So, she used to
just come and give me [ __ ] >> Yeah.
I was on. Who's the one I was on about
earlier on and you was videoing it and
it's all dark and you say to her about
we [ __ ] last night and she said,
"Yeah, who was that one?
>> Got to be the new It's got to be the New Zealand one."
>> I never actually see her
>> and I've been to Nottingham. Yeah. And
but I only got a [ __ ] cuz she was on
her period in it. So she gave me a [ __ ]
>> What was that from an approach?
>> Yeah. Nottingham.
>> Well, she was up there. You approached
her. Did you get blowy when you was up there?
>> Yeah. So, what happened was I went with
my friend on the Saturday, right?
>> And I was supposed to go back to Sunday,
but um I met her and we was Snapchatting
in it. So, we met up and then on the
Sunday in it and then she was like on it
and that in it. So, I'll just book a
hotel for another night. My friend went
back the Sunday and then I went back the
Monday. You get it? >> Yeah.
>> So, it was it was good, bro. It was good.
>> So, why didn't you go up and see her again?
I don't know, bro. I [ __ ] a lot of
chances up, bro. I was stupid, bro.
>> Did you have Did you have her number?
>> No, it was Snapchat. >> Yeah,
>> I think she was chatting [ __ ] after a
while. I think she was trying to say she
had a boyfriend or something after a while.
>> Was she well fat in it? >> Nah,
>> she weren't. >> Nah,
>> you must have done a fat thing before.
>> Yeah, of course I have, bro.
>> It's horrible, isn't it?
Yeah, there was one at my birthday. She
was kind of fat, but she had like big
tits and that. But yeah, I have done um
Yeah, I have.
>> I've done one. She was huge, bro. But I
don't think I was doing it. I was just
[ __ ] her roll.
>> You you you've been with ones that have
refused to give you a [ __ ] Is it? >> Uh
>> it must have happened in it.
>> I'm not sure. I don't think so. >> Really?
>> I can't think on the top of my head.
Well, you've done you've been with
someone that where you've not had a
[ __ ] in it. You just [ __ ] them now. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I can't have it without a [ __ ] Hey, bro.
>> Yeah. You like [ __ ] isn't it?
>> Yeah. I don't know why, bro, but um
Yeah. I don't know why I do, but I do.
>> Would you pick a [ __ ] over six? >> 100%.
I've never done a
>> Have you?
>> Couple of times.
>> No, I've never done that. I've never
>> I don't like it.
>> I don't eat people out either. I don't
like eating women out. I don't know about you.
>> No, I don't.
>> You have done though.
>> Yeah. So have you.
>> I've done it once.
But um no, to be fair, to be fair, to be
fair, bro. To be fair, yeah, if they're a virgin,
>> it would be all right. Yeah. Say they
were a virgin. Or or if you was like
married to them, then Okay. But other
than that, nah,
bro. Have you ever There was this woman
I was with before. She's like, "Oh, if
you eat me out here, I'll give you I'll
give you a blowjob." Bro, I went and and
I smelt her [ __ ] It stunk, bro.
>> Did it smell like fish? >> Yeah.
Yeah, I've had a few like that.
>> I still [ __ ] it, but obviously I
didn't eat her out. You know what I mean?
>> If I told you what to do, if you're at
her place, just go into the toilet, look
into her [ __ ] cupboard, just get like
some bit of shampoo or something and put
it underneath your nose mouth.
>> Or if there's nothing but it's going to
Yeah. But it's still going to taste
nasty, is it?
>> Yeah. Well, just you got to brea like
just not breathe through your nose. Just
breathe through your mouth and just try
and you know when they really stink.
>> Yeah. you. But but the thought of it is
going to make you sick cuz you know like
>> have you ever like Okay. Have you ever
like had to pick up like dog [ __ ] or
something like you know what I mean?
Like and even though you can't smell it
the the fuz cuz you know you're doing
it. It's making you feel sick in it.
>> Well, how far how close did you get to
her with your face before you smelt it?
>> Bro, not very far.
>> Did you still look her out? >> No.
>> Well, she just didn't give me a [ __ ] in it.
But when you went to do it, when you
went to do it and then you stopped, did
she not say, "What are you doing?" >> No,
>> I think what you I think I think though.
>> Yeah, but what did it smell like then?
>> It smelt like [ __ ] bro. It fishy [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I know. Exactly.
>> Woman I was with the week after didn't smell.
>> I know exactly the smell. You mean it?
It's like a mixer between fish and [ __ ]
>> Yeah, it's horrible, bro. It's horrible.
>> Have you ever Have you ever been Have
you ever [ __ ] a bird who's got BO? >> No.
>> What do you think about that American
giving me a [ __ ] in the alleyway? Do
you think that's disgusting?
>> Is that actually true?
>> 100%, bro. Everything I say is true,
>> Yeah, but where did you meet her at?
>> In the O'Neals. Okay, that's it, bro.
>> Yeah. Did you pay her? I approached,
listen, I approached her in the O'Neals, right? >> Yeah.
>> And we was talking for a bit and then
she couldn't find her friends.
>> Then we started kissing. Yeah. And then
I swear to God, this is what she said to
me, bro. She's like, I really want you,
but I don't think you want me, bro. I've
had some mad stories, bro. Even if you
don't believe him. Yeah. And she's like
coming on to me. I said like, "We can't
do anything here. Like people are here
kind of thing. Let me just get this
drink in it." So then I went out with
her and I took her like to the alleyway.
Yeah. And I started like fingering her
and I just took my I just like pull my
trousers down and she just started
giving me a [ __ ] in it.
>> Yeah. What's wrong with that?
>> And then her friends come and then her
friends like caught up like her friend
her friends found her so that's all I
got was a [ __ ] in it. I was trying to
get like a hotel but I couldn't get
there in time. No. What's wrong with
that? Like I mean did I mean like do you
do you think she knew what she was doing?
>> Well what what are you saying? What? You
don't Did she Did she do it or did you
force her to do it?
>> Obviously, she obviously I didn't force
her to do it. No, I just I just pulled
my trousers down and she started doing
it in it.
>> Yeah. What's wrong with that then? I
don't think that's wrong. There's
nothing wrong with that.
>> No, but I'm saying like did she know
that she was doing it like outside?
Like, you know what I'm saying?
>> Of course she did. Why wouldn't she? How
would she not know?
>> Yeah, but because we were both drunk.
Like we were I was drunk. I was drunk.
She was drunk. We were both drunk to be fair. Was
>> she fair? But
>> you must know. Yeah, but you must know
what you're doing in it. Right. >> Yeah,
>> that's Yeah, but like so you must have
had like a [ __ ] outside before it. >> Yeah. >> Really?
>> Yeah. I have years ago when I was when I
was younger in the park and that
people did people walk past to that. No,
it's just one of these big like big
gangs of us when I was 15 this year.
>> Well, you know, some [ __ ] you've had.
Yeah. They've been really good and some
are bad, isn't it?
>> Oh, yeah. Would you [ __ ] Would you [ __ ]
Would you have a free Yeah, with a man
and a woman, but you don't You both [ __ ]
the girl, but you don't actually touch
the man. Would you do that?
>> Maybe. Yeah. Yeah.
>> It's not It's not gay.
>> No. What's the chance of getting
someone? What's the point? What's the
chance of getting a free sim in this day
and age without paying? Sliming it.
>> Yeah, it's not. It's not happening. It's
really not happening.
>> Because you It's hard enough to get one,
is it? So, how you going to get two in
>> Yeah, it's Do you watch that? O, do you
watch that Ed Matthews?
>> Um, I've seen him before streaming.
>> You know who isn't it? Like he goes and
approaches and that isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, I watch some him sometimes, bro.
Have you ever had a free before with a
girl and a man?
>> Never. I've never had a free period.
>> No, I've never had a free with a girl
and a man.
>> What do you think of um Ed Matthew stuff then?
>> Uh I don't really know. I've only ever
seen a couple of videos with him. I
don't really know about him that does he
gamble as well.
>> Yeah, he gamble. He approaches. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> You know, you know that H you know that
HS is in it.
>> Yeah, I see a video of him. Apparently
he's finished now.
What do you mean?
>> He said HS Tik Toky is finished now. I
see it the other day.
>> Yeah, I don't really know who he is.
>> Yeah, bro.
>> PJ if you had like a million Instagram
followers, you could probably get women easy.
>> Yeah, PJ, have you still got your flashlight? >> No,
I've never I've never [ __ ] with them.
What are they?
>> I haven't. I haven't. I thought you
[ __ ] it in the toilet.
>> Nah, bro. Never.
>> That's what you said on the video.
>> With some guy. He stole it, but I didn't [ __ ] it.
>> You stole your flashlight.
>> Nah, bro. Never. Some guy stole it in
it. I was with some guy and he stole it in it.
>> What? Why was you both going to [ __ ] it?
>> I think so. Yeah.
>> What the [ __ ]
>> But I didn't I didn't know. He did.
Well, I don't know if he did. He might
He might have did, but
>> he was like, >> "No,
>> he weren't." >> Nah.
>> Oh, [ __ ] hell. So, you never actually [ __ ] it?
>> Well, you've never [ __ ] one. No.
>> No. I want to get one. >> Really?
>> Yeah. [ __ ] hell. I can't believe he
robbed you for your dick. For your [ __ ] flashlight.
>> Yeah. He stole it, though. It
>> You ever seen him again?
>> No. I don't know what happened to him,
bro. I had him on Snapchat in it. He was
from uh Do like Kent, in it. >> Yeah.
>> I don't know what happened to him. I
>> What do you think? He's dead.
>> No, he was talking about um
he was talking about saying that he
might be going prison and that. So,
that's might what happened, isn't it?
>> I bet he's in prison.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
>> Well, he has you messaged him and he ain't answered.
>> I'm going to message him. Yeah, I me I
just messaged him again now.
>> When he said to you he said to you when
you was with him that he was going to be
going prison soon.
>> He might be going prison. Yeah. He
didn't say what for, but yeah.
>> He He might be ignoring you cuz he stole your flashlight.
>> Maybe in it.
You're You are a troll, bro. Is it?
>> Who? Me? >> Yeah.
>> No, I ain't. I'm being serious. If he
stole off of you, then he's he's
probably embarrassed and don't want to
talk to you cuz he's embarrassed.
>> Have you have Have you Have you Have What?
>> Um I said, "Have you seen that Triple H?"
>> What happened there?
>> I don't know, bro. Have you seen that Triple H?
>> What? the one who comments in your streams.
>> Yeah. Have you seen him come on the like
stream isn't it?
>> Yeah, I've heard you talking to him.
>> He's got like a weird accent now.
>> Yeah. Where's he from?
>> Um Durham, like near Newcastle, isn't it?
>> Who was the one you was meant to be meeting halfway?
>> Oh, that's [ __ ] Jo. He's never going
to meet anyone, bro. And he's a [ __ ]
>> He said he'll meet you halfway.
>> No, he [ __ ] never. He wants me to go
to [ __ ] leads, bro.
>> Oh, it's a mission. I'm not going
[ __ ] Lee. [ __ ] off, man. You can you
can meet me in Nottingham. Is it simple as that?
>> Yeah, cuz Nottingham's still far from
you as well, isn't it?
>> Yeah, it's like 150 mi. It's far, bro.
>> You should have a look on maps and work
out where's halfway.
>> And Nottingham Yeah, Nottingham's only
70 mi from him. It's 150 mi from me. So, he's still >> Yeah,
>> I don't know. Apparently, he's going to
smash your head on what [ __ ] he was saying.
>> You could never smash my head in, bro.
PJ, you're probably
>> How tall How tall are you?
>> Uh, 61.
>> Oh, nice, man. I'm only I'm only 5'10.
>> I thought you was more than that.
>> No, but I think I've got taller in the
past I feel like I've got taller in the
past year and that. I don't know why.
>> You've been barbers lately?
>> A couple weeks ago, bro. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. No, I went about two and a half
weeks ago. I got to go again. probably
next week in it.
>> Yeah. What do you get? I normally get skin fade.
>> Skin fade, beard trim, eyebrows, face
wax. I get I get everything, bro.
>> Well, do you have your nose and ears in that dog?
>> Uh-huh. I'm a hairy bastard, bro.
>> You have Do you have a beard? >> Um,
uh, yeah. Not long, but I have one.
>> What does my beard look like? What does
my beard look like when it gets long, do you think?
>> Um, I have had it your I have had it
your size and it just gets itchy and
uncomfortable. So, I end up just shaving it off.
>> And then when you when you drink like
milk and it gets it gets stuck on the
most, isn't it?
>> Yeah. It's well annoying. Oh, yeah. Have
you been to that? Have you been that
last you know that place you went a
couple of months ago for an Indian like
six weeks ago? >> Uh-huh.
>> Have you been back there yet? That
Indian that you you put it on your
YouTube shorts? Oh, that looks so nice.
>> No. No, I haven't been back.
>> How much did that cost you? £60 in it.
>> Yeah, I think like 40.
>> You had like some sort of like chicken
booner or something. It looked [ __ ] so nice.
>> So, it's so nice in Liverpool Street,
bro. I love the Indians. Yeah, it's so nice. But
>> is that where you was? Liverpool Street.
>> Yeah, but you've been drinking there, haven't you?
>> I've been what?
>> You've been drinking there, haven't you? Before.
>> What? Liverpool Street?
No, I ain't >> ever.
>> No. Do you?
>> You've been there? Yeah. You've been
>> Yeah, I've been there. Yeah.
>> Yeah, I've been drinking there, bro. Of course.
>> I've never been drinking there, though. >> No.
>> Is there a McDonald's across the road
from the station?
>> No, it's KFC. Maybe it's about There's
Maybe there is. I can't remember. I know it's KFC.
Where did you go bowling the other week?
>> Romford life.
The Romford Brewery.
>> Yeah, I do like bowling. Are you any good?
>> Have you been to the Ronford Brewery?
>> No, I ain't.
>> Uh, am I any good? Not really. I like
pool me. I like a game of pool. >> Yeah.
>> You play pool?
>> Yeah, I like pool.
>> Is that one near you?
>> What a pool? Yeah.
>> Yeah. It's a [ __ ] hole. I'd rather go
and play in the pub.
>> I don't know how to play.
>> So, you're going to go drinking next
week, maybe? Yeah.
>> Yeah, probably. I don't know how to play
snooker. Do you? >> No.
>> So, where where you going to go? Where
do you think you're going to go then?
>> I'm not sure. I normally go into um
norally going to London somewhere. Hold
on, PJ. One sec. One sec. Nice, bro. Nothing. Mhm.
Stop going back or what?
Is he coming back? Yeah.
Is he coming back or no?
There's been another fight at O'Neal.
What the [ __ ] What's going on here then? Yeah, bro. Yo, bro.
>> Yeah, I don't know what happened. Oh, he
wants to come back in now. Hello.
>> Yeah, I'm back now.
>> Yeah. What was that, bro?
No, I was just making a drink.
>> Oh, what a cup of tea.
>> Yeah. How do you know that?
>> You know,
>> you know them ribe eyes that you buy? Yeah.
>> I don't buy ribeye steaks, but Yeah.
>> What's that big steak that you buy all the time? >> T-bone.
>> Oh, is it a T-bone? I thought it was a
ribeye. That T-bone? Yeah. What do you
pay for that?
>> Depends on the size. Like normally like 12 13.
>> That one that one you made like 2 months
ago with mushrooms that look [ __ ] nice.
>> Yeah. About 12 about 12 13 pound you get
from the butchers isn't it?
>> Yeah. Proper ones.
>> It's harder to find like a white
butchers now that you know like a
traditional white butchers. It's very
hard to find now. You know I don't know
about all foreign or African ones.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So it's hard to get the steak.
>> Yeah. I can't eat the meat from them
ones. Can you [ __ ] that?
>> No. No. No, bro. Definitely not. You
don't know how long the meat's been
there and that. There's a good butchers
in um in Stratford. White butchers, but
there's also good halal butchers as well.
>> There's good like Yeah.
>> Why are you Muslim?
>> No, but obviously No, I'm a [ __ ] But
like some of the like stuff like they do
like nice per stuff and that you know
what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> No, I'm I'm a [ __ ] Muslim, bro. What
religion are you?
>> Nothing. [ __ ] all.
>> You like you like bacon, is it?
>> Well, I eat bacon.
>> Yeah. You love bacon, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Same.
I had Savo and chips today.
>> Yeah. I heard you saying you was going
to go earlier. Savo is [ __ ]
>> That's nice, isn't it? Savo.
>> Oh my god, I love them.
>> With chips. Yeah, with salt and vineg.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
Yeah, you had it all. You had it
delivered before in it. I watched the video. >> Mhm.
>> I got is most of places where you are
allow, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> That so like you can't even It's hard to
even get like a normal traditional savoy
now because the allow places they put it
as chicken instead of pork and it's nasty, bro.
>> Yeah. No, I've had the really horrible ones.
>> Yeah, cuz it's chicken. If you get it
from like a Turkish place, it's chicken
because it's allowing it. They can't do
pork. It's disgusting, bro.
>> Yeah. Is that what it is?
>> Yeah, it's chicken. Yeah. I've tasted it
before. I was like, "No, this ain't
pork. It's chicken. They substitute it
with chicken cuz it's it's allowing it
to get it."
>> Yeah. Have you not cooked? Have you
cooked any nice food lately? You do.
I've got to admit, you do you always eat
nice food. I've watched all your shorts.
>> Yeah, bro. I tried it, but no, I haven't.
>> Why are you not been on the other account?
I can't go live on it for some reason,
bro. I'll post videos, but I can't go
live. I don't know why, bro. It don't
let me. Long story. >> Yeah.
>> So, I just go live on this one. But what
what did you eat today?
>> Say that again.
>> What did you eat today?
>> Just chili.
>> What do you mean?
>> Chili. Chili conci.
>> Oh, I like that. You know, that's
actually nice. You know, bro, people
take the piss out of it, but I actually like it.
>> Yeah, it's nice. I like it hot though. Spicy.
>> I like it.
>> Yeah, I love spicy food, bro. I love spicy food.
>> I know you eat vindaloo, don't you? I
can eat hot curries, but I can't do vindaloo.
>> You need to try that Carolina Reaper
burger, bro. It would kill you, bro. It
would kill you.
>> Do you reckon?
>> Dave's Chicken is it? You know the
place, is it? Slims chicken.
>> Yo, how hot is that?
>> Very [ __ ] hot.
>> Slims chicken.
>> A leaf before you eat it, bro.
How do you eat them vindaloo? I have one
[ __ ] one fork full. Yeah. One
mouthful there and then I need to drink
loads and I can't eat it. How do you eat
them? Do you finish it?
>> Yeah, of course. I had one um yesterday.
Not yesterday. Day before I finished it, bro.
>> Was your eyes crying and your head sweating? >> No,
my neck was a bit sweating to be fair.
But normally like mostly mostly, bro,
they're not it's just not too hot for
me. I'm used to it. I thought you drunk
three cans of Coke in it.
>> I don't know. [ __ ] bro. I stole my
first one. I didn't even drink half of it.
>> How though? It burns all your mouth and that
>> cuz people's got different taste buds in it, bro. >> Yeah,
>> but Madress is Madrasa is good. Madress
is Do you find the Madras hot?
>> Uh, not really.
>> When you go Nando, do you get like extra hot?
>> Yeah, normally. But I don't think that I
I get extra hot with extra extra hot
sauce. But I don't think Nanos is like
really hot in it.
>> I don't think that sauce that extra
extra hot sauce I don't think it's that
hot. I had that last time with the
halumi and it just didn't really the
little I got
>> you know anything in that Dave's chicken
is hot, bro. If you get anything from
there hot is it is hot, bro.
>> From where?
>> It is hot. Huh?
>> That Sim's chicken. Dave's chicken.
>> Yeah. What's that Carolina Reaper
burger? Is it really badly hot?
>> Yeah, it's the wor It's It's the hottest
in the world, bro.
>> Have you Have you tried it?
>> Yeah, it Bro, it almost killed me, bro.
I couldn't even I was I I took about
three bites of it, bro, with great difficulty.
I was dying. I was dying, bro.
>> Yeah, it's [ __ ] hot, isn't it?
>> And I didn't have shits the next day. Do
you know why, bro? Because I was sicking
it up. Yeah. As I was walking back to
the train station, I was just sicking it
up. It was bad, bro. It was really bad,
>> I bet you had diarrhea all night in it.
No, I didn't. I didn't because I I
sicked most of it up. You get me?
>> That's why you never had diarrhea.
>> Because where I sked most of it, bro, it
was bad. It was I want to try it again,
you know. But I'm not going to lie. I'm
a bit scared. I'm a bit scared. Huh?
>> Have you ever had food poisoning? I
have. That's nasty.
>> Yeah. Once from from Dixie Chicken, bro.
It's horrible. It's horrible.
>> Dixie Chicken. Where else? The one in
Lucian's a [ __ ]
>> The one uh where was it? [ __ ] Fat's house.
>> Did you have excruciating stomach pains?
>> Yeah. You you you got stomach pain and
you're be and you feel sick at the same
time. I've had it, bro.
>> Yeah. And no matter you go to the toilet
and it comes out like water the minute
you get back in.
>> You always get you always get it from
chicken. You always get it from chicken
as well. But you know what? >> Salmonella.
>> Yeah. Salmonella poisoning in it.
>> Yeah. You're on the toilet. I was you
being was you being sick and [ __ ] at
the same time? That's what I was doing.
>> And it only lasts for 24 hours, but it's
the worst 24 hours.
>> And it had [ __ ] stomach pain. And
when you're in the when you're in bed,
you literally have to keep going back to
the toilet. Is it?
>> Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Have you ever had this, bro? Have you
ever had this? Yeah. I don't know. This
might be me, just me, but have you ever
had it yet where you [ __ ] bank chair
and you have to stay on the toilet for
like half an hour cuz your dick's kind of burning.
>> It don't happen all the time, but it
it's happened, bro. And it's not an STI
or anything cuz I've been checked, but it's happened.
>> Say that again. So like you have a you
have a wank. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> And your penis is kind of like burning
and you have to go in the toilet and
pee. Like it's like every drop out
you're peeing. It happens to me but not
all the time. It don't happen all the
time. And it's not an it's not a sexual
disease because I've been tested as well.
>> Obviously after you come you everyone
needs to pee straight away.
>> No but it can be like No, no. But what
I'm saying is it can be like a burning sensation.
When? What bit?
>> Like did your dick kill in it?
>> Yeah, but Yeah, but when burning when
you're coming or burning when you're pissing.
>> No, after. No, after. After. After
after. And it lasts for like 20 minutes.
Bro, I can't explain it. It's weird.
>> Well, after you've had sex or after
you've had a piss.
>> After. No, after you've wanked.
>> Oh, after you've had a wank. But once
you've come and then it starts burning.
>> Yeah. For like 20 minutes. Then you have
to go in the toilet and it's like you're
pissing it out and then it goes away.
But not all the time. It's not all the
>> Have you You might have a [ __ ] STD, bro.
>> Well, no, I don't know. That's what I'm
saying. Cuz I've been tested. That's
what I'm saying.
>> You've actually been tested. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. No. What the [ __ ]
>> I think it's sometime I think it's cuz I
drink sometimes I drink Coke before
doing it. Is it?
>> Yeah. You [ __ ] Is it a friction burn?
Maybe. I don't know.
>> Maybe. Yeah. It's something. Yeah. It
don't It don't happen all the time. It >> Yeah.
>> It is. It is weird though. But um bro,
what you know you say you got food
poison in the air. What's what's the
worst pain you've had? Like what what is
actually the worst pain you've ever had? >> Um [ __ ] Uh
probably what's that? Food poisoning.
>> Bro, have you ever had like a tooth took
out and then 3 days later the pain? Bro,
>> wait. Hold on. I was just gonna say
actually I had a tooth taken out of the
back. But it was a [ __ ] tooth went
all like bad and that and uh Oh, that
was used to really really really really
hurt. And even after they took it out,
it just kept [ __ ] bleeding ridiculously.
>> And three days and 3 days after Oh my god.
>> Yeah. I was thinking about [ __ ] gal
and it would not stop bleeding or
hurting. It was [ __ ] killing me.
>> I had to take painkillers like every
four hours, bro.
>> Yeah. Mine was top two for the back.
>> Yeah, that was mine as well. Was it was
it um he was if he ate or anything
before they took it out, was it would it
be agony, throbbing and that?
>> Yeah, I could I couldn't eat until I
couldn't eat with it properly until 3
weeks after which is now like now like I
could eat but you would still feel it
but now obviously you don't feel it. Do
you get me? >> Yeah,
>> cuz it was still sensitive.
>> You had the worst pain I had was that
that worst pain the worst pain I had was
that foot thing, bro. No, that was the
worst. That was the worst.
>> What foot thing? So basically, yeah, one
day, bro, I don't know what I don't know
if I banged my foot in my sleep. I don't
know if where I was running, bro, but I
woke up. Yeah, I couldn't walk, bro. I
couldn't walk. I was limping. Yeah, I
could, bro. I couldn't walk for like six
weeks properly, bro. Like my foot. Yeah,
I was like limping and it was painful.
It was like throbbing in my in in my
foot, bro. Yeah. And it's this thing
called peran peranal tentonitis, bro.
And at night Yeah. It would f It would
wake I'd wake up. Yeah. It'd be
throbbing. It last It lasted for like 6
weeks. I don't know what where the [ __ ]
it come from. I don't know what it was,
bro. But it was painful. And I had to go
on a date and I had to like walk weird
and that. I said, "Oh, yeah. I'm going
to be walking a little bit weird and
that cuz I've got a foot injury." I
don't know. I still don't know how I got it, bro.
He's still there.
Oh, he left. [ __ ] knows.
One second. What happened there?
>> Yeah. So, I don't know how I got that
foot thing, bro. What? So, wait. Tell me
again about this [ __ ] Okay.
>> about this dick thing. What happens?
>> The dick thing. Oh, you just wank and
then like sometimes it it just burns for
like 20 minutes then it goes.
>> Yeah. What the [ __ ] that about?
>> I don't know. But that that foot thing
was really weird for 6 weeks, bro.
Imagine that. You can't you can't walk
on one foot. Like I'm I'm waking up
hopping, bro. Like you can't even walk on it.
>> What did you twist?
>> Did you twist your ankle?
>> I don't know what the [ __ ] I done, bro.
I might have banged it in my sleep cuz
where I was sleeping it was like next to
like a wall so I might have like just
banged it in my sleep or something.
>> Was it the worst pain in your life?
>> It was the worst pain of my life, bro.
It was I'd wake up at like 4 in the
morning and it would be thumping, bro. Thumping. >> Yeah,
>> it went away after a while.
>> You could feel your [ __ ] heart. You
could feel like your heartbeating in there like
>> Yeah, bro. Yeah. And and it would like
it would be all right. Yeah. It would be
okay. And I had to go to the doctors.
Imagine this, bro. I had to walk to the
doctors. Imagine trying to It took me
like [ __ ] 40 minutes to walk. Yeah. 10 minutes.
>> What did they say?
>> They just gave me some like painkillers
and they just said you have to put ice on it.
>> Yeah. It went after 6 weeks. It took
about 6 weeks though.
>> What was it called? You had tender what
night or something?
>> Some paranal tentonitis [ __ ]
>> He's What is it? Like a sprain?
>> Yeah. On like your tent, you know, like
your your foot. Yeah. Like how do I say
it, bro? It's like um I can't even
explain where it is. It's like here, bro.
It's like here. It was here, bro.
>> Right here. Oh my god. It was painful,
bro. So like right here. And where? So
they say that it's the slowest part of
your body to heal. You get me? So yeah. Bad.
>> So that so that other thing you was on
about. Yeah. Basically, sorry. Just tell
me one more time again. What is it?
>> You you just wank, bro. Why you
recording it? Is it?
>> No, I ain't recording it.
>> No. Well, you just wank. Yeah. And then
sometimes it just hurts for like 20
minutes and you have to pee. It's like
you're squeezing pee out and then I It's
hard to explain it. And then like when
you pee it's like a relief, isn't it?
>> Yeah. I had to get a [ __ ] STD test if
I was you.
>> Yeah, but I've already had one.
>> Have you had one recently?
>> No, I think it was actually a
>> Was it all clear?
>> You know why I got one? Because some
woman she said to me, "Oh, she's got
chlamydia and I slept with her." So I
was like, "Better get tested."
>> Did you have it? Yeah, bro. It's
horrible. You know, see me, bro. I'm not
scared of needles. Yeah, I'm not scared
of needles, but bro, that is some
different kind. Have you ever had one?
>> No, I've never had one, bro. They stick
some long needle and you actually see
your blood coming out. It's It's worse
than a blood test, you know? It's not
like a normal blood test with like a little needle.
>> What? Have you got a fear of needles?
>> No. No, I don't have a fear of needles,
but I'm saying it's just it's it's
weird. It's weird. Like you see your
blood like come out. It's weird. But no,
I don't I don't have a fear needles.
>> Where do they why do they Well, do they
inject you or something?
>> Yeah, they inject you. Yeah. With some
big ass No, I'm not scared of needles.
But I'm just saying it's a lot bigger
than a usual one, is it?
>> Yeah. Why do they inject you? I thought
you have tablets for comedy. No.
>> Um, no. They No, they they take the
blood test to see if you've got it. And
then obviously if you got it, they treat you.
>> All right. Have you Yeah, but have you
not had a full STD test where they test for everything?
>> Yeah, I have.
That's when they take blood and you have
to swab your dick and all that [ __ ]
>> No, I haven't done the swab in a dick one. But
>> no, I've had a one with the blood test.
But you've never Why haven't you never
had one? You must be scared of needles,
isn't it? You must be.
>> No, I ain't scared of needles. They
don't really bother me. Have you got tattoos?
>> Nah, nah, they've never appealed to me.
>> Would you not get one?
>> No, you've got them in it.
>> Yeah, I've got a few.
You're scared as a dentist, isn't it?
>> No, I'm all right with a dentist to be fair.
>> Yeah, a lot. My mom's scared of them. I
know people that are scared of them in it.
>> Some people have a massive fear of it.
What are you scared of? I don't like I
don't like flying. I don't like rats and mice.
>> I don't like rats and mice. I hate them,
bro. I'm the same as you. I don't like
rodents. Anything to do with rodents?
>> No, I don't.
>> Nothing to do even a scribble, bro. Cuz
if I see a squirrel, it just reminds me
of a rat. It just cuz their face is You
know what I'm saying? No, I don't like
Bryce. Mice, right?
>> Could you live in a Could you live in a
place where there's mice?
>> Um, nah. No, obviously not, bro.
>> I had mice. I've only just recently got
rid of them. Oh, [ __ ] horrible things.
>> I've had it. No, we have I have had it
where like we've caught them and that,
but yeah. No, I don't I don't like mice, bro. >> Um,
>> the only thing I don't like about the
dentist, bro, the only thing I don't
like is you know when they inject you. Yeah.
>> Yeah. And then and then you think it's
nuts. So you think it's numbing it and
then they start trying to do it and then
you start feeling the sensitive cuz they
numbed it properly. Then they got like
another needle in.
>> When they took my one out they give me
four injections and then it weren't numb
enough. They give me two more. I had six
in the end.
>> Yeah. That's what I'm saying. But no, I
mean like you know when you get like a
fill in like when they drill it like not
not take out when they drill it. Yeah.
And they give you two needles and then
they start drilling it and you still
feel the sensitivity then they've got to
numb numb it again. That's I don't like
the sensitivity, but I'm not scared of them now.
>> That's [ __ ] horrible.
Do your teeth get sensitive if you like
bite into an ice holly?
>> No, cuz I I brush my teeth, bro, like
three times that day. I look after them
in it, so I don't really I don't have
problems with them anymore.
>> Brush them every day.
>> Yeah. Do you?
>> Yeah. Do you have an electric brush? >> Yep.
>> Yeah. Same. The manual ones are no good in it.
>> Nah, bro. When you get an electric one,
you can't go back, bro. Can't you can't
go back in it.
>> PJ, who would you say has got the worst
the worst teeth in this community on
YouTube? It's got to be
>> very in it.
>> You said that at the same time it don't
understand with these people. Yeah, even
even nons legs. Yeah, even that [ __ ]
nons he's got missing teeth, bro. You
know dentist is free in it for people
with benefits. So what excuse have they got?
>> You know, that's the only reason why I
kept up with all of my dentist
appointments because you might as well
take advantage of something you get for
free in it. What one's What one's nons?
>> That wrong in central, bro.
>> Is he has he got he got black teeth?
>> He's got missing He's got like missing
front teeth. Like front teeth. Not back
teeth, front teeth.
>> No way. Well, you know that for a fact.
>> For a fact, bro.
>> You got any Have you got any fillings?
>> Yeah, too.
>> Yeah, same. How did you know you needed
it? Because when you bite it hurt, it
>> No, it just like I don't know. I could
feel it. It was sore on my tongue. >> Really? >> Yeah.
>> How did you know?
>> Because like Well, it's like when I was
biting it and that. So this tooth Yeah.
that got took How Well, but you know the
tooth that got took out, how did how did
yours how did you know with me? It was
thumping, bro. Like it was bad. It was
like a really bad nasty toothache.
>> Yeah. Same as me. And it would last all
night and I couldn't sleep.
>> Yeah. It was a nasty. And over Christmas
it would like like the thing is I you
could have kept it in and managed it but
the longer you keep it in the the worse
it's going to get. But bro when they
took mine out there was a smell. It
stunk. Well I don't know about yours.
>> Um I don't know. It might mine was all
infected so it probably did smell.
>> Yeah cuz they said we can either give
you filler or take it out. And they
looked as said oh no it's got to come
out and that is in it. So I was like oh
[ __ ] So when I first went, when I was
in agony, I managed to get an emergency
appointment and then they said, "We
can't take it out until the infections
are gone, so we got to give you
antibiotics first." They always say that.
>> Yeah, it's annoying, bro. Have you ever
had like an ingrown toenail that's got
infected? I used to have them when I was younger.
>> I've never had ingrown toenail. It's
meant to be absolutely agony.
>> Yeah, I've had it and it's actually got
infected and pus starts coming from it
and they have to give you antibiotics
and you have to wait like a month to to
get it removed.
>> Yeah. Is it really bad pain?
>> Yeah. Yeah, but I've not had it since I
was like 17. Yeah, it is bad. But you
can't walk with it, bro. >> Yeah.
>> And in the summer it's worse. And in the
summer it's because it stinks, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Cuz it's infected, isn't it?
>> What size What size feet have you got?
>> Um I used to be a 10, but I think I'm a
nine and a half now. I think my feet are
shrunk, bro. You
>> eight. Eight and a half. Oh, you lucky
bastard, man. You You get all the sales
then, is it, bro? Like when there's
cells on and that
>> sometimes um in certain trainers, like
if I get air force, I get a size
smaller. Otherwise, they just all loose and crease.
>> How do you have I can't imagine having
that small feet, bro. What? I always
thought it was to do with like height,
but I don't think it is. I think it's to
do with the width of your feet, isn't it?
>> Not sure. I'm size eight or eight and a half.
Yeah, that's quite small to be fair.
That's good, isn't it? That's good, bro.
Yeah, but I'm sure I'm n and a half. I'm
sure I've shrunk.
>> Have you Have you worn your stony jumper lately?
>> No, I ain't been going out, bro.
>> Not at all.
>> Not really. Well, I've been going out
like obviously I go out, but not like
drinking and that is it. Do you get me?
>> Yeah. When you go out approaching, you
should wear your stony gear.
>> I always do, bro. With my body jeans.
>> And put on fresh trainers as well. Don't
Don't wear trainers. I've got scuffs now
on them. Put nice trainers on. That's
one of the first
>> I've got, bro. I've got fresh vapers.
I've worn them twice.
>> Yeah. Wear them when you go approaching.
That's one of the first things I'd look at.
>> Well, I do wear them, bro.
>> Yeah. Well, you've never gone with
little scruff trainers. >> Never.
>> No. Never.
>> The only I've got scruffed harachis and
I just use them for everyday like just
got not like approaching and that
for like running around the shop and that.
>> Yeah. Literally. Yeah. And the they're harach bro.
>> You know harachis in it.
>> Yeah. And get um and get decent after
shave as well when you go approaching.
>> I got sage bro.
>> I wear it when you go approaching
>> bro. I do all this bro. I do all of this stuff already.
>> There must be something that you ain't
tried with approaching.
>> Um approaching in another country.
>> That's the only thing you ain't tried.
>> Probably bro.
What about what? Is there anything you haven't tried?
>> Well, I don't really approach. I've only
done it a few times and I've been pissed.
>> You just don't care enough, is it?
>> Yeah. It's just long.
So, like that night. Yeah. When they
told you they had boyfriends, you got
you obviously got a number from someone, in it.
>> Um, no, I didn't. What?
>> Cuz you only done it. What did you do it
like three times? Yeah, something like
that. Just one of them said she she got a boyfriend.
>> But do you know I'm surprised like
obviously you went Birmingham. Yeah.
Just to explore, but I thought you would
have maybe like Was it Was it busy? Was
it Was the club was it was the clubs busy?
>> It was um it was busy in the town and that.
>> Well, even on a Wednesday. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> What you thinking of going back up there
from London Houston? Nah, there's
nothing there for me, bro.
>> If I go there, I'll just end up I'll
just end up [ __ ] knocking Monty out,
bro. And he was talking [ __ ] about me
the other day.
>> Yeah, I know. I heard I heard
>> [ __ ] I said keep my I said keep my
name out your mouth, bro. Like, it's
annoying, isn't it?
>> I heard all I heard all of it. Why was
he saying that?
>> I don't know, bro. Like, I'm not
mentioning him, so keep my name out your [ __ ] mouth.
>> He's saying he's going to smash you in.
>> Why did you pick Wednesday to go? Cuz it was cheaper.
>> Um, no. Oh, that's what my mate could
get a day off work.
>> Oh, okay.
>> Why was Monty saying that he's going to
smash you in there?
>> I don't know cuz he's a [ __ ] idiot, bro.
>> Did you speak to him the other day?
>> Yeah, I just said, "Keep my name out
your [ __ ] mouth in it."
>> What did he say?
>> He just said, "Oh, no, no, no. I'm not
talking about you." [ __ ] off, man.
>> Who Who do you Who do you reckon would
win in a fight, though? Me or Monty?
>> I don't know. I've never seen you fight >> really.
>> I've only seen I've seen Monty have a
fight with Tim. That was [ __ ] >> Yeah,
>> that was pathetic. I see Monty have a
fight with Rise. That was just absolutely shocking. >> Yeah.
>> Know Monty says he can fight.
>> Did your mate speak to any birds then?
>> No, he's got misses. >> Oh.
Did any birds fight to speak to him? No. >> Uh,
>> so what time what time did you get the train back?
>> Uh, next day about 2:00. I got that
Popeyes up there. It was [ __ ]
disgusting. Don't ever eat that [ __ ]
>> Ah, man.
>> It was 6 15 quid for a meal. It was horrible.
>> You love You should go to You should go
to Liverpool next Saturday.
>> You love slim chicken, isn't it?
>> Yeah. It's nice, bro. I can't lie. The
chips are nice.
>> What? You're telling me you've never had Wingstock?
>> I've had it once. I've had it once. The
one in Westfield Strapford. It's It's
nice. It's not But it's expensive, bro.
Is it? Yeah.
>> I've never had it.
>> Yeah, I've had it once. I had to check
it out. Yeah.
>> What do you I bet you order salt and
pepper uh salt and pepper chicken from
the Chinese, isn't it? >> No.
>> What' you get? I get beef chain, chicken
fried rice, and sometimes like the
curry, like the Chinese beef curry.
>> I've never had Pizza Express. Have you
ever had that?
Pizza Express? What? That's the one.
It's like fancy, is it? Like thin pizza.
>> Yeah, I've never had I've never I've
never tried that. They have weird
toppings in it.
>> Yeah, but I've never heard it.
>> Why did you ban that person in the chat?
He was talking [ __ ]
>> What did he say? I didn't even see.
>> He was just trying to troll it, bro.
>> Go go go to Liverpool Saturday ain't it?
>> You're thinking about going Birmingham
this weekend, isn't you?
>> Oh my [ __ ] bro. Why Why would I do that
when I could just go to [ __ ] Chinatown?
>> Birmingham is a [ __ ] hole.
>> Was that your f your mate's first time there? >> Yeah.
He's been to other places in England,
aren't it? Obviously.
>> Yeah, he's been a few places. He went to Nottingham.
>> Yeah, Nottingham's good, bro. You should
try. That's all. That's That's a good
one as well. It's like three women to one guy.
>> Swear down.
>> [ __ ] hell.
>> Birmingham. The thing is with
Birmingham, it's two. It's big like
London, is it? It's the second biggest. So, >> it's
the second biggest city is it in the UK.
But I didn't even think it was that big.
No, it is it is big. It's just because
obviously you're only in like the city
center and it
>> Yeah, but it was like this even the city
center would look at like central London
compared to that.
>> Yeah, true.
>> Yeah. The thing is with London
everything's spread out. That's the only
bad thing is like Liverpool Street's nowhere near
>> like if I if I weren't from London.
Yeah. If I weren't from London like
that. The thing is like when I go
Manchester and that Yeah. You can just
use Google Maps and walk around
everywhere. If I weren't from London and
I come to London, I wouldn't know how
the [ __ ] to get about, bro.
>> Yeah, it's confusing, isn't it?
>> I'd be like, even still to this day,
like you still be like, you got to
double check and you and you're from
London. You know what I mean? So, you
get lost, bro.
>> What do you think is the best train
service in London? I think the Elizabeth
line I'm always lucky and get a seat.
>> Elizabeth line, but they need to make
the [ __ ] 24 hours, bro.
>> Yeah, they finish, don't they? Like you
you know Friday Saturday you can the
central line's 24 hours, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But the Elizabeth line isn't. And
do you know when you go out Saturday it
goes into Sunday hours. So you've got to
wait like 10:00 until the Elizabeth line
stop starts running.
>> Have you ever been to Woolage?
>> Uh no. Have you?
>> Yeah. It's a [ __ ] all
>> I know someone that used to live there
but I' never been. No.
Have you ever been to um Oh, I tell you
a [ __ ] a [ __ ] hole, bro. Nine Elms.
>> No, I've heard it's rough though.
>> [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Yeah,
you've been to um what's that place
called? [ __ ] I went to Gamblers
Anonymous there. What? Have you ever
been gambling anonymous?
>> I went to one meeting. I never went back.
>> I went to one as well. I went to only
>> Where was the place? Uh it was called
I think it was New Cross. Is it New
Cross? The the place in South London.
>> New Cross. That's a [ __ ] [ __ ] hole.
>> Yeah, that's where it was. Yeah, New Cross.
>> When you come Did you come outside the
station? Did you see how bad it is there?
>> Yeah, it's bad. It was bad. This was
like eight, nine years ago. But yeah,
>> they're crackheads laying on the floor.
When you was What did you think of the
gambles? Was you laughing and that?
>> Yeah. No, it was just [ __ ] bollocks.
Soon as they all started holding hands
and at the end, I thought, "Fuck this."
And I left. Really?
>> Yeah. Did you stay the whole meeting?
>> I don't think so.
>> Are you thinking about going to another one? >> Nah. Are you?
>> No. [ __ ] that. They're not for me.
>> You remember that guy on YouTube, Andy
Margaret, that that shared his gambling
story? You've seen him in it.
>> No. Who?
>> Oh, you know like some compulsive
gambling channels, isn't it? They say
that they've quit gambling and they they
say there's no cure for this illness and
then and they're 10 years strong in it
and they ain't gambled.
>> Yeah. No, I don't know who he is. I
ain't seen him.
>> Oh, no. It's just some channel where
>> Have you ever seen that newspaper? Have
you ever seen that newspaper article
about Timmy and he looks like a proper
fat [ __ ] in the picture?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> He said he says he lost 60 grand in a year.
>> Yeah, I saw that.
>> Do you think he looks like a fat [ __ ]
in that picture? Yeah, he's a [ __ ] as
well, bro. I don't understand how people
can go out looking like a [ __ ]
>> Why? Why? I don't know. Why is he a Why
is he a [ __ ]
>> He wears clothes that when when and the
colors don't coordinate in that. Do you
know what I mean? You don't even need to
wear designer clothes to look good. You
know what I mean? Like [ __ ]
>> Well, you're saying he wear he'll wear
like a a shirt with Traxxy bombs? >> Yeah.
Something like that. Do you know what
I'm saying? What would do that?
>> Yeah. Apparently,
>> are you scared? Are you scared of boats?
>> No, not really.
>> Well, like going over over Do you know
one thing I'd never go on? I a cruise. I
don't think I could, bro.
>> No, I could I couldn't I say not really.
I probably am. I'm a bit of a [ __ ] when
it comes to flying and boats and [ __ ] like that.
>> No. Do you know what it is though? No. With the
>> I couldn't go on a I couldn't go on a
cruise and be trapped on a cruise ship.
[ __ ] man. Cuz you know the thing is,
right? Yeah. The thing is with that
Yeah. It just reminds me of Titanic, bro.
>> Yeah. Yeah. 100%.
>> You know what? I'm I'd feel like you you
go to sleep, right, and you're waking up
drowning, bro. Like, I don't know, bro.
I just have it in my head.
>> Just imagine. Yeah. PJ, just imagine you
was on one and you're asleep. Just
imagine that feeling of waking up and
it's singing like Titanic. [ __ ] that.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying. How long
are they usually the cruises? Like seven
days, aren't they?
>> You can do People do four week cruises.
>> [ __ ] that. [ __ ] that, bro.
>> You know people that's done it, though. Yeah.
>> Have you done Have you Have you flown
before on a plane?
>> Only Yeah, bro. I don't really like it.
>> Horrible. It
>> It just felt a bit dodgy. It It feels
dodge like going up. When it goes up,
then it goes up and that it
>> Yeah. How many times have you flown?
>> Just a couple.
>> Yeah, same.
>> But it's [ __ ] though, bro. The Euro
stuff felt a bit weird going under. Have
you you never been on the US, have you? No.
>> It goes under It goes under water, doesn't it? >> Yeah.
>> What would you
>> I don't like I don't like motorways.
>> I don't care, bro. I'll say it, bro. I
don't I'm not scared, but I I'll say it.
I don't like motorways, bro. >> Why?
>> I just you cuz you just You just feel
stuck on him.
>> I just don't like him, bro. What about
you? You don't mind him, I guess?
>> Uh I don't know. I'm just a bit of a
wimp and stuff like that. I used to I
don't like recently I don't like
heights. I used to be all right with
heights but now [ __ ] hell my legs go like jelly.
>> Yeah, you wouldn't want to watch that
Ali Law channel, bro. Just watching him,
bro. You watch one of his videos, it
will make you shake just watching it,
bro. He climbs like bridges and [ __ ]
>> What? Did it make you [ __ ] feel like
lightheaded and that looking at it?
>> Yeah, bro. Yeah. So, like so so like how
how far can you like so if you go to
like a shopping mall, can you go right
at the top or now? >> Yeah.
But looking down in it, it's Oh, bro.
Just looking down.
>> Looking down, it makes me all lighted and [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> So, you can never go I don't know how
these people go bungee jumping, bro.
>> Yeah. [ __ ] that.
>> You know what it is? It's not even going
down. It's the hanging. It's the
hanging. It's the hanging um off for
that little bit, bro. Like, what if No,
that's the thing, is it?
>> Yeah. [ __ ] that. Technically, I could
do. I just don't. But I remember when I
was I was working in Bournemouth before
we went on the motorway, bro. And I
remember Yeah. The whole I think it was
about two It was long, bro. The whole 2
hours on the motorway, I thought I was
going to have a heart attack, bro.
>> Yeah. You might have been having anxiety.
>> Yeah. I just don't like the motorways.
This was years ago, though. This was
like again maybe 10 years ago. I just
didn't like it, bro. I just didn't like it. >> Yeah. It's
How long was you driving? Yeah, it is [ __ ] boring.
It was it was years, bro. Uh it was it
was about two and a half hours, bro. And
there was nothing I could do because
you're trapped. You're you're trapped, bro.
>> What was it really? Badly badly doing
your head in
>> badly, bro. Yeah. I thought, "Oh, I'm
just going to die."
>> Yeah. [ __ ]
>> I've got travel sickness. I've got
travel sickness. Travel sickness is
something else. That's another thing
I've got is travel sickness. So, if I'm
in a car too long, I'll start feeling
sick. But you don't get on trains. So
before you say to me, "Oh, how have you
been here? How have you been there?"
Because you don't get it on trains for some reason.
>> If you going along in a car and you look
at your phone, it makes you feel really
sick. But if you sit just going along on
a train looking at your phone, I don't
get it on a train. It's weird.
>> You don't get it on the train. No, you
don't. I think it's with the car, you
know, where it goes left, right, like
the motion of the car. Whereas with a
train, it's like straight. You get it?
>> Yeah. It's Yeah, it's always just straight.
The good thing with trains as well is
you can just listen to music and the
time goes like that. Whereas driving,
I'd never drive somewhere like Newcastle
or go in a car to somewhere like
Newcastle. Nah, bro.
>> Where's the furthest you've been on the
train? How long was the journey?
>> Um, well on the Euro, Amsterdam, and
then the other one Scotland like 5 hours.
Do you reckon you could do Do you reckon
you could do five hours on a train? Yeah.
>> It's long though, ain't it?
What time did you leave for Scotland?
>> Oh, early early, bro. Early.
>> No, I think No, no, the the furthest was
coming back from Scotland if that
counts. I I went back from Scotland, but
going on a train. Yeah, then it would be
it would be Newcastle and Amsterdam. But
I've come back from Scotland twice on a
train. That makes sense.
>> How did you get How did you get there?
Well, the first time I went on the
plane, no, the first time I was in
Newcastle. So then the second day I just
went to Scotland. It was an hour and 20
minutes from Newcastle in it. And then
this the second time I just went on the plane.
>> How long was the flight? 45 minutes
>> about that. Yeah.
>> Do you still need a passport to fly in in country? >> No.
>> Did you need a passport to fly to Scotland? >> No.
>> You didn't?
>> No, I don't think so. No, I don't think
I would have known. No,
>> you can fly to Manchester in it. But do
you need a [ __ ] passport for that?
>> No, I don't think you do.
>> Did you Did you have to have a passport
for your flight? >> No.
>> Yeah, I've never done it before. What?
You thinking about going back to Scotland?
>> No. What's there for me, bro?
>> I don't know. What's it like there?
>> You should You should go there, is it?
>> Is it Is it [ __ ]
>> No, it's all right. Edinburgh's nice, bro.
>> Did you get an ed school there?
>> Yeah, it was lovely, bro.
Where's the furthest you've been on the train?
>> Birmingham, was it?
>> Uh, yeah, that's probably the furthest
I've been. Birmingham.
>> I went Leeds once. I went Leeds once.
>> Oh, I've been to Leeds. Did you like it?
>> How long did it take you to get there? >> Uh,
two hours and something. >> Yeah.
Uh, no. I thought I went clubbing. I
thought it was [ __ ]
>> The bouncers. I had so much problem with
the bouncers, bro. Don't even get me
started. They just don't like they just
they just don't like southerners. I
didn't I didn't rate it, bro. Did you
get any birds?
>> No. No. No.
>> I reckon it's an all right I do reckon
it's still an all right place to go
clubbing on a Saturday though. I reckon
like if I I reckon it's busy enough though. No.
>> What? Did the bouncer beat the [ __ ] out of you?
>> No, he was just trying to get rude in
it. I had to tell him about himself.
Why? What was he saying?
>> He was trying to say like you weren't
letting me in and I said, "Oh, what? Why
don't you allow single entry?" And he
started saying I'm a launcher that I
said, "You're a [ __ ] launch, you stupid cunt."
>> What you being rude for no reason, bro? Yeah.
>> Did they try and beat the [ __ ] out of you?
>> No. He tried intimidating me with his
phone. I was like, "Bro, you don't intimidate me." >> Why?
>> There was there's a club called The
Space. Did you go there? I'm guessing you did.
>> Uh, I can't remember what it was called
years ago. But did you get you got birds? It
>> No, not when I was there.
>> You called to Did you try to talk to anyone?
>> Yeah, loads.
>> What did they say?
>> Just the usual [ __ ] I was just going up
behind and dancing in there and just
moving away. Just all the usual crap.
>> Well, how old how how many years was that?
>> Probably like
seven, eight years ago.
>> Were you by yourself or with a mate? No,
a few of us went. Why are you thinking
about going back to Leeds, isn't it?
>> No, I I I have said I'd go back one day.
I still think it's a decent place to go like
what you going to go in this club and
the bouncer just said he was going to smash
>> being a club. He was just I just didn't
like the whole like the the old bounces
there. I just didn't like the whole Do
you get what I mean? Like the whole
thing about it, bro. I But Sheffield was
good. Sheffield's really good. I
remember going to this barbers in
Sheffield, bro. Yeah. And I had to wait
a little bit. And they give you beers in
the fridge. She feels good.
>> Yeah. I bet you had to pay for it, is it? >> No,
they just gave it, bro.
>> I swear to God, bro. So you got a little
bit tipsy. Yeah. And then you're getting
your haircut. Time flies, isn't it?
Yeah. No, it was good.
>> Well, he never charged you £33 for a beer. >> No.
>> [ __ ] hell.
>> Yeah, Sheffield's good, bro. Sheffield.
I had a great laugh, bro, in Sheffield.
It was good. Better than leads anyways.
And you know leaded you got to pay to
get into clubs and that is it. You have
to pay in it.
>> Yeah. £7 I remember.
>> Well, they were saying they had
boyfriends and that.
>> Yeah. Usual [ __ ]
>> Yeah. I just know what that means when
you say usual [ __ ] in it.
>> So why did this bouncer call you a nons?
>> I don't know, bro.
>> I bet you forgot your ID in it. No, he
just said no single entry in that in it.
>> What? But you never forgot your ID in it.
>> Obviously not, bro.
>> I thought that's why he was just being a
[ __ ] He was just being a [ __ ] bro. It
was just trying to bully me and I
weren't going to have it.
>> Was he black?
>> Yeah, that's it. Kind of ruined it, but
yeah, to be fair.
>> Was he black?
>> No, he was white.
You see these bounces? They think they
can get rude to people in it. But I tell
them about themsel back. I'm not scared me, bro.
>> Yeah. But you need
>> about you. I'm sure you've had mad I'm
sure you've had madness, isn't it?
>> Yeah. With bouncers. Yeah. And know they
always [ __ ] they'll they'll join
they'll join together and beat the [ __ ]
out of you. You need to be careful.
>> Well, you've had it. Yeah. But bro, like
I'm Have you had it, don't you?
>> Yeah. I've been chucked out of places.
I've never had them beat the [ __ ] out of
me. I've seen them beating people up.
>> There was this B there was this Polish
one before, bro. Is it? Yeah. And he
says to me, "Oh, if you uh if you um" He
said, "Oh, if you keep using this
attitude, Jay, which I chuck me out for
no reason, I'm going to snatch the
drink." I said, "You're not going to
snatch no drink out of my [ __ ] hand."
And he tried snatching out of my hand
and that in it. And I pulled it back.
Yeah. And and the drink went everywhere
in it. I said, "Why don't you come now?
You you [ __ ] fat Polish [ __ ]
prick." He was a big guy as well, bro. I
weren't going to back down.
>> Did he punch you?
>> He was being a [ __ ] He was being a
[ __ ] bro. Like, he was being a
>> Did he smack you in the face?
>> No. Oh, you mad. But B, I'm the kind of
[ __ ] bro, that even if I bet if I if I
lost, I'd just go back with a hammer.
Like, I'm not going to be beaten, bro.
Like, and be and be like, "What about
you? Are you the same?" Like,
>> yeah, they What was he just being an absolute [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> What was his problem?
>> If No, but what I'm saying is if one
beat me, no, generally, if one beat me,
what I probably would do, Yeah. is just
buy like a load of like glass bottles
and just start chucking it. I won't I
won't I wouldn't go I wouldn't walk away
a loser, bro. [ __ ] that. Would you?
>> Yeah. No, probably not.
>> My friend told my friend told me, well,
not my friend, someone told someone that
like um the bouncer Yeah. smashed like
his friend's like front teeth tooth down
his like knocked his teeth out and that.
>> Yeah, they do.
>> Bro, if someone if someone done that to
you, but that's that's that's that's a
knife in them, bro. I can't lie on it.
It's got to be in it.
>> Well, you stab him up,
>> bro. If someone knocked your front teeth
down, your your front teeth out, what
would you do, bro?
>> Yeah, you'd have to. That's worse.
That's the worst. Would they knock your teeth out
>> in front of everyone? No, no, no, no,
no, no, no. Trust me.
>> I see that video. What What happened
with you and that black dancer when
you're arguing with him?
>> Which one?
>> And then you're arguing with the black
bouncer and then the girl sitting on the
table gets involved and tells you to shut up.
>> Oh, yeah. Well, you saw that time to
tell him. Why? Why was you round with a
black man, the bouncer? What was his problem?
>> He was kissing. He said to me, "Oh, uh,
can I um can I see your ID?" I said,
"Bro, you're asking me for ID when I'm
28 years of age." And then he kissed
these teeth at me.
>> Oh, I hate it when they do that.
>> Yeah. And then, and you see them trying
to get involved. I told him to [ __ ] off
back to Newcastle, bro. I told him I
told him back about himself.
>> Did he do that um that noise?
>> Yeah, he kissed his teeth. I was like,
"Why you trying to kiss his teeth and
that, bro? What the fuck?"
>> What does it mean when black people do that?
>> It's just rude. It's just disrespect, is it?
>> Yeah. So, what did you say to him? Go [ __ ] yourself.
>> Yeah. I just told him to go suck his
mama, is it?
>> Yeah. That that girl that girl started
mouthing you off. Her boyfriend was a
little [ __ ] is it?
>> I told him about themselves. They didn't
even stand up, bro. I said, "Look, have
you seen your [ __ ] self, you ugly
cunt?" I said, "Stop back to them, bro."
You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. Her boyfriend was a little [ __ ] ain't it?
>> But the people on this YouTube was
trying to act like they beat me. This is
what they do on it. They twist [ __ ]
That's what I'm saying on this community.
>> Everyone Everyone was saying that you
got owned and you were [ __ ] yourself on that.
>> Yeah. Like was I really, bro?
>> I wouldn't say Do you think I was
[ __ ] myself, bro? >> No.
>> You know what I'm saying? But that's
>> You were standing there right next to
him. They could have they could have
done something, couldn't it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Like that's what I hate
about people that you know when they try
to get themsel involved in that. Bro, in
London, don't don't get yourself involved. >> Yeah.
>> But what's the what's the worst thing
you've had with a bouncer though? Like
not tell me like a an actual thing
that's happened. There must have been
something that's happened.
>> Uh yeah, my mate was just pissed up and
we was going out to the smoking area in
a club and then you know when you have
to leave your drink, you can't take your drink outside.
>> My mate was just picking up all the
drinks and drinking them all out of his
nut. And then uh B come over and was
chucking my mate out. And then yeah, we
all just started fighting and they just
uh gave us a few digs and then dragged
us out and bled us.
>> What did you do when they gave you a few digs?
>> Uh [ __ ] all. I just pissed out my head.
I couldn't couldn't do nothing. I can't
lie. I wouldn't have been able to do n
those big massive muscly [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Have you seen that? Did you see
that video I done ages ago in Cardiff,
bro? That was a madness, isn't it? They
were fighting on the street in it. You
saw that in it?
>> Yeah, I saw that. Yeah. That was [ __ ]
mad, bro. They don't care. See, in
London, they've got to be a bit more
careful in London cuz they've got that
badge in it.
>> They've got to be more careful what they do.
>> Why in in um in Wales? Do they not have
that? Did they not have that SIA badge?
>> No, it just says it just said security
with a red top.
>> Why was they fighting?
>> I don't know. Something must have
happened in it in the venue. It
>> was proper punching the [ __ ] out of him.
>> Yeah. And he w he he wanted the bounce
in it. He weren't going to stop in it.
He says, "Come on then." Is it? Yeah.
So, PJ, tell me what happened when that
gazel got hit and died. Where where was you going?
>> Uh, I don't even know. I think I was
just walking into the town center.
>> You was getting boogies, isn't it?
>> Maybe. Maybe not. I can't remember, bro.
This was years ago.
>> In the video, you hear the noise, isn't
it? It goes bang.
>> No, you hear it. It's like this bam.
Yeah, you hear it, bro. Is it?
>> Yeah. And you you see it happen. So,
obviously you was looking at your phone.
What? So, what did you see him crossing
the road in the corner of your eye? No,
I didn't even see him. All I hear was a
bang and I hear him go flying. I didn't
even see him like on the on the road.
You get me?
>> Yeah. Do you reckon? Did you reckon he was pissed?
>> No, he was definitely pissed. Yeah, he
must definely was definitely pissed. Definitely, bro.
>> Did you do you reckon Do you reckon So,
do you know when he' been put in a coma?
Do you reckon he died? I reckon he did, didn't it? >> Yeah.
Did Where did it Did the car Did the car
hit smack him in the head?
I don't know where it smacked him, bro.
But he landed on his [ __ ] head.
>> The gazer.
>> I was kind of I was kind of a bit wary
to like go out after that, you know? I
still went out, but after like well a
couple days, I was kind of like, you
know what I mean? As anyone would in it. >> Yeah. Did you
>> have you ever seen Have you ever seen a dead body?
>> Um, no I ain't >> really.
>> No, I actually ain't. Have you? Apart
from that one?
>> No. I've seen one guy. He had a heart
attack in the internet cap. Is it
>> in the internet cap?
>> Yeah, he just had a heart attack and
just dropped dead.
>> [ __ ] hell.
>> I know it.
>> I swear. Yeah. Well, you've never seen a
dead body. Really?
>> No. Why was you in the internet?
>> No. I was walking past it in it.
>> Was you going there to use a computer?
>> Um, no. I was walking past it. I didn't
go in it. I was walking past it. >> Yeah.
>> Are you me?
>> Joey, do you
>> That's the only dead body I've seen.
>> You reckon Fat Dan's dead? >> No.
>> I reckon I reckon Shagger made that post?
>> Who do you reckon's behind the Five
Great Guys account?
>> It's Tra [ __ ] Davy UK, Shagger. It's
all them, is it?
>> You know, the Five Great Guys. Yeah. Is
it [ __ ] Is it Tramodol, Velli,
Shagger, Davyy, and [ __ ] what's Who
are the five great guys?
>> It's them. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Who is it?
>> I didn't do a football bet today. I lost
20 pound on the roulette. Yeah, but it's
them, bro. It's them. Them them. Yeah.
>> Yeah. But tell me what what five is it?
Who is it? Tell me the five. Who it is?
>> Who you just listed?
>> So, it's Tram. >> Yes. >> Shagger.
>> Um, the one with the black teeth. Davy UK. Yeah.
>> Uh, who else? Belly
>> and Jayen.
>> And Jayen. That's who. I didn't know who
the fifth one was. I don't know that
Jaden. Do you know him?
>> Yeah. He's He's from um Sheffield.
>> I don't know him. Apparently, he's a pedophile.
>> There's a lot of pedos on this
community, isn't it?
>> Yeah. I think Rise is definitely
>> He's [ __ ] ugly, isn't it?
>> He look like He looks like a frog, ain't it?
Yeah. Are you Are you fat or not?
>> Who me? No, I'm not fat. >> No.
>> Yeah, he's he's ugly. He's ugly, bro. Is it?
>> What do you think? Fat's disgusting.
>> No, not really.
>> Do you think Do you think Rise's eyes are normal? >> No,
>> not at all, bro.
>> I can't believe you didn't do your
football bet today. You could have won.
Yeah. Unlikely, bro. Unlikely.
I re I reckon you're going to gamble
tomorrow. I I got this feeling, bro.
>> No, [ __ ] that.
No, definitely not. That's no good. It
just ruins my day. Ruins everything.
>> Yeah. You got you got anger problems
like me in it.
>> Yeah. I can't stand it. And they just I
just hate it.
What I think about is like they're
[ __ ] they're they're they're feeding
their kids with my money and that, bro.
>> Yeah. I've been really horrible to the
staff in the bookies before and it's not even
>> you know what if some of them are really
nice yet I don't get rude cuz I feel bad
but if they're like any kind I've had
one before try and say, "Oh, come
outside. You're going to fight me." I
said, "Come on then. Let's go then. You stupid."
>> I remember I remember I remember you
saying about this. That was the boogies, wasn't it?
>> That was Bford. Yeah.
>> I'll give you my address. I said, "I'll
give you my address as well. Come off
the work. Come on then."
>> What did he look like?
>> Just some fat like Muslim guy, bro.
>> Was he swinging punches at you?
>> No, he weren't swinging. He was just
making empty threats to that. If you're
like if they're nice to staff, then I I
just calm down and don't want to do
madnesses. It just depends, isn't it? Like
>> how fat was he?
>> Just like fat and short, isn't it?
>> Yeah. When he said get outside, you
should have said come outside, you [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I said come outside. Yeah. And I
gave him my address as well.
>> Did he come out from behind the glass?
>> Did he? [ __ ] bro.
I said I don't care how many people you
[ __ ] know. That's what I said to him as well.
>> Bookies never give drinks in it. A
casino does, but bookies don't.
>> Yeah. No, they don't. They don't. They
>> And when whenever I've been in some
murkers, Yeah. they say, "Oh, do you
want a drink?" And I'll say, "Yeah,
Coke." And then I think they're going to
bring a can. And they all the money they
take off people when they can't even buy
cans. They buy bottles and try to give
you a cup.
>> Madness, bro. Have you know I used to go
to the Admirals in Wolfenstone and play
the 20p roulette. I used to win sometimes.
>> Yeah, I've been there. I was losing
>> Have you been to Wolfenste?
>> Yeah, I've lost in there. >> Really? >> Yeah.
Yeah. I used to cuz it's 24 hours, isn't it?
Yeah. Admiral casinos. Oh, yeah.
>> Yeah. Do
>> you go to them all the time?
>> I a been in ages, but I used to I used
to go. I remember I was 100 pound in
before I took 600 out. >> Yeah,
>> bro. I wish I could win, bro. But you
can't win anymore, man. It sucks.
>> Yeah, it sucks. You're better off just
sticking with the football bets, but
you've gone off with them as well, haven't you?
Yeah, but the thing is with the football
bets, bro, like you need to lump on like
to to win most of the time, you need to
put like 150 180 on two teams and then
the odds are [ __ ] on that now. Like
>> Yeah, it's not worth risking it, is it?
>> Not really. No, I mean, yeah, you can do
like you need to find a good lineup.
Well, to be fair, the other day, bro, I
put six pound on a bet. Yeah. And I got
um Oh, he left.
Yeah, as I was saying, bro,
>> the other day you
>> the other day I put six pound in and he
gave me like uh the option to take out
£36 like cash out. But obviously I
didn't. But think about it, bro. Imagine
I had £80 on that same bet. I would have
cashed out in it. >> Yeah.
That that video that you put up the
other week, you know, the one where you
said this is a video for Gregy and you
was playing roulette. >> Uh-huh.
>> When you lost like 150. Oh, that video was disgusting.
>> Yeah. The global the global drama, did it?
>> Yeah. That spin bar just [ __ ] you like
it does to everybody all the time. It
gave you a little pinch and then took it
all off. Yeah, that's what it does, bro.
That's what it does.
>> I bet you went to the cash machine after
that video and went back in it.
>> I went back and spat on the machine, bro.
>> Yeah, I bet you went I bet you got more
money out went back, didn't you?
>> No, I didn't, bro.
>> You actually didn't.
>> No, I don't chase my losses, bro.
>> Have you ever
>> Well, I get pissed off when I lose. I
just get pissed off. I don't feel like
putting more money in.
>> Well, that make you want to do what
Timmy does and pull your money?
I feel like an idiot in the first place doing it.
>> More money. You get me?
>> Makes me feel insulted.
>> I feel like I've been Yeah. I feel like
I've been degraded. >> Yeah.
>> And laughed at and mocked.
>> See, these people in here don't
understand what we what we're talking
about. They think it's about the money
and it ain't about the money.
>> Well, I just don't How come people say
gambling is fun?
>> It's only fun if you're willing. Think
about it. It's a It's a Think about it,
bro. When you win, you're high in it.
Like, it's a high, in it, when you win.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Of course.
>> And then when you lose, you're
depressed. That's the way it goes. It's
It's a high or a low.
>> Yeah. It's not really fun, is it?
>> No. Unless you [ __ ] win.
>> Would you ever go to Vegas?
>> It's never appeal to me, bro. Never.
>> Does it appeal to you? >> No.
>> Because it doesn't appeal to me. A cuz I
like roulette more. B. They tax your
[ __ ] winnings and it just doesn't
seem like the place it's never appealed to me. >> Yeah.
>> Is there a reason why you're put off going? >> Um,
yeah. Same. Just don't really appeal to
me. I just see as a place to go and lose
loads of money. >> Yeah.
>> You need a lot of money to go. Yeah.
>> Yeah. You need a bit of money to go
there. There's some nice 15 grand maybe.
>> I was just going to say between 10 and 20. >> Yeah,
>> that's just a [ __ ] disgusting waste, isn't it?
>> Yeah. If if you're thinking about it.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Seven Neighbors goes
there all the time, isn't it?
>> Yeah. That's where I think that's where
I link probably lost all his money.
>> That's where the side men go as well, isn't it?
>> Yeah. That's why that's why I agree with
you about Rock and Roller and a few
others. Like there's no way for this
many years they'd be on you run they'd
run out of money. >> Yeah.
>> That's why I know they're fake in it
>> cuz how they getting all that money from
what? You know what I mean? Like they
don't [ __ ] work [ __ ]
>> when you got a YouTube channel and like
you get money for it. I don't know how
much you get. Do you? >> No.
>> Like stop and step. What does he get
each month for like the ads and
>> [ __ ] knows bro? [ __ ] But it's not going
to be not it's not going to be a lot a
lot. maybe probably I'd say probably 800
700 pound maybe six.
>> You ever watch Do you ever watch his
videos like half hour when you get like
15 minutes in he loses a bit and he
always manages to draw it back every [ __ ] time.
>> Yeah. I've seen Have you seen that
roulette with with a comeback when he
hit the 23 and he made a comeback. It's [ __ ]
>> Yeah. He put his last£3 he was years ago.
>> It's [ __ ] He's a bullshitter.
>> Yeah. That was 23 in it. He put his
last£3 pound on it and then it got right
back up again. >> Yeah.
>> But the things the thing the things that
happened on his videos just wouldn't happen. >> No.
>> So, does he have deals with the with the
shops that he's in or what the [ __ ] is he doing?
>> Yeah, probably. Probably.
>> Well, you reckon Hyperlinks is going to
sell his fruit machines and now his skin?
>> Probably, bro. It
>> got bare fruit machines, isn't it? >> Yeah.
You reckon you reckon stop and step will
ever run out of money? Nah.
>> No, I don't think so.
Someone said in your chat earlier on
that he owns a bakery.
>> Bad. It's hard to make money nowadays,
isn't it? Yeah.
>> Yeah, proper.
>> You can't even win. You can't even win, bro.
>> No, it's bollocks.
>> When When did you When did you last work? >> Uh
about two months ago. Really?
>> Yeah. I got sacked.
>> For what?
>> Getting out my nut and not showing up.
>> What was it? >> Scaffolding.
>> Was it good money? Yeah.
>> It was all right. 180 though.
>> You just couldn't be bothered in it. No,
I just I just went and got out of my
knot and I No, the first thing the first
thing what happened was I ain't going to
lie, I got paid, gambled all my money
and then it just made me feel so low and
depressed and horrible and suicidal I
didn't even show up to work.
>> How much did you lose?
>> Uh 12,300. And then um the second time I
just got well I went on a bender and
just didn't go in. I had a hangover and
then I got sacked.
[ __ ] that, bro. 12. Yeah.
>> Have you ever wanted to kill yourself
after you've lost money?
>> P. Yeah.
>> Yeah. It makes you feel horrible, isn't it?
>> I take a codam to calm me down.
>> You take what?
>> I take a codal to calm me down.
>> What was that pain? >> Yeah.
>> How long it take you to lose that 12,300?
>> Not long. Half hour. 40 minutes.
>> What was that in the book is?
>> Yeah. Roulette, £30 worth of chips on
the thing and then just spinning around.
>> Was you up at any point?
>> That's only 650 presses.
Don't take long.
>> Was you Was you up at any point?
>> No, I just kept 10 to one. >> Really? >> Yeah.
>> Jesus Christ.
>> I have I've gone in before. or I got
right up and then I should have walked
away and I've been greedy and carried on.
>> Even if I won like 250, I'd be happy
with that, bro. But you can't even win that nowadays.
>> No, not not nowadays. You can't. No,
>> I got lucky.
>> You can't. You really, really, really
>> What are you thinking about?
>> Just bet on like a color. >> No.
>> Yeah, sometimes. But even that, it's
just [ __ ] impossible to get it to
land in the green.
It's [ __ ] man.
>> I bet you go gambling tomorrow in it. Broulette.
>> Nah, bro. Not really. No.
>> Are you having like Timmy, bro? I don't
play it like Timmy. I really don't.
>> Well, you honestly truthfully don't.
>> No, but I gamble. I say when I've gambled.
>> Yeah, I gambled 100 pound roulette the
other day. That was the first time in a
couple of weeks.
>> Yeah. It just made you feel pissed off, isn't it?
>> Yeah. What did you do? Five 20 pound spins?
>> No, they were all different. Like at one
point I was doing like two I done two 40
done 20 and I think two 40 spins.
Nothing. Same old area. Left side of
zero. Same old area.
>> Well, let's say the neighbors area.
>> Yep. That shitty [ __ ] area. It was
double six as well after that.
>> [ __ ] number six. You like it in it?
>> No, I hate that. It's [ __ ] disgusting
number. next to 34. Yep.
I hate it when you bet on 17 and it
lands on six.
Hate it when I used to do second dozen.
Do you know you know like you do second
dozen? Yeah. I used to bet the numbers
and I used to hate it when it used to go
on that [ __ ] four, bro. In between
both of them. >> Yeah.
>> You remember you know four. It's in
between 21 and 19 is it? Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. He used to do me that number.
>> Yeah. Second dozen. is um 13 to 24, isn't it?
>> Yeah. I used to love 1720.
>> 17 and 20 are opposite each other on the
ball, isn't it? Like zero and tier. >> Yeah.
The most I've ever hit was The most I've
>> was a 26 pound on 11 with a multiplier,
bro. Four grand.
>> Or was that online?
>> No, the casino. >> Yeah.
>> Mhm. It was a couple years ago.
>> How much? How much did you walk out with?
>> Four grand. I went in with 150. I walked
out with four grand.
>> Did you go and get it all back?
>> Nah, bro. Bought clothes, went out drinking.
It's just I was doing all sorts of [ __ ] bro. It
>> Did you gamble any of it back?
>> Yeah, probably over time, you know, as
you're doing it.
>> Yeah, you should have
>> not like at once where I can say, "Oh,
I've lost like you know what I'm saying,
bro. It used to be whenever I used to go
out drinking on a Thursday, I used to go
in with um 150 and that and that would
be it. You know, I go with 150.
>> You should have bought some trainers and that
>> I did.
I bought clothes with it, bro. I always
wear new stuff. I'm not a Trump like Timmy, bro.
PJ, do you reckon Timmy's ever won
money, bought like a new phone and
stuff, and then when he's lost the money
that he had left, do you reckon he's
ever gone and took the stuff back for a refund?
>> Yeah, just like Cases Mark has.
>> Yeah, I know he has. But you reckon
Timmy's done that?
>> Yeah, of course he has.
>> Do you reckon Timmy's ever been
>> want to quit? Would you want to quit gambling forever? >> Yeah,
I could do it for I stopped for a year,
bro. like not so long. I stopped for a year.
>> When you when you get paid, you go to
the cash machine after midnight and go
straight to Admiral Casino.
>> No, I used to though like 6 years ago.
>> Yeah, I've done that.
>> I don't I used to know what I used to
do, bro. Yeah, like I'm talking seven
years ago. 8 years ago, bro. I used to
go online as soon as midnight hit, bam, deposit.
>> Yeah. And then if you lose it just
>> Yeah, I've done it.
I got up to like 3,700 on Bet Fred
Roulette once and then lost it all.
>> How much?
>> I deposited 60. Got up to 3,700 on the
roulette and then lost it all on Bet Fred app.
>> I bet you felt like killing yourself in it.
>> Yeah, it's [ __ ] horrible. Should
>> have just gambled. You should have just
took two grand. [ __ ] it.
>> Yeah, but it's still just pointless cuz
even if I win, I just give it all back
anyways. It's just a waste of time.
>> I wish I I've never won something. I
haven't won that. I haven't won anything
like that on online, bro. That's mad.
>> Like what?
>> Like three three grand like you won. >> Mad.
>> Yeah, it was only the one that was only
the one time. I've never I've always
preferred just to go to the boogers. I
don't really gamble online. put 40 pound
in before I won,300 online. >> Online? >> Yeah,
>> online. The only thing is I It's better.
You ain't got to do that spin bar thing.
>> Yeah, but that could also be dangerous
though, bro. Like
>> pros and cons. >> Yeah.
>> The biggest spin I've ever done was 300
pound, I think.
>> What? Online? >> Yeah.
>> Did a number land? Nah, I used to what I
used to do is I used to go drinking and
then when I come back I'd gamble in
line. Sometimes even on the bus back
home I'd gamble.
>> Would it make you really angry? >> Yeah.
>> What's the biggest spin you've done?
>> Uh online. Not even that big. About 160
I think it was. And in the book he's obviously under >> what
>> did it hit?
>> I can't remember. Yeah. It must have
done a few times cuz that's when I got
up to 3,700. >> Mad.
>> In the end, I was just being silly. I
was just tapping the ball all over the
place. Didn't even know I was betting on. >> Madness.
>> You love 17,
>> not I I bet it, but my favorite's 11.
>> Are you going to go and put a score 20
quid tomorrow in Fri Frenzy? Nah,
>> I wouldn't even
>> No, there's no point. You just we just
live. We both done that. We both lose.
>> I I feel like playing online roulette
now, bro, cuz we're talking about it in
it. We just stop talking about it in it.
>> But you love it. You can't you can't
stop. You love it too much in it.
>> No, I [ __ ] hate it.
>> No, you love roulette, man.
>> I don't play slots when I do gamble.
Yeah. So, if I put 150 on roulette now,
will I win? >> No,
>> you'll lo you lose, isn't it?
>> Yeah. You You'll lose. It's not worth it.
>> So, there's no chance of me hitting. No,
>> obviously. I can't say for sure, but
it's highly unlikely.
>> You know, the thing is, yeah, just how
you know it's rigged. Yeah. Because like
you'll know. Yeah. Would it?
Because you know the thing is, yeah, you
look at the table before you join and it
seems like random. Yeah. And then as
soon as you start participating in a
game, it avoids all of your numbers,
bro. Even when you're covering 80 numbers.
>> Yeah, I know. I've noticed. Have you
ever Have you ever covered 30? Have you
ever covered every number apart from one
in the bookies and spun and it's landed
on that number? I've had that.
>> Yeah, in the bookies I have. Yeah.
>> But you if you do it with roulette, you
on roulette online, you have to leave
out how many numbers do you have to
leave out? Uh two numbers to make a
profit in it. Yeah.
>> So, couldn't you just leave out two
numbers and keep hitting?
>> Yeah, but then it still goes to their numbers, >> huh?
>> I've tried doing that and building the
money up, but it still lands on the
numbers you ain't got.
>> What? Two them two numbers. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Maybe after like how many times though?
Where you going, bro? One
One second. I'll be right back. about that, Yeah.
Why is this Where is he, bro? Is you
going to join?
Anyways, I'm coming off in a minute and
I won't be on for a little while.
I got stuff to do.
Nah, bro. I'm I'm coming off this [ __ ]
I'm going to wait for this guy to join. Nah, bro.
Some of us have got a life to live.
Uh because we've got other stuff to do
in our lives. We can't sit on YouTube every day
because you can come back on YouTube
when you're not doing stuff. Yeah. is [ __ ] virgins.
Where is this? Lat, >> huh?
[ __ ] weirdos in this community.
Anyways, I'm going. Yeah.
See you later.
Be back in a couple weeks. In a bit.