Bro, what the actual [ __ ] bro?
What the actual [ __ ] bro?
One second. Hopefully
music could be on here,
bro. Why does this fat ugly [ __ ] keep
mentioning my name, bro? Is he another [ __ ] Yo,
one sec, brother.
It's actually pissing me off, bro. Yeah,
one second. Let a couple of people mod,
bro. Why does this fat [ __ ] keep talking
about me, bro? Why does this fat ugly
[ __ ] Timmy, keep talking my name, bro?
No, no, no. On on a serious now, bro. On
a serious now. Why does this fat ugly
[ __ ] keep mentioning my [ __ ] name,
bro? Does he want me to message his
family? Bro, do I have to stop messaging
his family for him to stop? Stop
mentioning my [ __ ] name, bro. You
don't know how much money people have.
You don't know what people do, bro. Stop
mentioning my [ __ ] name. No. No. It's
not chats. It's [ __ ] videos. And I'll
message up his family, bro. If he keeps
mentioning my name, I will message his
family and I will do the D, bro. I'm
telling you right now, bro. It's
annoying as [ __ ] It won't even It's not
even on chats, bro. It's not even on
chats. It's on actual videos. Tell this
guy stop mentioning my name, bro. Cuz
I'll message his family. I will 100%
message this guy's family, bro. I really
don't give a [ __ ] I'm not ask. I'll
message Auntie Rose right now, bro.
Like, stop talking my [ __ ] name. I'll
message your family. I don't care. Stop
mentioning my [ __ ] name, bro. You
know, I was just talking about I just I
was just talking to Greavves about this.
You [ __ ] autistic [ __ ] ugly naunch
[ __ ] gambling addict virgin. Keep my
name at your [ __ ] mouth. And any more
responses, I'm going to message his
family, bro. I swear to God, I'm going
to message this guy's family.
PJ, PJ, PJ, [ __ ] off, you fat [ __ ] Stop
mentioning my [ __ ] name. It's
annoying, bro. You done the same thing
with Monty as well.
Yeah. You don't know how much people
have. You've done your balls in. Yeah,
you've done your balls in. Just like
your your skinned boyfriend, Nlegs, who
you whose dick you keep sucking. Oh,
he's got all this money,
bro. Stop sucking dick. You and him's
got no money. You're both [ __ ] skint.
That's why you go on about this [ __ ]
[ __ ] so on and so forth. I'm going to
message this guy's family, bro. If he
keeps mentioning my name, I'm going to
message his family, bro. Trust me. Trust
me. I will message his family, bro. I
don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah. Any more response from this guy,
I'm going to message his family. Anytime
he mentions me, I'm going to take it off
YouTube and I'm going to keep messaging
his family. It's as simple as that. Keep
my name out your [ __ ] mouth.
It's annoying, bro. It's been for the
past hour this guy has been mentioning
my [ __ ] name.
Yeah, people have sent me his videos.
I've watched these videos. [ __ ] off,
bro. It's annoying.
I swear to God, it's annoying when you
got some fat down there mentioning your [ __ ] name.
Yeah, you're skint. Your nonsleg's
boyfriend is skint. That's why you keep
talking about money. None of you have
got a couple of quid. None of you are
comfortable in any way, shape, or form.
Do we talk about summer again when you
both had nothing to show? You want to be
embarrassed again. [ __ ] stupid little
[ __ ] Stop sucking up your boyfriend's
dick. You and him both ain't got no
money. You're both skint. You're both on
benefits. You're both living under the
[ __ ] poverty line. Keep my name out
your [ __ ] mouth. Simple as that.
You know what I'm saying, bro? It's [ __ ] annoying.
And he will stop with me, bro. Trust me,
he will stop with me because when I
message his family, when I message his
family, he will stop. You understand, bro?
Do you know what I'm saying?
No, bro. It's not the truth, bro. Bro,
you're you're not you're talking about
yourself. Literally, I just I watched
your video, bro, and you're talking
about yourself. You don't know how much
money people have. You do not know how
much money people have. You're skint,
Timmy. This is where all of this coming
from. You're a gambling addict. You're skinton
legs is skint. You're skint. You're all
skinn. Your boyfriend nonslegs is skint.
You know what I'm saying? One more time.
One more time, I will [ __ ] message
your family. You mention me one more
time, I will [ __ ] bring your family
all over YouTube and I'll tell and I'll
tell my mom why I've done it cuz I've
asked you several times. Keep my name
out of your fat ugly faced mouth. Yeah.
Go suck your [ __ ] nonslegs dick
boyfriend. Oh, he's got all of this
money in his bed [ __ ] Oh, he's got a
couple of quid when he does not have a
couple of quid. Just like you do not
have a couple of quid when you got shown
money and you had nothing to show a
couple of quid. Right. So, keep my name
out of your [ __ ] mouth. Oh, I'm
messaging your family, [ __ ] Yeah. And
you can message all of mine all you
want. I don't give a [ __ ] Yeah. I told
you, bro. I will [ __ ] harass the [ __ ]
out your family. If that means you stop
mentioning my [ __ ] name.
Yeah. Talk. Think about it to me. How
many times you and your non-slegs
boyfriend have been show money and you
couldn't show damn nothing cuz you ain't
got it. You ain't got money. You are
him. You ain't got no money. You're
skint like him. You're on the same Skint
benefit, bro. Talking about me. You
don't know how much money I have. Timmy,
do you remember last February, bro? Last
February, you got shown £1,300 in cash
and you run away just like your
boyfriend. Nons legs. Skint like him.
Anyways, I'm messaging this guy's family
now. Anyways, bro, one second. Yeah.
Yeah. Let me message his family now,
bro. One second.
I'm on Facebook right now.
I told this [ __ ] "Stop mentioning my
[ __ ] name. I'm going to cause chaos
with his family." Now watch. [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Yeah.
See, Rose Eldridge. Chris Eldridge. Yeah.
Messageing your family right now, bro.
You're going to keep You're going to
keep my name out your [ __ ] fat ugly
mouth. You understand that? Yeah. You're
going to keep my name out your fat,
ugly, spazzy, skint mouth. You
understand, [ __ ] You skint [ __ ] Like
your skint legs boyfriend [ __ ] You
understand me? Yeah.
Right. Here we go.
There we go.
It's the profile. I'm going to message
your brother. Told you, bro. You need to
learn. You really, really, really need
to learn because it seems that even when
people beat you up, you still don't
learn. You still don't learn. Even when
people beat you [ __ ] up. Yeah. So,
this this will make you learn. Yeah.
When you're getting [ __ ] from your
family. Yeah. You keep mentioning
[ __ ] people's names on [ __ ]
YouTube. Yeah. One second. I'm just
finding your brother now. I already
message your Arley. Don't [ __ ] with me,
you stupid little [ __ ]
And you're lucky I don't live in
Birmingham as well, bro, cuz I would
have put up posters of you. Yeah, I
would have put up posters of you. There
you go. Found your brother. Going to
message your brother now.
Yeah. Anyone Anyone that knows any more
of his family, bro, tell me. I'm going
to message them as well. Messages his
brother right now, bro. Yeah.
You're not right about anything. It's
just you mentioning my name. It's
annoying. You got a big mouth. Yeah.
Just like Monty. I told Monty the other
day, "Nothing you say is the truth. Keep
my name out your [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] mouth.
Keep my name out your fat mouth." I
don't know how many times I had to tell
you this, you stupid little [ __ ] Now,
I've messaged both of your [ __ ] both
of your family members. You [ __ ] silly [ __ ]
We don't care about your autistic
community, bro. You're autistic. You're
a dumbo. Just like your skint nods legs
boyfriend. You're all dumbos, bro. This
is why people don't want to entertain
you. But since you want to keep bringing
up my name and bringing up my name and
bringing up my name and bringing up my
name and bringing up my name and
bringing up my [ __ ] name, [ __ ] it.
Simple as that, bro. [ __ ] it. I'll
message your [ __ ] family. [ __ ] it.
You know, it's as simple as that. I just
did. Keep my name out your [ __ ]
stupid [ __ ] mouth. You [ __ ] fat
bastard. You fat [ __ ] [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying, bro? You know
what I'm saying? I swear to God if I
lived in Birmingham, I'll put up posters
of you, bro. Just like I done launch
legs. I will put up posters just like I
done with that skin bastard. One skint
bastard and another skinn bastard.
Yeah, it's not escalated quickly. I've
told this guy numerous times, bro. Bro,
keep my name out of his mouth. Yeah,
I told him to keep my name out of his
[ __ ] mouth. Just like I told Monty
the other day and he shut his pants.
Same with him.
Yeah, I message your auntie and your [ __ ] brother.
Stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. You little
[ __ ] Get my name out, you fat [ __ ]
spazzy mouth. You [ __ ] queer. You queer [ __ ] Yeah.
And another thing is, bro, what you're
going on about, you're you're talking
about yourself, lad.
I don't have no criminal record at all,
but you keep thinking that.
I don't have a criminal record.
Anyways, I don't want to entertain these
retards. This is exactly why I didn't
come on here today because of these
[ __ ] retards. Have you noticed he
always does this dusty this Timmy? He
always does this. Yeah. When people are
on him, he always does this. He always
does this. This [ __ ] bro. When people
are on him, he mentions my name. Have
you noticed that? Have you noticed that
the only gambling addict is you? The
only skin [ __ ] is you. Literally, the
last time I showed money was to you and
you didn't show me anything.
Just like your boyfriend nonslegs cuz
you ain't got it. You and your boyfriend
ain't got it. If someone really had
money, bro, if you and your boyfriend
nonslegs, who's got all this money,
really had money, bro, why do you keep
letting me beat your ass at the money
game for [ __ ] 18 months? Cuz you
ain't got it. You are your boyfriend.
So, I don't know why you're bringing me
up and why you why are you bringing him up?
That's what he does. He always deflects,
bro. Every time. I swear if I ever see
this guy again, I'm going to knock him
out, bro. I swear to God, I'm going to
knock this [ __ ] out.
I swear to [ __ ] God, bro. I swear to [ __ ] God.
No, I don't feel bad for him messes in
his family, bro. He's starting [ __ ] with
me yet. I haven't said nothing today.
Yeah, I'm trying to get away from this
[ __ ] clown and he keeps making videos
on me cuz people have showed me he's
making videos, bro. What the [ __ ]
trying to tell people how they've lost
their lost 20 pound and meta. What the
[ __ ] is this guy going on about, bro? I
lost brain cells again. People have
lost. What the [ __ ] are you talking
about? You [ __ ] self-reflecting fat
Virgin. Just like when you project your
virginity onto people. You are the
virgin. You are the skint one. You are
the gambling addicts. Everything is virgin Timmy.
Just like every think he's virgin
boyfriend, bro. Do you get me?
[ __ ] annoying, bro.
Sorry, bro. It's annoying. Sorry, bro.
It is generally annoying.
[ __ ] I I I didn't come on here today
to get away from these [ __ ] to get
away from these retards.
Exactly what I said. And then this guy
is going on and on and on and on and on
and on and on and on talking how he's
going to meet. Bro, you're not going to
meet no one. Timmy, you've lost every
single fight on YouTube. You've been
battered. Yeah, you come to London
London. You couldn't even beat me when
it was a 2v one. Why are you still going
on about beating people up? You're not
beating no one up, you [ __ ] You know
what is so bad about this guy? He's
never even won one fight, unlike me.
when you you tell me one fight this guy
has ever won. He hasn't even won a
fight. So, how is he still how is he
still calling people out, bro? How is he
still calling people out when he has
lost every fight? Every single fight he
has gone in, he has lost.
That's mad. And that's not even happened
to me. Even with the LS I even with some
of the L's I've took, I've still beaten people.
Still coming on YouTube to like some
kind of hard man.
[ __ ] me, bro.
Stop asking self-projecting virgin
questions. Bye-bye now.
No, it's annoying, bro. It is annoying.
It's And if your boyfriend's got so much money, bro.
Why weren't he showing money like you
wasn't for two years, bro? When you got
shown money almost every day, all this
money to me, come on.
Come on, bro. Come on.
[ __ ] Come on, lad. Why? Come on, Mr.
All this money.
Can't even Can't lie to save his life.
Just keep my name out your [ __ ] mouth, bro.
It's annoying, bro. It is. It's very,
very, very annoying. You know,
if your boyfriend's got so much money,
why did he get beaten by me at the money
game for two years, lad? Mr. All this
money. But the thing is, Dusty, right?
You ask with with retards like him, you
ask them questions, they can't answer it.
You know, keep my name out your fat, ugly mouth.
[ __ ] annoying it is.
I've already shown this sub substantial
amount of money and I made you all run
away. See you later. We're not having
the same autistic same argument over and
over and over and over again.
We're not having the same argument over
and over and over again.
>> And stop going on like your boyfriend's
got money. Your boyfriend ain't got no [ __ ] money.
Just like you ain't got no money cuz you
done your [ __ ] balls in. That's why
you're doing a [ __ ] gambling vlog,
you stupid [ __ ] Jesus Christ.
I hope someone gets their hands on this
guy one day, bro. Really beats him up
like proper smashes him in. You know
what I mean?
It's more than what you people have ever
shown. Yes. See you later, lad.
Okay, the link's up. Is he going to join or what?
[ __ ] me, lad. No, they're not getting to
me, bro. I've just told this [ __ ] to
keep my name out of his fat ugly mouth.
Keep my name out your fat ugly mouth and
go suck your boyfriend's dick on his
channel. Oh, he's got so much money.
He's got a couple of quid, bro. I got
more money than you and nons legs. I've
said this now for the 12th time. I've
got more money than you will ever have.
More couple of quids than you will ever
have. Yeah. Do you know the last time I
done my balls in about 6 years ago?
Yeah. You don't know the people that
you're talking about, Fatty Eldridge.
Which is why I had to message your
family because you will not Yeah. You
will not keep my name out of your fat mouth.
Yeah. The last time I got my balls in,
bro, literally about six years ago.
Yeah. You don't know what people have, [ __ ]
[ __ ] hell. Do you understand, bro?
[ __ ] trying to get through to these
autistic [ __ ] people in this
community, bro. Waste of time.
Keep my name out, you fat, ugly [ __ ]
mouth. And if you do it again, another
video, I'll message your family again.
It's as simple as that.
Doesn't matter what I said to them, but
they've been messaged and it's his fault
as well, bro. No one went live today. No
one's talking about him. Why is this
[ __ ] doing videos talking about me?
No, I haven't gambled today.
No, not at all. Oh, [ __ ]
It's annoying, bro. No, it's very, very,
very annoying. Bonnie was doing it the
other day. Keep my name out your [ __ ]
mouth, bro. I don't want to be a part of
this shitty, gay, [ __ ] [ __ ]
biased, skint, [ __ ] [ __ ] community.
Yeah, simple as that. I'm going in five minutes anyways.
Keep me out of your [ __ ] gay [ __ ]
The lies is I was listening to this
video, bro. Uh
I was listening to this video.
This guy's proper self-p projecting,
bro. Telling people they've lost their
last 20 pounds. You don't know nothing.
You none of the people in this community
know anything about anyone. You don't
know who you're talking about,
you [ __ ] stupid fat [ __ ] I'll
[ __ ] keep messaging your family if
you do it again. You can message all my
sisters. My sis, bro, I don't even speak
to my [ __ ] sisters, but one of them.
I generally wouldn't I I won't care. And
I would exactly say why I've messaged
your family cuz this [ __ ] keeps
mentioning my [ __ ] name on YouTube.
Some fat spaz. Yeah. And and when he's
talking about meeting people, who are
you meeting, bro? Who are you meeting?
Who are you meeting? Really? Who is a
[ __ ] really meeting?
Who is a [ __ ] really [ __ ] meeting? No one.
>> You're not meeting no one. And I message
your family as well.
>> PJ, she said you're such a quiet baby [ __ ]
>> No, I message your family, bro. And you
keep mentioning my name. I'll keep I'll
keep messaging your family. You keep you
keep you keep using my name.
>> Tell them that you're a nons with a barcode.
>> Yeah, bro. And I'll just keep messaging
your family. The more you mention me,
the more I message your family. It's as
simple that it's the more it's listen
the more you the more you and your skin
your skin boyfriend you and your skin
boyfriend nons legs the more you keep
bringing me in your [ __ ] the more you
keep bringing me in your [ __ ] the more
I'll message your family
>> people's family keep my name out your
[ __ ] mouth keep my name out your
mouth then someone's family make sure
they haven't got your mom's address you dick >> bro
your mommy's next week to the dress.
Timmy, Timmy, last time you've come, I
beat you and Tiger. I beat you and
Tiger. You've lost every fight on YouTube.
>> Women, PJ,
>> you've lost every fight on YouTube.
You're not hard. You're a little spatic.
You're just like your boyfriend on.
You're both skinn. You're both You got
not a piss in. You're both weak. Yeah,
exactly. Leave cuz you know I'm [ __ ]
right. Leave cuz you know I'm [ __ ]
right, you little [ __ ] You know
people's addresses. You do know. And
you're going to do nothing. Come
tomorrow then. Come tomorrow then, you
stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] Come tomorrow then.
This guy has been mentioning my name,
bro, for the past hour. Yeah. So, I've
messaged his family. Don't cry. Stop
crying about it. Don't mention my
[ __ ] name. Simple as that. Simple as
You know what I'm saying, bro? Don't
like Don't mention my [ __ ] name.
Simple as that. Stop mentioning my name.
You [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
Go suck your nunchle's boyfriend's dick
and stop mentioning my [ __ ] name. You
know what I'm saying, bro? What the [ __ ]
It's the only way he's going to learn
this guy, bro. It's 2026. It's the only
way he's going to learn. Still talking
about meeting people. You're not meeting
no one. You're not meeting no [ __ ]
The guy is a is a [ __ ] bro. He's a
proper proper [ __ ] I am off here,
bro. And this guy this guy keeps
mentioning my name. That's the only
reason I've gone live to tell him to
stop doing it. And the more he does it,
the more he does it, I'm just going to
keep [ __ ] I'm just going to keep um
messaging his family. Every time he
mentions my name, I've asked him not to
do it. He's not being provoked. I'll
message his family. It's as simple as that.
And the thing is to me, you can have people's addresses
>> address that like you got 3 million
viewers on Twitter for
>> Yeah, that's nice. That's nice. But
you're not going to do nothing. But
you're not going to do nothing. So shut up.
>> Personal fella, Timmy. You've You've
lost every single fight. You've lost
every single fight on YouTube. Stop
calling people out. Stop calling people
out. You and you know what? You and
Nonss, you're both similar. You're both
skint. You're both [ __ ] keyboard
warriors. [ __ ] hell, bro. You need to
put all of this on your [ __ ] channel, lads. Yeah.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] idiot, bro. Yeah,
he started it, Dusty. He kept mentioning
my [ __ ] name.
So, [ __ ] him. Is it
topic again. Um, Timmy, you're a [ __ ]
virgin. You're still a virgin. You have
never even kissed a woman, let alone
[ __ ] a woman. Do you want to do you
want to go down the woman route again?
You want to go down the woman route
again? You know, you want if you want to
do your gambling vlogs and you want to
talk about gambling, bro, that's on you.
But don't start talking about people
that you don't know. Don't get
embarrassed again. Yeah. Because the
last person that I showed money to was
you in the pub back when I was living at
the old address. And what did you do?
You ran away just like your boyfriend
nonss ran away because you don't have
any money to show. This is why we don't
waste our time on you people. Not
because we don't have anything. Because
it's the same old pathetic [ __ ] I've
already messaged his family. Mr. B. I
messaged his family. I messaged Rose and
Chris. I told him, "Bro, stop mentioning my name."
I told him, "Stop mentioning my [ __ ]
name. Stop using my name to deflect
calling people out for fights, bro. Come
on, bro. Come on. Come on. Come on."
He's not even won any fight ever. Yeah.
You want to talk about me and Prime?
Yeah. But look at all of the pe Look at
the people that I have beaten. Yeah.
Look at the people that I have turned up
to and they've not turned up. Like this
guy has never even had a W.
He's never even had a W in his life and
he's still calling people out on YouTube.
I could understand if he's won a fight.
He's never even won a fight ever.
And he's still acting hard on YouTube.
What the [ __ ]
He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
I went on his video. Yeah, he's talking
about gambling. I'm thinking, "Okay,
let's see what this cunt's got to say."
Then PJ PJ and I'm thinking [ __ ] this bro. Yeah.
And you keep saying your boyfriend
nonslegs has a few quid bro but you
don't and he doesn't. Again you both
have been shown lots and lots of money
and none of you was able to double it ever
ever ever in that period of time. So
shut up. Stop ass licking and stop using
my name to deflect the attention on you.
You know what I'm saying?
Why don't he just do these gambling
videos on his channel? Why does he have
to keep provoking people when he's not
about that life? Why does he keep doing
it? He keeps provoking people. You get
when when he's not about that life, he's
never won a fight ever.
Bro, listen. The last time he come to
London with Tiger, he was scared. He was
[ __ ] himself. He was walking up the
road, bro. When Tiger was when Tiger was
trying to [ __ ] fight me, he was
walking up the road, bro. He was scared.
Why is he still acting big on YouTube?
Oh, you're going to do this. You're
going to do Oh, we've been hearing this
for 5 years.
You're going to fight this B, bro.
You're going to do nothing. You're going
to do [ __ ] nothing. Come to London
tomorrow and see me, big man. Since you
want to keep talking about addresses,
[ __ ] little idiot, bro.
You don't see me [ __ ] making videos
of [ __ ] London Taylor or any other
[ __ ] You get you know what I'm saying,
bro? No one could be bothered with it anymore.
That's it, bro.
[ __ ] proper [ __ ] He is
I was in Birmingham, but I would have
put up some posters [ __ ] up with
launch legs. I feel that's the only
thing that would would stop this guy
because he gets beaten up. Yeah, the guy
gets beaten up, he still comes back.
Like I've said many times, well, I stole
a quote from Tom Woods. It's like
playing chess with a pigeon. Even when
you be it, it will just strut around the
chess table and [ __ ] all over it and
pretend it's one,
bro. Even if the guy gets beaten up.
Yeah. He still Look how many times this
guy been beaten up.
Think about it, bro.
And he's annoying me because he's
mentioning my name now. Yeah.
Don't [ __ ] mention my [ __ ] name,
you silly little [ __ ] Unless you're
actually going to [ __ ] come and see
people and you've been doing this for
years, years and years and years and
years and years. Go back to [ __ ]
rehab. Because you know the thing is
Timmy, right? You what you're saying in
these videos you're projecting. I'm not
even addicted to gambling. I didn't
gamble today and I have not done my
balls in for about five six years. I
have not been skinned for about five six
years. Ah yeah. See, that just goes to
show that you don't know who you're
[ __ ] talking about. You don't know
who you're talking about.
You gamble every [ __ ] day. Every day.
Multiple times. I don't gamble every
day. Nowhere near [ __ ] every day. I
might have gambled a few times in
January and [ __ ] the other day. I
don't gamble every day. Nowhere near
every day. And I don't leave myself short.
Oh, I've got all this money. Oh, I'm
comfortable. Timmy, you had to live on
bread and water for a month cuz you done
your balls in.
I've done my balls in. I've lost all my
money before. Yeah. About 5 years ago.
Five five six years ago. That's the last
time I was skint. Like literally skint
even even Christmas. Yeah. Last
Christmas I was a bit low on money, but
I wasn't skinn
I haven't done my balls or my ball
sacking for many years. Many many many
many years. I've always had money. So,
stop talking about people that you
[ __ ] don't know, bro.
You know what I mean, bro? [ __ ] me.
You're talking about people's addresses.
Okay. You know people's addresses. So, what?
>> Off your period now.
>> No, you you keep mentioning people's
names, but you never Then stop talking about people.
>> Never get personal. If you play me 55,
it's going to come back to sting you. You,
>> Timmy, you do realize everything in your
video. Listen, Timmy, you've never had a
woman. You've never had a woman. You
You're a gambling addict. Your skin
You're projecting your life onto me.
Respect for your mom. I I've got no
respect for my mom.
>> Telling you to get a [ __ ] grip and
all you do is you've got no message cuz
you keep mentioning my name.
>> Let me talk to your mom now. Let me talk
to your mom.
Listen, Timmy. Timmy, you are mentioning
my name. So I'll message your family.
It's a way to stop you. It's a way to
>> Come on. Rattled. You are It's a way to
stop you. If you've got all this money,
this great life, why are you triggered
over me having an opinion?
>> No. Because you talk [ __ ] You talk. So
do you know how do you know how drain it
is watching a [ __ ] talk [ __ ]
>> A [ __ ] talk [ __ ]
>> Cuz I am coming to London. PJ,
>> bro, we've been hearing it for 5 years.
We've heard this before. Yes. Yes.
You're coming to London. Yes. Yes.
Timmy, how long have you been saying this?
>> Now thinking, "Shut up, you autistic."
>> This is This is deja vu, is it? Deja vu. Yeah. Yeah.
>> This is deja vu, bro. You said you was
You said you was coming to London 5
years ago. You're going nowhere. You're
going nowhere. The last time you come to
London, you ran away.
>> Come down yours and send everyone.
>> The last time you come to London. Okay,
come tomorrow then. Come to your mom.
No, please don't overdo it. Come the police.
>> Come. got this history this street you
have to stand on cuz you're okay then
>> come tomorrow
>> okay you're going to come tomorrow then yeah
>> yes and I will tell the neighbors what
you done to that woman on Twitter with free
Timmy's coming to London tomorrow people
>> you realize how serious this is you put
under strain because you
>> Timmy all the neighbors know me all the
neighbors know me all the neighbors all
the neighbors know me
>> Peter I don't think you grasp it Peter
>> Timmy All the neighbors know me.
>> You've already made your mom leave
Albert Square over YouTube.
>> Timmy. Timmy. All the neighbors know me.
>> You made your mom leave Albert Square.
I'm addicted to YouTube and you got
>> Okay, Timmy. Timmy, you've been on
YouTube all day. You've been on YouTube
>> You've been on YouTube all day.
>> You've been on YouTube all day. Explain
to your neighbors why I've done it.
Timmy. Timmy. The neighbors know me. The
neighbors, you will [ __ ] Okay, we'll
come to Okay, we'll come to London tomorrow then.
Okay. He's coming to London tomorrow
then. Yeah. Every everyone you heard him
say that he's coming to London tomorrow.
[ __ ] He's a [ __ ] proper [ __ ] He is.
No one's rattled, bro. I just don't like
people talking my name. I done the same
with Monty. Monty wasn't calling me skit
or anything. It's just him. I don't like
people talking my [ __ ] name.
Like, you know what I mean? that on the
video and that.
You know what I'm saying? [ __ ]
message that. Contact the neighbors.
Contact the neighbors. The neighbors
know me. You're wasting your time. All
the neighbors know me.
All the neighbors know me. Message who
you like. Contact who you like. No one
gives a [ __ ]
Please remind everyone tomorrow that
this guy said he's coming to London tomorrow.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
No, no, no, no. Do you know what it is,
Jamie? I'm sick of this guy, right? I'm
sick of this guy mentioning my [ __ ]
name. Yeah. No one's provoked him today.
I haven't even gone live today. I
haven't done no videos. I haven't made
no comments. And this guy's mentioning
my [ __ ] name. Yeah. To try to get the
attention off of him. It's annoying,
bro. It's annoying. And clearly since
he's been [ __ ] beaten up multiple
multiple multiple multiple times. Yeah.
And he still hasn't learned. Then [ __ ]
it. I'll message his family. Simple. He
has no reason to be mentioning my name
on these videos over and over and over
and over and over again. Self-
projecting. He's [ __ ] Enough is enough,
bro. Enough is enough. Simple. Yeah. Simple.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] fat [ __ ] Yeah.
So, message mention my more he mentions
my name on videos. Yeah. On on an actual
video, the more I'm just going to do it.
It's as simple as that.
Leave families alone. Leave me a [ __ ]
alone, you [ __ ] idiot. Stop
mentioning my [ __ ] name.
Everything you're saying is projection.
You don't know how much money people
have. You don't know anything about anyone.
People have lost their last 20 pound.
Timmy, what are you [ __ ] talking
about? You have got the biggest gambling
addiction than anyone I've ever known.
Jesus. I I don't think I know one person
that's worse. Maybe I do it every two
weeks. Money I can afford. Not like you.
Not like you. You're project You're
projecting. You're literally you was
[ __ ] in a newspaper over your
gambling addiction. You was you this guy
was actually put on an article in a
newspaper about his about his gambling
addiction. He's a virgin. He's [ __ ]
skint and he's and he's talking about
me. [ __ ] off, man. Absolutely [ __ ] off. Yeah.
I'm not provoking him. I haven't said
nothing to the cop today and I'm seeing
this guy mentioning my name. Simple, bro.
[ __ ] [ __ ] It doesn't matter what I
said to them, but I messaged them cuz he
keeps mentioning my name, bro. He every
video PJ this, P. Stop trying to use my
name to get out of the [ __ ] that you're
getting on YouTube.
guy, bro. He projects everything.
And your boyfriend nonslegs ain't got no
money either. Don't know where you're
getting this idea from. If you and him
really had money, why didn't you show
anything when I showed you thousands multiple times?
Can't answer it cuz you know I'm [ __ ]
right. The [ __ ] bro?
Your channel, your video says last six
weeks of gambling blog, but you're not
you're just talking about me. You're
self projecting on your video. You're
not even talking about gambling.
He's a [ __ ] He's a [ __ ] is he,
bro? A proper [ __ ] man.
Proper proper proper [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> The only [ __ ] is your out, Peter.
Pete, you do realize this stream has
been downloaded and it's probably gonna
>> Yeah, that's fine. That's fine. I don't care.
>> Peter, end up regretting this in the
morning. Trust me.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No, no, I won't.
I'm sick of you. I'm sick of you
mentioning my [ __ ] name.
>> When all your information
>> I'm sick of you mentioning my name. I'm
>> I know she's watching.
>> I'm sick of you mentioning my name.
>> Watching. Let's see how she feels.
>> Well, stop mentioning. And I'll tell her
that this [ __ ] [ __ ] on YouTube
keeps mentioning my [ __ ] name.
>> Respect for your mom and she's going to move again.
>> Listen. Listen. And I'll tell her that
this [ __ ] on this bastic called Timmy.
>> You've been by Tiger and your face was
in the mattress. You can't you ran away.
Timmy, you ran away. You ran away.
Timmy, you ran away. Every fight. You've
been You've lost every fight. You've
lost every fight. Videos two years ago
when you have lost. You have lost every fight.
>> No, no, no, no, no. You've never won a fight, Peter.
>> You've lost every fight that you have been in.
>> You haven't hit no one.
>> Every fight you've been in and you're
still calling people out.
>> Come to London tomorrow and beg for
>> Come to London tomorrow. You have
>> Okay. Well, come to London tomorrow by yourself then.
>> Okay. Come to London tomorrow. Come to
>> Talk full of [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Come to London
tomorrow then. Yeah.
>> Okay. No, Pete. I'm not coming tomorrow.
>> Oh, so you're [ __ ] then. So you're a
[ __ ] So you're a [ __ ] You're a
[ __ ] You're a [ __ ] You're a [ __ ]
idiot. You're going to do nothing.
You're never going to do anything. Stop
calling people out on YouTube.
>> I only tapped you last time and I
thought you'd have learned from your
>> You didn't even tap me. You ran away.
You [ __ ] ran away. You [ __ ] You
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] You [ __ ] ran away.
>> Just like your boyfriends. You're both
skin. You're both shitous.
You and your boyfriend are both [ __ ]
skint and got a penny to your name.
You've got a gambling addiction. You're
a [ __ ] virgin just like him. You have
so many similarities. But then again,
you both have autism. So you both have
autism. So you both have autism. So
>> you both have autism. So And you know
your little friend Tiger, mate, I
punched him to the I punched Tiger to
the [ __ ] ground, mate. Yeah. I
punched him to the ground and you didn't
even help him. You ran away. You ran a [ __ ] way.
>> You going to put your mom in the hangouts,
>> mate? Speak to your mom cuz I I
>> You don't need to speak to my mom.
>> I feel sorry.
>> Putting up with you.
>> You don't need to speak to my mom.
>> You lost your money and your
>> lost my money. I've got plenty of money.
I haven't lost any money.
>> I haven't lost any money. I've got
plenty of money.
>> I've got more money than you and your
boyfriend on Snake. I've got plenty more
than both of you. I've got plenty more
than both of you. You don't know what I
have. You don't know what I've lost.
what I haven't lost. You know your own
life to me. You know your own gambling.
You know your only gambling addict virgin life.
>> You only know your virgin life. That's
what you know. You're just an addicted
gambling little virgin. You can't even
[ __ ] avoid Wi-Fi. Yeah, man.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Yeah.
[ __ ] And look. Oh, look. Oh, what's
this? What's this short Timmy's done? A curry. Oh.
Oh, he's starting to eat curry now.
Oh, he's starting to eat curry now. I
wonder why that is.
Oh, he's eating curry now. Hot curry.
Oh, I wonder why that is. That's
interesting, isn't it? Yeah.
You little copycat.
He's a [ __ ] love little copycat,
ain't he, Timmy? Yeah,
he's another little copycat.
no mind of his own. You'll notice that
on his channel, he also he's another one
that has to copy people. Copy the crowd.
Follow the crowd. Like non-slaring as [ __ ] Embarrassing.
They're just They're just They've just
got so many similarities, isn't it?
Did you see Monty man comment on um Timmy short
for one? I love it. Yeah. So Monty.
So Monty must know his channel there,
didn't it, Dusty?
I don't know why that made me laugh.
Oh, [ __ ] what the [ __ ] So he must
know. So he knows his channel then, right?
I don't know why, bro, but that just
make that just makes me laugh. That
really makes me
I just can't believe this Timmy Aldridge
is still doing this in 2026.
And he's he's lost every single
he's lost Oh, I'm crying. He's lost
every single fight. Yeah. Imagine that.
Get He's lost every single fight. And he
said he's still on YouTube.
Some people just have no Some people
just have no shame. They really don't.
They really don't. I'm not ashamed some
of these [ __ ] people. Honestly,
they really, really, really don't.
Nah, they don't, bro. They don't.
Mad old videos. This guy is [ __ ] pathetic.
[ __ ] neighbor. Embarrassing. Absolutely embarrassing.
How does Monty know Timmy's channel? Dusty. He
He must have searched it or something.
He must have searched it or something it never 100%. Yeah.
That's how this community is never going
to stop because of this Timmy. He's the
one that's brought us into it and he's
the one that's starting all this [ __ ] again. literally Yeah.
Yeah. Timmy, bro. [ __ ]
The reason I was on his channel in it
cuz I was watching some of the gambling
stuff. Don't go on L. is not sub to
large. I am sub to Timmy.
And look, [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Harry, at least I've got pop noodles and
food in the cupboard as PJ can't even
afford a can of [ __ ] beans from Audi for 29.
>> What the [ __ ] are you?
>> You haven't got any money. You've come
on here because I've said in the
>> You know what, Timmy? When are you going
to stop talking about When are you going
to stop talking about How do you know
how much money I have?
>> Have your spouse attack.
>> No, no, no. I'm not having I'm I'm not
having a sp I'm asking you.
>> How do you know how much money I have?
>> PJ, you are obvious.
You're talking about yourself.
>> Innocent people because you
>> You're talking about your [ __ ] self.
>> PJ, your beef is with me, not with my
family. So why are you
>> No, no, no. No, stop mentioning Stop
Stop doing videos talking about me.
>> Stop doing videos talking about me.
>> You [ __ ] man up.
>> Do you not understand that you're the
one that you're the one that people
threatened family over YouTube?
>> You're the one that you are a baby.
>> You're the one that's skimped to me. You
have got no money. That's why you're not
gambling because you ain't got no money.
>> As I speak out, I can show you.
>> Who's the one who's the one sitting there TV?
>> 200 in the bank pizza.
>> Okay. Okay.
There's only I can show you the secret
assets if I really have to go that far,
which will make your heart melt.
>> Okay, let's go. Let's go back. Yeah, you
sold You sold your TV. You sold your TV.
I've never done that. We've seen We've
seen me with women. We've never seen you
with a woman. We've seen me with a
woman. We've never seen you with a
woman. You sold your TV. I've shown more
money than you. I've shown more money
than you. I've shown more money than you
and Nons. You and your boyfriend
nonslegs. That's two of you down the drain. Yeah.
>> Peter, you've got you've got if you've
got all this money, right, I know when
you've got money, Peter,
>> you don't know anything. You don't know nothing.
>> Yes, I do know nothing. You don't know anything. You're getting
Sorry for yourself.
>> You are skin. No, you are skin. You've
done your bollocks in
over me having an opinion
>> because I don't like you mentioning I
want you to keep my name out your fat
mouth. I was the same with Monty. I was
the same with Monty. But I don't go
about writing to their family because
they've got an opinion on me.
>> No, no, no, no, no.
>> Peter, you have lost all your money and
you can't place the
>> I've lost all my money. Timmy, you're
talking about yourself again. I've got
plenty of money.
>> I've got plenty of money. Unlike Unlike
you and nonslegs, I've got plenty of
money. Unlike both of you.
>> You haven't got any money cuz you
>> I've got more money than both of you.
But it doesn't process in your brain. >> Complete.
>> Timmy, you said people had no money last
time. You got beaten at the money game.
You got beaten at the money game and you
ran away. How long are you going to keep
doing this for social media so you
choose to you've got to accept spoken
aboutimmy? Unplug your fiber cable and
[ __ ] off. Apart from Harry Fraud,
>> Timmy, I've got more money than you and nons.
>> I've got more money than Do you not
understand more money? Do you do you not understand English?
>> I don't think you understand English is
it? I don't think your brain works
properly, does it? I don't think your
brain show me. Oh, not this again. Show
£20. Oh, not this again. Not this again.
>> 20. I mean, I've got money in the bank.
I can show you.
>> See you later, Timmy. You got shown
£1,300 last time and you ran away. See
you later, kid. You kicked. And this is
what it always is with these people in
this community. And this is exactly why
I didn't come on here today, bro. This
exactly why I don't waste my time with
this [ __ ] anymore.
This is exactly why I don't waste my
time with this [ __ ] anymore. Show me
money so you I can run away again. Nah,
same old boring [ __ ] People show them
money and then they run away again. Same
old boring [ __ ] Just in 2020. This is
why I don't come on here. This is
exactly why I don't come on here, bro.
This is exactly why I don't come on this
autistic disabled community.
I've only gone live to tell this [ __ ]
Timmy Aldridge about himself, bro.
And you know the the thing is, bro, I
thought more and more about this
community. It's so [ __ ] weird.
That's why I did go live yesterday. It's
so [ __ ] weird. This community is so
[ __ ] weird, bro.
Just a bunch of people talking about
other people that they don't know, that
they've not met, that they'll never
meet. It's [ __ ] weird. I'm live
daily. I wasn't live yesterday.
Nope. I don't think I was live
yesterday. No, definitely definitely wasn't.
And I'm not even going to be live for the hour.
Nope. Definitely not daily. I mean, I
was off of YouTube for 9 days. I wasn't
live yesterday. Yeah. No, definitely
definitely not live daily. Definitely
definitely definitely not.
>> Hello, Pizza. Have you calmed down yet?
>> Yeah. Have you calm down? Auntie Auntie
Rose is going to suck my [ __ ]
Auntie Rose is going to suck my [ __ ] Timmy.
Yeah, Auntie Rose is going to suck my [ __ ] mate.
The guy can't even afford decent Wi-Fi
and he's calling people skin.
Guy is a [ __ ] embarrassment, bro. Guy
is a [ __ ] embarrassment. Remember
I said any any more mentioning my name
messaging your family again lad. Yeah.
And there's no it's between me and you
because no one's provoking you. No one's
mentioning you and you're mentioning my
name. So there's nothing between me and
you. I want you to stop mentioning my name.
I want you to keep my name out of your
mouth. And if you're not going to do it,
then I'll message your family.
You're never going to come to London.
Even when people beat the [ __ ] out of
you, you still you're still coming on
here doing this.
So, I mean that family works fine.
There's no there's nothing between me
and you. I'm trying to get away from
this hunting place and you keep talking
my you keep mentioning my [ __ ] name.
You know, you don't want me to message
your family just like I don't want you
to keep mentioning my [ __ ] name every
day. But you do. So that's it. Simple.
That's a way out of it, you know.
But yeah, I've not done my balls in for
about five years.
Proper autistic, bro. Proper proper
autistic community. This is disabled,
gay as [ __ ] weird.
Just the [ __ ] they do on here is weird
as well. Even the people that not
haters, it's just there's no sense to this community.
There's literally no sense to it. I was
watching uh Timmy's
first video earlier that he done today
and I'm thinking, bro, you've been
saying the same thing for 6 years. Oh,
I'm going to meet you. I'm going to meet
you. There's no point of this whole
community. Unless anyone's going to put
gambling video up, gambling videos up.
There's no point of it. It's just weird
people that don't know anyone talking about
other people that they don't [ __ ] know.
Doesn't make no [ __ ] sense.
[ __ ] very creepy if you ask me.
[ __ ] off, man.
Make myself a hot chocolate
and go to bed.
It's so bad, bro. I don't even chase my
losses. It's so bad. And I don't even I I [ __ ]
I don't even I don't even put more money
in when I lose.
This guy is a proper addict and he's
talking about [ __ ] people doing their balls in.
He's a [ __ ] clown. Like when I was
gambling, bro, like them three years
ago, like when I had the house and that,
I gambled big amounts, lost big amounts.
I was never skin ever. I can't remember
the last time I've had to ask to borrow
some uh to ask ask somebody to borrow
money. No matter how much money I get
Yeah. I can't remember the last time
I've had to borrow money off people.
I can't even remember the last time.
Years ago. Five years ago, maybe.
Yeah, probably five years ago.
years and years and years and years and
years ago doesn't happen. Timmy is an
addict. You don't understand. There's a big difference.
Just projection, bro.
I'm going to make a hot chocolate now.
Yeah. Like I said, bro, we're starting a
new channel. Me, Grezy, Steven Howard.
We're starting a new channel, bro.
We're starting a new channel away from these people.
Why do you think I didn't come on
yesterday, bro? It's the same [ __ ] It's
boring as [ __ ]
Very, very boring. It's so It's [ __ ]
weird. Only these people this
people of this community have got a
[ __ ] life for a fact.
>> Got a life.
>> The people in this community ain't got a life.
Oh, show money. Show money. Show money.
Grow up, bro. This 2020 [ __ ] fix an idiot. >> Yeah. Yep.
There's not many good people on here, bro.
I was speaking to that guy yesterday. I
was live speaking to that guy yesterday.
He was all right.
They also hate it having they also hate it like
when you have normal conversations with people.
They hate it when you have normal
conversations with people on here as
well. Have you noticed that?
just weird. I just It's just a weird
weird weird pathetic gay projecting
downy community. I don't know what I I I
can then the more I put myself in these
people's shoes, the more bro, the more
you try to put yourself in their shoes,
the more weirder it is.
It's so It is such a weird community, bro.
And there's no sense to any of it.
That's the thing. There's no sense to
any of it at all.
It will just go on for another 15 years.
No one's met anyone. They're still
talking the same [ __ ] you know? Nice.
Nice hot chocolate.
Trying to watch a [ __ ] video, bro.
Anyways, I'm going in a minute, lad. Yeah.
There you go.
>> So you go, Peter. 20 10 20 40 >> Yeah.
>> 70 pounds. Peter, right now show more. I
can go and show a lot more because I'm
not a liar. Like who?
>> How much How much How much How much did I
>> show me 20 quid?
>> How much did I show you last time? >> 20.
>> Can't show 20 quid.
>> How much did I show you last time? >> 1300.
>> Yeah, last time.
>> Last time. And that's all the evidence I
need. Last time you quid, you can go to
the bank and humiliate. Can I Can I
Okay. Are you going to let me talk? You
show me a lousy 20 quid. Same argument again.
>> [ __ ] 20.
>> Listen. Listen. It doesn't matter if it
was last time. It doesn't matter if it
was last time. You showed nothing, bro.
It's still out. Just like your
boyfriend. Nons legs. Nons legs showed
nothing. Just like your boyfriend. Nons legs show.
>> Just like your boyfriend. Nons legs
showed nothing. And this is exactly why
I don't come on this community anymore.
And I'm coming off now anyway. See you
later. Yeah, lad. Uh, any more
mentioning my name? Um, I'll be
messaging your family again. So, and
trust me, I will be doing it. I've
already messaged them. So, any more of
you making videos, talking about me,
whatever, I'll be messaging your family.
Simple as that. So, see you later, lad. Anyways, bye.