Sorry about that, lads. The link wasn't
working. Right, we reset it now. I'll
put the link up.
Yeah. So, you've got to you got to
seriously seriously, bro. Put it up
twice just in case. You seriously have
got to be jealous of something.
You seriously seriously have to still be
doing this. You seriously seriously have
got some deep rooted jealousy issues.
You're in denial. Proper proper proper
The only thing that would make sense,
it's the only thing that would make
sense as to why you do what you do every
day. It's got it's got to be jealousy.
The way Timmy talked about people as
well, the whole like buy. It's got to be
some jealousy. Probably jealous that I'm
better looking than them that I can go
and [ __ ] go out and get [ __ ] I
can go out and have a life. They can't.
It's got to be something, bro. It's got
to be something. And you know the most
annoying thing about it yesterday. You
know what annoyed me yesterday is it's 2026
and they're still doing this in 2026.
They're still doing this.
I come off to get away from this [ __ ]
Yeah. I I went off here to get away from
these people. Right. It's as simple as that. Yeah. Anyone
that wants the new channel, you you
know, well, not anyone, people that
won't like dox it and stuff. We're going
on the new channel very soon.
And it's just going to be a couple of
decent people from this community and that's it.
So many benefits to it, bro. So many
benefits to it.
Yeah. We've never seen you with a girl, though.
Yeah. It's been so long. It doesn't
matter how long it's been. It could have
been 10, 15 years ago.
Yeah, I don't record my life anymore.
Just like I don't show money.
We've never seen you people with a girl
ever, even in 10 years. Again, more
self-p projecting. And this is exactly
why I come away from this place. Exactly
why I don't want nothing to do with
anyone on here. Because of these jealous
ass people. It's as simple as that.
Um, I can't tell you yet, bro. People
are going to have to email me and I'm
going to have to put it like I'm going
to have to put it sing like singularly.
Think about it, bro. The reason these
people like Timmy and Nonss do this is
cuz they're jealous. I'm seeing it with
Timmy now, bro. I'm starting to really
really really really see this with this
fat [ __ ] Timmy. All these people that
try to gang up with you, you're better
looking than them. That's another thing,
bro. Yeah, this is what I started
noticing. But I didn't even think I
never thought I never thought it was
Timmy, but bro, it's clear that they're
jealous of you. It's clear as day. They
can't even deny it now, bro. It's It's
obvious. It's obvious. It's obvious.
I find it so mad how you're better
looking than these people. That says a
lot, bro. That says a [ __ ] lot.
People are bringing up [ __ ] reasons
to [ __ ] bring your name up. You get me, lad?
So, when this wobbler doesn't meet me um
today, I'm done. I'm coming off again,
which is the only reason why I'm live. Yeah.
Keep my name out your [ __ ] mouth,
bro. It's so annoying, bro. The fact
that he was still doing it in 2026. Yeah.
Just it just seems like a community
trying to get people to bring they're
trying to bring you down to their level.
No. No. It seems like they're just
Ugly fat skin. That's all it is. There's
nothing in this community for any normal person.
For any normal person. There's nothing
in this community for any normal person. Nothing.
I'm getting some nuggets by the way. Grievy.
Laney bought me some nuggets. >> Yeah,
but just listening to it is annoying,
bro. Listening to it is annoying
when you got some [ __ ] wobbler
talking your [ __ ] name. I messaged
you about this yesterday on Instagram, you know.
Very annoying, bro. Very annoying.
Now I'm going to have to get my brain
cells back. Greasy. I'm going to have to
get my brain cells back.
But yeah, Ben, they are biased. Biased
with women, biased with money, biased
with looks. They're biased with everything.
Of course they're biased, bro. Of course
they're [ __ ] biased trying to sit
there and act like they've not been
shown thousands and thousands of pounds
and they've run away and how it doesn't
count because it's ages ago. Don't
everything these people talk about every
day a is ages and years ago.
Prime years ago, LT years ago,
everything that they talk about is years
ago. Literally everything that they
bring up is years ago.
That's what I'm saying. Exactly. You
know it's biased. Who cares anyways? [ __ ] them.
Think about it, bro. Yeah, think about
this, Grevy. It doesn't m The virgin
[ __ ] doesn't bother me, but think about
this. Yeah, this [ __ ] is calling me a
virgin and he's got six thumbs up on his community post.
He's got six thumbs up on his community
post of calling me a virgin when his
channel has been banned for pornography
and he's got six thumbs up. Does that
not tell you enough that you're kind of
like wasting your time with these people?
That you're literally like wasting your
time? I mean, six thumbs up. Come on, bro. Really? Thumbs up. Thank you. >> Yeah.
>> I was lying in bed yesterday and I'm
watching this person video and they keep
mentioning my [ __ ] name. Keep you
know when someone's mentioning you know
your keep my name out of your [ __ ]
mouth. And I said to them the more you
me mention my name I'm going to message
their family. That's the way we're going
to do it. If they keep mentioning my
name I will I will message their family.
It's as simple as that. Yeah. But I have
I have gave them the upper hand because
they're not going to learn otherwise.
See, Laney knows. Laney knows the score.
Laney knows the [ __ ] score. Simple as
that. You know, you can't keep [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying?
>> L wants to Oh, wait. We've heard all of
this before. This is 2026.
Time to get a life, lad. Yeah.
>> All right. So, anyways, you coming to London? Yeah.
>> Constantly talk [ __ ]
>> Yeah. I'm going to meet you. You're
coming to London.
Lee Green and Nazi Lony Lee Green is
defending you again. Well, I might put all
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, you coming you coming to
London then? Yeah. Like you said, your
mate's going to
>> [ __ ] nons.
>> So, are you coming to London then?
>> No, no, no, no. You coming to
Birmingham. You're the
Here we go again with Timmy. Here we go
>> Here we go again with Timmy. He said
that he's going to come to London. His
mate's going to drop him off. And now
he's telling me to go to Birmingham.
>> Autistic. It's not called an autistic
community for no reason.
>> You're autistic, PJimmy. Timmy, listen.
I will fill you in and your and your and
your skinned boyfriend. Nons legs. You
know your skin boyfriend and you keep
sucking his dick. He hasn't got no
money. You ain't got no money.
>> You ain't got no money. When you've been
shown money, you've run away. You ain't
got a couple of quid. You or him ain't
got no cut of quids. You [ __ ] do not.
>> I know you haven't even got 20 quid to your name.
>> I ain't got 20.
>> 20 [ __ ] quid?
>> How do you know how much money I've got?
How How do you know how much money I've got?
>> Rose says, "How do you know how much
money I've got?"
>> You are Rose J.
>> How does How does he know how much money I've got?
>> Skint versus
>> Okay, I'm skin Timmy. I've got more
money than you and your boyfriends. You
and your skin boyfriend who I'm going to
keep talking about and every time you
mention my name, you like to bring him
up to it.
>> Pathetic. And I've spoke to Izzy this
morning. That's nice, bro. You were that
[ __ ] [ __ ] at kissing. That's
>> you. You and you and you and your you
and your boyfriend launched or [ __ ]
skint. You're skint like him. I don't
know who's more skint, him or nunchle.
>> And I love it.
>> Who's who's more skintter? Him or non
legs? I think I think they're both as
skint as each other.
>> I love it.
>> They probably look at each other for
money to be honest. They're both skinn.
>> Oh, you come on. You make your hard and
you're going to do
>> Listen, come to London. >> PJ,
>> come to London.
>> Beat me up. Ain't going to happen.
>> Come to London.
>> No, no, no, no, no. You could. You said
that your friend was going to drop you
to London. Come to You can You can meet
up with LT as well if you want. You can
meet up with LT if you want.
>> No, no, no, no, no. Peter, I don't need
LT. When I meet you, I will punch you in one.
>> Okay. Well, come today then. Okay, good. Come today.
>> You got the choice.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Come today then. Get the
train to London. Get the train to
>> I've spoken to my friend and he's
available at the end of the week.
>> Right. I'll see you when you're in
London. See you later, lad.
I'm taking a bite of my nuggets now, Grezy.
Yeah, that's nice, bro. Let us know when
you're in London.
Let us know when you're in London, man.
Let us know when you're in London.
Let us know when you're in London. Is
that right, G? Yeah.
You know what I mean?
having my little nuggets.
I had two cinnamon swirls when I woke up. Greasy.
Laney bought me them. So, yeah.
That peppers was nice yesterday.
I ate a lot.
Whole chicken and chippies. Yeah.
Yeah. Timmy. Timmy's another one, bro.
It seems. Yeah.
They're so biased on here, bro. I am
actually coming off of this [ __ ]
I am actually coming off of this [ __ ]
bro. I tried to offer it. This guy
started to blow me the [ __ ] out
in 2026. He still hasn't got balls.
You know what I'm saying?
None of your business. When was the last
time you left your house and got a life?
When was the last time you [ __ ] got
off of YouTube and got yourself a little
life for yourself? Did Tim say he was
coming to London? >> Yep.
>> I hate to admit this
on a show on a show and he deleted it.
>> He was asleep.
>> He said he was coming to London.
>> Yeah. At 3:00 in the morning.
>> Slug, I hate to admit this, but PJ has
you here. If you say you're going to a
place, you can't get up the next day and
back out of it and call him to your house.
>> He said his friend was going to drive
him to London.
>> That's madness.
She doesn't have any friends that drive
apart from Tiger.