Just waiting for some
breakfast. Call me ready.
These people on the radio are [ __ ]
idiots. I'm telling you, bro.
Madness. It actually feels like a
[ __ ] Wednesday today. It doesn't feel like a
Tuesday. Feels like a Wednesday.
I'm just in a pub waiting for
breakfast. Uh fancy drinking dinner
today. I don't know why, but obviously
I'm not drinking for a few weeks, not
approaching for a few weeks. But even in
this pub, you you see people with the
same attitude. Even in this little local
pub here, you see people walking around
like their [ __ ] don't stink. It's
crazy. You You meet the same people.
Literally, every time you go out, you
meet exactly the same
people. Same entitled westernized
people. I'm leaving this country soon
anyways. I can't wait until my fridge
comes, but it's not coming till the [ __ ]
27th. But obviously, I'm not going to I
can't cuz the weather's nice, but
there I don't know when I'm drinking
again. Not for a while, man. Not for a
while. What's the point,
eh? I got [ __ ] late today as
well. I can't believe I spent £280 yesterday. [ __ ] hell. Damn.
At least we saving [ __ ] saving,
man. This is the whole purpose of getting the
fridge is crap, bro. The advice they
give on Reddit was like, "Oh, you have
to keep approaching." I was like, "Fuck
off, man. Did you just see what I just
shown you?" for the past [ __ ] 20
minutes. It was £103. But with the
fridge, it means that I can cook and
keep things in there so I don't have to spend as much.
Yeah, it's good.
Eh, man's going cinema today. There's
nothing in the cinema I want to watch,
to be fair.
It's a It's It's a little fridge. It was on
offer. It's a little fridge. It's not a
fridge freezer. It's just a little
fridge. It's not a fridge
freezer. It's just a normal little
fridge. Show you if you want.
Yeah, they always they always give the
same advice on Reddit. Oh, go to the
gym, work on yourself. Oh,
man. Yeah, I was laughing a bit at that
Morgan thing yesterday cuz it is a bit
funny. It is a bit
funny. You have to laugh at it. Is a bit funny, man.
From this is the
fridge. This is the
fridge. Obviously, you could probably
get like a bigger one cheaper, but I had
to have a brand new
one cuz Yeah, the fridge has to be brand
new. You can't get a fridge used. That's
[ __ ] stinking, son. You can get like
wardrobes used or like tables, TV
stands, but not a [ __ ] fridge, mate.
Not a [ __ ]
fridge. That's [ __ ] stinking. There's
some things you just can't get used.
It's like a phone. I would never get a
phone secondhand because you don't know
what people's done on it before you've
before you've got it. You don't know
whose hands have been on it. You don't
know if they've downloaded [ __ ] child
porn. You don't [ __ ] know what they done on it. Thank
you. There we go. But you understand
what I'm saying is it. You know the
point I'm trying to get at. Oh, breakfast.
Yay. Feel like side Mark, you know.
Yeah, cuz he used to do this, do
he? They never get the eggs
perfect. Nope. Don't like
beans. Very solid. A
Oh, that means me.
No, it might be time for the Reese
clothing very soon. Uh, Joe, do you
remember that expense them expensive garments we
got? Nah, I don't like beans. No,
no. Nice. I don't like beans, bro. The
fridge ain't coming to the
27th, but the fridge is good,
man. But I'm going to be start wearing
my expensive garments soon from race.
Yeah. But why
doesn't I saw that Ben talking to Tra
yesterday on John West and he was
saying, "Oh, the poster thing worked
well with me." The poster thing didn't
work well with me. I left that house
before them posters was even put out there. Yeah,
right. I had problems with a neighbor
due to gambling that caused havoc and
then my mom didn't want me living there
anymore. It wasn't because of the
posters. So, actually the posters didn't
work well because if anyone finds out where I live,
yeah, if anyone finds out where I live
and they start doing posters, I'm not
moving. I'm not moving anywhere. That's the difference.
So get your facts right, buddy.
You know the best thing to do with this breakfast. Yeah,
it is. No, re is expensive. Yes, it is
expensive, mate. It's like £110 for a
top. I spent like £400 there last
summer. I had all that money. Anyway,
look, this is the best thing to do. You
dip the bacon with egg and mushroom and
you just scoff it down you. I don't even
cut the bacon. I just scoff it in my mouth.
I do love my bacon. I do love
bacon. I like it. Would you prefer
sausage or bacon? I prefer bacon, hands
down. Oh, lovely,
mate. Yeah, I know. I fancy drinking,
mate. When I was here on a I think it
was a Wednesday, I think it was. That's
when I met the Irish guy like back in
December. And I weren't even planning to
drink, but where he was drinking and he
was making me laugh, I was like, "Oh,
[ __ ] it. We'll just get on it together."
and he went to Germany to work. I've not
heard from him
since lovely, man.
Where did the B go? Where did the B go? Nice.
No, it's not worth the drugs that I have. Trust
me, there's some good weather spoons in
central London. There's some good ones
in central I like the ones in central London. Yeah.
I was binge watching it in between us yesterday,
Joe. I was just binge watching
it. Yeah. Like not not
like Oh yeah, Grezy. I went last Saturday,
man. And it was so busy I couldn't even
hear myself think. I was trying to eat.
Yeah. And all I can do is hear people
talking and it wouldn't stop. It's
[ __ ] horrible when it's too busy when
you're trying to eat.
Yeah. It's horrible. It's horrible. It's
horrible. But the in between is it is
overrated. People was like, "Oh, it's um
yeah, it was Saturday." It was I'm sure
it was Saturday. It was horrible. It was
I think it was last was Was it last
Saturday or It was a Saturday, bro. And
it it just wouldn't
stop. I feel like I had people in my
mind. I don't like it when it's like that, you know? Yeah.
the one where um did the the person ends
up being underage. But what makes me
laugh is people try to say that it's
relatable. No, it's not relatable. It's
a TV show. How is the inbetweeners
relatable? No, I like that Mr. Gilbert.
He's patched me
up. He's He's patched me up. He's
[ __ ] hilarious, bro. I love how he
just bullies the kids. Like the teacher
kids. [ __ ] laugh, man. Yes, Mr.
Gilbert. That's funny.
We was like going me and my friend took
a me took a memory took a trip down
memory lane. No no nostalgia. We was
talking about like home alone. Um,
basically Kaye split up with him and live
together. Yeah, I lost 100 pound
yesterday. I don't win anymore,
man. Why don't we do it? [Music]
Yeah, Monty's man. Money man truly got
his life ruined by YouTube.
Yeah, I wish I had a [ __ ] 1.2K
win, but that ain't happening.
That is not happening. Is it? [Music]
So his life got ruined over the same
website. You can watch Spongebob. Imagine
that. Think about that for a second.
Yeah, my life's
fine. I already know what I need to do.
I need to leave this country. Save up a
bit of money. Leave this country.
Yeah, I wish I [ __ ] won 600 [ __ ]
quid. I spent £300
yesterday. [ __ ] yoke. It's a [ __ ]
joke. Yep, I can see as
well. That's why I don't gamble much no more,
Joe. Honestly, I don't gamble much
anymore. I really don't.
Boring. It's the same old sad song. It's
the same old story with
him. I don't
bother. I literally don't bother with it.
Yeah, women are evil.
E, look at what Katie
done. Women are [ __ ] evil. Evil
bastards. They're all the [ __ ] same
as well. That's what bothers me about
them. They're all the same. They're
literally all the same.
So I used to say to Shman I used to meet Sha
that I used to say all women are the
same. It's like you don't know all
women. I said they're no more
[ __ ] bye-bye you little
virgin. I see you on Monty man's. Yeah
you can [ __ ] off you little virgin. Go
get a life you down. Remember that account.
Bye-bye. Get a life you down and join me. off
YouTube sle bastard. Anyways, um yeah,
and he don't know all women. I'd be
like, I know more [ __ ] women than
you, you [ __ ] virgin [ __ ] That's
what I used to say to him. That's what I
used to say to him cuz I know more
[ __ ] women than you. I've been with
more women than you. I know all about
him. They're all
[ __ ] and people in general are [ __ ] as well.
If you actually meet women, they are
literally they're all the same. Their
minds are the same, man.
Bye-bye. Bye-bye now, you little downey.
I saw you on Monty Man's um last week.
You little downey. You was giving him uh
Timmy's address when he was calling the
police on Cosmic Kitty, right? He was um
you was giving him Timmy's address. You
little downey. Don't [ __ ] come on
here and try to troll. You don't have
the brains for it, mate. Don't come in
here with your little downy accounts and
try to troll me like I don't know what
you're doing. [ __ ] off,
mate. But anyways, Joe. Yeah, all women
are the same. They're
boring. And you can trust me. You can
trust me, Joe. You don't trust Monster.
You can trust me. Honestly, bro. Like,
I've been with more women than him. I
have more experience than him. And not
just with women. I've got more life experience than
him. Just because he's in a relationship
with a [ __ ] downey that can't talk, a
special needer who you don't even see on
the street, doesn't mean anything.
Remember, he's still jealous of the
women that I've been with. He only
wishes he could get with them. I know
more about women than he will ever know,
mate. Trust me.
And that goes to show Joe that just
because you're older than someone, it
doesn't mean you got more life experience than
them. What is he 3 years older than me?
And I've got more life experience than
he will ever
have. But then he could say, um, I've
actually been sort of I've actually
been, well, I was actually seeing somebody, that
19-year-old. Um, but even still, I can
say something because I've been on a
plane, I've been abroad, I've worked,
all of the things that he's not done,
all of the things that he's not done.
Just because he's in a sexist
relationship, it doesn't mean
anything, you know. Has he been abroad?
No. Has he been on a plane? No. Has he worked?
No. There you go. He ain't got no life
experience. And I have basically been in
a relationship cuz I met somebody about
11 times. So try again, buddy. Try
again. And this is another thing I um I
always have to say to people. They seem
to think that you need to be in a
relationship with somebody to know what
women are like. No. I've got sisters.
I've got a mom. I've been around women.
I know exactly what they're like. Yeah.
When you're in a relationship with
somebody, you're in a relationship with
one person, not multiple women. So why
do these these people general you you
you'll hear this. I think because
they've been in a relationship with one
woman, they know more about women than
you. That's not the way that
works. What? They're all the same, bro.
That's why I don't bother with women no
more. They're [ __ ] boring. the [ __ ]
bing. All the [ __ ]
same hash browns
now. They're all the same
NPCs, nonplay couches. Yeah. Mhm.
Nothing, man. Just probably going to go
Mackey's, get a Coke, and probably just
chill. There's nothing. There's nothing
in the cinema.
Byebye. Um, there's nothing in the cinema until
Friday. What makes me laugh is that you
think people on here, Joe, torment me,
but they don't. They torment themselves
because remember, they're the ones that
have to be obsessed with you all day,
every day. You've got to reply to them
only some of the time. They don't
torment no one. They don't
psychologically [ __ ] with anyone's head.
that Tramodal knows that there's no
point of him sending posters anymore
because a he don't know where I live and
b it doesn't bother no
one. That's why he was saying to Ben,
"Oh, I can't be bothered sending posters
anymore." Because, you know, it doesn't
work. You don't psychologically [ __ ]
with anyone's head, you little downy.
Otherwise, I still I wouldn't be on here.
um the horror film called Woman in the
Odd. So straight away on Friday, well
the first showing is like at 7:00 I'll
be there. I will be at the cinema.
Yeah, there is some things in the cinema
now, but not any good things. And man's
gone cinema today, but nothing I want to watch.
That's all you really got in England,
mate. Until you can leave football bets every week,
cinema, drinking every week or every two
weeks and then
leave. It's a depressing country,
eh? The people are [ __ ] as
well. The people are [ __ ] here, too.
That's the madest thing about it is the
nicest people you meet are from third
world countries. You know, that's that's
the most funniest thing. Even here, the
nicest people that you meet are from
[ __ ] third world
countries. Everyone in England are [ __ ]
[ __ ] Literally same
people. You go out and you meet the same
people. [ __ ] It bothers me, mate.
[ __ ] bors me.
Yeah. The women on [ __ ] the people
[ __ ] the weather
[ __ ] [ __ ] goblins everywhere. It's
almost [ __ ] in this country.
And what I've noticed with Reddit is um
people will just randomly um block you.
Not everyone, but you'll be having like
a normal conversation and then they'll just
randomly block you. It's proper [ __ ]
up. They'll just like randomly block
you. It's weird. Like mid
combo. Yeah. Social media ruined everything,
bro. You just you could just leave the
country is what I'm doing,
bro. I mean, technically, I could go out
every week drinking and save money, but
be bothered with it, mate. [ __ ] bors
me. This country,
you can't even say two words to somebody
without hearing, "I've got a boyfriend, Steve." You can't
even say two words without hearing that
boring line. Imagine
that. Yeah. Ant-Man went out Saturday,
Sunday, and then he got laid by a 40y
old. A 40y
old. Um I was just showing everybody the
fridge that I
bought. Where where's the best place to live? Thailand,
Australia. Um, as in like making money,
but the women are [ __ ] in Australia
obviously cuz they're
westernized. There's a few. There's
Japan, China, anywhere but this [ __ ] Yeah.
Anywhere but this [ __ ] hole,
mate. That's known as Great Britain.
There's nothing [ __ ] great about it.
You know what I'm saying?
[ __ ] I'm going to struggle to put my
football bets on this week though because of
um because of um I've spat in so many
bookies now. I don't know which one I
can get into and actually do a football on.
Hopefully it put I can put some food in it.
Hopefully I can put like at least two
three days food in it cuz I don't do a
week shopping. I do like two three days
cuz I don't know what I fancy on the day. You
see? So I don't know what I fancy. So
I'll buy something for like two days and
I'll just go do it over two
days. Hopefully if it's like at least
some pork chops in it or something. I'm
hoping it [ __ ] does.
a Guinness mate. I
do 103 pound but altogether it was 107 with the
delivery Guinness man but I'm not doing
it because when I have one I can't stop.
I'm not There's no half heart in it.
It's all going in. Bro, when I drink I
drink to not stop. I don't drink to
stop. I drink till I can no longer stop.
So no, that's not a good
idea. Lord love goodness.
But yeah, seems like Tuesday going out days now. E
yeah, good for the price, eh? You know
what I always wanted? like
£3. Yep, Steve. And it also means that
every time I'd have to keep going to the
corner shop to buy Coke cuz well I don't
have a fridge. It wouldn't stay cold
obviously, would it?
So yeah, I'm always
winning. But yeah, people on Reddit,
they'll just randomly um block you. Some
of them it's weird.
Yeah, it's a Weather Spoons,
buddy. And I'm not in central
London. It's a Weather
Spoons. No, I love
Guinness. You know what? I might just
have one, you
know. How is it? because it's a small
fridge. I lost £100. Yeah, I spent £300
yesterday. Pretty much. I pretty much spent £300
yesterday. Yeah, I might as well give it
whirl. I'm only having one
though. Yeah. cuz I don't want to go out
approaching. No, I'm not going to do it.
I'm not going to do it. Show fridge to
prove I'm winning. Why don't you suck my
dick? How about that
one? Why don't you suck my dick to prove you're
winning? No, I'm not going to bother
drinking. [ __ ] it. I'm
good. I'll save it for another time.
Yeah. No, there's no point ruining the detox. Nice
Coca-Cola. A bit of
lime. Guinness stinking. Guinness is
absolutely lovely. It's the best drink
ever. Obviously the Orington virgin
would be able to um take it. [ __ ]
virgin. I bet he masturbates over USA.
Is he every day Joe in it? USA is he is
he? I bet he masturbates over my sloppy
seconds. What a sad case. Yeah, Bob. Oh [ __ ]
No, he does it over um Izzy and cuz he
still mentions Izzy, you know, Joe, he's
obsessed. He still um he still mentions
Izzy, the one from six years ago.
And that's what makes me think, and I
know you keep saying that he's in a relationship and
t, but do you know why I think he's a
virgin? Because he literally goes out of
his way to try to prove that you've never had
sex. That's not normal for somebody that
has sex in a relationship is what I'm
trying to say to you. So that's what
makes me think that he he a is either a
virgin, he's definitely a virgin, or b
um he wants you to himself and he
doesn't want to accept the fact that
you've had sex and it's not with him.
Maybe it's that cuz if you actually look
on the comments, he he makes his whole
life trying to prove that you've not had
sex. That's only what a virgin would do.
I know you say that he's in a
relationship and t but I'm telling you straight right
now that literally is what a virgin
would do. Like I'm I'm not even joking.
Like I swear to God I'm not trolling
when I'm saying that. So he must be
gay. Way too heavy. Yeah. But she's got
big you know what. I'm not going to say
it out loud because I'm in a pub. Yeah.
Her teeth is actually [ __ ] up for
somebody that's from America and they
talk about our teeth. My teeth's better
than hers. She looks like rabbit teeth,
bro. She's got [ __ ] rabbit
teeth. Her teeth is not good at all. My
teeth's [ __ ] better. I'm from [ __ ] England. Yeah, man.
Yeah. 3.5. Yeah. Imagine that,
bro. 3.5 thinking that they're better than you.
E. Yeah. She's She looks terrible now.
aged. You know, imagine a [ __ ] 3.5
thinking that they're better than you. Imagine
that. It's crazy about it.
Well, actually, funny enough, when I met
her in London Bridge, I was like, "Oh,
she looks different to her photo." I was
like, "Oh, this is a bit
weird." But then I'm like, "Who am I to
be picky because I don't have anything
else?" And they're from America as well.
So, what do I have to
lose? Like, what have I literally got to
lose here? You know, nothing.
So you just add it to the game really.
You don't have anything to lose.
So got it
online. No, I met her from a cold
approach. I don't use dating apps. No.
I'll show you the approach if you
want. I can't even
fire. One second, bro.
What's it called
again? I actually was drunk, you know.
Actually, what happened? I actually I
actually um had like two drinks, right?
And I was like, let me approach this person from
behind. Let me approach them from
behind. Right. Just for the LS it. And
obviously I was a bit drunk, obviously.
Not drunk drunk, but tipsy. And then
they just stopped and talked and they
offered me their number. So I was like,
"Oh, [ __ ] it." And then they text me the
next day. So I was like, "Oh, I weren't
expecting this." I literally didn't even
I just approached them from behind. I
thought, "Fuck it." It's that day I
bought my first Stone Island and I
bought my new trainers. I thought I just
went out on a Thursday. I thought, "Fuck
it. Just go out with
it." But no approach has ever happened
like that since. Nah. Nah, mate. I've
never even seen it happen to any other
people unless they've actually offered their money. Yeah.
You [ __ ] Do you remember that
one, Joe? Do you remember that one, Joe?
When she called me a [ __ ] he said, "You [Laughter]
[ __ ] You're sick and Christian [Laughter]
I know this is
you. Do you remember it? No. Do you
remember it? I know this is you.
Stop calling yourself a downy. It's no
good for your mental
health. That's bomb. No, I don't think
it is bomb.
But that fridge thing is not a troll.
Like it only cost me pretty much £100
and I need a fridge anyway. So how how
is that mad? You would know if it's
bombed because they'd be encouraging you
to gamble. Anyone that encourages you to
gamble is trolling
you, you know? Like I can spot a mile, you know.
They'll say stuff like go and gamble and
stuff. I can tell my offer someone's Yeah. Oh
[ __ ] Yeah, bud.
I don't know, man. I don't know if I
said I won't shop if I have one.
So, don't really see the point. Whatever
it gets, please.
almost £4. It's gone up. Say again.
Again. So, how much is it going to be in April? Yeah.
Probably in central London they're like5
pound50 in the Weber Spoons.
Just waiting for it.
I'm not telling you my table number.
I'm not letting you know where I am either.
Okay. So, it has to I'm just looking how they do it.
Okay. I don't need drinks, mate. I got
my own money,
matey. I'm okay,
matey. Okay, I see. I see.
So that has to
Which one does Antman have? He told me
which one he
has. Cuz it's Co'sburg.
Yeah. Sure. Yeah.
taking an awful long
time. Wonder if I could tips it with just one
probably. I know. She got me onto the
beer. She definitely did. Thank you. Um
yeah, she she she got me onto the beer.
She was like, "Um, she was like, "Oh,
I'm Australian, so um yeah, I only drink beer." She
said, "I'm going to sit here to be honest.
Yeah, I let me try a beer. Um, let me
try Guinness." And
then I don't speak to her anymore. She
called me unhinged. You know what she
said to me? She was like, "Oh, darling,
you really are unhinged." That's what
she said to me,
"J said, you hate women so much now. How
are you going to get this [ __ ] that
you so desperately
want?" Yeah, that's the good. She was
like, "Um, you really you really unhinged,
darling." Yeah, cuz she was she was
being a [ __ ] She was being a [ __ ] Now,
she turned out to have all these
different issues. Like, she she was
wearing a wig. She was a stripper. Like,
she had issues, man. She did have issues. Ah,
lovely. Yeah. She's like, "Darling, you
really you really are unhinged." Yeah.
No, she had issues, mate. She was
telling me how she like gives this and
gives that and then she wouldn't give me
it and whatever. No, she turned out to
be a [ __ ] She had issues. She had
issues. She did have
issues. I didn't know, bro. When I'm in
these clubs and I'm approaching, I'm
[ __ ] I'm drunk and the lights are
off. I didn't know if she she had a wig.
Yeah, she was she had issues, man. She
had she had issues. She actually did have issues.
She got to the beer. We kissed a lot,
but we just didn't do
anything cuz I've never been on a date
with an Australian before. You should be
interested. I mean, I'm still on a
detox. It's only one, right?
So yeah, no [ __ ] But when you go on the
street, when you go on the street cult,
they all pretend they got boyfriends. So
you can't win, can
you? You can't win, can you,
lad? [ __ ] [ __ ] off. Yeah.
That USA Izzy was a horrible old
[ __ ] You don't think I did buy that
fridge? Well, I'm telling you I [ __ ]
did. I'm telling you I [ __ ] well did. Should
come. What's up
I did buy it, mate. It's from uh
Yeah, Robert D. The Robert D website. I
I did buy
it. Otherwise, I would say I bought it
if I didn't, would I? It's coming on the 27th. Victory
sip. Yeah. It's nice, man. When you eat,
you've always got to wait like 10 15 minutes before drinking.
Definitely. So today I spent
about£13 spoons. It's not bad, is it?
But yeah, it's definitely gone up
because before back in December the beer
was £350. Now it's £3 95. So, um,
yeah. Yeah, I got the black
one. Is there any football playing today?
No, we don't speak off of YouTube. No.
No. Oh, darling, you really are on the
hinge, aren't you, darling?
Why? Because I don't have a fridge.
That's why. Because I don't have a fridge.
Yeah. Yeah. You just know cuz Yeah. on
pitchbug. It's not always curry. It's
not always curry, but yeah.
It's not always curry.
I'm not flush, mate. I'm How do you know
that I'm flush? I'm skint, mate. No, I'm totally
skin. No, all in all, I did need a
fridge, though. All jokes aside, I did
need a fridge.
I did need a fridge cuz of um because to
put drinks in and stuff.
Yeah. But imagine that cult. It's for doing
nothing. It's for doing nothing as
well. But it's special for doing nothing in it.
I think that's the
point. Imagine having to [ __ ] work
for it as well. Just madness, lad. Yeah.
Yeah. That's a lot for not working, is it?
But it can go fast. 3K a month easy.
Like you you can buy a two grand
phone. You can buy a two grand [ __ ]
phone. You know what I
mean? You know, you can [ __ ] book a
holiday that's gone. So I booked to go
to America. That's two grand gone. See,
depends how you look at
it. It's actually like two point. I get
2.9. 2.9. I think it's like
2.9. But there's some people out there
getting like 40 grand a [ __ ] month.
40 [ __ ] K a month. Imagine that. It's
a [ __ ] madness.
Nah, mate. I got my
ways. I've got my ways, lad.
Yeah. Sorry, man. I I I can't tell you
that. Can't tell you that,
buddy. Everyone's out for
themselves. No, you can tell me on here.
You don't need to email
me, bro. It's not from [ __ ] benefits.
Of course it's not from [ __ ]
benefits, man. Use your [ __ ]
brain. Of course it's not from [ __ ]
benefits. It's like um what's his name?
Rice. He tries saying that he
gets 1.8,000 a month from benefits. No
chance. Literally no. No [ __ ] chance. No chance,
mate. There's no chance. So what? You're
in Glasgow and you get paid one 1.8,000
a month. Nah, he's a bullshitter. He's a [ __ ]
bullshitter. No, he's bullshitting,
bro. If he gets that, his housing
benefit. No, there isn't, mate. Trust me.
I'm just drinking this Guinness
here. Anyways, I'm not getting into my
business anyways. Just know that that's
how much I get and that's it. So, end
of end of story.
Yeah, I'm still on the good old Guinness. [ __ ] Yeah,
man. Can't be GIS, mate. Can't be
Guinness. Do you think the Virgin could have
Guinness? Do you reckon the Orington
virgin could have
Guinness? I don't think
so. You want to go job center?
Huh? They've called you in, have
they? [ __ ] hell, man. They've called
you in, have they, buddy?
So, how much do you want to be earning a month,
C? Trust me, once I get this fridge,
that 3k a month will be a
lot. That 3k a month will be a lot,
mate. Trust me. Really?
[ __ ] That's some
madness. There's a woman there. I should
just hold approach on it. Give it a
while. I would give it a whirl. A [ __ ]
women. I hate
him. Oh, darling. You really are
unhinged. Did that make you laugh when
that Australian said that to me, Grezy?
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. I got 2.9
all to myself. Well, I've got 100 pound out
going. Yeah, I've got But even I find that's not
enough. He doesn't have his address.
People have been saying for if you've
got his address, put it on your channel.
You don't need to email me. If you've
got his address, put it on your channel
and I'll go on your channel. You don't
need to email me.
Why did that make you laugh grievy when
she said to me, "Darling, you really are
unhinged." Yeah, electric, but it
doesn't cost that
much. So, I pay 100 and then all the
money to myself, but it still seems to
go. The money still seems to go
somehow. It still seems to
go. You really are unhinged, darling.
That's what she said to me. She said,
"How are you going to get this blowj job
you apparently so desperately need?"
That's what she
said. I don't know, bro. Just my
outgoings are 100 end of like that's it,
bro. I'm not going to get into it. But
yeah, but it does seem to still sort of go.
It does seem to still go for some
reason cuz you go out, you drink, you
spend money. You know, when you go out
drinking, you spend money. You know what I'm [Music]
saying? So, [ __ ] this Guinness, man.
What the [ __ ] shits, man? I think the
breakfast has kicked in.
Nope. Why would I need to sign in and
out? I'm not in a
HMO. Why would mate, you don't know where I
am? Nah, not my life because I'm used
to, you got to understand, I'm used to
having thousands and thousands and
thousands. Mate, listen. Okay, I'll give
you an example, Joe. Right.
So, say you get three grand a month. Yeah.
Listen, say you get three grand a month
and you want to buy a Samsung Galaxy
Fold phone that's £1,700. That's all
half the money gone already. Say you
needed a new phone or you wanted to book
to go to America or Australia. Your money's
gone. So, unless you save. Yeah. I mean,
you would save in it obviously, but
that's what I'm saying. It can go very
fast. I'm used to having thousands. I've
had like £6,000 in cash. So, to
me, you no matter what money you get,
you you um adjust to
it. How long does that phone last you?
It doesn't matter how long it lasts you,
man. It's a new one will come out. So,
you're miss I think you're missing the
point. And then maybe the next month you
might want to go to America and then the
next month you want to go somewhere else.
So, I think you would need about I've
already explained why I didn't pay it.
I'm not I'm not explaining it
again, but I'm using that as an example.
So, that's why I'm I'm finding other
ways to make money cuz even that's even
I need extra money. I spent £300
yesterday and I didn't even leave my [ __ ]
area. I didn't even leave my [ __ ] area,
mate. How mad is that? £300 like that,
These are [ __ ] [ __ ] man.
Yeah. Yeah, I get what you mean.
But still, I wouldn't pay that much for
a phone anyways. That was just an
example. I would never pay [ __ ] that
much for a phone. Can't justify it. The
cost I'm paying for oil is 300.
Yeah, 300 pound maybe.
Sorry, man. I was I'm having a
[ __ ] Have I lost all my pit money?
Nope. And I get more money than you will
ever have. More money than you will ever
have. You special
leader. Sorry, man. No, they haven't
found me. Sorry, man. I'm having a [ __ ]
They will never find me, bro. They'll
never know where I am.
That's a good
thing. And they're not trollers. They're
spastics as well. I'm still on the
[ __ ] toilet, bro.
No. I lost all my pit gambling, mate. If
I lost all my pit gambling, I'd still
have more money than you. But anyways,
let's just read the joke
from So what do they do then, Joe? They
save up for it, right?
Yeah, they save up for it, don't they,
Joe? No, I told you I'm done with it for
a couple of weeks. Do you not listen?
You have brain damage. I said I
literally don't care about it anymore.
I'm just having this beer. I'm only having one
beer. I'm not telling you exactly how
much I get. We're not Why are we even
talking about this? Why are we even
talking about this, bro?
Yeah, I can't get a credit card, so
that's what I'm up
to. Why are we talking about this? Stop this,
bro. Just took this beer and I'm [ __ ] off.
Simple. Don't know why. Just fighting one beer.
Yeah. Yeah. I told you I'm not I don't
care about the cold
approaching. I don't care about anymore. It's
boring. It's very boring.
Joining, you really are going to
um having loads and loads of money
doesn't affect your credit score. You
down. See what I mean with these people?
They're such downies in this community.
They don't know anything. Credit score
is not to do with how much money you
have and you [ __ ] [ __ ] There's
literally people that's got literally
way less money than me and their
credit's better. Do you not understand
how credit score
works? Well, these people really are
dowies. This is a Dowy community. I
think it's the it's the perfect um Yeah,
it's actually the perfect um name for
this community, a Dowy community.
Uh, I pay my bills on time all the time.
All my bills are paid on time. I
probably paid my bills, my internet
bill, my SIM
bill. But yeah, I would never get um
I'll never get another phone contract ever again. The door
knocking in just no
money. Moving on. Anyways, changing topic. Moving
on. Moving on. [ __ ] boring. Boring
community. Same conversation. Same
atmosphere every day. I'm skin. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm skin. Yeah. You're just you're
just being silly when you call me skin
because everyone knows I've got more
money than anyone on this
community. But you still call me skin.
It's a matter
today. H the same reason everyone thinks
that you're a Downey. That's why
Kimberly, the same reason everybody
thinks that you're a Downey. They told
me everybody says, "Yeah, this account
on YouTube, this Kimberly Jax is a
Downey." Yeah. Anyways, I'm banning
these people. I'm not entertaining these
people. Anyways, these spastics, these
idiots. These get some genuine people in
here, man. They [ __ ] up the whole chat.
These Downies, I swear to God, they [ __ ]
up the whole chat. These little YouTube
downey virgins. I swear to
God. sad for people in their 40s that
got no money. That's all these people
are in this community. It's people in
their 40s. They got no money. They got
nothing going for themselves. Why
they're on here every day? It's why
they're on YouTube every day. Like,
think about it. How many people do you
think Yeah. have tried finding out where
I am? Think about it. How many people do
you think have tried finding out where I am?
Oh [ __ ] Why the other people coming out?
Why is that lock? Yeah, man.
7%. Why do these people call people skin
every day, Joe? It must be because
they're skinned themselves, isn't it? I
think it's because they're skinned
themselves on benefits. Cuz I remember
being like I remember like when I used
to be like these people, bro, like where
the money didn't really last and
stuff. No. Try
again. No, it's not. Try again, buddy.
You will never know where I am.
Oh, you will never ever ever know where I
am. Try again, buddy.
Yeah. No, these people are so desperate
to know where I am, and they'll never
know where I am. And even if they did
know where I am, they still wouldn't do
anything about it. That's what I mean
with these mongos. They're [ __ ]
idiots. They're absolute [ __ ]
idiots. They don't know anything. They
really don't know
anything. They really, really, really
don't know anything. They're suchies. I
swear to God.
Such little childish little downies. I swear to God.
Yeah. I spend too much time alone. Story
of your life, buddy. [ __ ] So,
man. Yeah. Story of your life, man.
Story of your life. E, Mr. Loner on YouTube every
day. I know, bro. Story of your
life. That's why you're on YouTube every day.
E, that's why you're on YouTube every
day. You prove me right, man. You prove
me right. Look, I'm sat here in a pub
drinking Guinness. You people are sat at
home. Sat at home.
Literally like, "No, no, no. It's the
truth, though. You're sat at
home [ __ ] doing nothing.
Mad." Yeah, of course you are, man. Of
course you are. Of course you [ __ ] well
are. Yeah, of course you are,
man. I need to go in a minute anyways.
Let's finish this beer. [Music] Yeah. Yeah.
I could send some approaches right about
now. Nah, I can't be [ __ ] mate. I
bothered. This phone's going to die in a minute.
Y charge. I know. I don't.
Bro, stop talking about
yourself. It's no good for the mental health
deed. Nah, bro. I didn't cuz I didn't
think I didn't think I I didn't plan to have a
beer. Stop calling yourself a [ __ ]
It's no good for the mental health for
membrane. Yeah. Stop calling yourself a
[ __ ] It's not good, man. Stop talking about
yourself. Yeah. It's only
self-reflection with you losers. You
don't bother no
one. This is what I mean, Joe. You say
that these people psychologically [ __ ]
with your head, but they
don't. Like, I'm definitely not
psychologically [ __ ] with. They
definitely don't bother me. They don't
put any anxiety in me. They don't put
any fear in me. They don't do any any of
them things, bro. They don't do any of
them things. And guess what I can do that they
can't? I can show my face. These people
can't. Oh [ __ ] cuz they're too
ugly. I need I need a [ __ ] I need a
um I need a shave and a haircut at some
point. I can do something they can't show my
face cuz all fat and
ugly. I was um expecting people to
actually look at me when I said that
there. [ __ ] that. It's all good,
man. too. It's muddy.
Now, look, this is what I'm trying to
say to you, right? Oops. These
people there. These people don't
psychologically [ __ ] with anyone's head.
Not in the slightest. Look, I'm sat here
drinking a Guinness. No care in the
world. Not insecure one bit about my
financial circumstances. Not insecure one
bit. Not um bye-bye now. Not um No, I
don't live there. You will never know
where I live. You will never know ever
ever know where I
live. And and look, show my
face. Not a car in the world. Like, am I
supposed to be psychologically [ __ ]
[ __ ] with my head? I don't
understand. Did you say that these
people [ __ ] with your head
psychologically? They don't [ __ ] with my
head. Not one little
bit. It's a good word you use though.
It's a good word you used. It's a good
used. Yeah. At least I can show my face unlike
you. Yeah, man. At least I can show my
face though. Unlike
you. No, they didn't. No, they didn't.
And also I get things also another thing
is I get things delivered to different
addresses. Sometimes I get stuff
delivered to my mom's address, sometimes
I get um things delivered to that
address. You don't know where I live.
That's why every single time, right?
That's why every single time, right, you
say, "Oh, I'm coming to Elbert Square."
I tell you to come because I'm not
there. I tell you literally to come
because I'm not there.
And that's why I stay live and you never
come because I'm not
there and you have no video of you doing
doing any knocks and stuff. You know
what I'm saying? Yeah. I might get stuff
delivered to that address just like I
get stuff delivered to my mom's address,
but you don't know where I live. You
don't know where I live. It's the same
as having a a [ __ ] PO [ __ ]
box. Do you know what I'm saying?
on my Amazon account. There's two
addresses. My mom's address and there's
that address. I either deliver it to
like I delivered something to my mom
yesterday, she should get it today. Or I
deliver it to that
address. Yeah. They're the two addresses
that are on on on my Amazon account as
well. So, I either deliver it to that
address or that address. But you don't
know where I live. You literally do not
know where I live. Yeah. They might have
told you that something's been delivered
there. Yeah, just like stuff gets
delivered to my mom's
address. That's That's the address I've always
used. So, yeah. Try again, buddy. You
will never ever know where I live. Thank
you. I need a hair. I need a haircut, bro.
Yeah. But yeah, man. It's like I can
show my face. I'm not bothered. You know
what I'm saying?
You will never ever ever ever ever know where I
live. Ever ever ever ever ever know
where I live. And you will never
psychologically [ __ ] with my head. And
even if you did know where I live, you
still wouldn't do anything. So get a
grip. Get a grip. So
yeah, what I find so mad is you try to
find out where people live yet you don't
even know where I live. But why are you
even trying to do that? Because even if
you know where someone lives, right?
You're you're still not going to go on
their door. You're still not going to do
anything. So why would you even be
bothered where the [ __ ] someone lives or
where somebody doesn't
live? Because you're never going to do anything
ever. So what's the whole like obsession
and stalking? It's weird,
man. Proper proper
weird. I know they would never have
confirmed anything. The only thing that
they would have confirmed is something
has been delivered to that address.
Yeah, that's what they would have been.
That's what they would have confirmed.
So many autistic stalkers on this Downey
community. I swear to God, they're such
spastics. Honestly, they are such
spastics. Desperate to find out where people
live. But you are the ma. Stop calling
yourself a ma. You are the ma. Get
yourself gone, you repeating bastard.
But with these autistic [ __ ] weird
weirdo weasels, right? Why would they
even want to know where you're living
when they're never going to do anything?
Never. That's what I don't understand. It's
weird. That's how you know they got
autism. Proper proper
autism. Remember they used to do the
same thing to Monty, man, as
well. Weirdos, man. And you are the M.
Stop calling yourself a
M. Sad [ __ ] repeating bastards. Yeah.
Yeah, man. These people got severe
disabilities on this community. Severe
disabilities, severe goodness. No wonder
they talk about other people every day
living their sad little lives on here.
You know, it's
mad. That's actually
Right. This is B. Um. Yeah. [Music]
No. This bank as well.
The Bank of England,
bro. You are
m stars. And that that. Let me
see. Yeah, I get I get things delivered
to that address just like I get things
delivered to my mom's address. But you
don't know where I
live. Yeah. What do you mean? What the
[ __ ] Why are you so ass about where
people live? I don't even live
there. Stalkers. Absolute stalkers,
lad. Absolute stalkers. I don't live
there. If you really really think Why
don't go on that door then? Go on the
door. Simple. go on the door if if
that's what you
think. You know what I'm saying? Just
like I get things delivered to my mom's
address and I get things delivered to
that address. They're the two addresses
that I use. One of the two. Like I said
something to my mom the other day.
Simple. So it's a [ __ ] mini fridge.
You will never know where I live ever.
Yeah. And if you actually go on it,
you'll actually realize that as well.
You will never know where I live. Never.
Never. And that's the that's the fun of it,
bro. You know what I'm
saying? To protect my uh real dress.
Anyways, we're not talking about this, you little
weirdos. Yeah, we're not talking about
this anyways. It's weird. It's autism.
We're not talking about this, bro. If
you think I live there, that's on you.
Good for you. You can go on the door
then when I'm live and you'll see that
I'm not there. End of weirdos, man.
Absolute [ __ ] weird. I've never known
people so obsessed, right?
Yeah. Where someone lives. These people
have got autism. I'm telling you, these
people, they're proper mongos on this
community. Sorry, my phone's on 2%, bro.
It's going to die in a bit. You people
in this community, you're proper proper
proper [ __ ] mongos. You're so
obsessed with other people's lives.
Like, because you ain't got a life your
own. You're weirdos. Absolute weirdos.
Listen, go on the door and you will see who lives there. You
know, mini fridge around London. It's
not around London. It's the same place
in my [ __ ] area. You [ __ ] little
[ __ ] You little [ __ ] Who's that? Oh
[ __ ] Anyways, we're not talking about this anymore.
Anyways, you you little autistic people.
You little weirdos. Little autistic
weirdos. They ain't got a life.
My phone's on 1%. I'll go back live when
I come back. Just finishing off this beer.
Anyways, the lies are getting out of
hand. Yeah, you need to stop your lies
as well. You know, I I knew you was a I
knew you was a Yeah, you can ring who
you want, bro. You don't know where I am.