Just another machine that got stuck
on. He is very lucky. This time I did
not put a chair through that [ __ ]
machine. Next time I come in, obviously
we do it every month. 100 pound, 50,
whatever. And the same thing happens
again. I'm going to put a chair through
that [ __ ] machine. And he knows it as
well. It was right next to the
[ __ ] the house and that is it.
[ __ ] hell. I told him. He said, "Oh,
don't worry." I said, "Be [ __ ] 15
minutes where he's continuously winding him up
and so don't tell me about how you paid
out. I'm showing you and I'm [ __ ]
telling you that I've just put 100 pound
in this machine and nothing. I'm telling
you and I'm showing you. I don't care
what you say that you out. I'm showing
you my challenge.
[ __ ] moves the whole [ __ ] day. I
don't know how [ __ ] Joe [ __ ] does
it, bro. I don't know how Joe [ __ ]
does it literally the whole day,
bro. And that was And that was literally
the least amount I've gambled. I I don't
even [ __ ] do it much anymore. I just
thought, let me just try a quick
hundred. And it's the same [ __ ] The
same rigged joke. The same rigged joke.
Even if it's 100 quid, what the [ __ ] I
would do like one pound
spins. And I cut the video at the end as
well. I had to I had to give it a cheeky
spit. You know how it is. It literally never
changes. It literally never changes,
does it? Oh my god. Imagine that. Having the same
conversation. The same conversation. Imagine
that. The same conversation. Doesn't
matter what the amount of money is. It's [ __ ] crazy,
bro. [ __ ] annoying, bro. [ __ ]
me. I don't know how this Joe guy does
it. It's [ __ ] the
press. I had to send a [ __ ] um an
envelope up. So, I thought, let me just
try quickund, you know, being bred and
all. And it's the same story. It
literally is the same old Rick sad song.
It's the same
story. But that's me for the month.
Anyways, what is the
day? This is a madness, bro. Stop
calling yourself a n. It's not good for the mental
health. Where have we posted it to?
Let's make sure we got the right
one. You have to post something. So, I
thought, let me just try try kick a quick
100, right? Where is it posted
to? It's the same side.
Yeah. Same old
S. That cost me £8 to [ __ ] deliver
that. It's the same old S. Yeah.
Wow. It just goes to show that the
amount of money is irrelevant, which is
what I've been saying. Good little
tester. Well, the machines are still
really still can't get a little
tester. At least it got my spit, though.
I love it when it gets my
spit. So, [ __ ] annoying. I don't know
how people how people still [ __ ] do
it, bro. And don't break the machines.
[ __ ] wire me up. And it was only
fucking£100, which obviously to like a
lot of you is is a lot, but I mean
anything in it, man. You know what I'm
saying? And it's still [ __ ] whines
[ __ ] out of you. Wines [ __ ] out you. It
does. It's [ __ ] annoying, man. God is
so annoying. I mean like shouting down
the street and all
sorts. The rigged as a
[ __ ] It's literally as rigged as a
[ __ ] Literally it [ __ ] well
is. Oh, I'm I'm showing you I paid out
today and I said I'm [ __ ] telling y
that what's happening when you put your
money on the table. And that's exactly
why I don't do it
anymore. And that's exactly why I don't
do it anymore, buddy.
That is exactly why I stay clear from it
because it's the same conversation.
Doesn't matter whether it's in
November, December, January, February,
March, April. It's the same
story. It's the same story. E next door
to 400 numbers. That's what it does. It
likes to go next door to numbers to wind
people up. That's how people get
addicted. You see, that's how people get
addicted to these
things. Obviously, I'm B, but you know what I'm
saying? She was rigged as a [ __ ]
Madness doesn't even get funny anymore,
bro. Doesn't even become funny
anymore. [ __ ] madness, brother.
[ __ ] the whole [ __ ] Hey, don't
even if it's under
mad. You're so lucky I did not put a
[ __ ] chair through that [ __ ] machine, bro.
Imagine that. And it was only
£100. And it was only £100 as well.
Imagine that. Only
£100. It's [ __ ]
annoying. Yeah, spoon is the worst thing
you could do, bro. It's worse than
smashing it up, to be fair. Oh [ __ ]
bro. How people
stay stay calm,
bro. Man, that's annoying.
It's annoying as
[ __ ] but lots of people seem to stay
calm. I don't know, but it's so [ __ ]
annoying. I had to post something and it
was right by bookies, so I thought, let
me just try 100 pound
[ __ ] Yeah, I'm not put no more in.
You're bad, bro. I shouldn't have even
put that 100 pound in to be fair. [ __ ]
annoying. How did that even [ __ ] happen, bro? Mad, bro. What?
The machines are [ __ ] boring as
well. Them machines are [ __ ] boring
as well. They bore the [ __ ] death out of me,
mate. Them machines are boring, too. My
Yeah, the machines are dead boring.
They're [ __ ] boring,
mate. They're [ __ ] dead boring.
divide. I don't know how people could still do
that. It's such a buzz kill.
Literally such a [ __ ] buzz kill.
boring. [ __ ] bored me, mate. [ __ ] bors
me. [ __ ] bald me, man. Same old
story. Whenever you put your money on the table.
Oh, put your money on the
table. At least it was only £100, I
guess. Madness on it.
make the same mistake [ __ ] last month.
got [ __ ] under got [ __ ] sto an
escort and [ __ ] popped his vard
popped his [ __ ]
virginity going to do that but drop 500
pound and just give it to the virgin why
he stopped being such a YouTube virgin
all his life [ __ ]
virgin you know them things
Yeah. Hold on a sec.
[ __ ] balls me. It does.
The machines are [ __ ] boring. So
boring. Them machines are so boring,
man. It's the same story with them.
That's why I don't play him
anymore. Just thought, yeah, try 100 pound
whatever. [ __ ] bs me, mate.
Machines, they actually b me. I'm not
even joking. [ __ ]
boring. Something so rigged in my
life. Oh my
god. Next door. Next door. Next door.
door. No bonus. No bonus. No
bonus. What the actual [ __ ] So [Music]
fixed. Pause me.
What about you people [ __ ] me?
Yeah. Stock in the weekend. madness.
Probably going to save money to be honest.
[ __ ] the question is it so
rigged. They are so
rigged. Unbelievably [ __ ] rigged. Oh my god. Is
that [ __ ] dead?
It's the same old story with that mach.
them. They are [ __ ] boring.
Money down the
table. The [ __ ]
table. [ __ ] dead boring, man. [ __ ]
boring. Dead boring. Yeah.
Balls me, mate. [ __ ] bored me.
Dead ball. [ __ ] dead ball.
Jordan's the whole day
there. Yeah, I've been the whole day. What is
What makes me Hold on. Hold on. So, what
makes me an
incel? Am I an incel? What? Because I
know liquid men's asses. What the [ __ ]
is this guy talking about?
I'm incel. What? What? Because I don't
lick women's asses. Do you know the definition
of what an incel
is? These people in this community
really are downies, bro. Just like this cult.
Yeah, we'll wait for him to come on and
we'll go. This is what I mean. Why do these
people come on here, lick your ass in
your live stream, and then talk [ __ ]
behind your back and they always get
caught out doing it as well. They're
[ __ ] weirdos on this community, bro.
I swear to God.
But because I don't lick women's asses
and I'm not a white knight, that makes
me an incel. But I don't even go out and
approach anymore. How does that even
make sense? You people are the incelss. You just
self-reflect. This community is weird,
bro. I swear to God, it's weird. We'll
wait though. We'll wait. We will wait.
I know lick women's asses. That makes me
an incel. Okay, I'm an insult, but I'm the biggest
inel. Just like I got no life experience
at 27. Okay,
bro. Whatever you
say. There's no point arguing with these
[ __ ] bongos on this community. You
see, there's literally no point in it.
Literally no point in it. Yep, that's me. Sure
is. Yeah, this cold guy is a snake. How
am I an incel? What? What the [ __ ] What
makes me an incel? What? Because I don't lick women's
asses and I don't sit there defending
them all day. What the [ __ ] How does
that make me a [ __ ]
incel? Because I know what people are
like because I've got life experience,
man. You don't even make any [ __ ]
sense. I don't even cold approach
anymore, you know? But again, these same
people that are calling you incelss are
the same people that don't leave the
house. That's what you got to understand
with this community, you
know. That's what you have to understand with this
community. Just uh two accounts, my main
account and this account to go live on
because it doesn't let me go live on my
main account because it says it's
connected to too many
Streamyards. Yeah, I lost £100 on the
machine earlier. I just spat on it cuz I
had to go post something off. I was,
"Oh, let me try a little£100 in the
bookies." Literally was winding me up,
bro. It's still widening me up. It's why
I don't [ __ ] with it anymore. That's why
I don't do it anymore, bro. Because of
this exact reason. It's [ __ ]
annoying. God, it is so [ __ ] annoying, mate. You
know, so [ __ ] annoying. Is it 100
pound as well?
Only£100, but uh it's [ __ ] up, man. What the
[ __ ] It's not a lot of money to me, mate. But
still, yeah, it was £100. Not a lot of
money to me, but that's not the point. It's
annoying. I'm not I'm not going out
approaching or drinking for a couple of
weeks. I'm on a detox cuz I just can't
be bothered. So, yeah, just call that
the 100 pound you was going to use to go out with.
you would have spent more going out but
yeah see it as that even though we got
the cinema on Friday but still not going
to come to that so yeah see it as that in it
really the 100 pounds not a lot of money 150
is yeah it is a fool's game and it
creates mood swings as well spat on the
machine like I was so tempted bro to put
a chair through it and one of one of
these days I'm going to do it even
though I don't do it much anymore
Yeah, it was only £100. I thought I'd
just try £100. I'm not doing it again
this month at least. Trust me, I don't
do it anymore. But that was just a one
off. So, it's annoying. It is so [ __ ]
annoying. Creates mood swings, anger. It
does. It [ __ ] drives you. It was
driving me mad for like 40 minutes. It's so
annoying. It's so annoying. Like, I
can't explain it, man. It's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
And that's how you know it's not about
the money because £100 to me is
nothing. 100 pound to me is nothing. To
me it's nothing. Yeah. So that that
should tell you like it's a fresh month
basically. You've just lost £100 which
is not even 1% of your money and it
still gets you like that. That should
tell you a lot man. There you go. You
learned with £100 this month. Yay. So
yeah. Yeah. I don't I'm not going out
drinking for a couple of weeks. Can't
believe I'm not bothering with women. I
just can't be bothered with
it. Boring, man. I'd rather just chill
and sort some stuff out. I'm not going
out. Even though I really could deal
with a Guinness today, but I don't need
to go get help for my gambling. And I'm
not addicted. I've got all my bills
paid. I've got more than enough money.
I'm good. I'm sweet. I don't need help for
it. I don't need help for it. Look, I
just had £100 like an hour ago. If I was
addicted, I would keep doing it and
doing it and doing it and doing it and
it, but I'm not going to keep doing it
and doing it and doing it and doing it
cuz I'm more addicted to
it. Trust me, I fancy goodness today,
but we're on a detox. Trust me, £100. If
you lose that £100 in a month, for a
whole month, that's
good. That's good. 100 pound for the
whole month. I get 3K a month. You think
I care about [ __ ]
£100? Yeah, that was weeks ago. 200.
That was [ __ ] over a month
ago. Yeah, that was over a month ago,
man. Times have
changed. Yeah, it was 200 pound. That
was over a month ago. I don't do that
[ __ ] anymore. The only thing I do every
week is like a 20 pound football bet. I
do like a 20 pound football bet, but I
don't even know where I would do that
now because I'm banned from all the
local bookies. So, I don't even know
where I'd even do football bets anymore. I just
do No, I never was. I just used to lose
and it would give me mood swings and
[ __ ] But I will still do a football bet
every week. But it's uh it's it's where
where are you going to [ __ ] do it
now? They all kind of know me. There's
one place. But yeah, I get 3K a month. I
don't give a [ __ ] about losing 100
quid. I just sent my mom a [ __ ]
Mother's Day card with money in
it. Simple. You know what I'm
saying? Why? How much do you get a month
for you to say £100 is a lot? How much
do you get a
month? But trust me, think about it like
this. Yeah. Think about it logically.
Yeah, this is the only way to look at
it. Even though it is still Monday, like
think about it. Yeah. If you went out,
right, Friday or Saturday or Thursday
and you went out drinking and that, you
would have spent over £100 hearing, I've
got a boyfriend having like just think
about it like that and learn your
lesson. Like that's the only thing you
can do. Just think about it like that.
Like you would have spent more hearing
about fake boyfriends, women with
attitude, and you'd be [ __ ] hung over
for like two days. Like just think about
it like that. Yeah. You go cinema on a
Friday, it's only going to cost you
20£25. You get three grand a month. So
if you get three grand a month,
then I mean, how is £100 a
lot? Three grand a month. That's how
much I get.
But I need I want to I want to get
myself in front. This is why I'm not
going out for a couple of weeks. I need
to save. I need to do things where it's
going to get me more money. I need to
think about the future now, man. Like,
[ __ ] this country. [ __ ] the women in
this country. I don't give a [ __ ] about
it. I need to start really thinking
about. And after I've got everything
sorted and whatever, we got the ball
rolling, we can go out and have a drink.
It's not a problem, you know? But until
then, bro, we need at least two weeks
off of it.
You need at least two weeks off of it,
bro. At least the
minimum. Yeah. I can't be bothered with
the women in this country. I don't
really care about it anymore, man.
So, so if you get three grand a month,
then I got free I get three grand a
month. I got £100 outgoings. That's
electric phone bill, internet bill
done. So, I've got all that disposable
money. So, I'll be saving a
lot. Trust me, I'll be saving a lot, man. All right. So, anyways.
Yeah. Yeah. That's good, man. That
pre I've got my ways. It's called having
brain. It's called having a brain, mate.
That's what it's called, having a
brain. you know, bit of this, bit of
that. Yeah. Very, very
easy. So, £100 is not, you
know, it's not the end of the world, is
it? And I've got designer clothes. I got
my passport done. Let's get my passport done last
week. Maybe I do or maybe I
don't. Maybe I do or maybe I don't.
Yeah, I had to get my passport last
month for that. That cost a bit. But
this month, got
no pay my bills. All I need to do is
gas, electric, and I'm
done. All my bills are paid.
But yeah, I can't be bothered going out
talking to women anymore. It's [ __ ]
boring, mate. I need to go to my mom's
and get my clothes as well. I just can't
be bothered to do it.
probably going to go back there, but at
some point I will. Weather's changing, but yeah.
Yep. How do you get free grand a
month? I know, bro. I
know. Yeah, my phone got cut off ages
ago, but I just use it with the
Wi-Fi. But I just use it with the Wi-Fi, don't
I? I just use it with the Wi-Fi. I went
to post um a Mother's Day card for my
mom. Put some money in it. Then there
was um William there was a bookies near
the Yeah, but my phone's been cut off,
but I just use the Wi-Fi, so it's just
the same. When I go out, I just use
Wi-Fi. I'll get another phone, but I
don't want a contract phone. So, yeah, I
So, yeah, that's the thing. But what I
was saying is
um what I was saying is basically that
um yeah, there was the bookies and I
thought, let me just try
£100, which to be honest, man. Look, I'm
not going to go out drinking or
approaching for two weeks. So, I lose
the £100 or you're actually saving
money. But I'll do a football bet on
I'll do a football bet on the weekend.
That's 20. Yeah, you're still going to
be saving money, bro. Yeah, I don't do
these 150s no more, bro. [ __ ]
that.£100 a m a month maximum on the
machines and then that is me
done. That is literally me done,
bro. I lost a fucking£100.
You actually think a £100 is a lot of
money? You You actually think £100 is a
lot of money? You couldn't even go on a
night? Well, when I go out again
approach and I'm going to do Thursday
Saturday. I'm going to do Thursday. I'm
going to do Saturday. But yeah, I'm
going to do Thursday. I'm going to do
Saturday and I'm gonna Thursday,
Saturday. And I'm going
to And I'm going Thursday, Saturday.
Saturday and I'm going to um Thursday,
to spend no more than £100 drinking cuz
I'm going to free
drink £100 is not a lot of money, mate.
Do you know how much mate? I spent about
£400 last month on my passport, drinking,
food. It's not a lot of money, mate. Not to
me. Not really, mate. Am I on the
spectrum? Stop asking stupid
questions cuz you get stupid
answers. Have a word with yourself. Am I on the spectrum? You
wish. I assume you're asking me that
because I'm on this [ __ ] community.
Why the [ __ ] would I be on the
spectrum? But you know what I'm saying,
Stephen? You go out Saturday, mate.
Friday, Saturday, they'll say you got
boyfriends, so you might as well just
lost 100 in the machine. But I don't do
these 150s anymore. [ __ ] that. That's
too much. That's why I just I do 100. No, not
150. Can't just I can't believe I used
to do that, bro.
[ __ ] What a waste of [ __ ]
money. What a waste of money, bro.
I come across a special. How would I
special? Yeah, I come across a special,
mate. I'm more intelligent than you will
ever be. How do I come across this
special? Yeah. Can go out, no money, get
free drinks. Yep. But like I said, bro,
when I go out Thursday, Saturday, I'm
not going to spend more than £100 on
them two days. I'm going to spend like40
each. I'm just going to pre-drink, get a
bottle. That's it, bro. And the thing
is, Stephen, right, for me to go out
again, I need to get my haircut. I'm not
wasting money getting my haircut just to
get the same [ __ ] in this country. [ __ ]
that. Not for a while, bro. Not for a [ __ ]
while. Cuz it's pointless. It's [ __ ]
pointless. It's expensive getting a haircut nowadays,
bro. It's [ __ ] bro. It's
[ __ ] I think you come across as a bit
special to be honest, saying£100's a lot
of money. I think that's a bit special.
Don't know about you, but I think that's
that that sounds a bit special to
me. How can a £100 be a lot of money?
D. Yeah. I'll never be as special needs
as you, mate. I'll never I will never be
as special needs as you. It's It's funny
because you call me special needs,
right? But all you people do on on this
community is repeat yourselves every
day. You are special needs. You people
in this community are special needs just
like your skin as well. Self projection.
Yep. You people are special needs,
mate. Yeah, you are special needs. Stop
talking about yourself like
that. It's not nice to talk about
yourself like that, man. It's not good
for the mental
health. Yeah, I know. It's okay to have special needs.
Yeah, I just lost £100 on the machine
grievy and [ __ ] apparently £100 a lot of
money to um
Kimberly. She says it's a lot of money. Oh, [ __ ]
hell. It's a lot of money,
eh? She said it's a lot of money.
Yeah. Yeah. We're having none of it,
mate. The machines are [ __ ]
boring. [ __ ] boring,
mate. You still got anxiety,
Greasy. I love how these people ask you
how you make money. Like you would
actually tell them how you make money,
Grezy. I just sent my mommy a card,
Grezy, via the
post. Yeah, I sent my mommy a card,
Grezy. Yeah, when I make funny noises, I
make them intentionally.
And nah, you've got special
needs because it is boring. No, I'm
repeating myself because it is boring.
That machines are
boring, you know. That tells me No, that
tells me that I just repeated myself
four times cuz I just said it again. It
tells me that I've just repeated myself
four times. That's what it tells me. Do
you know the definition of special
needs? Special needs is what Monty man
has. It's what Laur has. It's what Sha
has. They've got special needs. Not
me. Not me,
matey. Could have got a [ __ ] with
that 100 pound we could have got a [ __ ]
[ __ ] I'm just looking at my penis
now. Quite nice. E.
Yeah. It's quite nice, man.
Yeah. I've got a different form. I've
never had special needs in my life. Go
look in the mirror. You'll see the
biggest special leader yourself. I will
never have special needs as much as you
[ __ ] people. You little low lives.
Never as much as you people. Yeah. You'd
rather keep the money. That sounds like
a good um idea,
Grezy. Yeah, but like I said, I'm not
going out for a couple of weeks, so I'm
good, bro. No drinking, no approaching.
Just on a detox, eh? I'm going to go KFC soon, I think.
Yep. Got good old KFC. Uh
They ask you how you get money. Like you
would tell these people how you get
money. This dy grassing community. [ __ ] hell.
Like say you sold weed. Yeah. Say you
was a drug dealer. Yeah. You think you'd
actually come on YouTube and tell people
that you sell
drugs? Think about it. You'd actually
come on here and tell people that you
sold drugs as an
example. Or say you clean houses. Do you
think you'd actually come on here and
tell people what you [ __ ] do knowing
these jealous little grasses and what
they're like? Come on, man. It's it's
it's Ricky doing
this. Am I saying I'm a drug dealer? No.
I'm using it as an example. You will
never know what I
do. And that's the good thing about it.
Yep. Is that you'll never know where I live. Yeah.
Apparently, Tram said, I don't know if
it was the real Tram, he says he knows
where I live. I said, "You don't know
where I live." And he said he's going to
send posters. And you know, I said,
"Grezy, I said, "Why don't you send
4,000 posters? Make it even more fun
because nobody cares because a you don't
know where I live, and b even if you did
know where I live, um, literally nobody
cares. Like literally nobody would give
a [ __ ] that the whole street no one
even [ __ ] talks to [ __ ] people. So
I told him to crack on, mate. Nobody
gives a [ __ ] You don't psychologically
[ __ ] with anybody's head. You're just a little keyboard
warrior. And that's it. That's what I
said. I don't know if it was the real
him, but I said it's in this
anyways. And another thing is I always
see the postman.
So if I go and see the postman and every
single every single letter obviously is
is sized exactly the same I will I will
physically take it off
him and then when they call the police
then you know the police will know what
these people YouTube are trying to do. I
see the post man all the time as well.
So you'd never win even if even if it
got out there you'd never
win. Yeah. And I've got more brains than
you will ever
have. And I've got more brains than you
will ever have. Because if you people
what what I don't understand with you
people, if you weren't disabled and
you're this and you're that, you
wouldn't be on here every day. I I stand
by what I say. You would not be on this
[ __ ] down community every day. If you
had something in your lives, you
wouldn't be on here. You literally would
not be on your job. You would not be on
the usual. I'm telling you, you would
not be on the usual. You would go and
have a life. I'm on a detox. I'm [ __ ]
not doing anything for a little
bit. Um, you people, you and other
people, you wouldn't even be on here.
You would not even be on here,
mate. I would never have special needs
like you people.
Yeah. It's like when you um when you
people come on here every day and you
call people skint, you're
skintselves. Self projection.
Yeah. When you come here and you say,
"Oh, you're skin. You're skint." It's
cuz you skint yourselves. You're on that £300 a
month. Yeah. I don't have special needs,
mate. I really hope so, too. I don't
have special needs. You do have special
needs. You're the one that I'm special
needs. Yeah, I get more money than you.
I get more money than you. I have much a
much better life than you, but I'm the
one that's got special
needs. Doesn't make any sense. I get
more money than you. I have a better
life than you. But I'm the one that's
got special needs and I'm reading
everything that you're writing. You are
the special needs one. You're a window
licker. You're a [ __ ] window licker. You're like
h your [ __ ] tongue off the window.
You window licker. That's why you can't
join the [ __ ] hangouts cuz you are
the special needs window
licker. That's what you are, bro. Yeah.
for your special needs. Stop licking
them windows. [ __ ]
[ __ ] You keep coming on fake Monty
accounts. I know it's
you. Like I know I know I mean I know
it's not Monty man. Why do you keep
coming on fake [ __ ] Monty man accounts? But
yeah, maybe sort your own special needs
out first, then come back to
me. [ __ ] losers.
Yeah, I don't I don't need help for
gambling, mate. I'm not addicted.
And there's no way you get freek a
month. If you think a100 pound is a lot
of money, there's no way you get freek a
month. [ __ ] no
way. No [ __ ] way, mate.
Yeah. There you go.
Yeah, you people are special
needs. You can't even show your [ __ ]
face [ __ ] out of the [ __ ] D. Yeah, you
[ __ ] self projecting because you got
nothing to your empty lives.
That's the crux of it. You've got
nothing to your [ __ ] empty lives. So you
come in and
selfject to try to get other people to
feel as down as
you. I keep repeating, mate. You are special
needs. You are special needs. So what
repeating yourself means that you've got
special needs. Really?
Okay. You are special needs. Stop
calling yourself special needs.
You know, this is the most disabled
community that I've ever come
across. I swear to God, it's the most
disabled community, bro. I promise you.
They're all [ __ ] mongos. They're all
self-p projectors. Everything these
people say about their own lives.
Special needs, disabled, skinned, no
friends, lonely. It's literally their
own lives that they're talking
about. Like, it's literally a reflection
of their own lives. Did you know that, Stephen?
Yeah, I know.
So sad, man. Is it? It's actually sad.
They all self
project. They come in here every day,
bro. Say you're skin, you're this. But
they don't know you. They don't know how
much money you have because they're
talking about their own lives. These little
loners. You know what I'm saying?
Bro, they're [ __ ] idiots. [ __ ] spastics.
Yeah, they all self project. They've got
They say that you've got anxiety when
they're the ones that have got anxiety
themselves. They've got mad anxiety,
these people. Mad anxiety.
When they tell other people that they've got anxiety,
smug it is. It's all it is, buddy.
Yep. Exactly, bro. He doesn't even leave
the house as well. You know, he doesn't
even leave the house or
socialize. Doesn't even go out drinking or nothing,
bro. Yeah. Oh, the beast skin as
well. Yeah, everyone's skin in it to these skinned
people. Everybody is skinned to these skinned people
here. That [ __ ] cult was talking [ __ ]
about me on large. He said, "Oh, PJ is
not that bad. He's an incel." Oh, there
you go. Um, Colt, what makes me an
incel, by the way? Cuz I caught you [ __ ]
about me on large. I'm an incel because
I don't lick women's asses and I'm not
white. How does that make me an
incel? What the
[ __ ] Get a grip, man. Just because I'm
not a white knight and I don't defend
women for no reason, it doesn't make me
an incel. What the
[ __ ] Doesn't even make sense.
Yeah, it is a disabled
community. It is a disabled community,
bro. But how am I an incel when I
literally don't even approach anymore. I
don't even bring it up. Well, because I
don't lick with artists. Please, bro.
That doesn't make somebody an
incel. You must be an
incel. You don't make any sense. Yeah, pretty
much. You're like that uh Ricky Milling
Millington account. You like to talk
[ __ ] behind people's back. How am I an
incel? Because I don't defend women
every day. Am I supposed to defend women
every day? I don't understand.
Madness. No, no, no, no, no. But what
makes me an incel? [ __ ] all that. What
Yeah. Yes. But you was calling me an
incel. Yes, I know. I read it. But how
am I an
incel? That's what I'm asking you. doesn't make
sense. I don't hate women. I don't care
about them. I just don't lick their ass, you
know? So, yeah,
bro. You're white now, mate. I don't
just because I don't defend women and
say they're all perfect and they don't
owe you anything, you know, to make
someone a [ __ ] im. Anyway, I lost
£100 on um fishing frenzy in roulette.
Yeah, I went to post a card and lost
[ __ ] 100 pound. [ __ ]
depressant. Depressed as [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
Uh yeah, man. I went to post something
and there was a bookies um beside it. So
I thought, [ __ ] it. Let me just let me
just try it.
Yeah. Oh well, at least it was only
£100. Just going to go KFC and chill.
I'm just going to go KFC and chill out.
Or should I go Nando? No, I'll go
KFC. I'll just go to KFC and chill out, man. [ __ ]
it. At least it was only 100. It could have been
worth I don't even do that anymore. Like
150s. It's too much.
So, but I'm not going to be gambling now
for a month obviously because I'm only off 100.
So, it's mad. It was going next
door. It was going next
door. Oh, next door. Next door. Next
door. 300 numbers. I didn't get some fishing penalty.
But yeah, same
old, same old, same
old. Oh, still almost went through that
[ __ ] toilet there,
man. Yeah, that's not me, mate. No,
that's not me. That £100, that's me for
the month. I'm I'm done. I'm not doing
anymore. No, no, that's not me, bro. I
should have even done it to be honest,
but I thought, let me just try quick
100. That's not me, bro. I know when to stop.
So, yeah, I'll try and win a football
game on Saturday.
Yeah. Well, like I said, I won't be
going out for two weeks, will I?
So, I won't be going out for a couple of weeks. Detox. So, good,
man. Stop talking about
yourself. Not good for your mental health, buddy.
I went to Selbury's at the weekend and
got two chubs. Two tubs of ice cream.
Yeah, man. Nice, bro. Nice. Nice. Nice.
Yeah. I'm going to get six piece
chicken. Yeah. These haters don't bother
me, bro. I don't even react to them
anymore, Cole. Because why you shouldn't
react to these people is because, think
about it, bro. They're only talking
about themselves. They're only putting themselves down.
So, you know, you don't need to react to them
because they literally are just
describing their own lives. They're
putting themselves down. So, there's
there's no reason to even react to them,
bro. You know what I'm saying? That's it.
So, L does it as well, bro. He self
projects a lot. They all self project.
They all sell project. Think of it. I
get more money than most people on
here, right? And I have more money than
most people on here, but they come on
here and call me skin. Why is that? Cuz
they're skin themselves. It's obvious, bro. You
know, they self-relect their own lives
onto other people.
But I might get an Indian today. I might
get I might get Indians
today. I might get an Indian today. I don't know.
But the thing is with Indians, they
don't [ __ ] open until [ __ ]
five. Unless you got a [ __ ]
shortage. I don't know about I don't know, man.
Yeah, they're all the same, bro. They're
same. I don't know.
an Indian for [ __ ] dinner. I'm not
[ __ ] rich. Jesus [ __ ] Christ. I'm
not that [ __ ] rich. [ __ ]
sake. I actually spent £40 on food the
other day, bro. I had McDonald's, India.
I think it was about It was about 40
quid, bro. I'm not going to get KFC,
then get India, bro. What the [ __ ]
I'll just wait until the Indian
opens. Yeah, I eat a lot out as well to
be fair. But it's not a waste of money
cuz you get something for your money, know.
Uh yeah. How much I spent today? Well, I
spent £100 on a gambling.
Obviously, I sent my mom a card. So,
that's I haven't ate today, have I? No.
Have I not? I'll just eat once. I'll
just wait for the new open. Yeah.
Yeah, it doesn't matter, bro. I've got
enough money. It's fine, bro. Don't
forget, I'm not going out for two weeks
drinking. I'm not going out drinking.
So, it's good, bro. I have
money. So, it's fine. I'm not going out
drinking for a couple of weeks anyway.
So, if anything, I've saved
money because if I went out, I'd be
spending a couple
hundred. So, just I'm not flim, mate.
I'm [ __ ] a fat bastard.
Yeah. Don't know, man.
Um, no, I just have no one big Indian. I
get chicken ticker, lamb in the
rice. So, how much do you get a month
with the um when you do the construction? What?
1,500. Yeah, but it's not as easy as
that. It's not as easy as
that. It's not as easy as that, mate.
Cuz I don't even have any pans. I don't
even have any pants. So, I just eat
out. I will start eating them definitely. Yeah.
Yeah. There's me getting [ __ ] free
grand. But I don't know what I'm going
to do, man. The past couple I'm not
going out drinking. Like, like I said,
I'm just going to go
cinema. Cinema on a Friday. Definitely.
I'm there, man. I'm the first one [ __ ] dare,
broki. I am the first one
there before you can say [ __ ] Jack
Robinson. You still have to borrow. See,
I don't, mate. Doesn't matter how much
I've gambled or whatever, I never need
to borrow money. I'll never get
skinned. Not like the Orington virgin.
What I was actually going to do was put out
£500 and give it to Shan so he could get
an echo and pop that vcard. Pop that
virginity. What do you
think? So he can finally So he can
finally pop that V card. What do you
think? He can finally
finally pop that V card.
Yeah. Yeah. And he can stop being a
[ __ ] virgin all his life. Yeah, mate.
Yeah. How do you get 900 a month
benefits though? It should be like
a,000. Should be like a,000.
because I don't have a um I don't have
um a working fridge. It's [ __ ] r It's
It's [ __ ] rank and I don't have any
pans. Yeah. And I don't have any pans.
So, I probably need to get something
like that this month or something. But
yeah, I don't have a I have a fridge,
but it's it's [ __ ] basically. So,
that's why I just eat out. So,
yeah. So, what do you think about Storm
Cult? Do you reckon he'll die a virgin?
I think he will die a virgin. He's
almost I think he's 30 and he's still a
virgin. [ __ ] hell. It's madness,
isn't it, lads?
Yeah. Yeah. I know. I
know. But I don't want to spend a lot of
money on a fridge. That's the problem. It
will. Yeah. But do you reckon it will
diverge in car?
Do I think I think he will die a
virgin? He will die a [ __ ]
virgin. Yeah, but the fridge is going to cost like
[ __ ] I don't know. I don't really
want to spend money on a [ __ ] fridge,
man. I get what you're saying. Obviously, got
[ __ ] we'll save you money. But the
pans are cheap. Well, they're not
actually cheap, but you just get two
pound 30 quid cutlery and
that. He doesn't cheat the benefit
system. He's [ __ ] skinned. How does
he cheat the benefit system? He's [ __ ] skint,
lad. Oh, you don't think he's a virgin?
Oh, okay. But when people call me a
virgin, no one sticks up for me, isn't
it? Even though I've been in bed with
women, I've had my dick sucked by women.
I've put it on YouTube. So, you don't
think he's a virgin, but when there's
evidence of me actually being with women,
right? You don't defend me. No one
defends me. Really, bro? Okay, let's
let's break it down. I've literally
shown me getting a [ __ ] I've shown
me in bed with a woman in Manchester.
I've showed me in a hotel room in
Nottingham in London. I've literally
been on dates with
people. But you but you don't think he's
a virgin. Why don't you think he's a
virgin? And don't say because he's got a
girlfriend. And don't say because he's
got a girlfriend because that doesn't
mean anything. There's people in
relationships that don't have sex.
There's people in relationships that
don't have dicks. There's m people that
are married that don't have sex. So
don't say because he's got a [ __ ] girlfriend, you
know. No, don't give them a reaction.
No, no, no, no, no, no. I'm saying why
do people not defend me, but they defend
him when he literally is a virgin. Like
he No, no, no, no. But with me, I'm not
saying it for reaction. He genuinely
genuinely is a virgin. Like I'm not
saying that to piss anyone
off or try to get reaction, but yeah, he
is a virgin. Like he generally is a
virgin. That's what I'm trying to say to
you. He actually is
one. How much is a fridge
anyways? Let me have a
look. I'll have to buy one soon. Did I do
it? Oh, there's one here at 85
quid. How big is that
though? That's not going to fit enough food in it.
1 looking at about
150. That's nice.
Yeah, I don't need a freezer. I don't
use a freezer. I don't believe in
freezers. Yeah, that one's one. What's it
135? What is it? A fridge.
No, bro. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. It has
to be a larger bridge here. We got one
here cuz I I don't need um I don't need
a fridge. I don't need a fridge. I don't
need Yeah, I've got my own kitchen, but
I don't I don't want to [ __ ] I don't
want a fridge
freezer. I don't put anything in the
freezer. I don't use the
freezer. I'm looking on
Argus tabletop. Yeah, underounter. Yeah,
there's one here. 135.
Yeah, that will be enough.
135. Let me see if it's in stock. I'll
go and buy
it. Nope, it's not even in stock.
Not even in stock. What the [ __ ]
199. One minute, bro. I'm trying to do
something. Hold on.
Yeah, there's a few of them, but one of
them is like
17, but they're quite expensive. They're like
180. Some of them are like 180.
180. There's a one here.
175. How big is
it? That one's big enough.
175. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, I have to get one at some point when
expensive. Yeah, I know, bro. It's a
madness. You don't think of it though,
you? You don't think of it like that
though, do you, brother?
I want a new one. I want a brand new
one. What website is
it? Just tell me the website. Probably
Amazon. Probably Amazon. Let me see. One
second. No, they're all like 130
150. Wait, there's one here. £ 109. One
second. No, there's one here. 109
quid. That's a
bargain. We got one here.
£109. Sound Yeah.
£110. There's black and there's white.
No, there's one 109 pound.
Let me see.
Yeah. One second. I've looked in one.
Yeah, I found it. I found
it. One sec.
I just showed the inside of
it. You sure that will be big
enough for like some pork chops and
stuff? You think that would be big enough?
Yeah. Is this the one you're talking
about? Is that the one you're talking
about? What is that? Oh yeah.
Yeah. I'm going to buy it then. [ __ ] it.
Yeah, I want to buy it. [ __ ] it.
I'm going to buy it now anyways. I'll be
back later. I'm going to order it now.