Yo,
you never guess what this site did. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] me, bro.
I don't know why it wasn't letting me
[ __ ] have this
uh eat this um wasn't letting me come on the Streamyards.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
You never guess what this site did. I
should have known it was dodgy by when
it was [ __ ] not letting me close my
account down. Bro, you never guess what
this site did. Yeah,
you never guess what this site did,
right? I I I'll tell you when when um
more people join.
One second, lad. No, I'll tell you what
they did in a minute. One second.
I didn't even lose yesterday anyways.
So, uh, yeah, let a few more people
join. And this is why this is why you do
not join [ __ ] you don't gamble,
period. And even if you do gamble, you
do not go on sites that are not
regulated by the [ __ ] UK. UK
regulated, right? I'll tell you what
happened. Tell you what happened when
you join. This is why anyone who's
watching this, I I'll tell you I'll tell
you exactly what happened.
One second. You're not going to believe
it. No, it's not about losing. It's not
about lo No, I won't go back on it. I
won't go back on it. I'll tell you what
happened. I'll tell you exactly what
I'll tell you exactly what happened.
They're [ __ ] scamming bastards. It's
not even about It's not even about
losing. No, it's not about losing. I'll
tell you what happened.
Join. Give me a minute. Yeah,
bro. And bear in mind, this is the first
that I've ever had. I've never had this
before ever in all of the years of
gambling, bro. You never guess what they
try doing, bro. So, 14 people joining,
right? That's enough. Okay. So, you
know, yesterday I got to £150 from 100.
Well, 200 done a 50 spin and I took uh I
took 1551, right? So, it was my money,
raw cash. Okay. Then I withdrew it. Went
out today, got some food, whatever. Come
back, chilled a bit. gone back on
account to see this the update of this
money cuz obviously I'm expecting this
£150 to go in my account. You know what
the little bastards done? They [ __ ]
reversed it and they said, "Oh, you need
to you need to clear rain." I said, "No,
I don't. That's [ __ ] my money that I
[ __ ] put in that fucking£100. I put
that£100 out of my own [ __ ] money."
And then they said, "No, no, no, no, no.
You need to you need to wager three
times the amount." And I said, "No, you
[ __ ] do not." And then they was like,
"Oh." Then they started showing me these
[ __ ] TNC's, which are not there.
They've clearly made up. If you go on
the website, bro. Yeah. You will see
where um uh um you will see where they
um where all the there's no policy that
says that. Never. It's never been a
thing. If you put your money in, you can
run away at any time, up or [ __ ]
down. And they come up with these TNC
saying you need to wager your own money.
Nah, nah. And I tried and tried to get
it back and they weren't having it at
all at all at all. Um, then I was like,
"Okay, let me try to wager it because
what else can I do now? They're not
they're not going to give the money
back." So tried to wager it, lost.
Dirty, dirty, stinky [ __ ] I called a
bank up and everything. They didn't
care. Um, bad, bad, bad, bad, bad. You
know, imagine you put £500 in, right?
And you got it to 12,3,400.
What the [ __ ] bro?
They are [ __ ] scammers.
They are scammers, bro. If I actually
lost you. No, I'll explain it again in a
minute. Bro, if I actually lost you for
my own will.
But you know what I'm saying? They
scammed me. They [ __ ] No, the this site
scammed me, rat boy.
Well, it wasn't another loss because
they scammed me. They scammed me. That's
how I lost because I got scammed. Not
because I gambled and I got greedy. They
[ __ ] wouldn't give me the money.
Yeah. So, basically, I put £100 in the
site yesterday, right? Got it to 200, re
respan, and then it got to 150. I was,
"Okay, I'll just take the 150." £50 up.
It's better than nothing in it. Like, it
pays for a day out. So, I withdrew it uh
last night. Still pending. Pending.
Okay, whatever. So, I've gone back on
the account later to see the the uh the
proc the process. Bro, they [ __ ]
reversed the withdrawal. I said, "Why
are you reversing my withdrawal?" I'm
like verified and everything. I should
have known when when they weren't
closing my countdown. They did. They're
dodgy [ __ ] And they were like, "Um, oh
yeah. Uh, you need to wager." I said,
"No, I don't. That £100 that I put in
was my own [ __ ] money. And anyone
that puts their own money in, they don't
need to wager anything. That's never
been a thing, bro. Unless they accept a
bonus, which I [ __ ] did not cuz I
don't I don't I don't play bonuses.
There, oh yeah, you got a wager. You got
a wager. I tried for ages to get the
money. They weren't having it. And they
were trying to show me these fake TNC's
on the website.
Yeah. They were trying to No, they
didn't say it was bonus money. They just
said you got to wager it.
I said it's not it's not bonus money.
This is real money. And they weren't
having it at all at all at all. Then I
was like, "Okay, well, I've got to try
and major it now. Is it what else am I
going to do? They're not going to give
the money back. The bank didn't help.
Bad, bad, bad,
bad, bad, bad. Bro, that is disgusting.
Imagine I put 500 pound in. Imagine
Imagine I put 500 pound and I got it to
£1,500 and they wouldn't give me it."
Could you imagine? No. No. No. No. Could
you actually imagine the seriousness of
this? And you've got these streamers
that are that are telling you to go on
nonUK regulated sites when they're
scamming. If I bro, if I lost through
greed, I'd be like, "Okay, I'd get mad,
but like, okay, well, it's my own
fault." They actually scammed me. I had
no choice but to carry on. They weren't
going to give me the money. If I if I
didn't beat the raid, which is why I
took why I withdrew the 150, cuz I was
happy with that.
Uh, it's called Brick Brick Casino.
I tried with a band, they weren't having
it at all.
Yeah. So, why
all of these people, you see, if this
was a UK site, they couldn't do it cuz
they'd get [ __ ] If this was like
William Hill or Lad Brooks, right, you
could have easily report them to and
they would be completely [ __ ] But
obviously, where they're not in the UK,
there's nothing you could do. I tried. I
made excuses why I needed the money.
They just did not care. All they done
was show the fake TNC that wasn't on the website. So
yeah, that is being scammed. And this is
the first time it's ever happened as
well like that. So yeah.
Uh they said you had to treble it. So
obviously I put £100 in. It was £129. I
had to I had to wager £300.
Why am I wagering my own money? You
don't need to wager your own money.
I was going [ __ ] mad at Laney. I
said, "You're selfish. Selfish dirty
cunt." Cuz I've been scammed, bro. They
scammed me. They weren't giving me
money. That was mine.
Yeah. Yeah. Basically. Yeah. And the
bank's not giving it back. The bank's
not uh the bank's not going to give the money back. Um
Yeah. The bank ain't giving the money
back. I tried. I was just on the phone
to them. So, I've basically been scammed.
But I've actually been scammed basically. Yeah,
I've been scammed. And I said to the
bank, you should let people you
shouldn't be letting people deposit on
sites where they they are scamming. They
are It's not a case of we're saying that
the ball's rigged cuz we've lost. They are scammers.
They are literally [ __ ] scamming, bro. So yeah.
Yeah. If anyone is ever going to gamble,
you make sure you stay on them UK regulated sites.
You make sure you stay on them UK
regulated sites, mate. As simple as
that. Cuz they can't do this because
they get [ __ ]
They they wouldn't be able to do that.
They wouldn't even try to do that, you know. No,
they actually scammed me, bro. They
actually scammed me. They didn't give me
money that they [ __ ] owed. They
actually scammed me.
What the [ __ ] bro? If I lost it through
greed, I'd be like, "Oh, well, I lost it."
Bad, isn't it? And what are you supposed to do?
What are you supposed to do now?
You just been scammed. You've been blatantly scammed.
No, basically what happened, Stephen
Howard, was I withdrew, do you remember
when I drew that 151 yesterday, I went
out today, I had some food, I had to buy
some stuff. I had to buy some stuff and
uh basically they they reversed the
withdrawal. I said, "Why are you
reversing my withdrawal? I'm verified. I
want that much 50 fair and square." Oh,
it's only 50 pound, whatever. But point
is, it's not their money. Then they're
trying to say, "I've got to wager it." I
said, "It's not bonus money. It's raw
money. I don't need to wage it. They
said, "Yeah, it's raw money, but there's
a requirements." I said, "There's no
requirements." Then they pull out these
fake TNC's that are not anywhere on the
website. They're nowhere to be seen on
the website, and they just refused to
basically give the money back unless I
waged it. Got it to 200, then lost it.
What else could I do? They weren't
giving it back. I tried about 10 times.
Tried calling a bank. What else could
have you What else was you supposed to do?
Yeah, mad. And then you got these
streamers [ __ ] telling you to go on
these [ __ ] sites.
>> Are you finished now, Pete? You done
your bulletin? I take it.
>> Right. We're not listening to this
today. Right. This is self projecting.
We're not listening to this [ __ ] today.
This self projecting [ __ ] Dusty. Do you
know what happened with this website?
I don't No, it's not what I could and I
could do the same thing now. I could get
a Vinder Lulu and do I've already got a
football bet for today. What do you mean
I could have? I still can. I mean I I
still can. I don't care about £100. It's
the fact I got scammed out of it and
they made up TNC's that weren't there. I
don't give a [ __ ] about £100.
What do you mean I could have? I still
can. I've got plenty of money. I still
[ __ ] well can if I wanted to. I've
already got a football bet. I had some
food today. I went out for food today.
Oh, dusty. Anyways, right, we're kicking
this self-reflector. Um,
uh, basically, you remember that 151,
uh, pound that I won off 100? Yeah. So,
I, so they reversed the withdrawal
and I said to them, I said to them, why
are you reversing the withdrawal? Yes.
The principle of it's because they've
scammed you out of it, not because
you've lost, it's because they've
scammed. They they reversed it and they
said that you've got to wager it. They
said, "Oh, you've got you you got to
wager it." I said, "No, you don't have
to wager it."
You know, "No, you don't have to wager
it. That's raw money.
They're the They're making up excuses
and making up TNC's."
But don't forget, these streamers are
the ones that recommend you these sites.
These streamers are the ones that tell
you, "Oh, don't go UK regulated.
Don't care UK regulated."
What the [ __ ] is this?
Yeah. 100 pound. Yeah. Yeah. By the way,
you're not going to rage mate me as
well, so there's no point trying to like
uh trying to uh Bro, imagine if they
done this with [ __ ] £500. We was just
saying this. Imagine you put £500 in and
you got it to 15,400. Then they wouldn't
pay you out.
Yeah. The rain basically means you need
to How do you explain rain? It's hard to
explain, but yeah, they they're scamming bastards.
They're scamming bastards.
They are scamming little bastards.
They are scamming little bastards. They
are. I'm Anyways, I'm going to time this
[ __ ] out anyways. We don't need to give
him any uh time. But yeah, this is what happens, bro.
This is the first time this has ever
happened to me.
Yeah. Imagine they don't with like £250
and there's nothing you can do.
Maybe I'll go to the bookies tomorrow
and do that Coke thing.
Maybe I'll do that Coke thing tomorrow
in the bookies.
I'm thinking about it, bro. [ __ ] 6 infield.
Maybe that's got to be the way, bro. And
if I get nicked, I get nicked. Simple as that.
I was raging. I was [ __ ] shouting at
Elaine. I said, "You're a [ __ ]
selfish [ __ ] You're a selfish lazy
little cunt." Because she is lazy. She
doesn't care because it doesn't affect
her. It's annoying, bro. Then they're
allowed to just scam people, get away
with it. I wouldn't mind if I lost it
through greed. Well, I wouldn't mind it,
but I wouldn't have been as whatever.
You know, you have actually scammed and
got away with it, and the bank don't do
nothing, and the bank doesn't do
anything about it.
Yep. There wasn't. They made it up. They
made it up and started pulling up out
some fake TNC's.
Pulling up some fake TNC's. And no TNC
say that cuz it was my own money. The
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
Yeah. I got scammed by a shady sighting.
I didn't want to pay out.
And I said to the bank, "You're allowing it."
Yeah. You glad I got scammed? That's
nice, bro. Go back to LJ's off your [ __ ]
you [ __ ] [ __ ]
So yeah, this is what these streamers
are trying to get you on. Nonregulated sites.
They're trying to get you on nonregulated sites.
Why are they trying to get people on non-regulated sites?
Uh, basically they refuse to pay me out basically.
Yeah, it is fake money.
Yeah, skin. Yeah, this is boring, lad.
We're not We're not dealing with you
self-reflectors. We're having a proper
chat about uh gambling. We're not
dealing with you self-reflectors.
Um, we're not dealing with it. So, yeah.
Um, basically what happened, Bob, was
that £151 that I got the £100 to, they
reversed it and they refused to give me
it because apparently I need to wager my own money.
Yeah. Doesn't even make sense.
No, but they're in they're trying to
influence other people, too. They're
trying to influence other people, too.
And don't forget, if any of these sites
[ __ ] you over, they'll get away with it.
UK sites can't do that because they
can't do that.
And they wouldn't even try to do that anyways.
You're not coming on to me. You're
banned, lad. See you later.
Stop trying to get attention, trying to
wind people up. Only for you. Oh, we
need SL to win. Come on, Slow. I've got
a nice football bet for today.
Don't tell me they missed the penalty. The buggers
don't. Come on, SL. [ __ ] them up. Come on.
We'll get this one in the bag, bro. If
they can beat them. I got a football bet as well.
Come on, SL. [ __ ] them up, man.
We need We need SL to win this, bro. I
got a nice I got a nice double. But
yeah, anyone don't don't ever go with
nonUK regulated sites. Even if these UK
regulated sites ask you for uh proof of
wealth, trust me, they'll pay you in the end. Um
they they will pay you in the end. I
should have I should have known Dusty
because they were trying like they were
doing everything to not close my
account. They were doing everything and
anything not to close down not to close my account.
They were doing anything and everything.
And I'm thinking, okay, but they surely
if you win, they're going to pay you out
in it. Cuz I've never had it before
where they haven't paid me out ever.
Then then they [ __ ] me over, bro.
That's my £100, bro. I didn't lose it.
Bad, is it bad?
No, it's not good, lad. It ain't good,
That isn't good. I wouldn't mind if I
lost £200. I wouldn't mind if I if I
gambled it. If I gambled it willingly,
then I would It would be my own fault.
Yeah, they're scammers, bro. They're
scammers. There's no TNC's on any of of
of the withdrawing thing that they were
trying to say about withdrawing. They're
scammers, bro. They're [ __ ] scammers.
They are [ __ ] scammers.
They are [ __ ] scamming little [ __ ] Yeah,
they got they're scamming bastards, bro.
It isn't good, is it?
See you later, lad.
You get kicked, lad.
I know. I know, Dusty. I know. They're
scammers. They're scammers. They said,
"Oh, it's not bonus." Oh. Oh.
Oh. Uh, they said, "Oh, uh, yeah, it's
it's not bonus money, but you need to
wager it." I said, "Why would I need to wager it? Why? Why?
Come on, slow, man.
Why would I need to wager it?
Me need to wager it? Really?
Why would I need to wager it? It's my
own [ __ ] money, you [ __ ]
That's what I said to them. They're
scammers, bro. Dusty, they're scammers.
And just, you know, it's rigged. The way
it was playing as well, you know,
getting me to 220, then [ __ ] me over
with [ __ ] number four again. Just the
way they've been right up until now, you
just know it's fixed. The way they won't
close your account down, the way you
just seem to miss when you're over a
certain amount. It's And now the fact
that they won't even pay you out.
You know what I mean, bro? It's not good, bro.
I'll just stick to the bookie site if I
ever want to gamble again.
But I've never had this problem before
on any sites. I've played in a lot of
sites, bro, and I never ever got problem
getting paid out.
And I, okay, what am I going to do now
other than try to complete the wagering?
What else am I going to do? They're not
going to give the money. There's no one
you can go to for the money.
I've got a double both teams to score
and a team to win. Do versus Horn
Church. Do to win and slow versus A3C.
Cotton and Slow to win.£10
returns. 10 pound returns £266.
So, it's a good return from £10 in it.
Not that it would make a difference
anyway cuz I've been scammed. So, I
don't even really care if this bet does win.
Come on, slow, man. I don't think they
will win, though. They're playing away.
Hopefully, give it a little while.
So, we just need slow to basically win.
They've already both scored, haven't
they? Have they? Yeah.
Yeah. I'm pissed off, bro. I'm not going to lie.
As you would be, as anyone would be, should be.
What if it was £500?
What if it was £500, bro?
What if it was £250?
Never go with a unregulated site.
Now I don't feel
they scammed me. They actually did scam
me, Dusty. So if they can pull all of
these tricks, why are people so
convinced convinced that it's not fixed?
Why are they so convinced that these
these things aren't fixed? Of course
they're fixed. Yeah, we just need SL to
win, bro, and then we're in the money.
No, I'm not all right, bro. I just
[ __ ] got refused to pay. I've just
been refused to pay out from a dodgy casino site.
No, I'm not all right.
If SL wins, bro, we're in the money.
I done a double to win and both teams to
score. Come on.
Come on. Slow. Be lovely.
Not this dirty, stinky [ __ ] team. £266 from£10.
That's good odds. Come on.
Do not get [ __ ] Yeah.
And I don't think Horn Church is going
to beat Dover.
Um, it was £300.
So, there was no way of completing it,
mate. It's hard enough to win nowadays.
Yeah, it's hard enough to win nowadays,
let alone [ __ ] It's hard enough to
win nowadays, bro. Let alone beat
[ __ ] wagering requirements.
Do you not understand how hard it is to
win? Let alone beat a wagering requirement.
Yeah. See you later, lad. You get
kicked. Um, see you later, laddy.
It's hard enough to win like to win.
It's hard enough to just double your
money. And they're and they're putting
wagering requirements when there's no
there's not supposed to be wagering requirements.
No, I just got scammed off a No. So
what? How can we gamble now, Dusty,
without this just happening now?
What if we gambled again and it happened?
[ __ ] then is it?
Yeah. Horn church ain't beaten over
mate. But it's just a slow game is it?
Come on slow.
No, there wasn't. They made up TNC's.
They made it up. There's no TNC's on
There's no TNC's on the websites that
say that. Why would you need to wager
your own money? That doesn't make no
sense. Why would anyone play if they
would have to wager their own money?
That doesn't make sense.
It's harder. It's harder. It's hard.
It's harder to um Yeah, you get banned,
Virgin. Um it's hard enough to double
your own money.
now like double. Why would anyone pick
wagering requirements with their own money?
I was raging, bro. I was raging. My mom
was like, "Oh, there's kids next door."
I was like, "I don't give a [ __ ] I'm
owed [ __ ] money. That's more
important." And and I think I'm right.
I'm owed money, bro.
Not to be not to be funny or anything,
but if if someone owes you [ __ ]
money, I've got a right to [ __ ] shout
and go mad.
I don't give a [ __ ]
Oh, is little Darlow not playing today?
Darlow's not playing today, lad.
Who's going to win a SL or this?
See you later, lad.
Was there any? Uh, no.
None at all. Uh-uh. Nope.
There was none at all, lad.
None at all.
Yep. They scammed me, bro. And it's not
on the TNC's either. And it's not on the
TNC's either. They won't close your account down.
Yeah, they're scammers, bro. Proper scammers. Imagine that was4500.
Now I'm scared to ever play again on any
site, but I'm sure Lad Brooks will be
all right. Come on, SL. [ __ ] score,
man. You dirty [ __ ]
No, Timmy, you're not coming in. You can [ __ ] off.
I didn't even want to come online today,
bro. This just made me want to come on
and talk about it since it is supposed
to be a gambling community.
Yeah, but I just figured that obviously
if you want money they'd still pay you.
Proper scammers, JNA. Proper scammers.
Come on, SL man.
Don't get beaten by this [ __ ] home team.
Come on, slow. Yeah.
Yeah. Basically, what happened was I was
waiting on 1511.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying, Billy.
Yeah. Uh uh I was waiting for that £151
and then they reversed the withdrawal.
Well, obviously, yeah, of course I lost
it all trying to complete the wagering.
Nope. They didn't pay it, bro. They
scammed the [ __ ] out of me. Couldn't
even get the money back from the bank.
Nope. They they reversed it. I said,
"Uh, why have you [ __ ] reversed my
withdrawal?" "Oh, you need to complete
wagering." I said, "There is no wager
in. This is raw money. Then they pull
out some fake TNC's. Tried to get it
back. Tried and then tried again.
They [ __ ] me royally, lad.
No. Straight cash. Straight cash, lad.
Nope. No balance. Nope. Nothing at all.
There was nothing there, bro. It was raw money.
I put £100 in. No, it was raw money. We
need SL to win, bro.
We need SL to win this bet, bro.
Then we win the money. No, I didn't take
a bonus. For the 100th millionth time, I
did not take a [ __ ] bonus.
I know what I'm saying, bro. I've been
gambling for [ __ ] years. No.
Oh, they got a red card. Oh, come on, Slow.
Come on, Slow. Come on, SL. Come on, SL.
We need them, bro.
Yeah, I know. I just see that.
What should be in now?
I withdraw. I with I I withdrew 200 and
something pound. Yeah, I withdrew 200
and something pound.
I withdrew 200 and something pound, but
obviously I with I deposited 100, so
obviously I probably waged it. Do you
get what I'm saying?
I withdrew once before. Yeah, but I
assume I probably just wagered it
because I was going back and forth. I
didn't know there was wager in.
Obviously, I wouldn't have deposited,
would I? It's hard enough to win, let
alone completing [ __ ]
uh completing uh wagering requirements.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, a couple of times and I've only withdrawn once.
Yeah, 30 times away. Yeah, I got [ __ ]
bro. Basically, I got [ __ ] in it.
Come on, SL.
We need these [ __ ] to win.
They said that I was 129 out of 300.
I just got scammed in it.
Come on, SL. Bro,
brother, I never take bonuses.
I'm [ __ ] praying for this slout to win, bro.
Stakes£10. and it returns £266.
I tried. No, I tried Fire Stick. I've
just come off the phone to the bank.
They didn't care because they said if
they give the money back, they're just
going to say that it's still it's not
going to work. But I tried
so I got royally scammed basically.
Yeah, I only need SL to win now. Well,
DOA and Horn Church, both teams to
score. Dober to win. And then slow and I
just need SL to win. Same thing. They
just need to They just need to win.
cuz the other one's already won. And
that ain't going nowhere, mate. So, yeah.
Yeah. I just need slow.
[ __ ] [ __ ] I could have had a nice cash
out if I done this online. [ __ ] It's 1 76 minute,
but I reckon it's probably going to be a
draw, I'm guessing. Come on, slow. So, yeah,
I tried ringing the bank, bro.
Come on, slow, you dirty [ __ ]
Yeah, I probably won't win to be honest.
I got do horn charts. Both teams just go
on do to win. That's 3-1. So I think
we've got that. And then obviously the
slow one, isn't it? We just need slow to win. Yeah,
doesn't matter. They can still score,
bro. It doesn't matter if they're down
to 10 men, they can still score.
We need slow to score. Come on. Yeah.
I've withdrew once before, bro. Once before. Yeah.
No, they're not going to win, bro. I don't think
Yeah, I'm on GameStop. Yeah,
like they scammed me, Fire Stick. They
[ __ ] scammed me, bro.
They scammed the [ __ ] out of me, lad. Yeah, once.
Yeah, once, bro. Once.
Yeah, one time, bro. H yeah,
I don't have a problem. I don't have a
gambling problem. I've still got money.
I've still got food. I don't have a problem.
I got scammed. No, I don't have a problem, Dad. Yeah.
Come on slow.
They having a [ __ ] basically.
No, it's not good, bro. Now you're scar
Now you're scared. Fire stick of
gambling. Now, now after this, you get
scared. You get me?
You get scared of gambling now. Do you get me?
Because it's like, well [ __ ] even if
you win now, [ __ ] you get [ __ ]
So yeah, [ __ ] basically, bro.
You reckon SL is going to win?
No, I think you can bother with bookie
sites. If you have a bookie site, I
think you're all right.
Yeah. Well, yeah. Pure gun stop. Yeah,
basically. Yeah, because the thing is
pric if they [ __ ] you over there's
nothing you can do. If a UK site if a UK
site tries to [ __ ] you over, if a UK um,
basically they can't because you can
just report them and then they get [ __ ]
With these sites, they don't give a
[ __ ] So, can't do anything.
They refuse to pay me out. Is it?
Come on, slow, you little buggers.
Yeah. And then you got these streamers
saying, "Oh, don't don't give the UK
sites your money." I guarantee you every
single UK site would pay you out,
though. Every single UK site would pay you out.
Leo Vegas, Bet Fred, whatever the site
is. Kasumo, I bet you they'd [ __ ] pay
you out there, wouldn't they? Yeah. Yeah, man.
Come on. Score, man. In it.
They probably won't score. They'll probably draw.
Yeah, because they wouldn't pay me out.
I know it's [ __ ]
You don't need to tell me that. I know it's [ __ ] Come on.
Yeah, but they probably I already had a
takeaway today. I already went out
eating. I already ate out today.
Uh I got it to 220 and then lost it. Yeah.
Then it kept being 431. Same old [ __ ]
Same old rig [ __ ] that he loves.
Same old wig [ __ ] that it loves. Yeah.
Oh, come on, man.
Was it my last 150? Stop asking stupid questions, bro.
Stop asking stupid questions. That's my
answer to you, lad.
What a stupid question.
Is that my last 150? Bro, stop asking
stupid questions, bro. Then you get
stupid answers, you see.
But yeah, we're just just lucky it's not
more, bro. Just lucky it's not more,
brother, because I don't leave myself
with no money. I don't leave myself skin
under any circumstances.
It's it's it's only £150. No, no, no,
no, no, no. It's £150. That's my money.
So, yes, it is something major. It is
something major when it's your money
that they owe you. And I'm pretty sure
you'd agree with that, wouldn't you, Fire Stick? It's money
that they owe you.
So, it is a [ __ ] It is a major thing.
It's money that they owe you. Not money
that you lost fair and square. It's
money that they owe you.
Yeah. That £150 money that is mine could
pay for a date. That could pay for a
night out. Well, yeah. Yeah, because
they scammed me. Well, yeah, cuz they scammed me,
bro. I lost a 100 of my own money, bro.
I lost 100 of my own money.
Yeah. Well, no. I lost 100 of my own
money, but yeah, but 150. Yeah, that is
a lot of money. You can go on a nice
night out with that. Nice haircut, nice food.
How is that not a lot of money when it's
your money, bro? Of course it's a lot of
money. It's your money.
Come on, SL. What are you doing?
I reckon they're going to draw me. Yeah.
Yeah. You don't even have £150, lad. You
don't even have 150 to your name.
You ain't even got 150 to your name, lad.
Yeah, they're leaving it very late. Yeah.
They need to score, bro.
Cuz this do game is definitely winning. Come on.
I reckon they will. I reckon they will score, bro.
Give him time. Give him time.
Give him time, lad.
Do's just scored again. [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah. Well, we're not all
millionaires like you people on here,
lad. We're not all millionaires.
But £100 is a lot to me when it's not
their money. Do you understand me?
Yeah. See you later anyways, lad.
Yeah. I'll just wait for a goal.
You'll you'll wait. Yes. Until they score.
Come on, slow.
What are you doing? Um,
so Fire Stick, you reckon uh you're okay
on UK sites, right? Basically. Yeah.
Yeah. And they need to score, bro. Come on.
I need SL to score, bro. Come on.
They need a score, bro. What the [ __ ]
are they doing?
So, what would have you done if that was
you? Fire stick and it was £500. Just £266.
See you later, lad.
See you later, [ __ ]
I just need SL to score, but don't think
Yeah, but I was I was waiting for that
£150. I weren't going to give that £150 back, bro.
I weren't going to give that £150 back. Come on.
Nah, I don't think they're going to
score, bro. Yeah, it's fun lasted.
I would I would have took the money and
I would have went back to it in two
weeks. Five stick. But nah, they had to
[ __ ] me over.
Come on. Why they not scoring, bro? Pop
me up for £266.
Yeah, I don't think I'm going to score, bro.
What will happen is the other team will probably score.
No, they're not going to score, bro.
No. Whatever. Doesn't matter anyways, does it?
Yeah, I don't think they're going to score, bro.
It's a 90th minute. Yeah.
Oh, 8 nil. [ __ ] hell.
Jesus. What? What? Maid Stones 8 against
Enfield now. That's [ __ ] mad. That's mad.
That is mad, bro.
Oh, sorry about that, lads. Yeah.
Done in a shop, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, I don't think they're going to score. No.
Nope. I don't think they're going to score, bro.
No, they ain't got a penalty.
I'm watching the scores, bro. They ain't
got a penalty. No,
no, they ain't got a penalty, bro. I'm watching it.
No, they don't I don't think they're
going to score, bro. No.
Not do. It's slow. Do's already winning,
bro. We don't need to worry about them.
No, we're [ __ ] lad. I think we got
about two, three minutes.
Nothing ain't got a life in it.
Couple minutes left. Yeah.
Yeah, we're [ __ ] bro. I think.
Damn. And that's how football always get
you. Always one that lets you down, isn't it?
There's probably like 2 minutes left, I think. Yeah.
See you later, lad. Yeah.
Yeah. And I think we've lost as well.
And I think we've lost that as well. Yeah.
Well, I'll probably be in bed for a
couple of days depressed.
That's it. In it. No raging on my
behalf, bro. Probably just be in bed for
days and days and days now.
Got money, get money tomorrow. Don't
care. Doesn't make a difference.
I'm glad you find it funny cuz I don't.
I'm glad you find it funny, lad.
Cuz I [ __ ] don't.
Nah. Not even bothered lonely. Just fed up.
Just fed up. Been scammed by a casino
that took money that belongs to me. Lost
a football bet.
Yeah, bro. It's not good, is it? Bad.
I felt like slitting my wrist today.
Fire stick, bro. When I [ __ ] found
out they scammed me for money, bro. I
felt like slitting my wrist and [ __ ]
Yeah, I felt like slitting my wrist,
bro. I'm not even joking.
Yeah, bro. That's depressing as [ __ ]
bro. You should have heard the stuff I
was saying to my mom.
>> Yeah, I think it's over. Yeah.
Doesn't matter what I was saying, bro.
Enough in it.
Yeah, they're not going to score. It's
obvious. It's It's so obvious. You know
it's not going to score, bro. You know
they're not going to score. It's obvious.
Yeah. One minute left.
Oh, it's funny, isn't it? Yeah.
You know, um yeah.
Now, they weren't going to score, bro.
They saw the white man coming, lad.
They saw the white man coming, dad.
Yeah, they saw the white man coming, bro.
Yeah, they saw the white man coming. I
just told Laney she's a selfish [ __ ]
It's as simple as that. Cuz she is a selfish [ __ ]
Like I said, they just saw the white man coming.
Yeah. No one cares about that skinned
ugly fat loser him celebrating. He's
just a little virgin that's got no life
that needs to come out the closet, bro.
No one cares about that fat, ugly, gay
loser. You know, I'm celebrating that
he's been stalking me for years and he's
got no money for doing it. He's a loser.
He can keep stalking me cuz he's gay and
he can hate the fact that he's gay and
keep taking it out on other people.
But yeah, he's a [ __ ]
He's a gay fat gay boy. [ __ ] little
virgin that hates the fact that he's
gay. And you know I'm correct as well,
bro. You know everything I say is
correct. I love the fact that he's a gay
boy with no girlfriend and no money. I
love that as well. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm getting these suicidal
thoughts again Fire Stick. I'm not going
to lie to you, bro.
Really getting him again, bro. And I've
got plenty of money. Doesn't make any um difference.
Right. We're going to ban you anyways
cuz you're not going to make up stuff
and try to wind people up, bro. getting
a nasty suicidal thoughts and I've got
plenty of money. Doesn't make a
difference. Um, is that the 13th 14th
time you've said that? I think so. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. No one cares about that skin [ __ ]
in a council bed. See you later, lad.
You get a timeout.
Anyone that's trying to like wind people
up and stuff, you're just going to get
yourself kicked. So, don't even waste
the time. Yeah. Uh
yeah, that's the way he gets you, Rat
Boy. And I've got plenty of money, lad.
Plenty, plenty, plenty of money. It
makes no difference. Losing is enough to
put anyone into a depression, a manic
depression. Um doesn't matter how much
money people have, how much money people
don't have. I don't care. Could be a
millionaire. I don't care. I reckon I'm
going to go and smash the bookies up
tomorrow with that um can of Coke. Well,
smash the bookies up. throw the can of
Coke in the bookies because obviously
I'm not going to get that 100 pound back
that they owe me. So, [ __ ] it. Got
nothing to lose. Simple.
Yeah, I think it's going to have to be
done tomorrow, bro. I reckon it's going
to have to be done
good and proper. I reckon so, lad. I reckon so. Yeah,
I reckon it's going to be done.
Definitely going to be done.
What are they going to do? Nick nick you
and make you pay a fine, bro. So, I
don't give a [ __ ] I won't pay it.
Simple as that.
It's put me in a bad mood basically
later on today when they scammed me out
of that £100. Yeah.
I don't give a [ __ ] if I get nicked. I
don't care. I don't care. Simple as
that. You know why I'm like greasy in
it? I don't care, bro. I don't care
about getting nicked. I've been nicked
about 30 times before. I don't care.
Simple as that.
It's that bad now. You get nicked, you
don't even care, bro. Like, what? You
don't even get anxious in in in being
arrested. That's how bad it is.
I don't give a [ __ ] if I get nicked or
not. I don't give a [ __ ] They have to
catch me first as well,
which is never going to happen. So yeah,
that's never going to happen. I just
want to give it one bang all over that
machine, bro. Make them feel how they
make you feel. Scamming you, not paying
you money that they owe you, [ __ ]
this whole football [ __ ] I chose to
do it and I'm choosing to do something
about it. Smashing it up with coke. So,
I chose and I'm also choosing this as
well. Yeah. To answer your question, I'm
going tomorrow, bro. 100%. I'm going back tomorrow.
First thing in the morning, I'm going to
[ __ ] smash that coke everywhere.
Watch. And I'm going to send it to Grezy
as well. I'm not send I'm not putting it
on here because the grasses and stuff,
but trust me, you'll get it, Grezy.
You'll get it.
It was online. Yeah.
Uh, William Hill.
But you're not going to know which one I
do in. You're not going to know which
one I do in, lad.
I don't understand how these kitty
fiddlers didn't score.
I don't understand how these little
kitty kitty fiddlers didn't score. See
you later, [ __ ] Thompson. Another gay
boy. Come out the closet, Gay Thompson.
See you later, lad.
Yeah, exactly. I'm not going to say
which one. Are you mad? They're not even
going to know what area I'm going to do
it in. Are you mad?
I'm going to make them feel how they
make me feel with them machines not
paying me. I'm going to make them feel
about how they make you feel. Just the
same as you argue with them. That's what
I'm going to do. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying?
I don't give a [ __ ] if it's not their
fault. They're the still the same.
They're still the same establishment and
they're the next best thing. They're the
next best thing. What else am I going to do?
It's as simple as that. I don't give a
[ __ ] if it's not their fault. I'll make
it their fault. Simple as that. I will
make it their fault. Yeah. I don't give
a [ __ ] I'm just going to go to any
bookies and innocent bookies. I don't
give a [ __ ] Simple.
So that's it. I don't give a [ __ ]
See you later, self-reflector.
Two people by now. No, no, no. I'm not
going to spit, bro. I'm not going to
spit because people don't like spitting.
I'll do it. I'll do it a more I'll do it
a more dignified way. I'll throw Coke
all over it.
Coke is better.
Yeah, they're weirdos, bro. Just leave
them fire stick. They're just
homosexuals, lad. Just leave them, bro.
They're just homosexual [ __ ] They
hate that they're gay. Just leave the
gay boys, bro. Just leave the gay bully
victims. I just laugh at them, lad.
That's why I don't react to them. No,
no, no, no. I'm not making decent food.
No, no, no. Some cunt's paying. No, no,
no, no, no. Some cunt's paying. I'm not
moving in. I'll move on when I'm [ __ ]
ready. I'll move on when I do damage.
Yeah, how about that one? I I will move
on when I [ __ ] do damage.
When I do damage and I see that coke
splat all over that [ __ ] machine,
then I'll move on. I'll move on when I
want to move on. Simple as that. And I
don't care about getting nicked. I don't
give a [ __ ] about getting nicked. I
don't give a monkeys [ __ ] Simple. It's
as simple as that, bro.
No, I'll be horrible to her all I want
cuz she's selfish. She's a selfish [ __ ]
She's just a lazy, selfish little [ __ ]
That is what she is.
She's just a selfish little [ __ ]
Yeah, she just doesn't care about anyone
but herself. She's selfish. All she does
is sleep all day. [ __ ] lazy bastard.
She's a selfish selfish selfish little
[ __ ] I told her to drop dead today as
well. I told her to drop dead.
I said go and [ __ ] drop dead. I meant
it as well, bro.
Yeah, I'm not even joking. And it's
annoying cuz it's selfish. She's so
selfish. She's such a selfish [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? She's a
selfish little [ __ ] bro.
She's a selfish little [ __ ]
I know someone that done the bookies.
Fire stick. I know someone that done the bookies about
12 years ago.
I think they lost
I think they lost £1,000 odds. It was
maybe it was more than that. They went
they went back home, smoked a spliff,
went back with a hammer.
They got done for it though. It was
someone who I like knew of.
Yeah, they went back with a hammer. They
got They got done for it though. They
had to pay a fine that. My man went
home, smoked a spliff, and then went
back with a hammer.
Oh god. We shouldn't even We shouldn't
even laugh to be honest. Yeah,
he got a fine. I think it was like a
grand fine or something. They wrote I
think the police just wrote to him.
That's mad. That is mad.
Yeah. I don't think he got community
service, but he got a fine.
Is that all he got for for doing four machines?
That's all he got is a fine and
community service, bro. That's That's worth it.
But also, don't it's not about smashing
the machines, bro, because don't forget
they've got insurance on it. You want to
bang that Coke and make it go all over
the shop and they're going to have to
clean it up. And there's going to be no
easy way to clean that up.
Yeah, they're going to have to clean all
that [ __ ] up as well.
You know what you should do? Just go to
bookies and have a [ __ ] Just have a
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] She's a selfish [ __ ]
She's a selfish little [ __ ] Mad.
Madness, isn't it? How much did he lose?
Yeah, I'll be in a bad mood now for
probably about a week, I think.
I'll probably be in a bad mood for a
week. And I've got money, lad.
Yeah, I've got money as well.
Does it make a difference? I don't care.
I literally don't care, lad.
Not about money. Never has been, never will be.
I'll just be depressed, I think, for a
week now, lad. Yep.
So, what you do is you you you tip the
can of Coke, you fizz it all up, and it
goes like really puffy, and then you
just splat it all over the machine.
Then you just splat it all over the
machine, and then obviously they're
[ __ ] Basically, it's going to go
everywhere. It's going to go absolutely [ __ ] everywhere. Absolutely everywhere.
It will break the machine. It [ __ ]
will break the machine, bro. Yes, it will.
Yeah, same, bro. I got scammed out of
money today. Got [ __ ] over by the football.
I thought we was I thought we was I
thought we was to a good start, man. I
think we was good. I think we was good.
I think we was going towards a good
start of the week, bro. But nah.
Nah, I'm not doing anything, bro. I'm doing nothing.
I'll be depressed now for like, yeah,
probably a week, bro. I won't feel calm
in the morning, bro. I'll be in a bad
mood now for a week. You don't know how
I like You don't know how I'm like, bro.
You don't know my mood swings. You don't
know what I'm like. I won't feel calm in
the morning because I've been conned out
of money. You understand? I've actually
been scammed out of money. If I lost
money, then maybe I would feel better.
But I've actually been scammed. [ __ ]
off. Eat my dick. Suck your mama. [ __ ]
off. I'll be the same tomorrow when I wake up.
And trust me, when I gave up when I gave
up with the dating game, I gave up. I
was getting mood swings for like two
weeks. When I first gave up, I was I was
I was getting mood swings for two weeks
every day. All day. Every day for two
weeks, bro. Trust me, it's not going to
go in the morning.
No, they're not.
Trust me, bro. I know how my mind works.
I'm [ __ ] Trust me.
Yeah. Probably longer than that, to be honest.
Yeah. So, that's where we're at, lad.
Got [ __ ] over by the football.
This life never changes, bro. I actually
took an overdose today. I'm not even
joking. I actually did took an overdose today.
I took eight cocons
because of this gambling [ __ ] them
scamming me out of money and that. Trust
me, I did, bro. You don't know what I'm
like. I'm [ __ ]
cuz people don't people don't record
stuff. Well, I don't record stuff.
It's [ __ ] my routine up. I was a I was
in a good mood yesterday.
I was in a good mood yesterday, lad.
I was in a good mood yesterday.
I was in a good mood yesterday. Now I'm
in a bad mood. Now I'm in a bad mood.
One second, bro.
No, I just messaged Solo G. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I was just messaging someone.
Yeah. I'm not going out this week. No,
I'll be in bed. Yep.
I already ate
See you later. These comments are not
going to you're not going to wait.
You're not going to rage bait me.
So there's no point, bro. You're not
going to like rage bait me, lads. You're It's pointless. Yeah.
Anyway, I'm going to go now. Yeah. So,
I'll catch you
in a bit. See you later.