Yo,
he's chat, bro.
So many self projectors. I was laughing
my ass off, bro. Is this actually Did
you see it? Yeah.
It was funny as [ __ ] man. Then he just
ended his live stream. So many self-p
projectors, jobless people trying to
tell other people to get a job, trying
to project their failures onto you.
They're [ __ ] It's It It's funny
though, man. It is funny. It is funny.
UK asylum. You know why they say to you
uh like you do this, you do that, you do
this and it's so random? It's cuz
they're talking about themselves.
That's why they they come out with these
like most random things like you can't
afford a big arch or you can't go out
drinking until tomorrow because they're
talking about theirelves. They're
actually talking about their [ __ ]
selves. These people had I get money
every week. I get four different [ __ ]
payments. You don't know what I get. You
don't know how much money I have. Again,
self-p projecting. But to the main
point, the main point is um how are you
telling people, how are these people on
on Timmy's? Yeah, he's got most people
blocked. Telling people to get a job
when they're on YouTube 24/7
from the time they wake up to the time
they go to bed. Shouldn't they be
getting themselves a job before trying
to tell other people they should have a job? Madness, lad.
Proper self projecting is in it, bro.
That's what I wanted to say.
Yeah, they're proper proper self projectors, lad.
Proper self projectors.
Proper proper self projectors.
No life little virgins. Have you seen it
on Timmy's, bro? They're just little
lowife little virgins. Yeah. None of
them have got a job between them.
None of them have got a job between them.
And they're telling other people to get
a job. It just doesn't really make a lot of sense. Yes.
How can I help you?
the random delay lead. So yeah,
just let you know, UK silent, it's never
happening, by the way, bro. Like Timmy's
never ever coming to London. He's never
meeting no one.
Just so you know, he's never meeting anyone.
Just to let you know, like don't don't
don't rely on it, bro.
This guy said,
"PJ, you hate women because you're a
virgin." Yeah. Yeah, I'm a virgin. I
called him a s. I was calling the guy a
little white knight s. Did you see my
comments? I said the women are never
going to sleep with you because you're
defending them and then apparently I'm a virgin.
Oh, bro, you couldn't make it up. I
would say there's probably more of a
chance of you being a virgin when you're
sat there on the internet at your age
defending women, you sad, pathetic bastard.
I say there's more chance of you being a [ __ ] virgin.
So, what have these what what have these
people what job have these people got?
Ask them what what job they've got UK
asylum. What? Being sat on YouTube 24/7
from the time they wake up to the time
they go to bed.
Is that their job, lad?
Not in this community they don't, lad.
Not in this community they don't.
So what? So So so all of the people that
work on this community
have their own business.
They're telling other people to get a
job, but they don't even work themselves.
These people in this community don't
have a lot of money.
No one on this No one on this
community's had an has a lot of money
to be fair. Not one not one of the
people in this community has loads and
loads of money, lad.
They're just on benefits just like everyone else.
All I Rose, you got that [ __ ]
nonslegs [ __ ] sing over you. I think
he's getting jealous. I think he thinks
you fancy me cuz he knows that no one
could ever fancy him because he's
[ __ ] ugly as [ __ ]
You just stop making posts about me,
mate. You're getting this jealous virgin going mad.
Bless him. Bless him all him. He thinks
by defending you, you're going to give
him some of your ass. You're going to
give him your pun. Yeah,
he thinks that you're going to give him
uh your pontang.
Trying to look good for women. So many
people in this community doing this.
Yeah, he's coming Wednesday apparently,
Mr. Bean. Yeah,
he's defending you. He's singing over women.
Sing doesn't work. You're still going to
never upset, you [ __ ] virgin.
You [ __ ] virgin [ __ ] That's what you
used to say back as well to him. This
little virgin thinks he's going to get
laid by [ __ ] trying to look good for
you and that. What a virgin. What an
absolute virgin. Oh, you go inside them.
Yeah. It's like them people right when
you when when you see them first riding
a bike and they [ __ ] at it. What an absolute virgin.
You're a virgin at this. You virgin. Is
it? You [ __ ] virgin.
So, you're a [ __ ] virgin. I want some
I want some Oh, did you see that shot
yesterday with them [ __ ] sideburns? [ __ ] hell.
Did you see them bloody sideburns, lad?
[ __ ] hell. With the Dr. Pepper.
Jesus Christ. No wonder you're a [ __ ] virgin.
No wonder he's a [ __ ] virgin. UK
asylum. He'll never [ __ ] get laid,
mate. And then he wonders why he's a virgin.
I'm going to message that Miles in a bit
and I'm going to tell him about [ __ ]
Britney and stuff. I'll tell him like,
um, yeah, he was he was grooming this
girl from Canada and she rejected him.
Then he started going on some [ __ ]
I'll tell him I've met the [ __ ] seven,
you know, seven times. seven or eight times, lad. Yeah,
I'll message this guy in a bit, bro. I
just can't be bothered in a minute cuz
I'm going to have to write like a
paragraph. He'll know exactly who he is
anyways. I'm sure he will [ __ ] virgin.
Oh, [ __ ] me. Do you remember when Timmy
had to live off bread and flour for a
month cuz he done his bulls in?
He done his bull.
Do you remember? Yeah. All
it come off. I don't know why.
>> Oh, when would it be ready? >> Okay.
Yeah, I got chili concardi being made for me.
It'll burn my tongue out. Yeah,
there's a coke, isn't there?
No, I want it.
I can't have that without without a drink.
Sorry, I was just talking to Laney.
Do you know what I feel like doing UK
asylum? Just going out and doing
something really dafted.
Something really, really dafted.
I don't know what but
just going and doing something really
dafted, you know. Yeah.
[ __ ] Miles McCoy.
Miles Mai is your bully, mate. I
couldn't find the other one.
He never told me the other one's
Facebook, but it was Jackary. I remember his name.
Defending women, thinking you're going
to get laid.
Why are you You're depressed. Why are you depressed?
People in this community think you need
to be skinned to be depressed.
Oh, is this virgin boy?
This is virgin boy number two.
Who's that? Timmy.
Hopefully the link works.
There we go.
Do you think the dating game is going to
change in this country UK asylum?
Do you think one day it's suddenly going
to get better?
So, you going to join or what? You want
the link? There it is. You [ __ ]
virgin. And stop licking [ __ ]
nonslegs's ass, Timmy. Your skin and his
skin. I've already proven it many times.
Your boyfriend is skinn. He's never seen
20 grand in his life. Just like you've
never seen 20 grand in your life. Stop sucking dick.
>> Hello, Peter. Let's have a serious
conversation about you getting on a wobbler. >> Hello.
>> You say you've got all this money, so
why do you still live with your mom?
>> I can't hear anything.
>> I can hear you. Fine.
>> Oh, this [ __ ] phone, man.
I'll come back in. Let me rejoin. I
can't hear anything. One sec. Hello.
I couldn't hear anything, bro. [ __ ] Try again.
>> Can you hear me now?
>> I can't hear anything, bro.
>> Oh, I can hear you.
Say you've got all this money.
>> Reset my phone. Yeah. One sec.
>> Yeah. Two seconds.
Hopefully it works. Nah. Yeah.
See what LJ was saying. He says, "Oh,
you get money tomorrow, you're going to
be out drinking." You learn something
new every day.
I will not be out tomorrow and I will
not be out today.
It just shows that they don't know
anything, is it? That the people that
they're talking about,
they don't know about they don't know
about anyone, bro. They're talking about
on this community. Yeah.
Yeah, I do. I don't I was saying say to
these people, bro, I don't live payday to payday.
You get me? I don't live like money to
money, payday to payday like these people, bro.
That never ever ever happens.
You get me, Mr. Be.
That don't happen, man.
I was looking at that slow bet. That
would have been nice, bro, if this
football bet won the other day.
No, he hasn't got no money. He's He's Skint, lad.
I don't need to wait on any payment,
bro. I've got I've got money to do what
I want when I want. I don't have to wait
on any money. I get money every week as well.
Not that I should even be saying that,
but I get money every [ __ ] week. So,
how does that how does that work, you know?
So, I could never be skimp
cuz people don't want to go out and drink.
You know what I mean? Hello. Can you
hear me now?
No, I can't hear any.
>> Well, I can hear you. So, I'm going to
ask you a question. You got all this
money and you say you got all this,
>> but why do you live with your mom? Why
do you live with your mom? You are full
of [ __ ] I'll come back. I'll come back.