Hold on a minute.
Why go live? Let me
Hello. Let me
Now it is I don't know what happened there
to go live wasn't showing up. Yeah. Um
so basically right I'm going to be retiring.
Yeah I'm retiring. That's
retiring bro. Oh [ __ ] [ __ ] hell.
I don't know why it was why it was quiet today.
Just come back from the [ __ ] pictures.
Is that still warm? Oh, it is lovely.
Yeah, I just went to the cinema to watch Scream 7.
Decent movie if you ain't watched it.
Um, bit too busy for my liking, but
nonetheless, it was still good. Think downstairs. Yeah.
No, [ __ ] all, man. I I'm actually I met
I saw my friend in the pub before I went
to the cinema.
Uh before I went to the cinema, I saw my
friend in the in the in the in the pub
and he was having a beer. Obviously, I
had a Coke. I wasn't going to drink. I
said, "If you're still here, by the time
I get back, we'll get on it." I come
back at 9:00.
It was gone. The pubs were [ __ ]
empty, bro. Empty.
Empty, bro. And it's the It's the end of
the month and it was empty.
That's how you know this country is
poverty ridden, bro. No one can even
afford to go to pubs. There wasn't like
anyone in there. There weren't like
obviously it's not going to be busy as sen
busy as Saturday.
Um, obviously it's not going to be as
busy as Saturday, but yeah, I do know
how to use a washing machine. Maybe I'll
do a video on it, a guide on how to I'll
do two I I'll I'll say two Rick's mace.
But no, there was no one about, bro.
Really? Obviously, the cinema was packed.
[ __ ] too busy, bro. I don't like it
when it's like that. It's hard to
concentrate on the film. Don't like it
when it's too busy, bro. Yeah, I do.
Yeah, I washed my bedding before I went.
I washed my bed sheets.
How are you going to be 38 and you don't
have to use a washing machine? [ __ ] me.
That is insane, bro.
I'm retiring, lads. Oh, I got this pick a mix.
Yeah, but no, seriously, it was dead
today. I don't know why it was so dead
today. There should have been more people out.
That's weird, isn't it? It's people's
got to be skinning it like Virgin Boy. Oh,
they've got to be skinting it.
I don't know why it was so quiet.
I don't know how these places are for to
stay open. No, I went to the cinema.
I popped in the pub for a drink because
I was a bit early. I come back and there
was no one out. I said to my friend, "If
you're still there, we'll have a few beers."
But it was dead. Completely dead. It was
like 9:40 and it was dead, bro. There's
like hardly anyone out.
The country's The country is [ __ ] povertyridden. Scream seven.
Yeah, the country is proper poverty ridden, lad.
That's weird, though. You would have
thought um you would have thought it
would have been um
it would have been uh um
one second, bro. One second.
Read something here.
Lane's all right. I had to get some I
had to get Laney some cigarettes
on my way back.
Yeah, I went to watch Scream 7, but it
was too busy, bro. I don't like it when
it's busy like that.
It's just you can't watch the film
properly, I don't think.
Bro, she doesn't take dip. Are you stupid?
has a pans for anxiety.
I was tempted to go into the Brookies UK
asylum. I was so tempted cuz I'm still
open. There's a couple of arcades, but I
never done it, bro. I never done it.
As a pun for anxiety, lad.
He had a little lap. Yeah. Oh. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, it wasn't busy at all.
Yeah, you should. Yeah. S shoes.
So, what you going to watch the new
screen or what?
What are you [ __ ] up to, man? You
should watch it. It's good.
But it it I don't know, man. I don't
know how long I can keep watching these
horrors for, bro.
It's kind of disgusting. Some of it is
actually quite vile, lad. I just watched
Scream 7 and some of it is quite vile,
bro. I'm not going to lie to you. And
bear in mind, I've watched like loads
and loads and loads and loads of horror
films. There was like a couple of scenes
I was like, should I should I still be
watching this, bro? Like, some of it is
just gross, bro. It is disgusting, lad.
I just watch I just went to watch Scream
7. Joe, I went to the pub beforehand cuz
I had to go pee. Bumped into my mate. I
had a Coke. He had a beer. I was there
for about 10 15 minutes. I said, "Yeah,
I need to go watch a movie. Finishes at
9 something. If you're still here, then
we'll get on it." Went back. There's
literally no one there, bro. No one in these pubs.
It's a povertyridden
country this is. And there weren't even
like people. There was literally no one
there in these pubs. Pubs. There was
like a bar. Quite quite a lively place
to drink. It was just dead. No one was
really out. Maybe three people. Weather
Spoon's dead. What the [ __ ]
Thursday should have had a couple of people. Yep.
I would have had a few beers if you was still there.
The beers are cheap. They're like £3
something. I would have just But I don't
really I didn't have a beer before I
went cinema cuz I didn't really want to drink.
But yeah, some of these scenes and these
these horror films are quite depressing,
bro. I'm not going to lie.
They're quite depressing, bro. when
someone's like almost going to survive
and they just get killed in the most
brutal way. Bro,
what would I rate out of 10?
I'd say seven, but you know, it's the
the thing is with these horror films,
yeah, is most of them are quite predictable.
There's there's rarely any twists in any of them.
There's Oh, there's some good ones
coming out, though. Oh, bro, I watch I
watched the trailers. Yeah, Elijah Woods
in one of them. I don't know if you
anyone know who Elijah Wood is. I
definitely know who that is. That kind I
ain't seen that [ __ ] around for years,
bro. And then there's one and there's
another one. But the Scream 7 was good.
It was good, but again, predictable again.
Something that some of these these ones aren't.
Yeah, that Elijah Woods in a horror
film. Green Street. Uh, Will Fred. I
don't know if anyone remembers Will Fred
on BBC 3.
So, we got two more coming. I just
watched the Scream Fire Stick. I'd give
it a seven, but again, like I said, it's
predictable. Most of these horror films are
most of them pretty much are, bro. To be
fair, and some of the scenes are just disgusting, bro.
My mom could have never saw that, bro.
[ __ ] hell. I didn't like The only
thing I didn't like about Five Stick is
it was too busy, bro. I don't like it
when it's too busy the cinema, bro. It's
just I just don't like it. You can't
really focus on the film properly in it.
Just the way some of the people got killed.
Just the way some of they them got killed, bro.
You know that you know that delayed you
know like the delayed killing like you
think they're going to survive and they
just get killed in the most brutal way, bro.
as opposed to just getting like just
stabbed. This woman, bro, she was
[ __ ] hanging off of these lights and
then she fell like straight into like
the knife on the ground and then she got
set a light, bro. It's actually quite
vile to be honest. There was one I
remember, bro. Yeah, there was one I
remember, bro. I think it was called
Heart Eyes. It was Valentine's. I think
it was last year, bro. It was so brutal.
The head got crushed and the Oh, bro. just Yeah,
some of it is quite nasty, bro. I'm not
going to lie.
Yeah, this Indonesian guy said, "Oh, we
should go out today." I said, "I'm not
going out, bro.
I do know it's not real." Really?
What? That's not real.
Damn. I didn't know. I I thought that I
thought that actually happened in real life. Really? Damn.
Damn. I thought somebody actually wore a
screen mask and went around killing
people. It's not real.
[ __ ] hell. Why didn't Why didn't my
mom tell me this, bro? Oh my god. Stop
messaging me, you [ __ ] Indonesian
guy. Oh, let's go out. Let's go out,
bro. Go out yourself, bro. Just like I
did when I went to [ __ ] approach
women. Go out by yourself. It doesn't
matter if they're in a big group. You're
going to go central London. There's
going to be people that you can talk to,
bro. Just cuz you're scared. Don't use
me. This is what I hate about This is
what I can't stand with people, bro.
Yeah. They try to use you. Fire stick.
You know what I'm saying, bro? No. It's
all right when you get out the cinema,
Joe. It's all right when you get out the
cinema, but when you're in the cinema,
it is quite disgusting, to be honest.
It is quite disgusting, bro. But again,
predictable again. Again, it's predict,
bro. Go out yourself, man.
Trying to get me to go out so so you're
not scared to approach people. [ __ ] off, man.
Me go then? What do you mean I go then?
I don't want to [ __ ] go out, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
I don't want to. You do.
What the [ __ ]
What do you mean I go out? If I wanted
to go out, bro, I'd go out. [ __ ]
hell. I went out [ __ ] two I went out
like a couple weeks ago by myself.
[ __ ] I met I got five numbers. You
could do the same thing, man.
No, to be fair, he's a nice guy, bro.
Yeah, he No, to be fair, he is a nice
guy. But the thing is, yeah, I don't
like people that just try to meet you
for like ulterior motives, whatever the
word is. There's always like a motive
behind it. And with him, it's getting
women. It is, bro. 100%.
It is. I went out a few weeks ago by
myself. I didn't go out with anyone.
I didn't go out with anyone, bro. I did
not go out with anyone at all. Trust me.
And it was weeks ago, bro. It was a
Thursday. It was like early February. I
got five numbers. I'm talking to
someone. That's it, bro. You can do it
then. If I can do it, you can do it.
[ __ ] me, man. Jesus Christ.
I still got some Tik Toks.
Yeah, like I don't like people that do that, bro.
I kind of had a I had a go at Ant-Man
for like recommending me this person. I
said, "Bro, like the thing is, yeah, I
know you might have been trying to do me
a favor and stuff, but you knew what the
guy was like
before recommending me him. It's all
over anyway, so I kind of do hold you a
little bit responsible. cuz it's not
like you didn't know what the person was like.
Yeah. Long story. Anyways, so
basically you're just best off not
dealing with anyone to be fair.
Uh or don't rely on anyone rather.
That's better word for it. Yeah.
I see a lot of guys today with these
women and these women were [ __ ] ugly,
bro. Oh, Fire Stick, you dare, bro? I
see them. They're like They were either
like fours out of tens or five out of
tens. Um, I just saw like random like
there was like a few people out. Most of
them weren't couples. Most of them
weren't couples, but I did see a couple
of them. I told Antman about it as well,
and I said, "It's just purely [ __ ]
It's just purely circumstantial, isn't it?
It's purely circumstantial. It's got to
be, bro. It's got to be. Just like it
was with me, you know what I mean?
None of them were my type of, but I just
said to Ant-Man, like I just basically
said to Ant-Man, um, I messaged him. I
basically said, I kind of I don't wonder
how they do it, but I'm intrigued to be
honest with you,
how like they've how they how they did.
And it's probably through years ago or
they got lucky or they might have met through work
um that you look at and you think like
it is actually so hard. How do people
[ __ ] do it? But but deep down I know
how they do it anyway. So but yeah, of
course he's still abroad. He lives
there. He's never coming back.
He's never ever ever coming back.
He's never coming back, lad. He has a
job over there. Just like a lot of
people when they move there they don't
come back. A lot of people A lot of
people are doing it.
Can you blame them?
Is he fuckloaded? No, he ain't. No. He
gets about £700 a month. 6700 a month.
But obviously 6700 a month over there is
a lot more money than it is here. So obviously like
obviously yeah he might get 650 700 a
month but over there it's worth a lot
more than it is over here. So I mean he
just teaches English.
That's how you know bro that this guy
was sick of it. This guy was scared. He
was he was scared shitlessness of
flying. He was getting decent money from
benefits right and he left and he left
and he and he left that all behind just
to go out there. That's how you know
it's bad, bro. That's how you That's how
you know it's bad.
And he's not tried as much as I have. He
has not tried as much as me.
He ain't tried as much as me, mate.
And as soon as he won five grand, he
went straight back. He went straight
back. Soon as he could, he went straight
back until he could permanently live
there. And this guy was scared of flying
as well. He was [ __ ] scared of flying.
Scared of flying, bro. He was never
going to fly again, but he knew it had
to be done.
It had to be done. Yeah. And that's the
thing with this community, you know,
Ricks was saying yesterday, once you
come on this sector, Yeah. you can't get
away from it. Like there's lo no one
that gets away from it. Ant man did get
away from it. 100% he doesn't look on
YouTube, bro. I swear to God, he doesn't
look on YouTube. He doesn't comment. He
doesn't He's done, bro. So yeah, I
Rick's race is right, but there were a
few people that like just just [ __ ] it
off. I'm sure he's not the only one, you
know. I'm sure there's a few people and
he doesn't look on it, bro.
Yeah. And and even if you don't like
someone, you have to give credit when
where credit's due in it, Joe.
You have to give credit where credit's due,
whether you like someone or not. So that's it.
That's what makes me laugh. Like people
on here can say what they want about
him, bro. And I'm not even being biased
because I talk to him, but at the end of
the day, bro, like
he managed to get off YouTube and he's
and he's made a life for himself.
So there you go. And he's never coming
back ever. So ever coming back on
YouTube, ever coming back to England.
Mad, is it? That is mad. D.
Of course he gets birds. He's in Thailand, lad.
Of course he does.
Of course he [ __ ] does, bro. Who
doesn't Who goes to Thailand and don't
get women? Come on.
But it's not even just about women.
There's different things as well, bro.
That's better over here. There's so many [ __ ] here.
You have to you don't have to put up
with any of that when you're in Thailand, lad.
Well, I don't know why the pubs and that
was so quiet today.
In Thailand, right, gambling's banned.
Um, there's no [ __ ] You don't have
to wait for everything like you do here.
It's just a better life.
It's just a better life overall. Um,
you know, this country, they don't even
help their own [ __ ] people. Fire stick.
They don't even help their own people,
lad. It's quite disgusting if you think about it.
You know what I mean?
I will be, bro.
I will be if this person [ __ ] me over.
And all you really need to do is book a
one-way flight, bro. It's only [ __ ] I'm saying
it's only it's only a one-way flight.
But, you know, we we'll see in it, bro.
We'll see. We still got some time, bro. Uh yeah,
he said if he ever met anyone here, he
would come back. He said that's mad
though. That is actually mad when you
think about it. Fire stick. You can't
[ __ ] You can't um He had everything
but just not a woman. That's why he
left. Overall the country is better.
Like obviously overall the country is
better but like that's the main reason
why he left but obviously
the country is better at the same time.
Does that make sense?
But yeah, I'm going to do a nice
football bet on Saturday, bro. I need to
try again. I can't believe Slow [ __ ]
me up for that 266. The bastard [ __ ] man.
Would have been a nice win, isn't it?
How the [ __ ] didn't they win, bro?
I'd [ __ ] to it.
I might put £500 on a double both teams
to score, Joe. Would Would that be very
brave of me?
Would that be very brave of me, Captain? Imagine, bro. Yeah,
imagine that, bro.
That's [ __ ] scary. It's mental, in it.
No, I've won a lot of football bets, Mr.
Bean. I won 200 pound or 20 pound a few
weeks ago. I've won a couple of double
both teams to score.
I've won a few, bro.
Oh, it's just um this isn't the exact
dog, but it's the breed of the dog that
Nons legs um that Nles legs used to have.
Uh it's a breed his mom used to like
throw the dog on him and [ __ ] That's
where his fear of dogs come from. Not
that exact dog obviously,
but yeah, he used to abuse him with a
dog. That's where the fear of dogs come from.
He was put into care at a very young age.
Is that your plan? Yeah, but 200 isn't
enough, bro. Because the odds are [ __ ]
now. Yeah, I get what you're saying, but
the odds are [ __ ]
Like, the odds are terrible, bro. Have
you Have you not look Have you Bro, I
got £224 back for five both teams to
score from 20,
bro. It's [ __ ] odds. They should have
gave me a lot more than that when I won.
Should have been at least 500 pound for
five teams. Sometimes you can't even get two.
Um, yeah, he's scared of dogs.
But yeah, they should have gave me more
than £224, bro, for five teams. What the [ __ ]
I might try correct score, Joe.
I might do two correct scores.
Then we're talking money, matey, ain't
it? I might do two nil nils.
Bro, you done two or three nil nils.
Yeah, you're [ __ ] laughing. It's like
150 to one.
Three teams. I don't really like doing
three teams. No, what you need to do
What you need to do is you need to do a
double both teams to score.
You need to do a double both teams to
score and the specific team to win.
Look, I almost won £266 off of the
tenner, but obviously I I I only bet
home teams usually. If SL was playing
home, I would have won.
Um, obviously just don't put as much on it.
No, but three teams, bro, it's it's too much.
Three teams is a bit too much, bro. To be fair,
I only like [ __ ]
Bro, but then I did get five. So Um,
I bet you And I bet you wish you had
more on it, didn't you, Captain? I bet
you wish. Oh, what if I had 20 pound on it?
Yeah, I bet you wish you had about 20
quid on it, right?
That's the first thing that would go
through your mind there. When it's
little stakes and it returns big, you
wish you had more on it in it. Be honest.
Be honest, bro. Be honest.
Oh, National League or the National
League leagues playing Saturday North.
No. Oh, they are.
Okay, let's have a little look. Is Slow
play? Is SL Oh, Slow's playing home as
well. Get in. I'm going to have a nice
bet, bro, on Saturday.
Get in, bro. Do you know what I'm going
to do? I'm going to do three teams, both
teams to score on the specific team to win. Yeah, bro.
Oh, they're they're all playing home as well.
>> I got some mice for you, boss. What?
I got your cigarettes, Ma.
Uh, Scream's not happy with you, Mo. He
wanted to know why you didn't come and watch him.
I said to Scream. He wanted to know why
you didn't come and watch him.
You would have liked him more. He's got
a lovely mask. Yep.
No. No link.
I'm not putting a link up for Tibby,
bro, because he just starts [ __ ] and he
doesn't meet anyone. We're not doing
that, bro. [ __ ] off.
You show you're about it and you come to
London and then I'll put the link up.
Simple. That's that, bro. I think that's
fair, is it? I think that's fair.
That is fair, bro.
No, I've just done this wrong. Shut up.
I'm trying to concentrate, bro.
Both. One second. No, no, no, no.
Just shut up. I'm trying to do something.
Yeah, look. So, that's a double. Enfield
Town and Slow.
Both teams to score, but both Both teams
should score on them to win. That's £179
back from a tellenna.
Now, what would it be if we add another team?
Big money, I'm guessing. I reckon.
Yeah, it's on the bottom more. Right about
I didn't forget about you. Ma,
don't leave mine like that
because Yeah, because if you don't they
they [ __ ] go hard and [ __ ]
The cinema was packed, man. Oh, I saw
Timmy. Yeah, I went to one of the pubs
and saw him and I just sat down and had
like a coke and stuff. He didn't get my
message. He showed me. He didn't get my
>> Yeah, I think he changed the sim and [ __ ]
Um I said, "If if you're still there
when I come out the film, we'll get a
drink." I went back, "Mom, all the pubs
and was like empty." Dead. Absolutely dead. Right.
Well, you're right, Laney. You sure?
You do worry me, lady. Huh?
>> Oh gosh.
>> Oh, it's 79 to one.
[ __ ] hell. 79 to1. Jesus Christ.
79 to one. [ __ ] me.
That is lot. That's lots, isn't it?
That'll be hard. But I think that's I
think he's got a chance, mate. Jesus.
What are you doing? Get a ball in it.
Get a ball. All right, mama.
>> Yeah, Joe, it's it's it's 79 to one.
Yeah, I know.
[ __ ] hell, bro. I'm not put 100 pound
on it, but put 50 on it in it. Jesus Christ. That's lost.
That is mad, bro.
One second, bro.
Oh, it's not letting me do the link.
Why? Okay, I need to reset this, bro.
It's doing that link thing again.
For [ __ ] sake.
One second, man. I need to reset.