We're laughing at you, mocking you.
Them [ __ ] were laughing at you.
They were laughing at you. Looking mocking
them [ __ ] were
them [ __ ] were laughing at you, mocking Yeah.
We're laughing at you, mocking you.
laugh. It's not my phone, bro. It's
YouTube. Rick's had the same problem.
It's not my phone, bro. It's YouTube.
But yeah, I think I'm going to do that
football bet, bro. I don't know whether
to do two teams or three teams.
I reckon with two. Yeah, you got it in
the bag, bro. Definitely. it.
No, I think three is too much.
They were laughing at you.
They were laughing at you. Mocking you.
No. Fire stick. Fire stick. Fire stick.
They were laughing at you. mocking you.
I love that, bro.
Monty's one sec. Let me investigate. Can
it, man? He's a [ __ ] cat.
I like that team,
Dr. Eko. I like that team.
No, I'm not going on his channel, bro. [ __ ] him.
[ __ ] him, lad.
Should I have a drink this week? Nah.
Not this week, lad.
Maybe. I don't know. One second.
I like that team.
I like that team. Okay with you, [ __ ]
Is that okay with you, [ __ ]
Okay with you, [ __ ]
Why would I want to? I've already won
slow bets, lad. Fraser Fraser doesn't
even come on here anymore.
I'm trying to think. Should I do three teams?
Three teams or two teams?
I think if you're betting more money, do
two teams. If you're betting less money,
obviously do three teams. You can't do
any more than three. It's never going to win.
That would be a miracle, bro.
If I start that Lad Brooks account, I'd
probably do three and stick like 150 on it.
And any cash out I get, I would just
cash it out. Trust me, bro. It will be a
huge cash out if you had like
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Depends, bro. Uh,
I don't know how many teams were.
I reckon I think two.
I think two, honestly.
Just stick 80 pound on two of the teams.
That's like over That's like,5600 back.
No, she doesn't know about gambling.
She doesn't know about gambling.
One sec, bro.
I like Timmy. You know,
Timmy's not um
Timmy's not a gambler. Um Joe, sorry.
He's not a gambler addict, is he?
He's not a gambling addict, is he?
Nah, he's not a gambling addict, Timmy.
Is it Steven Howard?
You can tell me on here, lad. I'll put
the link up. I'm not going on Monty's.
I'm not joining these [ __ ] bro. You can [ __ ] off.
Did you know that Rick's Mace can't use
a washing machine? Joe, I'm going to do
a video to Rick's Mace. How to use a washing machine?
What do you think of a little video like
that? Joe, do you reckon he'll see it?
What do you think, UK siling? Do you
reckon he'll see it
on the same website? You can Bro, you're
saying I'm a troll? He used to [ __ ]
stir, bro. Every time I used to go on
these panel, man.
I'm not I'm not trolling. He said he
doesn't have to use a washing machine.
He He's took some L's as well in it, Ricks.
No, I don't care, bro. He used to [ __ ]
sto a lot, man. He used to [ __ ] sto a
lot of [ __ ] Sorry.
So [ __ ] bro,
I'm not trolling either. It's okay. I'm
[ __ ] trolling, man.
Nah, never, lad. Never.
You think a hostel is bad? And even if
that did happen, you think a hostel is
bad, bro? There's people that out there
that are homeless.
There's actually people that don't even
have a hostel, mate.
Huh? There's people that worse than hostiles.
What do you mean LT wants Ricks?
Well, has he done a video or something? Nah. Really?
What? He's calling him out. Really?
Called him out where? Who was the And
who would have who would have been the
cause of that?
I'm not I'm not sub to LT lad.
Who calls that then? Joe, who calls that?
If [ __ ] if LT is going for Ricks, who calls that?
No, I didn't cause it, mate. Not me, bro.
Nah, not me, mate.
How did I cause it?
Nah, not me, lad.
Nah. [ __ ] off, bro.
Ryan start no beef, bro.
I said, "Do you still talk to LT?" And
he starts saying that he's a fake black
guy and I didn't call I didn't make him
say that, did I?
What has he been posting? I'm not sub to
his channel, bro.
Ah, one second. I might be able to find
him. One sec. No, bro.
I didn't think. No, I can't find any of
his [ __ ] bro. He must have deleted it.
I don't even have his channel.
Oh, here we go.
He hasn't posted anything about Oh, he
has. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ] me. He's on He's
He's on a 28 minute video.
Yeah, he actually has. Yeah.
All that wasn't me, bro. That actually wasn't me.
28 minute video. So he must be watching
then. He must be watching to know what's going on.
He must be. He must be watching to know
what's going on.
No. Listen. Listen. One second.
I haven't traveled to the shops in two
days, bro. I leave the house every day.
What is he going on about? Second of
all, yeah, I literally said, listen to
me. Yeah, I literally said, I'm not even
chatting [ __ ] If Timmy comes to London,
I would meet both of them because I know
exactly what's going to happen, Joe. If
I met Timmy, right, I know exactly
what's going to happen. That's why I
added LT into it. Because think about
it, bro. What What do you think is going
to happen if Timmy come and I met Timmy?
What do What do you think is going to happen?
Like what do you literally think is
going to happen? He's going to get
involved. So you might as well just say
like, "Yeah, I haven't left to go to the
shops in two days. How do you work that one out?"
Really, bro? Really? Really? I leave the
house every [ __ ] day. Yeah.
No, I don't need to defend myself, bro.
Uh, Timmy, if you want to join, you can join.
Nah, the worst one is that Mark Samson.
He's the worst one. That Mark Samson is
Oh, I went to watch Scream. Greasy. Yeah,
Yeah, man. I got to pick a mix. Got a
couple of mice cuz obviously you can't
just have one suite. That's like being
with one woman. Who wants to be with one woman, >> right?
>> Hello, PJ. Can you hear me this time?
>> Yeah, I can hear you now. I don't know what
>> Oh, good, good, good. Okay, PJ, let's
talk like adults. Only you like kicking
me out the box and all this and all
that. You say you're a man. You say you
about it. So, let's talk like men. Yeah,
without you kicking me out. You You said
>> I will be coming down Wednesday, Peter,
because you ticket.
>> Yeah, man. That's fine. That's fine.
>> No, it's fine cuz Peter, it's none of
this like, "Oh, you shake my hand like
last time." that like people I'm being ser
this is what you do humiliated you but
you make out Peter that spasticated No
Peter you are that spasticated nobody
runs away from among
>> so you're coming on Wednesday
>> yes Wednesday Peter right to your mom if
you don't come out
no Peter I don't want to come down I've
got to travel 150 miles to see you cuz
you think you're about it right I want
to prove No, you know about it. You've
been humiliated by every person on
YouTube. You have been like you're
telling Joe to go to London. Why? Why
don't you go to Joe's? Why don't you go
to Yorkshire? Cuz you ain't got the
minerals. No, no, no, no. You can't
handle the truth, Peter. You can't
handle the truth. You're that artistic,
that spasticated. Yes, I'm coming to see
you, but you keep going about Joe going
to London. So why don't you go meet Joe?
Cuz Joe's laughing at you and you're the
triggered monster. See what he does?
always the flex, bro. This is why I
don't have him on the panel. And it's
not going to be some no shake a hand
thing, bro. If you come anywhere on this
door, it's not going to be beaten up.
You're going you're going to be put in
hospital. Trust me, you're going to be
put in [ __ ] hospital.
So, and that's that. And stop talking
about other people, you [ __ ] idiot.
See, this is what he's doing. He's
deflecting, deflecting, deflecting,
deflecting. Like, bro, why are we even
having this argument? He got booked a
cab. He didn't get in the cab. Why are
we even still having this argument? And
you got booked to cover. You
>> Why are you kicking me out PJ? I'm
meeting you on Wednesday. That's clear.
And it's not a game, PJ. And when I get
on the train at half 10, I will be going
live on the train when I'm on my way to
London Maro. You think this is a game,
PJ? It's not cuz I've got But you won't
call me boring on Wednesday, Peter. When
I'm on that train,
>> you won't be calling me boring then.
You'll be sitting your pants like you
did from Lord Jay getting the hammer
from the [ __ ] door.
>> You're not going anywhere.
>> Yes, I am, Peter. We'll see Pet when I
book them train tickets and I'll put a
video not a communal post a video with
the poo. You're not going to say that
then are you get paid Tuesday and I get
paid Wednesday. I'm booking the tickets
Tuesday. So you're not going to say that
are you kicking I'm kicking I'm kicking
him. He just keeps talking over me. Bro,
he just keeps talking over me. There's
no point. I'm not shouting, bro. Yeah.
You're not about nothing. If you was
about anything, you would have went in a
cab. End of Yeah. And then what you're
saying, you're waiting to get paid to
get a train ticket. So that must mean
you're skin, [ __ ] If he can't
if he can't if he can't afford if he
can't afford um a a 50450 train ticket,
does that prove that he's skin? Does
that not prove that he's skinn? Never
once have I ever had to say, "Oh, I've
got to wait until I get paid to get a
train somewhere." What the [ __ ] bro?
What the actual [ __ ] I've never ever
had to [ __ ] wait for a monthly money,
bro, to get a [ __ ] train ticket. Your skin.
>> Right. Right. How can you call anyone's
skin when you live with your mom
scrouching off your mom and sister for a
takeaway? You can't call anyone
tomorrow. Let's be honest.
I'm giving you a week's notice because I
haven't got time tomorrow cuz it's
birthday. No, I've got money, Peter. I
can show you money right now and I could
wipe the smile off your face.
Okay. So you show I'll do you a deal.
You show me 20 quid. I'll show you 40.
You haven't shown any money. You haven't
shown any money for months because we
all know we all know you got no money
and you rely on mommy's [ __ ]
>> this guy comes on Wednesday. I'm going
to seriously seriously hurt him, bro. I
swear to God I'm going to seriously
seriously seriously hurt him.
>> Seriously, because this has been going
on for so long now, bro. Years and years
and years. And I don't care if he's got
disabilities. Yeah. I don't care
anything. I don't give a [ __ ] bro. I
seriously seriously seriously seriously
don't give a [ __ ] This has been going
on for way too long now.
You know, I'm going to put an end to it.
I'm going to beat him so bad, bro. He's
not ever going to come back on this
community and start [ __ ] running his
mouth. I swear to God, I've had enough
of it, bro. I actually have, you know.
Stop talking. You said you're going to
come Wednesday. That's it. We'll see.
[ __ ] stupid little prick.
See you later.
You're not coming back in. Simple.
[ __ ] [ __ ] lad. Yeah.
Yeah. Like, come on Wednesday, bro. And
that's it. You said you're coming
Wednesday. Cool. Stop arguing. It's the
same old [ __ ] It's the same argument, bro.
But I don't care if he's got
disabilities. I don't care. I'm going to
I'm going to beat him the [ __ ] up, bro.
I don't give a [ __ ] if he's got
disabilities, cuz this has been going on
for years, bro. This has been going on
for [ __ ] years. years and years and
years and years and years and years and
years. Do you understand me, bro? Yeah. Serious, lad.
So, yeah. How is uh LTC that if he says
he doesn't go on YouTube? I haven't been
to the shops in a couple of days. Really, bro? Really?
No. The plan is he's coming on
Wednesday, bro. I'm not listening to it
anymore. It's boring. He's doing my
heading. That's why when he comes, I'm
going to seriously hurt him badly, bro.
When he comes, I'm going to seriously
seriously seriously I'm going to
humiliate him so badly, bro. And I'm
going to put it all over YouTube. So, I
hope I hope he does come on Wednesday.
I hope he does come on Wednesday, bro.
It's been going on for years and years
and years. I'm sick of this [ __ ] now,
you know? I'm going to really [ __ ]
hurt him. I don't care about him having
disabilities. I don't care. He's He's
mentioned my name enough [ __ ] times.
I don't care, bro. Yeah,
bro. We've already made a I'm not even
listening to this, bro. It's boring as
[ __ ] It's just the same regurgitated
[ __ ] This guy can't fight. He's not a
hard man. Why is this spaz coming on
YouTube acting like he's a hard man?
He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. And you're
you're going to see that on Wednesday as well. Stop talking.
Stop talking and come. It's as simple as
that. Why didn't Why didn't you get in that taxi?
Why didn't you get in that taxi? Did he
give the an actual reason why he didn't
get in the taxi even though he said he
would? He's a [ __ ] He's there. There's
no chance he's coming to London, bro. He
doesn't have the balls. He doesn't have
the bottle. Yeah. People like him and
and and this money mate, they'll never
travel anywhere by themselves, bro. Never.
They'll never travel anywhere by
themselves. They're [ __ ] houses, bro.
They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> [ __ ] houses. Buy some money with his
mom. Yeah. Okay. Right. PJ actually be a
man a little baby thinking you own it.
Right. Peter, my disabled rail card is
coming in the next two days. Right. And
when that comes I will be don't argue I
am coming Peter I don't want to go that
way mate but I could do the day I like
trains and you listen Peter I don't
think you understand why because I'm not
going to go no [ __ ] [ __ ] is going to
go in a cab one way you [ __ ] [ __ ]
big man who's too skinn
you were too skinny
and you bollocks in the next day anxiety
about anything you would have went Oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah.
So like Lord Jane on 8:00
you really are you really have got the
imagination of a [ __ ] you have really
got I'm not about Lord J
Peter this ain't going to be like last
time you I'm going to one you I'm going
to one lamp you go cuz you'll be on the floor loos
Peter see you Wednesday and no talking
out of I'm giving you a chance to get
out of Yeah, you'll see. I'll be going
to Tuesday night and you'll be [ __ ]
your pants. See you later. See you
later. I gave you a chance. See you
later. You're not coming. You're not
going back. Don't Don't even book a
return, bro. You're wasting your money
cuz you're not going back.
>> Yeah, it's as simple as that. I don't
give a [ __ ] if this guy's got
disabilities. He's not going back, bro. >> Seriously,
he is not going back. If I see this come
on this road on this door, I'm going to
seriously, bro, do him dirty, bro. Trust
me. Really, really dirty. Yeah. I'm
going to humiliate him so bad, bro. He's
not even going to know what's hit him.
I'm telling you. Yeah.
He needs to learn, bro. He needs to He
needs a big He needs a He needs a lesson
taught to him. This [ __ ] needs a
lesson, bro. He needs a [ __ ] good
lesson. I'm telling you, bro. Yeah, he's
serious, bro. If he was serious, he
would have went in a cab. He would have
went in that 200 pound cab, which
apparently I couldn't afford if he was
serious. He ain't no ser he's not
serious, bro. He's not serious. And I'm
going to do him dirty, bro. Trust me.
Really, really stinky dirty. Just for
the sake of this has been going on for
years and years and years and years and
years and years and years now, bro. I'm
sick of seeing this [ __ ] on YouTube.
Yeah. Talking people's names. Yeah. I'm
going to I'm going to I'm going to
humiliate him so badly. He is never
going to come back on it. I'm telling
you, bro. I'm telling you. Yeah.
I gave this [ __ ] multiple chances to
keep my name out of his [ __ ] fat ugly
mouth. Yeah. Like his fat out of his
fat, ugly, disabled mouth. So, bro, you
want to think you're going to come bad,
you're going to be bad and you're going
to come to London, bro. You can't even
turn up to a fight by yourself.
You know, you know you're
you're uh six, bro. Timmy's not going to
beat me, bro. He ran away last time. He You know,
Christian Tay, huh? The [ __ ] you on about, bro? Yeah.
Yeah. He ain't serious, Joe. He won't go
anywhere by himself. He will never go
anywhere by himself. let alone London.
These people are not made the way that
I'm made when I've traveled in the past
and I've gone to places by myself. Who
else has done this? No one else. He's
never He's never doing that. He's going
to come all the way to London by
himself, mate. You got more chance of
winning the lottery. This is all talk
talk. He's a talker.
He likes to get attention on YouTube,
but he's not trying to meet no one, bro.
He's not try. He has never turned up by
himself. You know that? Even when I went
to Birmingham, do you know what he done
the first time I went to Birmingham,
Dusty? He tried getting money Mike to
beat me up. He tried getting Money Mike
to fight his battles.
Yeah, I'm built different. I don't need
to I don't need backup when I've when
I've when I've [ __ ] when I've
traveled to meet people in the past. I
don't need backup.
You get me, lad? But anyway, he has
never turned up anywhere by himself,
bro. Never. He has never ever turned up
anywhere by himself.
Never. He has never turned up anywhere
by himself. I'm telling you, bro. Money
Mike Tiger. I'm a lying, bro. I'm a
lying when I said this [ __ ] has never ever ever.
And you know what? It was annoying me
the other day, bro. I really hope he
does come. Yeah, he was annoying me the
other day, bro, when he was mentioning
my [ __ ] name. Just fat [ __ ] Yeah.
And I don't I don't care when N legs I
don't care when N legs does it and that.
And like it's the way he was doing it
like mentioning my name. over and over
again. Please come on Wednesday so I can
smash you all over. Like, please do,
bro. Please come so I can smash you
[ __ ] all over.
And it's going to be and it's going to
be worse than Ben Gregory, bro. I really
do hope you do come
cuz I'm sick of this [ __ ] fat [ __ ]
mentioning my [ __ ] name. Yeah, you
saw when I went live the other day, bro.
You saw when I went live the other day.
Yeah. And it's not like other people.
Don't start Don't start mentioning my
name thinking it's going to wind me up
now. It's just the way that he was doing
it. Yeah. It's just the way that he was
doing it. He was [ __ ] doing it, bro.
It's [ __ ] annoying because he done
his balls in trying to [ __ ] put me in
a mood. That's what he was doing, bro.
He was trying to put me in a mood. He
Yeah. He was trying to put me in a mood
cuz he done his balls in trying to draw
me out. That's what annoyed me about
this [ __ ] skinned [ __ ] Cuz he done
his balls in. You know when he's done
his balls and he starts [ __ ] trying
to suck nonsex's dick and start talking
about his [ __ ] skin life on me, bro.
Do you get it? Yeah.
No, mate. Mate, if there's three of
them, I'm not [ __ ] Bro, you you think
I'm going to let someone come here and
I'm going to lose? It's not happening,
bro. He ain't even coming. We've been
through this before. This has been going
on for seven years now, bro. Seven
years. Seven years this has been going on.
If there's three of them, bro, then
that's that, in it.
But I hope he does come, bro, cuz I'm
just going to bang him and I'm not going
to stop these gay little videos. Him
keep mentioning my name. I'm going to
spit all over his face as well. I'm
going to say this is for you and non
legs and I'm going to spit all over his
face. I swear to God, bro. Trust me,
I've got a temper. I've got a temper.
I'm going to do the dirtiest thing, bro.
Trust me, I'm going to spit all over
him, bro, as well, cuz I'm sick of these
little gay self-reflecting videos. Yeah,
I'm going to just keep spitting on him,
spitting on him. And trust me, no one on
this community has ever been spat on.
I'm going to knock him out as well.
Trust me. Yeah. Keep my name out your
mouth, you fat [ __ ] You fatbellied
[ __ ] autistic [ __ ] I don't care,
bro. And you can bring London Taylor if
you want as well. I don't give a [ __ ]
bro. Yeah, I don't care, bro. No, I
don't care. No, he's the one bringing
trouble. This guy kept mentioning my
[ __ ] name. The other day I was
chilling, bro. Yeah, I wasn't even on
YouTube. And this fat, ugly [ __ ] will
not keep my name out of his mouth, bro.
He will not keep my name out of his
mouth over and over again when he's done
his balls in. This is what he does every
single time he's done his balls in.
Yeah, he does this, lad. He does this.
Yeah. So, when he comes, let him come.
Let him come, bro. Let him come. Let him
come, bro. So I can knock him out, spit
all over, and [ __ ] send him back to
his boyfriend legs so we can suck his
dick some more. Yeah, simple, bro.
Trust me. If he if he wants to meet
somewhere, if he wants to meet somewhere
like then I'll meet him and then it's
going to be a bit different. But oh, if
he thinks he's coming on the door,
that's it. I'm going prison. Simple as
that. If this fat [ __ ] thinks he's going
to start banging on people's door, I'm
going prison, bro. There's there's no
rules. There is no rules. I'm going to
do it dirty. If he thinks he's going to
show off for YouTube, if he thinks he's
going to come on this, Bro, if this guy
even thinks he's going to come on this
road, Yeah. and show off for YouTube,
bro, he's not coming back on this
website. And he's not going back to
Birmingham. I'm telling you that right
now on my mom's life, he's not. I don't
care who he brings. I don't know how
many I don't care how many people he
brings. If he thinks he's going to start
knocking on people's door, he ain't
going back to Birmingham, bro. Trust me.
Trust me, bro. And that's a promise.
Yeah. And I'll be live on Wednesday as
well. Yeah. All because he's a [ __ ]
I've had enough of this guy. Yeah. For
years and years and years, projecting
his virginity, projecting his skittness,
bro. Like, and it's someone that's been
doing it as well. So, it's fine by me,
bro. I'll just spit all over his face as
well, and then he'll think twice before
mentioning my [ __ ] name, the foureyed
ugly [ __ ] Trust me, bro. Trust me.
Trust me. Do you know what I'm going to
make a piss pot? Do you know what I'm
going to do tomorrow? I'm going to make
a piss pot already. I'm going to make a
piss pot already because the thing is
with these people, fire stick. Yeah,
I'll tell you what it is. Yeah. Even
when you beat these people, Yeah. they
keep coming back and coming back and
coming back. Do you know how many times
this guy's been beaten up? You know how
many times this guy has been beaten up
and he keeps coming on here. He needs a
good beating. He needs a proper beaten.
If he if he if his disabilities, bro.
Yeah. If his disabilities really will
not allow him to come off this
community, then he needs a good old
beating, bro. He needs humiliating. Like
humiliating. No, no. Not beating humiliating, bro.
That's That's what Yeah.
I'm going to make a lovely little piss
bottle, bro. That's what I'm going to
do. I'm going to I'm going to I'm going
to make a piss bottle and and wait until
Wednesday, bro. Yeah. And it's going to
stink as well. Yeah.
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] Yeah. It's
not happening, bro. It's not happening.
This guy is jealous of me as well. This
Timmy is another one that's jealous.
Look at him, bro. Iva [ __ ] mock. Iva
Mong, four eyes. [ __ ] skint, bro. He
done a video eating McDonald's, bro.
Yeah, he he he done a video eating
[ __ ] McDonald's. He's another jealous
little [ __ ] that can't keep my name out
of his mouth. Yeah, he's another one.
He's another little jealous little virgin [ __ ]
that blushes every single time someone
goes that someone goes past him. He's
another one, bro. Just like Nons, just
like Red Scott. He's just another one, bro.
He's another one, bro. He's another one
of them. And that Jamie Thompson, he's
another one of them, bro. Trust me,
he's another one of them, bro.
He is another one. Trust me, he's
another one, bro.
He is another one, lad. One [ __ ] 100%. Yeah. Simple.
And that's what it is, lad.
I'm going to piss in a bottle tomorrow,
bro. when I wake up. I'm gonna hold it
in when I wake up. Trust me, bro. He's
not going to come back on this website.
I wouldn't be I wouldn't mind, bro. But
this is this has been going on for
[ __ ] years now, bro. Years years.
>> Yeah, bro. That's it. Hello. You keep
going on about you're the hard man, but
I'm going to upload video many video two
years ago when you ran from every single
person. And PJ, you'll see the video
where you ran from me.
>> Peter Peter, you want people to come to
London so you can hide from your mom.
That's why you so you can hide in mommy's bedroom.
Swan dance like Terry being a packet. I
am coming. I am coming. So if I got the
train tickets, PJ, and it said
Wednesday, you're going to say I'm a liar.
Are you going to say I'm a lawyer then?
Are you going to say if I booked them
train tickets? Are you going to call me
a liar? Yes. No, no, no. Answer the question.
>> Let me let me answer my question. I will.
>> You're not going back.
>> No, no, no, no. I Peter, you will not
meet anyone else. You're scared of Joe
cuz put you six foot under in the patio,
mate. And you know, so why don't you go
Yorkshire? You make this big man. Why
don't you go up Yorkshire as my money on
Peter? going to eliminate anyone. You
ran from a 12y old. You ran from a 12y
old. You are trying to act in front of
your cable friends. You're going to end
up ugly. You're going to knock one out.
You guys have got it in you. You got it
in you. You're just calling me virgin.
Oh yeah. Yeah. And what about your mom
chain smoker? a chain smoker who can't
even stand his own son that she has to
smoke a load of [ __ ] weed because you
[ __ ] wins like a little me make me a
little [ __ ] make me and your
looks like your mom my brother knock you
out Peter my brother would knock you out
Peter you met my brother Peter I swear
to God you would not be all right you
would be nice at all these little
[ __ ] monies all these and all that
You can mouth as much as you want
because when comes you'll be [ __ ] it
and you'll be like
I don't think you understand that the
reason why nobody meets you Peter
because you will hide behind your mom's bed like
okay you have an anxiety attack
on Wednesday and you sit
>> some [ __ ] IBA virgin and he killed
himself that's literally what I'm
talking about his dad and everything
he's not going to do nothing. This
little IVA virgin is not going to do
[ __ ] nothing. Yeah.
Yeah. I will be looking forward to
Wednesday. Something that's not
happening. You just want everyone on
YouTube to think that you're a hard man.
But you're no hard man. You're no hard
man. Because let me tell you something.
Yeah. If you really was a hard man, you
would have you would have went in that
taxi. Listen, did he not say that he
would get in this taxi, right? Listen,
everyone, he can make any excuse now.
Yeah, he can try and make any excuse.
But did he or did he not say he was
going to get in that taxi? He did say he
was going to get in that taxi.
He said exactly that he was going to get
in this taxi. Yeah. Yeah. He said that
he was going to get in this taxi. So why
didn't he? Oh, another excuse. Oh,
another excuse. And there's going to be
another excuse on Wednesday as well.
Yeah. There's going to be another excuse
on [ __ ] Wednesday as well. You
[ __ ] Iva monk. You've done this to
Monty. You've done this to a few people
as well. And I don't even like Monty.
Yeah, I don't even like Monty.
You skint Iva Mong that can't even
afford a [ __ ] McDonald's.
Oh, he's a [ __ ] skint [ __ ] bro. He's
a [ __ ] skin [ __ ] Loser. Another
jealous loser. Just like Jamie Thompson,
just like Red Star. Just like Nonsex.
The [ __ ] jealous losers. Like they
You can tell it's jealousy with them,
bro. Deep down. Yeah. Deep down with
them four, four, five people, you just
know it's jealousy with them, bro. You
know it is. You know it is, bro. Like
you've done some gambling. Yeah. You're
doing a gambling vlog and you're
mentioning my name. You just know it's
jealousy. You know it's jealousy from
the IVA virgin. You really know it is
deep down. You know it is.
You know it is deep down. You know it
[ __ ] is deep down, bro.
You said you was getting in that taxi.
It cost £200. Why didn't you get in the
taxi and stay in the taxi?
If you was a real man, you would have
done it, bro. If you was a real man, you
would have done it.
But you didn't. But you said you was
going to do it. [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. He
just wants to talk. He just wants to
talk. That's all he wants to do is talk.
He just wants to yap. All he is is a yapper.
>> Yeah, it is. It's true though, isn't it?
All he is is a yapper. He's a yapper.
He's a [ __ ] mouth.
>> He's a [ __ ]
Can't even judge when he quit. He has to
rely on mommy.
>> Yeah. I can't grow yourself.
When you going to live by yourself I
can't live by yourself. I have to do
things for people because you're a
little [ __ ] You're a [ __ ] I'm the
non. You're the one who says you want to
create children. Nobody else in this
community. You're the only one who's ran
away from a 12y old. You're the only
one. Yeah. Yeah. Alcohol to kids.
Alcohol. I've never said I'm going to
rape a child. I've never said I'm going
to rape a woman. Pet, I'll upload all
the videos on a different channel so I
don't get my How many children you said
you're gonna How many videos you're
Peter and nowhere near as bad you said
Peter I mean he likes to defend the nons
he Yeah cuz Peter Peter Peter there's
channels all over YouTube how many women
you said you're going to how many you're
going to like PJ you've been in trouble
with the police someone's tried to climb
through your window and you shut it you
had your house [ __ ] tormented by
London Taylor and you still don't
[ __ ] love it. You still don't learn.
I am coming Peter. You understand? And
Peter, when I come down Wednesday,
you'll be like, "No, you will run away
and hide." Okay. Okay. Let's have a
chat. Why can you defend your mom? Why
couldn't you defend your mom when J come
around? No. No. Honestly, serious
question. Why? I'm not neglecting Pete.
I'm telling the truth. Why couldn't you
defend your mom? because you're not
about it trying to show up to a bunch of
spastics who you're never going to
[ __ ] meet. I will see you Peter. You
know what's going to happen? I'll ring
your mom's doorbell. Your mom will come
out and press the buzzer and you'll I can
tell you one thing. You won't tell me to
shut up you on the floor. Okay, Peter. I
don't want to do anything.
You're not going to hurt no one, bro.
You couldn't even beat me with Tiger.
There there was it was a 2v one and you
still couldn't beat me three years ago.
You still couldn't you still couldn't beat me. You literally
you bro you couldn't even beat me with another person.
You can't take this guy serious, bro. Honestly, bro.
Oh my god. You couldn't even beat me
with another person, bro. So, how you
going to beat me by yourself?
You got to laugh, bro. Is it? Come on.
You've got to laugh.
I agree. You're still there, mate. You
need to put this on the cinema for
Wednesday. Yeah. You need to go to the
cinema and put YouTube on and watch this
in the cinema on Wednesday.
That would be [ __ ] beautiful, man.
You'll be let down though. You will be
let down because this [ __ ] ain't showing up anywhere.
Yeah. [ __ ] spaz.
Oh, [ __ ] me, bro.
This weird [ __ ] man. >> Hello.
>> Hello, PJ.
>> Yeah, I'm waiting. I'm waiting for this
[ __ ] to come on Wednesday. He's full of
>> Tim will always be skinned to this lush.
>> I know he is. I know he will be.
>> Teach him a lesson.
>> I will. Damn [ __ ] right. I will. Why
didn't he get in the cab the other day
when he said he was going to Mr. Bean?
>> He's a coward,
>> you know. He is doing it.
>> Proper coward, mate. Proper coward.
>> Smash his face in.
>> Yeah, I [ __ ] will.
this community. Of
you actually can't even take this
community seriously, can you?
You got [ __ ] LT doing videos on
Rick's. You got disbucking hell, bro.
Oh my god, bro.
Oh my [ __ ] god. Imagine
that, bro. Someone that's 42 trying to
look good for YouTube. What a [ __ ] embarrassment.
But yeah, deep down Timmy is a is
jealous. He's just a jealous individual.
Yeah, we've seen what Timmy looks like.
We know Timmy's skin. >> Yeah. Yeah,
you just got to look at the people in
here. Just ugly. Ugly as [ __ ] He is
ugly as [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, he's ugly as [ __ ] Look at Timmy,
bro. You can't even try and say that
Timmy ain't jealous. Of course he is,
bro. He's ugly. He's skinn. Look at
Timmy, bro. Look at a lot of these
people. He is [ __ ] ugly as [ __ ] bro.
Ugly as [ __ ] bro. Cuz he's a virgin.
Listen, how long has Timmy been on this
community? How many times have we seen
Timmy with a woman? Never. Never. Cuz
he's a virgin. Yeah, he's a [ __ ] virgin, bro. [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
Did you see his video on Rick's mace? LT,
did you see LT's video on Mix Mace?
Did you see it, bro?
I need to watch it. It's like 28 minutes
long. Jesus Christ, bro. [ __ ] hell. I
thought I'd done long videos.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
What is this? Come to Joseph Farra, you know.
But no, he deserved it because he he
annoys me, bro. This guy annoys me, bro.
How does he know about what uh Rick said
though, Joe? Unless he's watching.
How does LT know unless he's watching?
[ __ ] weirdo. It is so This is a
really weird community, bro. No, I
didn't start all of this [ __ ] Timmy
started all of this [ __ ] recently cuz he
won't keep my name out of his [ __ ] virgin mouth.
So, no, actually, Timmy started this
[ __ ] this time. Yeah, Timmy always
starts it though. Timmy always starts
it. He started it with Monty. He started
it, bro. He has actually started this.
We started it with a lot of people. And
I brought up LT to Rick. Yeah. But I
didn't tell LT um I didn't ask Rick to
start talking [ __ ] about him. I didn't stir anything.
I just said, "Oh, you cool with LT?" No,
I didn't stir anything. So yeah.
>> Yeah. This is just so weird, bro. It's
just so weird.
I didn't start any of this [ __ ] bro.
But this has been going on for far too
long, bro. So, I mean, if he's kind
enough to give me that chance and
actually come on Wednesday, he will see
what will happen to him.
He will see he will see what will happen to him.
I'm sick of it. No, I actually am sick
of it, bro. Seriously,
self-projecting virgin. He's [ __ ]
voice everything, bro.
Right. Hold on. I think LT is talking
about me. One sec.
Oh, you better be ready for uh
Wednesday, Grezy. Go plug [ __ ] Go
plug YouTube in the cinema screen with
your little popcorn and your little picker mix.
This is crazy. There's no way I'm
watching this London Taylor video on the
same website you can watch Robert the
Bear on Grezy.
It can't be, can it? It can't be. It
can't be. But listen, you're going to be
disappointed Wednesday, bro. Because if
this guy was really, really, really
going to come, he would be there. He
would come either tomorrow or Saturday.
Yeah. Cuz obviously it's busy Fridays,
it's busy Saturdays, right? So, um, if
he was really going to come, huh, Tim's
had a lot of reward. Tim's had a lot of
rewards if he wins fight against, bro.
He's not he's not going to beat me, bro.
Some fat [ __ ] like that is not going to beat me.
It's going to be a bull excuse from him.
Yeah, because if he was serious, he
would come tomorrow or Saturday. He's
not busy. He don't work. It's [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] He does this every time.
If I was going to meet someone for a
Okay, let's just say hypothetically,
right? I'm I'm listening to LT now. One
second because you're typing, bro. Yeah.
If you If I was going to meet someone,
say I had a problem with somebody in
Liverpool. Yeah. I would go there either
Friday or Saturday. Simple. There's You
wouldn't be going there Wednesday. Why
is he coming to London Wednesday?
Because it's [ __ ] He ain't going
nowhere. If he was going to go anywhere,
he would have Why can't he jump an hour
and 20 train tomorrow? It's [ __ ]
It's excuses. There's going to be another excuse.
He does. And he can't turn up alone
anywhere. He's a [ __ ] Like, he's
actually a [ __ ] trying to act hard on
YouTube. How does How is that possible,
bro? How can a How is a [ __ ] trying
to act the big man on YouTube? It don't make sense.
One second. I'm listen I'm listening to this LT.
Man's calling me an incel. Yeah, when he
trying to he trying to get with my
sloppy seconds. Man's trying to call me
an incel. He trying to call me an incel,
bro. When I've had more ass than he
would ever. Man's trying to call me an
incel. Yeah. Really? You're trying to
call me an incel? When have I ever ever
begged any woman on the internet? And
you're and you're calling me an insult,
bro. Come on. Come on now. Please. I'm
so much of an incel that you have to try
to message people that are my sloppy
seconds. That's how much of an incel I
am. But okay,
my friends I fell out with. What the
[ __ ] is this guy talking about, bro?
No one mentions your [ __ ] name. Not
like Timmy mentions my name. No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, this is funny, bro. This is funny.
Are you watching? Are you watching it, BC?
You're not watching it, are you?
So, I agree with you. You know, when you
made that comment earlier on Instagram,
please don't tell me you deleted it.
Please don't tell me you deleted it and
you was just doing it to show me
[ __ ] hell, bro. Someone is seriously
going to get killed on this website one
day, a Grey.
Oh, Grezy, someone is actually going to
get killed. Oh, look. I'm watching
Scream 7 on YouTube.
What website is that on
Yeah, but you're Yeah, but LT is kind of
contradicting himself because he's
saying, "Oh, well, that's a you
problem." Yeah. So, that's the same with
Red Star stalking me from the time he
wakes up to the time he goes to bed. I mean,
but you didn't think that was weird. So,
you're kind of contradicting yourself.
You're kind of contradicting yourself,
bro. To be fair.
All right. I'm this scream. uh trailer.
Grievy is not on the same website you
can watch Timmy Eldridge, is it?
That's not the same website you can
watch Timmy Eldridge, is it? Nah,
can't be. Can't be.
No, it can't be, bro.
I think you've been messaging Christian,
Izzy, haven't you? Greavvesy. I think
you know her name and everything. Seriously, Greavvesy,
I'm scared you might find her and stop messaging her.
I'm scared you'll find her, Grezy.
Not possible, bro. Not possible.
LT cool. LT called this a toxic sector. Grezy.
He called it a toxic sector.
I don't know why that just made me laugh.
So, what about Rit Bear?
Is he on a toxic uh sector?
Yep. He's talking about V straight away.
All right, bro. This is mad.
So what makes me an incel then? Because
I don't lick women's asses. Grezy, do
you know the thing is? Yeah, this incel
word needs to stop being overused. It
needs to seriously stop being overused.
It's boring now. It's very overused.
It's very boring. Like believe it or
not, Greasy. Yeah. Few years ago
there was a thing where people was like,
"Oh yeah, people were incelss and stuff
and there was actual documentaries." But
now now they'll call you an incel if you
just don't agree with women. If you just
don't if you
if you just uh am I lying a
you simply don't agree with white
knights and simps and you don't think
women are innocent, that's enough to be
called an incel. Am I lying? Be be
honest. Am I lying? Like they will call
anyone that doesn't lick a woman's ass
an incel. They they generally generally
generally do. It is true, bro. Like
that's the word they use now.
Like they really really if you do not
lick a woman's ass, they will call you
an incel. I'm not surprised. I'm
surprised you're not calling incel.
No, but there isn't no greasy because
I've given up with dating. I don't give
a [ __ ] about these women. I just think
that they're not I just think that that
what they do is nasty shitty things. So
what? That makes me an incel then. So
that makes me an incel even though I
don't even try anymore. No, it doesn't.
No, it [ __ ] does not.
I mean if you
like if you so much as complain, they'll
call you an incel.
that complaining is enough to be called
an incel, bro.
So, because I don't lick women's asses
and I don't believe in the double
standards, that makes me an incel. Even
though I don't even approach anymore,
even though I don't try, but I'm an
incel. How do you work that one out?
So, what would not make me an incel
then? Licking women's asses?
Like, tell us, bro. I want to know. Yeah.
I'm just I'm watching out here.
No, that doesn't make any sense what LT
is saying. Grezy, he's saying that he's
made an account. He's made a new account
to get away from these people. No, you
haven't. Because how many times has he
messaged How many times has he commented
on my channel? If he was making a
channel, right? No. No. If you was
making a channel to get away from these
people, they would never have found you.
Think about it. I've got a channel,
approaching channel. Yeah. No one knows
it. No one's ever going to find it. If
you was really trying to get away from
these people, no one you would no one
would find your channel. Am I lying,
Grezy? You've commented on live streams
and people have found you through live streams.
That's not trying to get away from these people. Yeah.
No, no, no. What he's saying doesn't
make sense because if you was trying to
get away from these toxic people, why
are you commenting on my [ __ ]
Because no one is ever going to find
this approaching um channel that I've
got. Why? Because I make sure I don't
comment on it.
Do you get what I'm saying? So, you
didn't try to get away from these people.
Trust me, if you was trying to get away
from these people, you would start fresh
and you would never come on here again
under your new account. That's what I do
with my new account. No one will never
find it. I will never comment on
anyone's [ __ ] So, that doesn't make any
sense. That does not make no sense at all.
A hunchback funny, bro.
Do you know what I might do? I might get
this screen mask. Greavvesy and me LT
with the screen mask.
Would you like to see that?
That's a legendary mask, but it just
like come up with like get a knife and
that in it
like they do with the scream. Is it Grezy?
What do you think? I'll be sick in it.
Yeah, man. Just get like a knife in it.
Okay. But what I just wearing a masky
So would that be a good video then
How did I go to the cinema? for today.
Greavesy if I've got anxiety. Huh?
If he's got anxiety his feet go. Yeah. LT.
Do you remember when LT had a problem
with me calling Nons a virgin, but he
didn't have a problem with nonslegs
calling me a virgin?
That was funny, bro. That was a funny
period, isn't it?
Very, very funny, isn't it?
He had such a problem, but he didn't
have a problem with people calling me. Strange.
Strange kid, bro. Strange kid.
So, it's it's a it's a toxic sector,
Greavvesy. I'm going to use that saying
from now on. Toxic sector.
This guy doesn't know about nothing.
Living with my mom at almost 30.
Firstly, I'm not almost 30. And second
of all, loads of people live with their
parents. people that are even older than
me in London or near near the London
area. And if you knew people, you would
know that. You think many people
nowadays in London are working here to
sp all their money on rent?
To sp all their money on rent?
Who's doing that, bro? Who's really
doing that? People in London, they
either live in a room or they or if they
have a partner or they live with their parents.
Special needs. Special needs. This guy's
trying to call me special needs, bro.
How many times have people have to
explain the same thing to you? And
you're calling me special needs.
And you're calling me special needs.
Yeah, that's funny, bro.
Okay, one sec.
Sort out myself. So now the guy is
trying to be a s. Sort out myself. When
have I ever begged a woman on the
internet, bro? When have I ever ever
ever begged a woman on the internet?
When have I ever ever ever begged a
woman on the internet, bro? Never in my life.
Never in my [ __ ] life, bro.
Like I done that video in 2026 because
it's facts. Cuz it's the truth, bro.
Yeah. Because that's what somebody
that's got a mind of their own would
say. Yeah. Simple, bro. One sec.
This guy doesn't make no sense, bro. You
know what? He He's calling people
special needs. Yeah. But all he's doing
is contradicting himself throughout the
whole video. He's literally just contradicting himself.
He's And I would say I've I've had more
ass than this guy, bro. Sir, bro, I've
had more ass than this guy. What? What
do you mean? No. No. No. No. No. Bro,
what do you mean? No. No. No. No. No.
You're loving this, isn't it, Grezy?
No one's go. ed you into smashing
anyone's house, you idiot. I asked you a
simple question. Why are you being
biased? Yeah. And then I said to you, I
don't believe that you've got kids. Who
has who has goded you? Who has goded you
to try to smash someone's house? Are you
mad, bro? Are you mad? Are you mad?
Yeah. You was You were saying stuff.
Yeah. And I wasn't And I wasn't going to
back down. Simple as that. I'm not some
little female that backs down. No one
was going you into smashing anything.
Yeah. No one was going you into smashing anything.
Yeah. I'm going to respond to this guy,
bro. He's talking so much [ __ ] Now he's
trying to [ __ ] stir. One second.
Well, he would you would have saw what
would have happened. Yeah. If you come
that day, which was the which was the
last time I was waiting for USA, you
would have saw what would have happened.
Yeah. Trust me. Trust me. You don't know
anything, bro. You really really don't
know anything. Yeah. No one's trying to
go you into anything. I just I was just
trying to stop you doing it because if
you did, bro, that's it. I'm going
prison. I don't give a monkeys. [ __ ] I
don't care. This has been going on for
too too too long now. And you know what?
Yeah. If you really have a problem, come
with Timmy on Wednesday. Come with Timmy Yeah. Simple.
You're more than welcome to come with
Timmy on Wednesday if you want. Yeah.
Simple. Because And that's the reason
why we brought your name up because you
always do it every time. Yeah. Simple.
Trust me. If he if bro if anyone come
that door that day, somebody would have
been getting it, bro. Trust me. Yeah.
Trust me. I was lying in bed. I was
lying in bed next to Crash. Yeah, I was
lying in bed next to Crash waiting, bro.
Didn't stir anything up. And that's the
one of the reasons I said I emailed you
saying, "No, there's cameras and cameras
and cameras, bro. Because you're not no
one's going to come and smash windows
and get away with it." Yeah, that was
that was your idea. Yeah, that was your
idea. Cuz I asked you why you're being
biased. Yeah, I want to respond to this
video, bro. One second. This guy needs
to get his facts. This guy needs to get
his facts straight. Yeah.
Bro, bro, listen. Listen. When your
friend come and smash the windows, I was
not even in the house. Yeah. Get your
facts right. I wasn't even in the
[ __ ] house. Yeah. Yeah. I proved I
was not in the house. Yeah. Multiple
multiple multiple multiple multiple
multiple times. Keep living in the past,
bro. Yeah. That's that's that's a that's
the fact you want to get right, bro.
That's the fact you really really really
want to get right. Yeah.
man said that I was I I was trying to
stir it. I weren't stirring it, bro. I
was trying to calm it down because if
anyone smashed the windows, they'd be
getting done the [ __ ] in.
Yeah, they'd be getting done the [ __ ]
in. And I mean it, bro. Like, you can
you can live three, four years in the
past, bro. No one cares about three,
four years in the past. Who knows? But
let me tell you something now, bro.
Anyone comes on here thinking they're
smashing up windows, bro, it ain't
happening. It ain't happening. Yeah. You
started that [ __ ]
Yeah. I'm going to do a video, bro,
putting this guy straight. Yeah, cuz
he's mentioning my [ __ ] name. Yeah,
he's mentioning my [ __ ] name. And
why? And and I mentioned you. Listen, I
mentioned you because you're going to
get involved. Yeah. With the whole Timmy
thing, you're going to get involved
because you're always watching that. You
say that you try and get away from these
people. If you're trying to get away
from these people, why are you
commenting on people's [ __ ] Simple. It
doesn't make sense. Doesn't make no
sense, bro. Like, you can't for someone
to say that someone's got special needs,
you're you're you're really
contradicting yourself, bro. Very very
very very contradicting yourself.
Like, you really are, bro. You are
actually contradicting yourself.
So before accusing people of having
special needs, you might want to not
contradict yourself as much in the
future, bro. You know what I mean?
This guy says that people are going him.
He said that people are going him. No
one's going you. I was asking you why
you was being a biased [ __ ] for somebody
that doesn't like biased people. I was
asking you a simple simple simple question
and then you and then I'm saying oh and
then you're trying to call me stuff
thinking that I'm not going to say
anything bro because you think I'm just
scared of you like these people. That's
what it is. Yeah.
Trust me. If someone was goating you,
they'd be talking about you every single
day. Yeah. They I would be talking mad
smack every single day.
You know what I'm saying, Grezy?
About females in 2026. Yeah. Cuz people
do make excuses for them. People do simp
over them. And and and what's your
point? It's the It's facts, bro.
know what I mean?
That's it, bro. Yeah. Know what I'm saying? Simple.
Yeah, 100%. I'm going to do a video back
to this guy, bro. He contradicts himself like mad.
No, he actually does contradict himself
like mad, bro.
Say that people have special needs. I'm saying
people's emailing you asking you why you
being a biased little [ __ ]
That's that's that's what people's
asking you. Yeah. For somebody that
doesn't like that doesn't like a biasist.
Yeah. For some that doesn't like people
being biased with a question. Yeah. Mercy, bro.
Man's telling me I ain't got no friends,
but the guy don't even know me. The guy
has never met me, he doesn't [ __ ]
know me that. You know what I'm saying?
Is it okay if I do a video back in
return? Can I do a video in response?
Can I do a video in return?
Is that all right with you? Gucci boss.
No. Have you watched his video, bro?
He's talking proper mad [ __ ] bro. He's
talking bad [ __ ]
Yeah, he's talking mad mad mad mad [ __ ]
You don't see someone saying You don't
see someone doing videos about you every
single day, bro.
Just because someone's not going to let
you like start trying to bully them or
that. That's people go. That's people
going you on.
Yeah. Right, bro. Yeah, [ __ ] right.
You know what I'm saying?
Guy is a [ __ ] mad. He's a bad [ __ ] Yeah.
as [ __ ] Like, this guy is [ __ ] bro.
No, he's mentioning my [ __ ] name,
bro. He's mentioning my name. Don't try
and say that people are trying to go
you. Yeah, Timmy is what you call trying
to go people, trying to draw people the
[ __ ] out, which is what he was doing on his channel.
You know what I'm saying? No one. All I
All I emailed him, right, Stephen Howard
was, "Why is this guy got such a problem
with me calling Longlegs a virgin
because of the guilt?" But then when is
calling me a virgin, someone that's
proved they've had sex. You don't have
the same You don't have the same energy.
That's all I asked
for somebody that doesn't like biased
people. It was a question. It's a It was
just a question.
It was just a simple dimple question
that he tried to turn it into something
the [ __ ] else. Do you know what I'm saying?
You know what I mean?
Imagine bragging, bro. Imagine, you
know, that's another thing. Imagine
trying to brag about smashing an old
woman's house, thinking that makes
someone hard, bro. Imagine actually
trying to like brag about that, bro. It
doesn't it doesn't make no sense.
It doesn't doesn't make any sense. So,
you might want to make sense before
trying to call other people's special needs. Yeah.
And if you really want to get out of
this little sector, then maybe refrain
from messaging people under your [ __ ]
account and then they won't find you
because ain't no one found my channel,
bro. And ain't no one gonna find my channel,
you know? And then you're trying to brag
about making an old woman scared, bro.
Seriously. [ __ ] seriously, bro.
You know what I'm saying, lad?
You know what I'm saying, brother?
It's [ __ ] weird. It is weird, lad.
Yeah. And then you're telling people
you're saying that people are go and
you're trying to say people are going
you. Please, bro. Yeah.