[ __ ] Sorry, my phone
died. Yeah, about that. Had to do some
stuff. Nah, man. You people really are
weirdos, aren't you? Proper proper
stalking. You know what? On my way back
here, I was walking for like half hour
like these people in this community are
are proper autistic.
Like that's why they create the same
atmosphere every day because they're
proper bongos. I was actually thinking
about that. They're actual proper proper
bongos on this
community. Same people, same accounts,
same self projection. It's a madness,
bro. You don't know where I live. You do
not know where I live. And another thing
I wanted to say is why do you even want
to know where I live? Like are you
obsessed with me or something? Like you
want my Yeah, I'm like no I'm not there.
I've just explained that for the past 10
minutes. I'm not talking about this
anymore. You people are
weirdos. You people are absolute
weirdos. Yeah. I can swear to you on
anything I like. I don't And if you
think I live there, that's on you, bro.
I don't really care. If you think I live
there, then Well, you know where I live
then, don't you? Apparently. And why are
you so asked about where people live?
This is what I'm saying with you people.
It's autism, is it? It's got to be
autism. It's got to be autism, isn't it?
It has to be, bro. It's got to be autism
and jealousy. It's got to be, bro. It
has to be with you people. It's No, no,
no. It has to be. 100%. It has to be.
Can I come around? You can't come around
anywhere because I don't live there. You're
weirdos. Absolute weirdos. Why do you
think I gave that
address? Why do you think I said the
company and I gave that address? You're
weirdos. You're absolute weirdos. You're
obsessed. You know what I'm saying?
Fancy. Uh, no thanks. Because you don't
know where I live and you will never
know where I live. [ __ ] YouTube
spastics. You people are obsessed. Oh my
god. I and you know the maddest thing
about it as well is that why would you
even want to know where I live because
you would never do anything anyways. I
don't understand why would you and you
wouldn't even send posters cuz said he's
not even doing it anymore. Why would you
actively try to find out where someone
lives when you're not going to do
nothing? Like are you obsessed? Are you
gay? Like do you want to bum someone or
something? Do you want to do you want to
come to their house and bum them or
something? Because if you're gay, it's
fine. It's fine if you're gay. I've got
nothing against gay people, you know? It's
fine. Like, if you're gay, bro, it's it's all
good. It's all good if you're gay.
There's nothing wrong with being gay,
but just admitting that. Just admit it.
You people are [ __ ] weirdos. Absolute
weirdos. Guess what? All of my clothes
are at my [ __ ] mom's house. Does that
mean I live at my mom's house? No. Weirdos. Absolute
weirdos. When? Let me ask you this question.
Seriously, when are you people going to
get off of YouTube and get a light?
There's a serious cuz I'm
I'm I was walking back here and I'm
thinking I think about this sometimes.
Yeah. When are you people going to get
off of YouTube and actually get yourself
a life get yourself laid instead of
coming on this community every day
trying to troll people but you're not
good enough to do it? Like when are you really really
really just going to like when are you
just going to get off of YouTube and get
a life? And I'm probably half your age
as well saying this stuff, you
know. When are you going to get off of
YouTube and actually get a life? Look at
yourself in the mirror and be like,
"Fuck, I'm I'm too old for this. I need
a life." So, have you got disabilities?
You must have disabilities. You people
must have disabil. The day I go live and
nobody comes on YouTube, right, and no
one comes on YouTube projecting, I'll
say I'm wrong. But that will never
happen because I'm right about all of
you people on here. You're [ __ ]
weirdos. Absolute [ __ ]
weirdos. I'll give you £1,000 if you can
stay off of YouTube for a week. Nah, you can't do
it. How come I had to get a new fridge?
Stop asking stupid
questions. Anyways, we're over this anyways,
bro. You're weirdos, man. You're actual
you're actual stalkers too, bro. Why
give like fake addresses? I swear to
God, you're actual
stalkers. Like, you want to know where
someone lives? You don't know where I
live. But then even if you by the off
chance found out where I live, then
what? You're never going to come and do
anything. Autism, bro. These people in
this community have got proper proper
autism. It's bad autism. And again,
that's why they say that you've got it
because it's their own lives, their own
selves. They talk about their own lives
every day. [ __ ] that gave you the [ __ ] bro. That
breakfast. Yeah. A month. It would never
happen, mate. It would never happen.
These people can't go a day off of
YouTube, let alone a [ __ ] week, let
alone a month. They can't. YouTube is
all that these people have.
Do you know what I'm saying? Bye-bye
now. I didn't tell him
that. YouTube is all these people
have. Bye-bye. We're not talking about this no
more. You don't know where I live. End of
story. But you still didn't answer my
question. Why do you want to know where
I live when you're never going to come
and do anything?
It's [ __ ] weird. You don't know where
I live and you will never know where I
live. I am not talking no more about it.
If you think you know where I live so
much when you don't, come in the door
and record it
then. Simple. You people are [ __ ]
weirdos, man. Absolute
weirdos. There's only one way to find
out. And there you
go. And I don't even find the drama
funny. I think you all weirdos,
man. I think you're all weirdos, buddy.
You know what I'm
saying? Stalking little self-projected
little weirdos. Most of the people on
here that hate yet, they're basement
dwellers. Fat, ugly, in their 40s. They
got no money and which is why they're on
here every day doing what they do.
That's proof in the
pudding. They got nothing in their
lives. They got nothing going for
themselves. That's why they're on here
every day. Trust me. Truest. Truth be
told. No, not in this community.
No, I don't watch anyone of this [ __ ] down
community. They're weirdos, man. They're absolute weirdos. Weirdos.
All my stuff is at my [ __ ] mom's and
um I don't have nothing here, bro.
Yeah, go for it, man. Why
not? I'm [ __ ] tired, man. After that
breakfast and that [ __ ] beer.
Yeah. Give it a whirl,
eh? Give it a good old
whirl. I mean, I'm still on a detox. I
had one bit, but it was only one. It
doesn't count, does it? Only one beer,
does it? Hey, does it count? No. Nah,
bro. Maybe I will. Maybe I will.
What do you reckon will happen if I go
out Saturday approaching women brick
bomb? What do you reckon the response will
be? What do you reckon the response will
be? I don't I don't really drink much anymore, bro.
Doesn't matter how hard you send it,
you're still going to get the same I've
got a boyfriend.
Maybe a couple of numbers that [ __ ] you
around. It will still be the same old.
It will always be the same
old. Doesn't matter how hard you send
it. That's why I don't bother no more. I
didn't go out last week. Not going out
this week. Not going out next week. Nah,
it's boring. It's the same old. Well,
you never know. Um, I know because I
went out um last Tuesday. I went out
last Tuesday doing it. So I [ __ ]
know, mate. I [ __ ] know cuz I went
out Tuesday. I went out last Thursday as
well. Um, last Tuesday and then the first day.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Um, no. If you try,
you're just going to get the same [ __ ]
No, no, no, no, no, no. If you try,
you're just going to get the same old
I've got boyfriends. You're just going
to make yourself worse. Trying makes it
worse because when you try, you're going
to get the same negative results and
it's going to drive you insane. You're best giving
up. That's what I designed it to do.
There's no point trying when it's always
going to be the same result as it's been for
years. So, no, it's a mug's game. If you
try, you're just going to keep getting
the same results. I recorded some
uh Yeah, you might have got free
numbers. I get numbers. I go out, I get
numbers. But guess what? The numbers are
not going to go
anywhere. Doesn't matter if you got
numbers. I always get numbers. But the
numbers don't go anywhere. If you keep
trying, you're just going to make
yourself worse. It's not just giving up
and going to Asia. That's my odd. Even
just like another country.
Yeah. I'll probably just give up for
like six weeks like I did last time to be
fair. Just give up for like six
weeks. So yeah, you're best off giving
up. I I'll send you some approaches I
done on Tuesday if you if you're
interested. Now you should give up,
man. You should definitely definitely give
up. The negative experiences. It's
[ __ ] It's boring, man. These are two
approaches I don't I know a lot of them,
but these are some two.
No, that was last Tuesday. So it was a
week today actually.
Yeah. Yeah, it was a week
today. Wasn't the best I had to be honest.
Nah. Now when you actually go out and
you try Brit Bong Dez, you would know
exactly what I mean. Trying doesn't
change your situation in this country.
I feel like calling it at 27. Not even
joking. Just calling it at 27. It's [ __ ]
boring. It's so boring. Like, it's not
even just that. It's like, why should
you have to go out and deal with their
attitude? Why should you have to go out
and deal with stuck up
[ __ ] Even if you was to get
somewhere in the end, it's like, why
would you even disrespect yourself like
that when you don't need to, you know,
with these stuck up [ __ ] [ __ ] that,
bro. [ __ ] trying, bro. [ __ ]
that. I'm going to sleep. I'm [ __ ] tired. Yes.
I recorded like
three. Yeah, [ __ ] trying,
bro. Don't know why people would tell me
to keep trying old
result. But you think I I could stay out
all day today if I wanted to and send it
easily, bro. Very
easily. But why would I do that?
Who in their right mind would do that,
bro? When it's just the same adult. It's boring. It's boring. I'm
saying I won't sleep soon, bro.
Tired. Nice beer.
Well, this is what I'm saying to you,
Grezy. When I say that these these
people in this community, right, they
don't have any life experience. I'm not
being awkward. I'm not trying to say,
"Oh, I know everything." But the way
they speak about women and stuff, they
have no life experience. Like if you
went out there, right, and you actually with
women and you would actually know what
they're like and how it actually is, you
know, it's all well and good basement
dwelling white knights saying, "Oh, it's
not women's fault. Oh, it's your
attitude." But these people don't know
anything because think about it. When
was the last time these people left
their basement? Probably a [ __ ]
decade ago. You understand? They don't know
anything. They literally don't know
anything about [ __ ] No. Well, when
you're approaching, you're trying to get
in a relationship. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no. Because when you're
approaching, you're trying to get in a relationship by
approaching. You know, whether
it's a relationship, whatever it is you
want, they're still going to say they've
got boyfriends. It doesn't matter what
the [ __ ] you want from
them. They literally just don't know how
women work. They literally don't. They
have no life experience. They really don't. My chance.
Well, want a relationship. They're still
going to say they've got
boyfriends. You know, it doesn't matter. Yeah.
So that's it, bro. Isn't
it? It told me to keep fishing. Keep
want me to keep fishing. [ __ ] that for a game of
soldiers. And now the weather's getting
humid now. It's even more tiring thinking about
it. You can't win in this country. It's
either too hot or too
cold. You know what I'm saying? Greedy.
[ __ ] Too hot or too [ __ ] cold. It is bro. I'm
tired. I'm leaving this community.
You're [ __ ] weird,
man. But yeah, anyways, I'm trying to
get a relationship by approaching
Grezy. What's the excuse
there? What's the excuse there?
Oh, darling, you really are unchanged.
Greezy, what do you think about that?
Greasy. Well, I mean, dating apps don't work, Greezy.
So, you know, dating apps don't work.
So, I mean, I thought I'd try the old school way.
Greasy. The old school way.
Re. Oh, darling, you really are
unhinged. Why did that make you laugh though,
Greasy? Oh, sweetie. You really are
unhinged. Why? Why does that make you laugh? Yes.
Why did that make you laugh though,
Greasy? Now, she was being weird though
about that Australia because she was
like, "Yeah, you should try and find
somebody that can give you the attention
that you need." So, I'm thinking like,
"Well, what's the point of even going on
a date with someone if you're not like,
so you got a date?" See, the thing is,
right, these people go on dates to pass
time or to use you. They don't go on
dates seeing you as a potential partner
or a potential shack. They just do it to
pass time. Like, they'll just go on
dates full of lows. That's what a lot of people don't understand. So,
yeah, that's what a lot of these people
don't understand. They ain't got no life
experience in this community. That's
what I'm saying. These people in this
community have zero life
experience. I'd say you've got more life
experience than them, Grievy, and you're
[ __ ] younger than
them. Do you know what though? I
sometimes think these people in this
community are robots cuz they repeat
themselves for years. It's the same
people for years. It's like they're
robots, you know? Same spastics. Like
you see that newest Phil Slugger
account? That's Bastic. I saw my body the other
day. And he thinks he's so good at
trolling, but he's such a downy. Like he
is such a proper proper dowy. Like he
has a Louiswis Phil Slugger account and
then a Louiswis Phil Slugger 2 account
and he is just such a big
dowy but he thinks he's good at trolling
but he's not. He's just a [ __ ] dowy, bro.
[ __ ] Louisville [ __ ] slugger.
Yeah. Oh, music, mate. Music. yeah.
Yeah. I mean, you can be a weirdo at
time, Grezy. You can be a weirdo at
times, but not as bad as these
mongos. Do you know what? I sometimes
wonder why they do what they do every day on
here. I really do, bro.
Yeah, I was speaking to one of the
neighbors. Well, up the road, Grezy.
He's an old man and apparently his
neighbors were trying to get him out,
like calling him a queer, calling him
this, calling him that. Like, they've
been trying to get him out that house um
by complaining. I was dead. I said,
"Well, I can't exactly call you a queer because I
mean just because obviously you're not
gay, but even if you was gay, what are they
[ __ ] homophobic or sexist or
what? That doesn't make sense. They can't
I just messaged my mom. I ain't supposed
to [ __ ] ages.
What? So yeah, that's the thing, man.
But yeah, it doesn't how can they call
you a queer and try to get you [ __ ]
out your house, bro? It doesn't make
sense. But apparently like he's had
loads of um
um people have been complaining about
him. That's mad,
bro. That's [ __ ] wild, bro.
Yeah, you know what he said? Uh,
England's got a new one of the new
managers, a German guy. Greavvesy tall [ __ ] he
is. I told the old man about USA. Is he?
And I said, "You would go there,
wouldn't you?" He's like, "Too [ __ ] right." I
would grey. He was like, "Too [ __ ]
right." I would. He said, "Yeah, old
[ __ ] He's got to be in his in his
70s. He's got to be in his 70s. I'm sure
he's in his
70s. Yeah, it's all [ __ ] who he is."
Yeah. That's [ __ ] embarrassing.
Oh, should have got it. You should have got it,
mate. You should have got
your Where's it going, sir? That's
Almost should be One second.
No, he's not doctor me. He doesn't know
where I live.
I see you got
One second, guys.
They've got this parcel. Hold on.
Yeah, I did get delivered. Yeah.
Yeah, it did get delivered. You got freaking
mug. All right. Be back later.