We are, bro.
[ __ ] hell. How the [ __ ] did I wake up
at this bloody time? I woke up late, bro. Yeah.
[ __ ] Yeah, I woke up late, man. Late.
still calling people a month of virgin in 2026.
I don't know how these people can can
can do this every Well, it doesn't
matter how many times you explain it to
them. They're backwards. I don't know how like
you know what. Yeah, I would love
somebody to join the panel one day and
explain it to me. But how you can sit on
YouTube? I've just gone on Joe's
channel. I've just seen this um thing. I
was waiting for it. How you can sit on
the internet being jealous of a man you
don't know every day.
This is called the disabled backwards
sector more than anything. Um, and stop
telling people they're back again, lad.
You can't even take a day off of
YouTube, which has already been proven.
You're on you, As soon as I'm live,
you're straight on my channel. Um, so I
don't know what you're trying to take
the piss out of. You can't even take one
day off of YouTube. Not even if it not
even to save your life. Not even one day
off of YouTube. That's already been
proven, lad. So, stop trying to take the
piss. And it's weird, bro.
[ __ ] me. I've got more I've got more
people obsessed with me than [ __ ]
Timmy does, bro. That's facts.
What is it with these closeted men on
this community? They need to come out
the closet as gay.
You know, that wasn't your day. I feel
like you're on YouTube every day, man.
You're on YouTube every day. Calling
people monsters that are better looking
than you. Calling people virgins that's
proved they've had sex. One of these
people actually going to get a life.
You're supposed to be like you're
supposed to be a role model. You know,
you're older than me. You're you're
supposed to set a good example. You
know, they say that you're supposed to,
you know, learn stuff from your elders.
And all you people have done for the
past 15 years is come on here and talk
about people that you don't know. You're [ __ ] weirdos.
Honest to God, you actually, you know,
the whole thing about like this
community is just disabled. Like, forget
about like the whole people not having
lives or whatever. [ __ ] all of that for
a second. Yeah. The [ __ ] you do on this
community is so so so disabled.
Coming online every day talking about
men that you don't know. It's so disabled.
You know, I feel like I'm I'm I'm like
I'm I'm like I'm like going down to your
level, bro. When I was replying to this
LT yesterday, I'm thinking, bro, what
the [ __ ] am I even [ __ ] doing? The
whole thing is so disabled. All of it
is. What you people do on here. It's
weird. It is so [ __ ] weird.
No, honestly, it is. It No, no, no. It
generally generally generally generally
is. That's not somebody being that's not
somebody being triggered. That's talking facts.
And we know it's jealousy as well. We
know deep down with you people it's
jealousy as well. We know you know deep
down it is because if you had anything
in your lives, you wouldn't come online
talking about people every day. It's
[ __ ] weird, bro.
It's [ __ ] weird, lad. It is so weird
what you people do on here. It is weird.
It is proper weird
calling people that are better than you
every day. What a life, bro. What a life
you people have. Sad [ __ ] So yeah,
thanks for the two thumbs up on my LT
video. Yeah, I'm right. You know I'm [ __ ] right.
You know I'm [ __ ] right, bro. You
can't start calling people disabled. You
can't start calling people special needs
when you're constantly contradicting
yourself. How about do a video where you
don't contradict yourself?
Why am I even arguing with these low
life people, bro? Like I don't even know
why I'm even arguing with these little low lives.
[ __ ] 3:00 in the [ __ ] bastard
morning. In the bastard [ __ ] morning, bro.
Yeah, but what's going on, man?
That's funny, bro.
How you people like, yeah, we're just
talking about these weirdos, Bob, that
sit on here and call men that they don't
know every day. It's so It's just such a
disabled sector, a disabled community.
It's not a toxic sector. It's a disabled
I went on Joe's video and I see this
person saying, and I don't care. It
doesn't trigger me. I'm just saying like
what they do is just weird. Obviously,
it doesn't nothing they say bothers me.
They just talk about themselves. Just
remember while someone like yourself
post great when somewhere else there is
a virgin mon crying over losing 20
pound. You're talking about men at 8:00
in the morning, bro, that you don't even
know. Like you literally wake up and
you're straight onto YouTube cuz you
ain't got no life and you're talking
about other men. It's a disabled
community. That's what I'm saying, bro.
We don't call this community disabled
for nothing. They are severely severely
in denial, bro. If these people don't
think that they're jealous of something,
if they truly think that they're not
jealous of something, they've got to be,
bro. They have got to be. I've tried I
have tried putting myself in their shoes
multiple multiple times. these fat, ugly
old men that have got no life. Um, and
you just wouldn't do it. Someone that's
got more more than you in life, someone
that's got everything would not come on
YouTube talking about men. Nuh-uh.
Uh-uh. No way. Trust me. Unless people
are jealous of something. That's the
only reason these people would do what
they do. And that's it. And I'm not even
reacting. I'm I'm still I'm talking
facts. People are allowed to have an
opinion on what on what these people do.
And it's the truth. It's 100% the truth.
You wouldn't do this to a woman that you
was obsessed with and in love with. They
casually do it to men every day because
they're jealous. Because they're
jealous. It doesn't matter. Every day it
will be the same. It will be the same
people doing it. It is jealousy. It's
the same thing with Timmy. Jealousy.
That's why they do this, bro. That is
exactly why they do this on this community. Facts, man.
So now he's not coming to London.
Nah, they just they're just weirdos,
bro. They just need to get a life, lad.
They just need And no, there's no
gambling, bro. I'm done with that [ __ ]
I went cinema yesterday. I'm going to
have a sweet in a minute. Yeah, man.
Yeah. No gambling. I'll do a football
bet tomorrow and that's it, lad. Yeah, man. Yeah.
Do you like my little video I posted?
I was waiting for a reply back.
I was waiting for a reply back, but I
didn't get it, lad.
Why is that? Cuz you know I'm [ __ ]
right. That's why. Cuz you know I'm
Cuz you know I'm [ __ ] right. That's why.
This is crazy, bro. Someone tagged me in
something. The UK biggest nonser. And
you know what? I'm reading this and I'm
thinking, lad, like
I'm still talking to her and I'm not
talking about my business on here, bro.
It's as simple as that. Yeah.
Just listen to your just listen to your
video on LT. Why won't you stop lying?
He asked you. No, no, no, no, no. What
he told me was his cousin was going to
come on the door and slap my mom in her
face. Yeah. You stop lying. Everyone saw
it. Yeah. And this is what I mean with
this people in this community. Hey, did
you see my video on LT?
Did you see my video on LT, bro?
It's facts, bro. Is it? It's actually
You You contradict yourself a lot.
You're an offer a big hypocrite for
someone that's got that that's
apparently not special needs. Rare r
you're enough you're enough um you're
you're enough contradict yourself. I'll
give you that bro. You really really do. [ __ ] idiot.
I hate these people, you know, bro. I
hate these people. Seriously, bro, on
this community, bro, I really, really,
really, really do. And it's jealousy
with them as well. This is why they do
all of this [ __ ] It is jealousy deep
down. That's that's that that is the
thing about it, bro.
That is the thing about with with this
disabled community. It's just a disabled
community, bro. I swear to God, it puts
me in a bad mood as well, you know.
That's why I was in a bad mood
yesterday. Yeah. Because of these
people. They put you in a bad mood.
How was I calling out Timmy Greavvesy
when he was when he was mentioning my name?
When he was mentioning my name.
And it's okay for him to go for notch
legs. It's okay for him to want to beat
up notch legs. But when it's me or you
go for the weaker target,
[ __ ] off, bro. You've been doing this
for years now. [ __ ] off.
You know what I'm saying? [ __ ] off. I
don't know what's for dinner, bro. I'm
not sure. Yeah. And now he said he's not
coming. I never said I was going to meet
Timmy. I said if he if he knocked on the
door and he come on the door. Yeah. He's
he's finished. That's it. Simple.
Yeah. Simple as that, bro.
But yeah, that LT, he shouldn't know
about any of people in this community.
People should know about his channel.
Grieves. You think about it. If you
actually made a channel to get away from
this community, people wouldn't have
found you. Do you understand? People
wouldn't have found you.
You understand? So that doesn't make
sense to begin with.
If you're off here, you're off here the
same as the same as Ant-Man.
My no one knows my new channel. It's got
My new channel's got one subscriber.
My new channel's got one subscriber and
it's not any of you people. this
community, mate. So,
yeah, we've heard it all before, bro.
Well, they never they never found me. Uh-uh.
I was talking to Christian, Izzy, last
night. No, no, no, no, no. But with this
guy, No, no, no, no, no. But with this
LT guy, he's commented on my live
streams. That's how they found him.
They found him because he's actually
commented on on pe with people on this
community. That's what I'm trying to
say. That doesn't make any sense.
He's trying to say Nons is a weaker
target. He's trying to say nonsense is a
weaker target. Oh, this guy is so
hypocritical, bro. It's unbelievable.
This guy is so so so hypocritical.
It's It's unreal, bro. It's unreal.
You know, the thing is with this guy,
um, Harry F. Yeah. Let me tell you right
now. Yeah. If there was another person
on this community, right, that um that
matched his energy, right, that like
went to the gym or trained, I don't
think he would meet them. I generally
generally generally don't think he would
meet them, bro. What I think Yeah. He's
come across this little spasticated
sector. Yeah, where he knows people are
not going to meet him because I mean,
let's face it, they won't even meet me.
And he takes advantage of it. I
generally don't think he would. I
generally generally generally don't
think he would, bro. And I'm not even
trying to wind people up. I don't think he would, you know,
cuz on this community with these
spastics, he feels like he feels like
the man. You get it? Because, you know,
no one's going to, you know, just no
one's going to meet. So,
yeah. Funny how it's this [ __ ]
community as well for the spastics. I
don't meet anyone. Yeah.
Oh, the Rick's mace bit was funny though, Grezy.
The Rick's mace bit was funny.
Did you watch it, Grezy?
That was funny as [ __ ] bro.
I don't know what I'm going to get
today. Maybe a curry. Yeah.
Yeah. He always watches. He's He always
for someone that's not a part of this community.
I was watching Timmy's I was watching
Timmy's um I was watching Timmy's vlog
because I thought he was just going to
talk about gambling and he started
mentioning my name.
So that's how I know cuz Timmy's the
only I've only sub to Timmy and Monty. Yeah.
So this is all started from Timmy basically. Yeah.
This is basically all started from Timmy.
So what you're saying Gre is Timmy's the root cause.
Yeah, he is.
I think um yeah basically basically yeah
I don't know what am I going to do two teams tomorrow
or am I going to do three teams
I'm going to I think I'm going to do two
but I'm going to stick with my
Yeah, bro. I think yeah
about losing 20 in a fobte. Well, duh.
Of course I cried about losing 20 pound
in a fy cuz it's not about the money.
And it was yesterday, man.
No, bro. It's um I'm doing the both
teams just go on a specific team to win.
And I don't think you're going to get four.
Don't think you're going to get four.
I think everyone in this community just
needs to meet up for a drink and just
squash this [ __ ] What do you think, Greavvesy? LT,
Mark, Samson, Terry, we could all have
like a night out
and put it put it to rest. What do you
think? Like a good old piss up.
Everyone has a little meet up. What do
you think? What do you think, Grezy?
Have like a little or like a little house party. You know,
it sure is, Captain.
It sure is, Captain.
I could do I could do with a lovely
pint, Grezy. Pint of beer. Yep.
I could deal with do with a lovely pipe,
bro. Can't lie. But sorry, bro. I'm on a detox, lad. way.
These are yummy.
The only funniest thing is I only have
one meat. I only have one sweet in the
pick a mix. I literally only have one sweet. Yeah. Like crazy.
When I went to the mall yesterday, I got
I got a can of I got a a a plastic
bottle of Coke. I was going to get two,
but there was only one. You know, like
when you go sainsburries and like you
know the fridge bit where they're cold.
the other fridge bit where they're cold.
Um, I bought one wasn't to save money. I
actually done a video at the cinema.
It's cuz I don't like Pepsi
and they only have Pepsi at the cinema.
I don't like Pepsi.
It's I only like Pepsi. I don't know
about anyone else, but
I don't like Pepsi.
So, I I had to make it last obviously
cuz the popcorn's quite big. I just had
to make the Coke last.
Um, there used to be a Coke machine.
Never stalked women. Simpo.
Never ever stalked to women. Simpo.
We're not talking about women, lad.
Don't Don't kill the mood. Don't kill
the vibe, bro.
That kills the vibe in it, Greasy. When
people talk about women and dating,
don't kill the vibe, lad.
Don't kill the vibe, bro.
That's depressing. Don't talk about
that. That's depressing.
That is depressing.
Ew. O, did you add it to your saying
collection, Grezy? Ew. A simp.
No. A wild simp.
Have you added it to your collection?
Your saying collection.
A wild simp.
The Powerpuff Girls.
I come up with that one.
What about this little toxic sector, Grezy?
this little toxic sector that made I
don't know why that kind of that made me
laugh yesterday. This little this little toxic sector.
I don't know why that made me laugh, bro. Um
I I'm going to get I'm going to get a screen mask.
I think I'm going to get a screen mask.
Is that okay with you, boss?
I'm going to get one online, I think.
No, you need you need you need a
costume, don't you, Grezy? Oh gosh. Grezy,
do you reckon I can get the screen mask from Amazon? Yeah, definitely.
I used to have one and you and you
squeeze it and blood comes out. [ __ ] hell.
And they still have it. £753.
Yeah, that's the same one I had all them years ago.
It needs to be a costume, I reckon.
I like it when he calls them up. He
says, "Do you want to play a little game?"
Yeah, but what size is it?
He says, "Do you want to play a little game?
Yeah. What is that horror film called?
that Elijah Woodson.
One second. Horror.
It's called It's coming out. This is
coming out soon.
I ain't seen that [ __ ] for a long time,
bro. There's one called Passenger as well.
So what does that make me? Um copying LT saying Greavesy.
Release date March 20th.
What does that make me?
Okay, Greasy. Well, I like I like X Factor.
Yeah, I was I was speaking to Christian
yesterday, Grezy. She was saying about
like she's stressed and stuff. We was
having a little chat
at 3:00 in the morning. Grezy
3:00 in the morning. Grezy, how cute is that? Passenger film. Right.
So, that's coming out. It's coming out
in May. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah. I don't like it, Greasy, when
there's loads of people at the cinema. I
like it when I'm by myself. There was
someone sat next to me and you know when
you could just feel people around you. I
just wanted to watch the film in peace.
We It's nice when you're the only one at the cinema.
I've had it before when I'm the only one
at the cinema. It's peaceful.
Yeah, it's quite peaceful.
But obviously that was going to happen,
isn't it? You know, the new screams out. So,
it was going to happen. I'll never
forget that day I went on Valentine's
Day in Gree. I was the only one there.
I was the only one at the cinema
back where I used to live. It was lush,
bro. Oh my god, it was lush.
It was [ __ ] lovely.
But to be fair, it weren't bad
yesterday. People weren't like people
weren't talking or fake laughing. You
know, sometimes when there's loads of
people at cinema, people just like talk
throughout the whole thing. Uh,
so I need to top up on my vitamins today, Grezy.
Yep. I need to top off on my little vitamins.
Hurry up. [ __ ]
hurry up, Christian. [ __ ] hell. This
is getting expensive. Where's he?
Do you want me to Do you want me to get
a Scream costume, Grezy, and go around
like the mall with like a knife? Like a
like the plastic knife they give you?
put it on YouTube
to see the reactions that I get like
just dress up.
Oh, that'd be a lovely site, is it, Grezy?
Uh, no, I'm not going out tonight. I
don't go out drinking,
as you know.
As you know.
As you know,
you know what I don't like about the
cinema though, a lot of the staff have
got attitude in it, Grezy.
I don't know if you've noticed well,
you've not been cinema much, have you?
But they've got like a lot of them have
got attitude, don't they? You know,
a lot of bus drivers do as well.
A lot of bus drivers do as well.
Maybe not where you live, but uh yeah, a
lot of bus drivers have attitude.
Like you could tell by their body
language and stuff. Grievy.
Miles McCoy leaves the Miles McCoy lad.
I wonder if he knows about Mick Jonathan Robinson.
Yeah, I wonder if he knows about Mick
Jonathan Robinson and his dark dark but
very devious past.
Nah, bet he doesn't, does he? Disgusting [ __ ] Oh,
Grezy, speaking of washing machines, I
need to do a little video to Rick.
Look, my bed's there. Look that I washed.
my bed is washed there. It's going to
smell very It smells very nice, Grezy.
So, should I do that video to Rick? How
to use a washing machine, Grezy?
Cuz I need to do another load of washing
at some point.
I can I can I can I can teach him the ways.
Now, do you know what makes me laugh the
most about this YouTube is how everyone
knows each other's channel. Like there's
there's Robert the Bear Grievy. There's
Rit the Bear, there's Spongebob, there's
Scream. All on the same website you can
watch Timmy Eldridge.
Do you understand what I mean, Grezy?
All on the same website. You can watch Timmy Eldridge.
It's a little sector, isn't it? This
place is a little It's the toxic sector. Yeah.
I wouldn't even say that it's toxic.
It's just weird.
I would say it's just more weird and
negative. What about you, Greavvesy?
I get what you mean by toxic, but I'd
say it's more weird and negative. Yeah,
Timmy's just jealous of Peter Belly, lad.
Yep. He always sleeps well.
I know he's a virgin. That's why he
calls me a virgin cuz he's a virgin himself.
He's a little He's a little non legs
lover. Oh. Oh, you know Nles has got a
couple of quid. 22 grand. No, he doesn't
have a couple of quid and he doesn't
have 22 grand. Oh, and I thought the
pass doesn't count anyways.
Such a disabled community. This is, bro.
I know. He's a virgin. He's a virgin.
He's skin. He's alive. He's just like
nons. He's nons his brother. There's crash grieving.
He's a cute little toy. Any Grezy? Oh
no, bro. You know when I went to the
cinema? Yeah. No, no, no, no. Greasy.
When I went to the cinema yesterday,
because they're self projecting, Leslie,
you saw my video on LT, right? You saw
my video on LT.
LT defends [ __ ] nonslegs. I call legs
a virgin, but when calls me a virgin, he
lets it slide. Weird when he says he
doesn't like biased people. But anyways,
when I went cinema, Grezy,
you know there's an arcade next to the
cinema. So when I'm on the escalator,
when I'm on the escalator, Gre when I'm
on the escalator, Grezy, you can see
like the new toys on the machines. Bro,
they've got Spongebob and Patrick Star.
I want Patrick Star. Greavesy.
They got Patrick Star now because
obviously it's changed. I haven't been
there for a while. I want Patrick. Grezy
crash little friend. I want Patrick
Star. Greavvesy. He's cute in it.
You'll see tomorrow what the pics are.
Greavvesy. I want Patrick.
That's cute, isn't it?
Yeah. What I don't understand with him
yet, what I don't understand with him
yet is he says that these people are
biased. Yeah. We've been a victim of
their biasist. And all I emailed him
was, "Why are you saying that nonslegs
can't be a virgin because he's got this
[ __ ] girlfriend, but when he calls me
a virgin, you're nowhere to be seen."
And then he started getting mad.
And then he started emailing me. And
then he's the one that said he's going
to he's going to come.
No one [ __ ] tried coding him to code
in anyone's [ __ ] door. Just the same as Timmy.
Timmy done his balls in and he wanted to
start self reflecting on me again just
like what Launch Legs done. So I said,
"Okay, I'll message your family. The
more you mention my name, the more I
message your family." It's as simple as that.
It's cuz they're virgins themselves,
JNA. That's why they call people
virgins. Cuz they're virgins themselves. So,
no, I'm not trolling you. I'm being serious.
Look, Russ wants a little friend. He's getting lonely. God bless.
He's cute, isn't he?
No, he's cute. Crash. I want Patrick
Star, though. I do want Patrick Star.
I already told you horn church slow and
town both teams to score on them teams to win. Mom,
you know what they've got in the arcades
now? I went up the escalators and
obviously you know you can see a bit of the arcade. >> Yeah,
>> they've got Patrick Star. >> Yeah.
Do you know who that is?
>> Yeah, I want it. Can you win me it?
I don't want Spongebob. I just want Patrick Star. Spongebob Squarepants.
Yeah. Did you Did you eat all your mice, mama? >> Yeah.
>> Can you get the mice from anywhere that
does pick a mix? You can't, can you?
What about pound shop? Nah.
See, the ones that I get, you can only
get them from the cinema.
You can only Yeah.
You never come cinema with me, Ma. He
was waiting for you yesterday.
Ma the little ghost, huh?
You don't like that that kind of stuff,
do you, Ma?
Do you remember the car scene, Mo, when
the person looked and they and they had
them little masks? Really, Ma?
more than like horror films.
Yeah, I know. I saw it. 8 nil. Yep. Oh gosh.
Take mama fight. Yeah, I call I've
always called lady mummifi. Greavves.
Yeah, that's another thing this guy
remembers. I always call lady mumaf
cuz mama's back spacked me up a lot, you
know, in the past.
Yeah, mama fike. Ah, you remember that
then, don't you? Oh, bless
mama. There is no dada fight. Dad fight
died. Greasy. So, there's only Mama Fike.
Ah, how cute is that? Grievy. Ah.
Yeah, it's cute, isn't it?
You still there?
It's not even about him watching this
community. It's more of how do people
know about his channel.
Like I said, it's just a weird little sector.
Meow meow meow meow meow meow. Greasy
meow. That's enough Tik Tok for today.
They went [ __ ] mad. That's it.
Oh, really? What? From like the stakes and stuff.
I should be getting them.
I should be getting them from Christian Izzy soon.
You'll never replace me. Bark rest.
I pip smoker.
Nonslegs is a massive s.
Nonslegs is a big massive s.
So many. I think there's got to be like
10% people in the world that aren't simps.
I'm part of the 10%.
He's a proper s. He's done it. He's done
it with that Alton Rose. He's scared
that Autumn Rose fancies me because she
comes across as obsessed and obviously
cuz he doesn't have the looks to get
anyone fancy him. He's a bit jealous.
He's very jealous when Peter Betty has
new women cuz he can't get anything
normal. Insecure little virgin.
Yeah, he simps. He's a proper proper s.
He's He's probably one of the worst to
be fair. Proper s that one.
And women don't like him. Women are
never going to sleep with him and and he
still defends him. [ __ ] mad.
It's crazy, Pip. it the way their minds
work. These little simps
sticking up for women. What losers? A
pip smoker. What absolute losers.
What absolute They're not going to sleep
with you. They're not going to let you
hit it, dog.
Nons said I wished breast cancer on
women. Nah, never grievy. That made me laugh.
Imagine that wishing breast cancer on someone.
Sorry, bro. That made me laugh. Tiger
Grezy, do you remember my Tony the Tiger
face mask during CO?
Right. I'm I'm going to have to do this
video to Rick's May soon, lad.
I'm going to be like, "Yeah, I heard
that you don't know how to use a washing
machine, so I I'll give you a helping handy
a helping hand.
I should have done it with the bedding
yesterday, but I went to the cinema and
stuff." So, yeah. This is how you work a washing machine. Not hard.
You might have to You might have to buy
the same model. Just buy a Hindisen's
washing machine. They're quite good. The
Heisen's washing machines. Greavesy.
You know, when you get your your next
bit of money, Ricks. When you get your
next bit of When you get your little
next bit of money, Ricks. You know,
you get yourself a little washing
machine. He said he gets £800 a month.
So, a washing machine. You should be
able to get one for about 280. A nice little Hinds.
Are you looking forward to the video to
be made, Greavvesy? But you're going to
have to wait.
You You okay waiting, Grezy?
Waiting for the video to be made.
Okay with you, [ __ ]
You You wait.
You You wait, Grizzy.
You You wait. Ah,
let me ask Margaret what she thinks. Margaret. Margaret.
Just a second.
Yes. Greavesy said that he wants to wait
until the video has been made. Okay.
Margaret said that's okay. Greasy.
Yeah. Margaret said that's completely fine.
Oh, do you remember that account,
Greasy? They could have gave baby Peter some milk.
That account that said, "Poor fucker."
It asked me. It said, "Did you touch Isabelly's boobies?"
So immature, in it.
That is so immature, in it.
Did you trust his boobies? I greasy. Oh,
greasy. That's That's so immature, is it?
That's the same account that said poor [ __ ] Poor [ __ ]
Which one? Which one's my mama? There's
been so many of them.
There's been so many, Izzy. So, which one?
Do you remember? Do you remember Triple
H? Autumn Rose can be your mama for the winter. Greasy.
Him trolling with his little uh his
little northeast accent. Greasy.
With his little northeast accent.
Well, he said something like that to be
your [ __ ] winner.
What about Signo? Grezy
is sigma my mama.
What's sigma mama grieves?
Sig was never your mama.
So anyways, Leslie, why don't why don't
LT say anything to Nlegs when Nles legs
calls me a virgin? Then
he s he says stuff when I call Nles a virgin.
That's not fair, is it?
That's not fair, is it? Uh, Leslie.
But yeah, like I said, anytime anytime
there's been there's new stuff on this
community, Greavvesy, like there's a
fight that's going to happen or
whatever, make sure you book a screen in
the cinema or you can just buy yourself
a little projector.
I used to have a projector at the old house
and order yourself a lovely McDonald's. Lovely.
That'd be a lovely site.
That would be a [ __ ] lovely site.
What a lovely site.
I'm on Reddit. I need some dating advice. Greasy.
Answer me, Leslie. Answer me.
Answer me, Leslie. Answer me. I asked
you a question. One second. also
write down. Greasy, did you also write
down? Did you also write down taking a
baby away from its mama?
That was also a good one.
I love that little saying, Greasy.
Taking a baby away from its mama. O
Leslie, answer my question.
So, how comes when I call launch legs a
virgin, LT always says, "Oh, you can't
call someone that's got a girlfriend a
virgin. That's immature." Rare. But when
he calls me a virgin, that's completely fine.
LT said that he didn't like biased people,
but he's being biased himself. I've
shown me getting my [ __ ] sucked. I've
shown me uh in bed naked with women.
I've had women admitted to sleeping with
me. I had a friends with benefits
that everyone saw.
So yeah, that's what I mean. Like he he
will come on this sector, right? Right.
And he will complain about them. He will
complain about these people doing what
they do, but he doesn't even realize
he's exactly the same as them.
He doesn't even realize that he is the
same as these people.
I know, but they still say that I'm a
virgin. Madness, isn't it? They still
say that you're a virgin.
One second. That
Yeah, Leslie Hag. Sorry, lad.
Yeah, Timmy's definitely self projected.
If you watch Timmy's channel the other
day. Yeah, Timmy was saying about how
Timmy was saying about how um I can't
afford a big arch. I've done my balls
in. I'm thinking, what the [ __ ] is this
guy on about? And it's clear that he's
talking about himself. A big arch. Who?
I don't even eat I don't even eat McDonald's, bro.
Very rarely do I eat McDonald's. I've I
can't remember the last time I done my
balls in Gablin. I've always got money.
So yeah, Timmy definitely is a self
projector. He's one of the biggest self
projectors on this community. I can't
afford a big arch. What the [ __ ]
And then he goes back to licking Non
Legs's ass again, saying, "Oh, he's got
all this money." But he doesn't have all
of this money. He doesn't have any money
at all. And then the same thing happens
again and again and again.
Yep. I'm having a I'm having a nice I'm
having I'm having a lamb curry today. Yeah.
It's funny, Leslie, because they call
they try and say that I'm a bun.
They try to say I'm a bun, yet I'm
better looking than all of the [ __ ]
people in this community. That's funny,
bro. Is it?
I'm a ber, but I'm better looking than
all of these people in this community,
mate. That makes sense. Yeah.
So, what's my mama then, Grezy?
They don't like him. No, no, no. Leslie,
Leslie, Leslie. They They don't like
him. Well, it is because he goes for me.
That's why no one says anything. It's
like people don't like me, bro. People
don't like me.
Watching my gaff. I don't give a [ __ ] if
he's watching my gaff, bro. I'll go out
whenever I want. I'm not scared of no, brother.
I'm not scared of no [ __ ] So you can
you can keep watching my [ __ ] G. I
don't give a [ __ ] Simple as that. Um uh
Greasy, listen. Uh no, one second. One
second. One second. One second. One
second, bro. You made me forget. Yeah,
it's like people don't like me on this
community. Sorry, bro. But because when
I was going for Timmy,
everyone like everyone didn't mind
because I was going for Timmy. So
people's, it's because he he goes for
me. That's why people just like tolerate him.
Same if I went for Timmy every day,
people will like me. Even though they
don't like me, they'll pretend to like
me. Do you get it?
Do you get what I'm saying?
Yeah, but I know what you're saying.
It's just jealousy with this people in
this with these people in this community, bro.
You should see some of these channels,
Red Star, uh Jamie Thompson. Their life
is to be sat obsessed with men every day.
Yeah, man. Their life is to be obsessed
with men every day. Yeah.
Yeah. But yeah, I don't give a [ __ ]
who's watching the gaff lad.
I don't give a [ __ ]
And anyone steps to me, bro, they will
know what time it is. Simple as that.
Yeah. And that's it, bro. 100%.
about of what may happen. Nothing will
ever happen. Nothing will ever ever ever
Believe that, bro. Nothing will ever
ever ever ever happen. Yeah. That's it.
You love this, isn't it, Grezy?
Well, if I come off of here, they would. Yeah.
Yeah. It makes you scared. Doesn't make me scared.
He doesn't make me scared, bro.
It doesn't make me scared one little bit.
Not one little bit. I don't know about
anyone else, but Yeah.
If anyone come on that door that day,
bro, you would have saw exactly what
would have happened. You would have saw
exactly what would have happened.
And I never ever said I was stronger.
I've never said I was stronger than than
him. Never. I I've never said I was
stronger than him ever. Stronger than
him. I've never said that. But I know
I'm madder. I know my temper, bro. Trust
me. I know my temper. Yeah. I know how
psychotic I am. Trust me. Yeah.
Uh, Timmy's the same, bro. Timmy's far
up his backside as well. Timmy's exactly
the same. Oh, he's got all this money.
He's got all this money. Yeah, he's got
all this money. That's why I beat him at
the money game multiple times. Yeah.
Okay, bro. He's got all this, bro.
Timmy's the same. Timmy's the worst for it. Yeah,
T. He's the same, bro. The Timmy's the
same. He ain't got no [ __ ] 10 grand,
no 13 grand, no nothing. He's got no
money. He's [ __ ] skinned. He waits
till he get he gets his little housing
benefit and shows it off on YouTube.
Leslie, listen. These people, right? Oh,
my brain's hurting again, bro. Yeah.
Listen, bro. These the thing is with
these people, they they've already shown
about what money they've got when they
were shown different amounts of money
and no one could show nothing. They was
already they've already been shown, bro,
what they're about when they got shown
money multiple times. Then they have got
no money. I've shown two grand, 1,500,
three grand, four grand, five grand,
five grand, 5.7 grand and they all run away.
Mr. Couple of quids ran away. So Mr. got
all this couple of creds run away.
They've already been proven what they
we're about, bro. They got no money.
Yeah, but like like you said, it's
biasness. That's that's another thing
that they're biased. They're biased with
the money game. They're biased with
women. They're bi They're biased with everything, bro.
But yeah, we need to try to ignore it
now anyways, bro. Because Timmy Timmy
will try to to try he will try to draw
people out again and again and again.
And then what will happen is you react.
He's going to start saying that he's
going to meet you. It's never ever going
to happen. Then the whole thing goes
around in circles again.
So I ordered this guy a taxi. He
wouldn't jump in the taxi. Yeah.
Yeah, he wouldn't get a taxi and LT was
saying, "Oh, you never do that for me.
You never do that for me." But the guy
said he was going to come on the door
and knock on the door.
It the same goes for anyone else. If
they come on this door, they ring the doorbell,
they're ringing the doorbell,
they ring the doorbell, they knock the
door, they're not getting out this
house. It's as simple as that. And that
goes that goes for anyone. black, white,
Indian, short, tall, [ __ ] whatever
the [ __ ] they are, bro. The same applies to anyone.
And I and I would have humiliated Timmy.
And I don't even mean just with violence.
I mean like piss bottles,
mad [ __ ] bro. Trust me. Because like
it's got to stop. You know, years and
years and years this little clown has
been coming on here trying to annoy
people, right? And it's not disability,
bro. He doesn't do it cuz he's disability. Yeah.
He does it he does it on purpose to get me.
No one ever took Izzy off me, lad. No,
that's not what happened.
Nope. No one took Isabelle off me. From
what I remember is he walked home.
Nope. No one's ever took Izzy off me.
I didn't even like her anyways. But yeah.
Yeah. I don't know why they're up his ass.
Greg, I don't know why they're up nons's
ass, especially when when when Dave It
just doesn't make sense. It don't make
But it doesn't matter anyways, Leslie.
Anyways, like if we call someone a
virgin now and they interrupt us, we'll
just keep calling them a virgin. It
doesn't matter, does it? It doesn't
really matter, does it?
I'm sure they'll live.
You understand, Greavves? I'm sure they'll live.
Yeah, I'm sure they'll live, lad.
I'm sure they'll live.
Yeah. And how does he know about Rick's
Mace? Rick Mace only said one thing. It
took less than 20 seconds for Rick Mace
to So yeah, he is always watching.
Definitely always watching.
Oh, he's got informants, which you
shouldn't have informants if you're off this sector.
Launch Legs talks about me all the time,
but I know Virgin Boy will never meet
me. He's just an internet keyboard
warrior, which is why I don't like say,
"Oh, what I'm saying, lad.
Yeah, he can watch it all he wants. I
don't give a [ __ ] bro. He can watch it
all he wants. I don't care.
But yeah, Timmy is um and it is jealousy
with these people, Leslie. Look at the
way Timmy looks. Yeah. Look at the way
Nons looks. That's why they all do this, bro.
No, I'm not saying to no I'm not saying
sorry to no one, bro. No one's going to
try and bully me. I'm not saying sorry
to no one, bro.
No thank you. I'm good.
Yeah, that's good for him, bro. I'm not
saying sorry to no [ __ ]
I'm not saying sorry to no [ __ ]
Simple as that. No thank you, bro.
I don't know, bro.
I said to Timmy, the only re the only
way I would do something to Timmy is if
he came on the door.
He's trying to say that I was calling
out Timmy. No, I wasn't calling out
Timmy at all. When he was talking about
me, yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] if
someone's too big or too strong. I don't
really give a [ __ ] to be honest with you.
I really, really, really, really, really don't care
to be honest with you.
Uh whenever I need to put the whenever I
put the washing on
my next load of washing. Yeah.
Yeah. There's a lot of people up nons.
And that's how you know it's jealousy as
well cuz look at the the state of these
people in this community. They're just
[ __ ] ugly as [ __ ] Ugly Timmy. Ugly nonslegs.
This is why they do this, bro. This is
seriously seriously why they do this, lad.
That is literally why they do this.
They're [ __ ] ugly as [ __ ] Timmy nons legs.
But yeah, Timmy's up his ass as well.
Trying to forget Leslie about all the
times I've shown them money and they've run away.
Yeah. All the time I've shown these
people money and they've run away and
then they come up with another excuse
and they still call people skin. They're
just retards. They're just jealous
little life loser retards. There's a lot
of people that do this, lad.
A lot of people that do this, lad. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Yeah, it's funny, bro. It's funny.
It's mad, is it, bro?
It's actually mad.
madness, bro. Yeah. And all he tries to
do is try to bully people in this
community as well. That's what he tries
doing, bro. Yeah. Because he knows that
the people in this community are not
going to meet him. It's facts, bro. It's facts.
And yeah, they do use weapons. They do
definitely definitely definitely use weapons.
Like the time of the tenant, they do use
weapons. 100%. They use weapons.
They do 100 million% use weapons, bro.
But he will deny it. He will deny it anyways
because not I don't know about him, bro,
but I know all of the people that he's
brought to the house before wouldn't
beat me without a weapon. I know that
for a fact. You can talk four or five years ago
rare rare, bro. You just wouldn't. Cuz
why? You've had a weapon every single
when there's been people that's come,
they've had a weapon every single time. Yeah,
but all I know is if anyone came on that
door the other day, they would have been
getting cheffed up like a crush. Trust
me, they would have they would have been
getting cheffed the [ __ ] up, bro. In
like an Italian restaurant. I know for a fact.
Yeah, my mom was watching YouTube and
stuff, bro. She was like a bit scared
and that. I was like, I'm not scared.
I'm not scared at all.
This is the time that I was talking
talking to this Christian Izzy, bro.
They would have some They would have
been getting cheffed up. Trust me, they
would have. They actually would have,
bro. I'm not even joking. Yeah,
they would have been getting chef the
[ __ ] up in their stomach. I'm not even
tell. I'm not even joking.
That is cheeky. That is, bro. Very,
very, very cheeky, you know.
That is very cheeky, bro. Very cheeky to
start saying stuff like that. Yeah.
But anyways, it just comes to jealousy
on this community. That's all it comes
down to, lad. Hate to say it, Leslie,
but that's that's the truth. That is the
That is the truth.
You said stuff about living with your
mom. Oh, that's all irrelevant. That's
why I didn't bring it up cuz that's just
that doesn't that's irrelevant, lad.
That's just irrelevant.
But look, if you need to think about
this stuff yet, if you look like Timmy,
you'd kill yourself. I would kill
myself. I don't know about you, Leslie.
If I look like If I look like Timmy, I'd kill myself.
He's got an IVA. He's [ __ ] skinn.
He's a virgin. No wonder he talks about me, bro.
You would actually kill yourself if you
look like half of these people in this I
know. I [ __ ] would. If I look like
some of these people in this community,
I would [ __ ] kill myself, bro.
I said this I said this yesterday, bro.
I said this yesterday.
Could you imagine? Like, we take the
piss out of it. Yeah. Imagine being Timmy, bro.
Imagine being Timmy. Could you imagine being Timmy?
Could you imagine being Timmy, bro?
No. Can't imagine it.
Is your chest
bless Grezy if you're scared of leaving the house. Oh, grievy.
Bless you, Greasy. If you're scared of
leaving the house, bless you.
I'm not scared of leaving the [ __ ]
house at all, bro. No [ __ ] way.
Who is that? I've never That looks like
Manchester. I knew that were London.
Well, bless you then if you're going to
the shop in a minute.
All Grezy, do you remember
X Factor? I want to watch the X Factor.
What's your opinion on that?
I want to watch the Xbox and we
nope. That's enough Tik Tok for today.
I love the X Factor Grezy. X Factor.
The X Factor.
Oh, it was a trend, bro. Big trend.
Oi, Leslie, why do why did not why did
Nons say that if you don't like Cheryl
Cole, you're gay? Do you remember?
Greavvesy can't answer this one for you.
It might be it might be a trick question.
Do you remember that? Do you remember
that? Do you remember that, Leslie?
He's getting some milk and eggs. Bless him
for his little diet. Yep.
Yeah, bro. It's funny, isn't it?
Yeah. Fit in with the crowd.
Yeah. Fit in with the pop. Yeah.
They look at you weird. At least that
trend's over now. Anyways, at least that
I saw more people wearing Canada Goose
Coats yesterday, Leslie. I'm sick of
that trend. Just a bunch of copycats.
The people got no [ __ ] mind of their
own or something. Uh Yeah. Boom.
Uh, I went once. I went once. Yeah. The
first time I met him. And obviously I've
always been into Vinderoo, right? And he
said, "I just will have what you're
getting." I said, "I I don't think it's
a good idea you you getting a Vindaloo,
mate." And he was like, "No, I'll get
what you're getting. I'll get what
you're getting. I said, "It's really
it's really really hot. I don't think
it's I don't think you're going to like
it." And he says, "No, I want that one."
In in his little gay voice, right? So,
he got the same as me. Vindeloo
literally didn't even finish the lamb.
This is hot. This is hot. This is hot.
I'm thinking, I told you you're not
going to be able to [ __ ] take it.
It's too hot. He started [ __ ] downing
a glass of water and [ __ ] everything.
Then he just finished the um chicken
ticker. Literally woke up the next day.
[ __ ] got a missed call. Call him
back. I'm thinking what what the [ __ ]
Oh man, I got I got the [ __ ] I can't
get off the toilet. I can't get off the
toilet. I got diarrhea, mate. I said, I
[ __ ] told you it it'd be too hot for
you. And this was a [ __ ] vinderoo.
First time we met, there's a Indian at
by the back of um where was it? You
know, you know Lester Square train station.
If you keep going up, there's a Indian
Indian cuisine. I've done a delivery there before.
Yeah, I told him it's it will be too
what for you. He wouldn't listen.
That was the first time. Yeah.
Yep. I'm a Everybody knows that I'm a
crazy [ __ ] Leslie,
you would never be able to have the
Carolina Reaper burger.
I'm a mad man. I told you these cries
are for big, strong Turkish men that can
pull American women, Leslie, and can get
one night like stands. They're not for
little virgins that live in Kent like you.
I said that many times. They're not made
for for virgins.
And I said to him, I'll take him waxies
one day, but the manager won't allow it.
They don't allow virgins.
They just don't if they if they suspect
someone as being a virgin, you need to
prove to them that you're not a virgin
before they let you in. It's just a no virgin policy.
I don't know what happened, why they've
um why they've why they've they've done
that, but yeah, he's a big, you know, he
will need to prove that he's not a
virgin before they let him in. Now, I
don't make the rules. I have no part of
this, mate, but that's what the policy states.
So, I don't know, man. You know, how do
I eat a foul? I told you cuz I'm a big
strong Turkish man.
But they still weren't they weren't as many vitamins
as USA. Is he gave me vitamins?
They're expensive vitamins and they're
not the same, but they're just enough to
keep you going, Greavvesy.
The vitamins aren't as strong, but
they're good enough to keep you alive.
Do you understand, Greavvesy?
That's how I get my vitamins now from
curries and stuff.
So, yeah. So, I just manage on that to
be fair. I'm managing well, you know. Um, but yeah,
hopefully Christian Izzy will give me
some vitamins soon.
Even if it's as simple as handh holding,
that' be nice, wouldn't it, Grezy?
That'd be lovely. She sent me kisses
yesterday. Hey, Grezy.
Any more stories? Um,
yeah. When I when I first met the Virgin
uh in Victoria, this undercover police
officer stopped me and he was he looked
like a businessman and it was quite
weird. And I'm thinking, what the [ __ ]
Um, and then he tried chatting up this
Spanish worker in Eminem shop. And I'm
thinking, this guy is an absolute
virgin. I didn't I didn't say anything.
um you know and he he he got he got rejected
um and yeah he just walked away which
he's he's always said that he's he's
never been rejected it's part of his
little ego he doesn't want to admit it
to himself I've never been rejected I've
never been rejected Britney rejected you
literally [ __ ] the the the woman in
Eminem shop [ __ ] rejected you his ego
is so he will never ever admit he's been rejected
he can never ever admit it. He's like,
"Nope, I've been rejected when you
literally have been rejected. You got
rejected by Britney
and Aisha, you went nowhere near that
girl. Nowhere near that girl sexually,
isn't that right, Leslie?"
Uh, yeah, he was a virgin. Yeah. And I
and I would tell him I I told him about
like this escort story cuz I had I was
like 17 and and for love money, he
wouldn't believe it. He had my mom
telling him over the phone and he would
not believe that I paid a woman for sex
no matter how many times I tried. And
I'm thinking, bro, you know, you go to
most people and and if you say to them
that you've used an escort, they'd
believe it. But him, he would not he
would not have it under any circumstances
that I've had sex cuz he's never had sex
and he's a virgin.
No matter what, no matter how many times
he would he wouldn't he wouldn't admit
it, bro. He'd be like, "Nope. Escorts
asked for ID." I was like, "They [ __ ]
don't, mate." Because I [ __ ] use them.
But obviously, I didn't know that he was
just projecting back then. I thought
like, I don't know, bro. But yeah, it's
cuz he's a virgin himself and he still
is a virgin.
Sarah ain't giving him no [ __ ] ass, bro. So yeah.
And um yeah, basically
never meet anyone with autism, Leslie.
That's all I'll say, lad. That's all I
That's all I'll say. Yeah.
Yeah. Of course it was that, bro. He was
making up all of these excuses. No.
Escorts ask for ID. Escorts ask for ID.
I'm thinking, well, they [ __ ] well
don't. And he was just making any excuse
to to disbelieve it. Oh, because he's a big virgin.
He's a [ __ ] big virgin. That's why. Yeah.
Got rejected by Britney.
And then when he started telling me
stories about his dad, that's when I was like, "Nah,
nah, you missed the approaching vids."
Well, there's one way. There's one way
to get the approaching videos back.
There's one way to get the approaching
videos back, bro. Make your own ones.
Isn't that right, Grezy? Why don't you
You should do your You should do your
own approaching videos, Bob.
Then you'll be part of the action.
You'll be part of the madness.
Uh because what he was trying to say is
because I was 17, you have to be 18 to use escorts.
But because basically I was 17, in it
when when I first met the virgin. So
what he was just doing is trying to make excuses.
Um he was just trying to make excuses to
make the story not true.
So obviously he was trying to say, "Oh,
you need to be to use escorts." I was
like, "No, you don't." Um but you can't
you can't you can't win with people like that, bro.
You know, you can't remember people like
that. Can't remember little virgins like
Yeah, he was speaking to underage girls. Yeah.
I was 17.
17 years of age.
Never ever ever did they ever ask me how
old I was. So,
bro, I don't even think they would ask.
But yeah, he was just making any excuse
basically to just not believe it cuz he wasn't happy.
Unless you're a virgin like him, he's
not going to be happy. So that's why he
was making up all of these things.
They've asked you for ID because he's a
virgin himself where he was meeting you.
You had to be a virgin like him. And if
you're not a virgin like him,
um he's not happy.
He loses his [ __ ] So he'll make up all
of these excuses.
So that's basically what it is. The same
thing as he um as he stalks women that
I've been with in the past and tries and
he will and what he will do is he will
come from a place of sympathy knowing
that he's going to get the answers that
he wants. And then think, "Oh, oh, he
didn't have sex. He's a virgin like me.
Britney rejected him like Brit. He's got
been rejected just like Britney rejected
me." That's literally his life, bro.
That's literally his life.
No, I didn't have any friends. He used
to get bullied
in college. Uh, PlayStation. I'm going
to message that guy anyway. Is that
Miles? I'm going to message him at some
point, bro. When I can be bothered.
Yeah, Miles McCoy.
Oh, old [ __ ]
But, you know, I'll still message him anyways. Yeah.
He got bullied by two Scottish lads. One
was called Miles and one was called
Jackaryi. But I don't know the other
guy's Facebook. I only know Miles cuz he
sent me the link years ago. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. All Leslie, do you remember
that video? Yeah. Where I approached USA
Izzy and she's like, "Do you want my
number?" Nons was getting so jealous cuz
these virgin ass could never do it. Do
you remember the community post and
stuff? He was like, "No, it's not a me
and Britney situation." He was losing his [ __ ]
Oh, he's always been a strange. Yeah, he
was always strange. But I just thought,
you know, I felt sorry for the kid, you
because he used to [ __ ] he used to
get bullied, lad.
Oh, bless a little message, bless you, bless you.
But yeah, um yeah, Leslie,
still calling me a virgin even though I
proved I've had sex. Another nonslegs lover.
Oh, what did you say I am? Greavves is psychotic.
Yeah, cuz it's jealousy, Leslie. It's
jealous cuz he can't get anything.
Yeah, it's it's jealousy, lad. Cuz he
can't get anything. Normal. Yeah.
Who the [ __ ] dresses like that? He used
to dress like that because he used to
think uh he used to think that women was
going to he used to think women would
have got with him.
He used to think that if he dresses like
that women would [ __ ] him.
>> Oh gosh. >> Oh's life.
>> The only ver the only virgin is you.
Peter, you're the one who go on about
females non-stop and I'm the only one
that show you couldn't even
seen with females. >> Anyway,
that doesn't mean you had sex, Peter.
That doesn't mean showed me getting my
dick suck. Everyone's been sex.
>> Shut up, Iva virgin.
>> How can you go about my IPA? The only
virgin to [ __ ] virgin.
Don't you Peter just as bad?
How can you go about when you owe all
that money to phone contract you
know you can't [ __ ] try to make out
that you anyway? Anyway, Peter, I've got
the whale card through Wednesday. You're
going to get owned. Make sure you get
the hammer out like you did before and
this time [ __ ] use it.
>> Yeah, you're going to do nothing. You're a little
Little boy, I'm going to h I just
attention on YouTube. Let's talk about
I'm not a virgin.
>> I will see you on Wednesday.
>> You You are going to do nothing, Peter.
See you on Wednesday. I'll see you on
>> Peter, do you know what? It'd be a good
day out cuz I can go to the
rattled on YouTube for 9 hours after
ownage making out. I've done nothing cuz
this is what you do. That [ __ ]
You are so autistic that everyone laughs
at you. Go legs. Go and cry over your
boy for being called skin.
>> Anyway, virgin. Anyway, I'll see you Wednesday. Virgin boy.
You [ __ ] know about yourself. You let
me try and explain this to you again.
>> The only virgin is yourself. You have
never been seen with a woman unlike me.
The only virgin is you are non legs. You
are the only virgins on this community.
You know what happens as well, Grezy?
When he comes on Wednesday, I'm taking
his phone off of him as well. I'm going
to rob him. Silly, bro. What? Watch what
I'm going to do on Wednesday, bro. And
yes, LT, I'm going to do it. And if you
want to come and do something about it,
you can come as well. You can come with
him. Yeah, you can come with him as
well. Simple as that. You can both come.
Yeah, it's as simple as that. Do you
know what, bro? I'm going to take his
phone off of him. I'm going to, bro, I'm
going to I'm going to make the [ __ ]
leave in these boxes. That's what I'm
going to do, bro. I'm going to make this
[ __ ] leave in these boxes. That's what
I'm going to do, bro. Yeah. I'm going to
take his phone off of him. I'm going to
smash his glasses and I'm going to make
him go home in these boxes.
>> Watch. That's what I'm going to do, bro.
I'm really I can't wait to humiliate
this IBA virgin. I can't wait to I can't
wait for the IBA.
I can't wait for the virgin with his
dead. And you've lost all your
>> I can't wait for the dead virgin I dead.
>> That's all you can do. You're going to
fight the same.
I will tell you what
call me what you want. You're still
going to get [ __ ] You're still
going to get owned and there's nothing
you can do. Let's have a talk. Why are
you calling out London Taylor? We all
know London Taylor.
Even London Taylor.
Let's be honest, Peter. Peter. Peter,
calm down. I know you don't give a
mommy's not giving you any more money cuz mommy's
okay. Calm down. We all know you can't
have a bindaloo this weekend. No
vindaloo for pizza. No vindaloo for
pizza. Your dad died of cancer. I'm
going to have you know he's not getting
a vindaloo this weekend.
No vindaloo. No vindaloo. Vindaloo.
Listen. Bring your legs. Anyway, why you
calling out London Taylor? London video.
London Taylor would floor the [ __ ] out of you.
>> You and London Taylor about nothing. I
want London tires in again and then you
and you'll come back on YouTube London
tires done nothing has done nothing
because I'm a big [ __ ]
>> you're both so much money to simp
>> yeah yeah anyway when are you going to
pay back PJ when are you going to pay
when are you going to lose your
virginity virgin when you going to lose
your virginity virgin
with no money at the money ID
I BEAT YOU AT THE blood
and even if I
you'll do a win test against the kingdom
of heaven still be matted over me and
come back and make out I've done nothing
and come back from the dead
I could you and you'll still say I've
done nothing you're that autistic PJ
you're that autistic it's affecting your life
>> mate have you seen
>> you can't nothing sunshine you trying to
impress some [ __ ] spastics on Just
make sure you let's be honest here.
London Taylor's wife. Everyone trolled
you. Even Dustin
London Taylor will kick your ass. Go to
London Taylor. I will I will speak to
London and I guarantee you
stop talking [ __ ] No for
>> listen. Come with London Taylor on
Wednesday and I will do both of you.
That is my promise to you. I will do
both of you at the same time. It is as
simple as that. Doesn't matter how I'm
going to do it. I will do both of you
[ __ ] and I will make sure you never
come back on this website again yapping
your [ __ ] Yeah. Stalking people and
bothering people again. Come with your
boyfriend on Wednesday, big man. Bring
whoever the [ __ ] you want. Yeah. Don't
forget you're saying that you're coming
to my territory. Yeah. So bring whoever
you want. Simple. That's that, bro. That
is simple as that.
Simple as that. I don't give a [ __ ] if
he's hench. I don't give a [ __ ] JNA, I
don't give a [ __ ] Who said we're
fighting? Who said we're fighting clean,
bro? Who said we're fighting clean? I
don't give a [ __ ] if he's hench. I will
not lose. I I'm saying something right
now, bro. I'm telling you right now, I
will not lose. Yeah. Simple. Who said
we're fighting clean? Simple.
Listen. Who said we're fighting clean?
I never said I'm fighting clean.
Yeah, because at the end of the day,
bro, when stuff has been going on for so
many [ __ ] years with these jealous
ass [ __ ] people, you get sick of it.
I'm not I'm not fighting clean. I'm not
fighting clean, bro. I'm not even going
to tell you what I'm going to do, bro.
You You don't even I'm not even going to
tell you what I'm going to do.
[ __ ] madness, bro. Anyways, we're
clicking this guy now cuz he's just
annoyed. And he's just talking over
people. No, not even that, bro. No, not even that.
Not even that, bro.
You will see what will happen, bro. You
will see exactly what will happen.
Yeah, not even that. No, not even that, bro.
How's the dating going? I haven't tried
for a while, DH.
So, we can't have a normal conversation
with these spastics.
Yeah, we can't have a normal
conversation with these [ __ ]
spastics. Anyways, he's not coming back
in now cuz he's just talking a load of
[ __ ] and he's not doing anything. He's a
talker. He's still talking, but he's not doing anything.
You know, he's a talker, but he's not
doing anything. Do you understand? He's
just a talker. Talker talker talker with
all this talking you and you know, I
really does hope he does he does come on
Wednesday. I really do hope he comes
with that London Taylor. I really really
do hope I can do him dirty. Both of
them, bro. I really, really hope, bro. I
do really hope.
You know what I'm saying? I really,
really do hope they both come. I really,
really do hope. You know that, bro. I
really, really do. Yeah.
Simple. Yeah. I gave up months ago. I
went out a couple of weeks ago. That was
the first time in months. Just this
[ __ ] Timmy, bro. Just Timmyy's
[ __ ] I just said to Timmy, "Yeah,
just come on Wednesday." Yeah. Just come
on Wednesday with London Taylor and I
will do you both in. It's as simple as
that. I will do you both in. I'm sure
you saw my video to LT because he keeps
bringing LT up. LT is trying to get
involved. Just come on Wednesday and
I'll do you both in. And it's not going
to be and it's not going to be clean.
It's going to be dirty, bro. It's going
to be dirty. I'm I never said I'm
stronger than anyone. I might not be
able to beat anyone with my with my
hands, but Yeah. It will be dirty, bro.
It will be disgustingly dirty. Trust me. Yeah.
Yeah. He can sniff around all he wants,
bro. He can sniff around all he wants. I
don't give a [ __ ] You saw my video on him.
It's the truth, bro. It's the truth.
He's a hypocrite, bro. How many times
has he tried going for this nonslegs?
Do you know how many times he's tried
beating this non He would beat Nonss up
if he saw him. He doesn't like nonslegs
and he's trying to say nonslegs is the weaker target,
bro. [ __ ] stirring again. Trying to [ __ ] stir again,
you know. Just come with Timmy on
Wednesday so I can do you both in. Just
stop talking, bro. I'm sick of these
[ __ ] now. I'm actually I'm actually
really really sick of these [ __ ] now,
bro. You know, I'll pick on both of you.
Him and him. Trust me, bro. You're not
going to win against me. I I can swear
to you, God, right now you're not going
to win against me, bro. Yeah, because I
I I wouldn't be saying it if if that was
the truth. Yeah.
Simple. Like, show us what you're really
going to do. Like, show us really you
smashing a window when someone's in in
front of their mom. Show us really what
a big man you really are without
running. Let's see it, bro. Let's see
it. Yeah. Let's see what you're really
really about. You know, simple. It's as
simple as that, bro. No, he's bringing
trouble. No one's bringing trouble to
people's mom's law. This [ __ ] is
bringing Trump trouble. This little
biased [ __ ] is bringing trouble, bro. He
is bringing trouble. So, he'll get
trouble. If he wants trouble, he will
get trouble. Simple. This little jealous
[ __ ] LT, I don't know how long he's
been doing this for now. If you want
trouble, I'll give you trouble. It's as
simple as that. Just like the other day,
bro. You don't know what I was going to
do to that [ __ ] if he come on the door,
bro. You don't know what was going to
happen. If you want trouble, I'll give
you the trouble that you want. Simple.
It's as simple as that. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying, bro? I will
give you trouble. It's as simple as
that. No one's bringing trouble to
anyone's mom's daughter. He started it.
As I've already explained on the video,
with his bias list and his dick sucking
and he didn't like it. Ooh, he got a
girlfriend, bro. Don't say that, bro.
It's bro. Like, [ __ ] off, bro. [ __ ] off.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Like,
[ __ ] off. Really [ __ ] off.
You understand? He's jealous. Ass is
bringing trouble. Yeah, he is bringing
trouble. No one's bringing trouble. This
is the same dude that's watching people.
Like, if you want trouble, I'll give you
psychotic trouble. You know, trust me.
Cuz I never ever said once, never have
come out of my mouth, I'm struggling
London Taylor, but I know I'm more mad
than this [ __ ] I know I'm more
psychotic than this [ __ ] Trust me, I
know I am, bro. I know for a fact I am.
Yeah. Trust me. I'll just do [ __ ]
without thinking. Do you think he's
going to come and and and and and start?
I was actually waiting for for it that
day, bro. Even though I emailed him
saying, "Oh, don't bro." I was actually
waiting for it. Trust me.
I was waiting for it, bro. Trust me. And
this is all jealousy as well with Timmy
LT, Nox. This is a mad thing. It's all
jealousy with them. That's the thing
with them. It's all jealousy.
It's all jealousy. And that's the
saddest thing about it with these. It's
all jealousy with them. Yeah.
It's all jealousy with them. That's what
it is. It's all jealousy.
That's what it is, bro.
Like, just come on Wednesday, big man,
and see who's going for the weaker
target. Just do it. Just do it. Cuz I'm
going to do it some so badly, bro. Yeah.
And I'm not And I'm not going to get
nicked either. I'm not going to get
nicked. Yeah. Because obviously they're
coming to where you are about. I know.
You don't tell me who I can go for. I'll
go for nonslegs as much as I want. I'll
go for Timmy as much as I want. And I'll
go for you. If you come for Timmy, I
will go for you as well. Yeah. I will go
for whoever I want. However, however I
like. You understand me? Yeah. [ __ ]
coming on here like, "I'm not these
little females, bro, that you try to
like bully." No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. You know,
simple, bro. Yeah.
[ __ ] idiot, bro. [ __ ] stupid
jealous ass loser idiots on this
community, bro. I swear down. I [ __ ]
swear down, bro. Yeah,
I've done him a better deal. They can
both come together.
Yeah, it's as simple as that. They can
both come together, bro.
You [ __ ] both. You both suck nods
legs dick. So the more the marrier
[ __ ] stupid little bias little [ __ ] [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying?
Ah, look at this. Look at this. Trouble
is my friends have been to his house for
the past two days and he's not even
taking a short walk. I leave the house
every single day. I leave the house and
it's always your friends. This is what
I'm saying with this [ __ ] With this
absolute [ __ ] Yeah. It's always
friends with weapons. He's a [ __ ] This
is what I'm saying, bro. And I've left
the house. I left the house yesterday. I
left the house the day before that.
Like, brother, I leave the house every
single day. So, I don't know what your
friends are telling you. Yeah. You're
just a [ __ ] This is what I'm saying.
Friends again. Friends again. How about
this, bro? Yeah. I'll give Listen.
Listen. [ __ ] the friend [ __ ] Yeah. Come
on the door and slap my mom in her face
and see what happens to you. Just Just
think you're going to knock on my door
and see what happens. Yeah. Trust me.
Just see what happens and I will stay
live. Simple. Big man. Big man. Forget
the friends. Yeah. Forget the friends.
You come directly on the door and I'll
show you trouble and I will give you
trouble. It's as simple as that. Come
on. Come on. Like, bro, trust me. Trust
me, bro. I will give you all the
Tottenham trouble that you want. Yeah.
It's as simple as that. Yeah. It's as
simple as that. Big man. Big man. Do it
yourself and I'll give you any trouble
that you've wanted over the years on
this community. Please. And that way I
know that you can't grass. Yeah. I know
that you can't start running to the
police and dry snitching. Yeah. Simple
as that. You little stalking little
weirdo bastard. Watch. I'm going to do
another video to this [ __ ] bro. Yeah. I
will. Bro, just do it. No friends. Just
do it, bro. Let me embarrass you in
front of everyone. Come on, bro. You
wanted trouble. You want to be the hard
man looking good for women on YouTube? I
will give you any trouble that you want.
You wanted trouble, I'll give you it.
It's as simple as that.
You little gay little stalky little
homosexual bastard. You bastard. Yeah.
Just like your little nodle legs gay
boyfriend that dick. I'm telling you all
these things that you are not I'm
telling you right now. No one or anyone
that you know is coming anywhere near
this address if you knew what was good
for you, bro. It's as simple as that,
bro. Yeah. It's as simple as that.
Get in your friends. You little gay
bastard. You're just like nonslegs.
You little [ __ ] [ __ ] little
bastard. Shut up, bro. About friends
have been coming for days and days. No,
no, no, no, they have not. No, they just
have not. Yeah, because I leave the
house every single day. No, they just
have not. Friends again with weapons.
Bro, you can't fight. Not one, bro. Not
one of them can fight. Not one of them
can. You little [ __ ] gay bastard
trying to look good on YouTube. [ __ ]
little sad bastard, bro.
Friends, friends, friends. It's always
friends. Why is it friends and not you?
That's You know what I'm saying? You
know what I'm saying, bro? You little weirdo.
You little [ __ ] gay nonslegs loving weirdo. Yeah.
[ __ ] little weirdo, bro. Yeah,
I'm sick of this little gay boy, bro. I
swear to God.
No, serious. Serious. Let me come. Let
me chef you up. Come on. Try and look
good for women on YouTube. Come on. Come
on. Come on. Let me let me let me chef
the simp up on YouTube. The big man.
Come on. I'll send it to Ricks as well.
Come on. Come on, bro. Come on. Come on.
Just come on. You might make an old
woman scared, but you don't scare me one
little bit. Not one person from
Tottenham scares me. Not one little bit
do you scare me, bro. Yeah.
He's just another nons legs. He's a
little nonss lover. He's just another
little nonsle legs. That's all it is,
bro. That is literally all it is. Yeah.
That is literally all it is. He's just a
gay low life. He hasn't got no kids. He
ain't got no family. And I'm saying that
and I'm saying it proudly. He does not.
This guy does not have nothing in his
life. He's just a little jealous gay
bastard that likes defending nonslegs
cuz that's his boyfriend. He won't have
any bad for words said about him about
your friends have been doing this to
doing that. [ __ ] off, man. Come in the
door today, big man, and don't run away.
Come in the door today, big man, and
don't run away. I'll give you all the
trouble you want. I'll give you all the
trouble you [ __ ] want. And if you're
not going to do it, shut the [ __ ] up
with your gay little videos. Stop
lurking around trying to bully people.
Yeah, it's as simple as that.
Yeah, it's as simple as that, bro.
Yeah, with your little bully boy tattoos
like you scare anyone cuz you don't
scare no [ __ ] You don't scare no
brother. It's as simple as that. Yeah.
Come and make me scream like an old
woman. Come and make me scream. Come and
make me scream like an old woman.
[ __ ] stupid. And there's not going to
be no fair fight. There's not going to
be no fair fight either. It's not going
to be fair. So, just to let you know,
it's not going to be fair. Just like
it's not going to be fair with Timmy
because it seems to be with you people.
It seems to be with you people, right?
Even when fair stuff happens, like
Timmy, you still come back for more. You
still come back for more. You still come
back for more. So, it's as simple as
that, bro. If you really really want
trouble, I'll I'll give you trouble. You
knock on that door, you I will give you
trouble, bro. I will give you trouble.
It's as simple as that. And if not, shut
the [ __ ] up. It's as simple as that.
Then shut the [ __ ] up, you weird,
jealous little homosexual
little low life. Yeah. And that's what
you are. That's literally all you are.
Yeah. Go defend your boyfriend nonslegs
and cry when I call him a virgin some
more. Go and cry about him being called
a virgin some more. Oh, he's got a
girlfriend. Go cry some more, bro. You
get your cardio that way. You get your
It's as simple as that, bro. Go get your
cardio that way, lad.
Simple as that.
[ __ ] stupid little coward, bro. Yeah.
Stupid little coward.
You know what I'm saying? He's a He's a
He's a coward, bro. He's a proper proper
proper little coward.
Yeah. And I'm telling you another thing
as well. If anyone if anyone does, let
me tell you something as well. Yeah,
I'll tell you right now. If anyone does,
if anyone did stop me on the street,
bro, they're they're carrying a weapon.
Friends, friends, friends. Why is it not
you, big man? But you've claimed all of
these wins in the past. You understand
what I'm saying? You've claimed all of
these wins in the past.
Yeah. So, what what what you It's bro,
like talking about people Yeah. not
having stuff going for themselves. Yeah.
Oh, they ain't got this, they ain't got
that. Bro, you're telling me that you
have got people around the house, bro?
Is this really your life? Trying to look
big on YouTube for females? Is that
really what you're trying to do?
Is that really, really, really what
you're trying to do, bro?
You'd first defend a [ __ ] nons, right? Yeah.
Please, bro. Come on. Come on. Please.
Right now, please. Come on. Come on. Is
that really? You're talking about bot.
You're talking about people that need to
work on themselves. People that live
with them. I'm broke. You're saying that
you've got people. Yeah. You're saying
that you've got people
that you're weird. You're a proper weirdo, bro.
You're actually a proper proper weirdo.
And you can't you can't even say people
are going for weaker targets. I've gave
you the same opportunity as I gave
Timmy. Yeah. I gave you the same right
opportunity as I gave Timmy. Come on the
door. You're not coming back on YouTube.
I'm humiliating you. It's as simple as that. Yeah.
Coming on YouTube being a [ __ ] in
2026. Get a life, bro. Get a [ __ ] life. Yeah.
Weirdo [ __ ] bro. It's proper weirdo. Is
it weirdo [ __ ]
Anyways, we're not entertaining this
clown anymore. Anyways, sorry. I was
just reading these [ __ ] comments. Yeah.
Stupid [ __ ] idiot, bro.
Stupid [ __ ] idiot. Why are you not
going after the people that tried [ __ ]
serving stuff? Huh? Why are you not
going after the people that try [ __ ]
serving stuff instead of defending them?
Oh, he's got a girlfriend, bro. I'm just
saying it. No, no, he's got a
girlfriend, fam. Like, bro, like, why
are you not trying to get the people
Yeah, that's tried to get you in some
big trouble here with the police.
Come on, bro. Come on. Come on. Let
answer that question. Like, shouldn't
you be getting shouldn't you be trying
to meet like these people that have got
you in trouble
instead of being up my [ __ ] ass like
bottle like a butterfly on [ __ ]
the [ __ ] Oh, what is it, man?
This phone is [ __ ] This phone is
[ __ ] bro. Sometimes it does this.
I have to reset my phone. Sorry about
that, bro. [ __ ] hell. Yeah.
This is weird. All of you people in this
community are weird, bro. You're weird.
You're [ __ ] weird as [ __ ] bro.
Weird as [ __ ] Weird as [ __ ] bro.
>> All right, penis head. Have you calmed down?
>> Yeah, I've calmed down, man.
>> No, you haven't calmed down. Mommy can't
afford a curry, can she? You want beans
on toast, aren't you, this weekend, my lad?
>> PJ PJ, I know what's going to happen.
You're going to [ __ ] it. Mommy's going
to press the panic alarm. Then if the
police do turn up, we'll have to explain
that. They should take they should take
a bacon off the internet who wants to
abuse and break women and all this and
all that. Peter, you're going to do
nothing. Peter, London Taylor came to
you today. If I gave London Taylor 200
quid today and he came to your door, you
would hide behind the bed and Bobby
would pull the lead and your sister
would come out. Not today. Not today,
London. Not today, London. I said,
remember Christmas day, your sister
with London, I'm not getting a taxi one
way. You wrote about this, Pet meal, Peter,
it's happening Wednesday.
to get your tax
to pay for his tax like you said you
would. You had your chance. You didn't
get like that. Like you didn't get a
taxi like you said. You didn't get a taxi.
Like you didn't get a taxi. Like you
didn't get like
on the phone.
I will be
tonight cuz you're going to do nothing
Peter. Even Mongol who been it was the
most pathetic punch has got more about
it than you.
Yeah, even the lowest low stand in the
UK has got more about it than you.
Anyway, Peter, enjoy having a weekend with no
vindaloo. No vindaloo la. See like a penis head.
>> You're a talker. You're talking. This is
all you are. You're a talker. That's all
you are and you'll ever be. That's what
you are and you will always be forever.
You're a talker. You're nothing but a
[ __ ] talker. It's as simple as that.
You're a talker. Yeah.
It's as simple as He's a talker. He is a
Think about it, Leslie. Right. What is
he doing today? Nothing. He's doing
nothing today. Right. So why can't he
come to London today?
So why can't he come to London today? Huh?
Crazy. What did that account say that I
I've watched Scream and I know what to do now?
That's funny, isn't it?
Yeah, it's funny to be honest. Yeah. No,
not even, bro. No, I'm just I'm just
sick of this guy trying to bully people
on YouTube, bro. To be fair, I'm I'm I'm
just sick of it to be honest with you, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. To be honest with you. Yeah. To be
honest. To be honest. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
Same with this London Taylor trying to
call [ __ ] bro. Yeah, he said he said
he's coming Wednesday, but now he's not coming.
Yeah, now he said he is coming
Wednesday, now he's not coming. [ __ ]
off, man. I You people here need to just
get off this [ __ ] and get a life, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. All right, Dick Brown. How's it going? >> Virgin.
>> Yeah, I'm not too bad. Dick Bra anyway,
Dick Bra. Yeah. Um, Steven Harshaw, you
know that you know Steven Harwood,
sorry. Pip loft count because we all
know it's him. Thinks you're going to
win the fight when I'm going to
humiliate you again.
>> What's your plans for today?
>> My plans I've just said I've got a
family meal later so I can't get to London.
You really are a penis head.
I'm not going to be like you. Mommy
can't afford a curry.
Mommy can't afford a curry.
If you got this money, Peter, get
another. Get a vindaloo. I know it's not
going to happen.
>> I'm getting a vindaloo tonight.
>> Oh yeah. Are you Are you going to ask
mommy to get
>> Are you going to ask mommy to get a Mr. Lender?
>> Let me see what I need.
>> Mommy, I need a Chloe. Get me a Mr. I
eat. Let's see what you eat.
>> Let's see what I eat and let's see what you eat.
>> Yes. You going to go and get a payday loby? Yeah.
>> I don't need to. I've got more money
than you. I've got more money than you.
Penis head. It's in your head.
on your skin.
>> I love it, bro. I love it. And he's not
going to do a damn thing about it. And
he's not going to do a damn thing about
it. Yeah. It's as simple as that.
And he is not going to do a dang thing
about it on a Monday or a Tuesday or a
Wednesday or ever. Yeah. Virgin. [ __ ]
virgin. That's what he is, bro. Virgin. Yeah.
Yeah. Simple, lad.
Yeah. It's as simple as that.
Did you watch my video on LT? Uh uh Joe,
what did you think? Cuz he's mentioning
me, you see. So if you're mentioning me,
I will I I will respond back.
Yeah, it's as simple as that about your
friends have been around. Bro, I leave
the house every day. Unless you're going
out at like 2:00 in the morning, I'm out
this house every day.
Like the [ __ ] bro. I'm out of the house
every single [ __ ] day. Every day. So
unless someone's coming at like 2:00 in
the morning or 1:00 in the morning or
12:00 at night, then obviously I'm not
there. I'm not out the house, obviously.
But like, what the [ __ ]
Meet up and have a straighter, bro. You
know, you don't even know these people.
Why do Bro, we don't even know these
people, bro. Like this is, you know,
when you're saying this, like this is
normal. Fire stick here. We don't even
know these people. This is so weird and
pathetic. This is exactly why I said to
This is exactly why I said to Timmy.
Yeah, I'm not meeting you anywhere, but
if you come in the door, I'm going to
finish you. It's as simple as that. Why
do you think I don't go to Birmingham?
Why do you think I'm not going to meet?
Because, bro, you don't even know these people.
You know what I'm trying to say about
you don't even know these people that
you're and and you're meeting them for
fights. I'm not doing that. I said
strictly if you ring this doorbell or
you knock on this door or you do any
damage to this house, you'll get your
finished. It's as simple. It's as simple as that.
[ __ ] It's And I said the same thing
to Timmy as well. Yeah. And that's it.
Yeah. I've heard about it, bro. I've
heard about it. You know,
it's weirdo [ __ ] bro. It is really,
really weirdo weirdo [ __ ]
All Joe, he's a proper hypocrite. He's a
proper proper hypocrite, bro. This LT I
don't He's a proper hypocrite. It's a
weaker target when it suits him. Do you
get me? Yeah. It's a weaker target when
it suits him. Do you get it? That's
That's it, bro. That is literally it.
That's all I really have to say is that
you're a hypocrite and you contradict
yourself. That's That's all I really can
say. You You do, though. No, you
definitely do. You definitely definitely
definitely definitely do. That's what I
picked up on that video, bro. 100%. You know,
that's it, bro. Like, we get it. We
understand what you're trying to do,
bro. Like, you're trying to look good
for women on YouTube. I get it, bro.
It's cool, you know. But you're not
going to do that with me, bro. You're
not going to start knocking on people's
doors. You're not going to start
smashing people's windows 5 years later.
That's just not happening, you know?
And at the end of the day, bro, like, am
I innocent? No. But don't try and tell
people that they're bringing trouble to
anyone's door. No, they're [ __ ] not.
You started it. It's as simple as that.
You [ __ ] started it. Yeah.
If I was bringing trouble to a door, I'd
be doing videos every day saying,
"You're this. [ __ ] you. You're race.
Come here." That's what bringing trouble
means. You just didn't like the truth
and then you started coming with your
bully boy tactics. That's what That's
what you was trying to do. Yeah.
That's that, bro. Anyways, I'm done with
these little retards anyways, bro. Yeah,
I've said the same thing to Timmy. I've
said the same thing to anyone unless
somebody physically damages a window or
they just come in the door. I'm not
meeting no one. It's I've said the same
thing to Timmy and it goes to anyone
else. It goes to everyone and anyone
else. Doesn't matter what you look like.
How about that one?
Yeah. How about that one?
That's it. That's all I got to say. Simple.
You know what I mean, bro?
What the [ __ ] does a torpedo mean?
Have you literally got nothing better to
do? Like, like seriously, seriously.
Have you got nothing better to do, lad?
Have you got nothing better to do?
Like, seriously, nothing better to do, bro. Seriously. Madness.
I'm going to unsubscribe from Timmy, I
think. Anyways, bro. Um, yeah, cuz he
was the only one I'm subbed to.
I think I'm going to unsub to Timmy now,
Joe, lad. He's a lot. And I think I'm
subscribed to Monty, man, as well. So,
yeah, I've unsubed, lad.
I can't stand that [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Um,
you can find his channel on the UK
biggest nonsers website, lad. Simple as that.
Oh, and also he was biased when I stuck
it on the bouncer and I stuck it on them
people sat down. Do you remember that
video? Fire stick. Do you remember that
video? Fire stick,
right? Do you remember that video? Fire
stick. That was also biasness. So, bro,
I understand I've took L's. Yeah. Yeah,
I have took L's, bro. Yeah. I've also
took a lot of wins, but then when I took
the wins, you made excuses as well. So,
oh, the bounces at work. Okay. Then,
what about them four people that sat
down when I [ __ ] when I told them
about themselves? Like, you've always
got excuses even when people take W's.
Uh, so what you have you have little excuses anyways.
Okay. And say the bouncer was at work.
Okay. Okay. The bouncer was at work.
Okay, fair enough. So then what about
the other four people that tried running
up their mouth and I had to tell them
about themselves. What was the excuse
with that one then? You're full of excuses, bro.
Doesn't matter if me and Rick's took
L's. It doesn't matter, does it? Because
even when people take W's and they do
redeem themsel, well, you're biased.
Simple as that. And we're not just
talking about the bias. We're We're not
just talking about the bouncer. We're
talking about multiple times.
We're not even just talking. So, you've
always got excuses. You've always got
excuses. Whether it's a bouncer, whether
it You will always have little excuses.
It's as simple as that. So, who cares
who's took L's, bro? Really? Come on.
It doesn't matter if they thought I was
crazy. They started it. I didn't start
on them. They started They started it
with me. And the way I spoke to them in
front of them women, they didn't even stand up.
They didn't even stand up. That is embarrassing. So,
so yeah. I mean, I didn't back down from
that, whatever it was. But look, we
don't know who any So, does it really
matter anyways? You know,
bro, what do you mean they was laughing?
I was laughing at them. I told them to
[ __ ] off. I call them ugly. It doesn't
matter if they were laughing, bro. They
done nothing. I was laughing at them.
I told their girlfriend to [ __ ] off.
Like, they can laugh all they want. I
don't really care at the end of the day.
So, that's the new excuse. When somebody
backs out, they're laughing. Okay,
that's a new excuse then. You know, I
was laughing at them. I said, "Fuck off.
Back to Newcastle, you silly, ugly
cunt." They done nothing. They done
nothing at all. Laughing. Not laughing.
They didn't even if that was if that was
somebody that was seriously about
something, they would have stood up.
They would have literally stood up if
anyone But again, you just always will
have excuses. So, the whole thing's irrelevant.
It doesn't really matter because you're
always going to have excuses anyways,
so it doesn't matter. Yeah. Okay. They
were laughing. Okay. Okay. That's your
excuse. So, that's another excuse you're
going to use now that they were
laughing. Well, let me tell you
something, mate. The bouncer wasn't
[ __ ] laughing. Yeah, I can tell you
one sec. For one second, the bouncer wasn't laughing.
That he wasn't laughing one little bit.
Oh, but he's at work, so then there's
another excuse. So, this is what I mean
with you people. You're always going to make excuses.
Does it does it matter? You're always
going to make excuses. That's why no one
shows you money. That's why no one shows
you anything anymore because you always
just make excuses. So there's no point.
You get me, lad? So that's it,
you know? And I was laughing at them,
bro. Like telling them to [ __ ] off back
to where they come from. I was laughing
at them as well. I told them my trainers
is worth more than your whole outfit for
[ __ ] sake. You know,
but that's what I mean. You're always
going to be biased, so there's no point
at this place. This is what I'm saying, you know?
I've spat on people before. They ain't
done nothing. Oh, there's another
excuse. You always have excuses.
And you know deep down you've always got excuses.
You know deep down you've always got excuses.
So the whole point the whole thing is is pointless.
People prove to you they've had sex, you
come out with a load of excuses.
People stick it on people, you come out
with a load of excuses. People beat you
at the money game. Well, with that time,
no, you came out with a load of excuses.
So, there's no point with you. There is
no point with people like you. I just I
just allow you on the channel because
[ __ ] it, why not? It's funny, but deep
down, bro. Deep down, you always come
out with excuses.
You always come out as excus with excuses.
It's a bit like LT as well, right? I
guarantee you if LT done the same thing
as Prime done, this is the biasness
about it. If if LT done the same thing
to me as Prime done, people wouldn't
have that. People would say, "Oh, you
didn't hit him. You didn't beat him up.
You didn't hit him. You didn't beat him up."
Yeah. You didn't hit him. You didn't
beat him up.
That's what exactly what they would say
to LT. I already know. I know this. I
know this little sector. Yeah,
it's true though, isn't it? You got to
laugh at this place, bro. You got to
laugh at this place.
You got to laugh at these jealous people
in this community, bro. You got You got
to laugh at it, man.
I feel sorry for Paul Laney to be honest. Yeah.
I'm not scared though. No, brother.
Do you understand what I mean? Fire
stick. You're not scaring. No, brother.
It's the truth though, isn't it, Greasy?
You're intimidating. No [ __ ]
Do you understand, bro? No [ __ ] at all. Yeah,
you're intimidating no [ __ ] Yeah,
it's true, don't it, Greasy?
You never know, Grez. I could go outside
and someone with a screen mask could
just go and stab me.
with a screen with a screen mask in it.
Taking a baby away from its mama. Yeah,
that's how I felt at one point. Yeah.
Yeah. When a woman left me before, I
felt like I got took away from my mama.
No, Greasy. But what would happen if you
actually went out? Yeah. And someone
with a screen mask stabbed you?
You're not intimidating. No [ __ ] Yeah. Oh.
Oh, Fire Stick. You know about Timmy's
channel, isn't it? Yeah.
Oh man, that's funny, isn't it?
Like make scream in real life, in it, Grezy. Yeah.
Make Scream back in real life, in it.
I love it. I love it. Yeah, bro.
Do not scare me. No, brother.
Imagine that someone done that to you,
Fire Stick. They they break into your
home over YouTube. What would you do?
You'd be scared, isn't it?
And a black cape. Yeah.
Well, do like do like scream in real
life. Influenced by scream in it.
What? Be influenced by scream in it, Greavvesy.
What? Be influenced by it. Yeah.
Like like a pistol in it. Yeah.
He's a [ __ ] He's a weird fellow.
This guy is a weird fellow. Really, bro?
Really? Yeah. Do you know what I find
funny? Yeah. Fire Stick. YouTube has got
like thousands, millions of communities
and then there's this community where
everybody knows each other's channels.
Do you not find that weird?
Do you not find that like really weird? Grezy. Yeah,
it is weird.
You can watch Scream on this website, Spongebob,
and then you come to this little toxic sector.
This little sector.
This little sector, you know. [ __ ] hell. Yeah,
this guy looks like he's on some kind of mission.
This little sector,
this little Well, I don't understand if
someone's got a family in that. Yeah.
How How do they have so much time to be
on this YouTube and do this [ __ ] Fire
stick. I don't understand it. me lad, you know.
Yeah, he said that he was going to give
me his address and that. Maybe he should
maybe I'll take his address and then
just go to his house with the screen
mask with another person in it.
We'll just dress up a scream and
just troll the [ __ ] out of him in it.
Yeah, just troll him in it, bro. since
he wants to troll people. Yeah.
Simple, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. For real, lad. For real.
I don't understand. This guy made a new
channel, yet everybody knows about his channel.
Yeah. Everybody knows about his channel.
How does that make sense? How have you
made a new channel? Yeah. Um,
how have you made a new channel
and then [ __ ] people know about it?
That doesn't make no sense, does it?
O Fire Stick, lad. Fire stick. You need
to try this. Um, you need to try this foul.
Yeah, he's an ugly bastard, bro. He's
Yeah, I do as well. I'm the same. Fire
stick. Whenever I see Timmy, I just
laugh. Yeah, I'm the same.
>> Hello, this is Mr. We've we've had to
decline um Een's application because
you've had too much credit and you've
got too many letters from Lao and you're
behind on your council tax by about £355.
So there's no curry for you tonight, PJ. No vindaloo.
No vindaloo. How do you feel that you're
going to have to eat slop tonight? My
>> the only one with IB no
mommy can't get you a vindaloo straight
away. She's been declined by Mr. Linda.
>> Why can someone send me Can someone send
me the screen?
>> No. Vindaloo second. One second.
>> No vinder.
>> Are you coming? Wait, are you actually
coming on Wednesday? Yes.
And you can enjoy your weekend with no
takeaways for pizza. No take away.
>> He's going to be all night on YouTube
because of Vindaloo. I'm going to order the costume.
>> I'm ordering the costume ready. Yeah. No
vindaloo for pizza. No. I'm going to I'm
going to get the costume.
>> Yeah. I'm going to get a touching ready.
>> How do you feel about that?
>> Yeah. How do you feel that you've got no
Vindaloo, Peter? I guarantee you you
won't be having a takeaway tonight cuz your skint
get a takeaway. Expose me. Own me. Get a
>> I will. I am getting a take away.
>> Expose me. Get a take away.
>> I am getting a take away. I dare you.
You know what I'm going to do? I'm going
to get some extra chicken ticker today
just for you, Greeny. I'm just I'm going
to get an I'm going to get some extra
chicken ticker today just for Timmy. I
wasn't going to get that. I was just
going to get a curry. I'm going to get
some extra chicken ticker. Okay, boss.
Okay with you, boss. Greavves. I'm going
to get the mask ready for Wednesday. Yeah.
I'm going to take the scream thing and
I'm going to do it in real life.
Obviously, if that's okay with you,
you know, if that's okay with you, boss,
if that's okay with you, Captain,
I want that mask, bro.
Yeah, I want that mask in it.
Do you want to see the mask?
Well, but we need a cape as well.
Oh, that's Tilly.
Tilly the Dam. I do like Tilly the Dalmatian.
Oh, he's cute. Tilly the Dalmatian. >> Look.
All right then, Peter. I want to see
this takeaway uploaded for 24 hours.
Expose me. Come on. Own me.
>> Yeah, I will. I will.
>> Get a 35 take away. You have to wait. 35
take away. Cuz YouTube matters, bro. YouTube matters.
>> You're going to have to wait.
>> Anyway. Anyway, are you going to go and
get this takeaway? Come on. Expose.
>> If I get a takeway. If I get a take. I
will do. You're going to have to wait
until it opens. You're just going to
have to wait until it opens. I get a
take away. Expose me. You'll have to wait until
>> Yeah, you'll have to wait until it opens.
>> I dare you to get an arm bread, a rice,
a bindaloo, some chicken ta chicken, and
some pter bread.
>> I will. I will do.
>> That'll come to £3956.
>> Yep, I will do that.
>> Okay, go on then. Expose me.
>> And then when I do that, when you when I
do that, can you show me £500?
>> Yes, you can expose me then. Yes.
>> Okay then. Deal. Everyone's heard it,
right? That's a deal. Deal. Yeah. Deal.
>> No. Peter, I can't show you anything.
I'm just taking the piss here. Come on.
Expose me. Come on. YouTube. YouTube
means everything to you. Expose me. Come
on, Peter. Finish me. Expose me.
>> Yep, I will.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I will.
>> Yeah. £3950 takeaway. I want to see
chicken wings. I want to see chicken
vindaloo. A fried mushroom. I don't have
chicken vindaloo. I have lamb vindaloo.
I don't have chicken. I have lamb.
>> Okay. So, have a lamb vindaloo then.
>> A mushroom fried rice.
>> A mushroom fried rice. They don't do
that in India. You [ __ ]
>> Yes, they do. Yes, they do. You [ __ ]
[ __ ] No. Okay. So, have a cubby next
and I'll show you in an Indian mushroom
fried rice. You're going to look like an
absolute failure. Ain't you PJ? Oh,
yeah. I'm the you honestly. No, no, no.
Serious PJ, calm down a minute.
Seriously, you honestly don't think they
do a mushroom fried rice in an Indian. I
have it all the [ __ ] time, Pet. I
have it all the [ __ ] time.
>> No, they don't. Okay, listen. I'll do my
takeaway today and you show us yours.
>> No, no, no, no, no. You can show us me.
You make your takeway.
>> Let's see who has a better take me.
Expose me. Are you going to get a
mushroom fried wife to think what you
don't think exists? Let's see who gets
the better voice.
>> You [ __ ] as you call me.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'm gonna show you. I'm
>> You little You [ __ ] virgin [ __ ]
>> Come on, Peter. Excuse me. Go on.
You [ __ ] lie to me, Peter. It is to you.
>> You [ __ ] virgin [ __ ] It's
>> okay Peter. It's how it's going to go.
You're going to get a lamb tikka and
chicken tikka mixed meat. That's £13.
Yeah. Some pizza bread, a naan bread, a
mushroom peeler voice, and a lamp in
daloo. Yeah. And some samosas. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> You get all that. You've exposed me. >> Okay.
>> You're Listen. Listen, Timmy. You're not
intimidating. No, son.
>> Timmy, you're not intimidating.
>> Still coming Wednesday.
>> Yeah, you can come, man. Bring London
Taylor with you as well. The mask will
be ready as well. I'm going to be
getting the mask ready.
Creepy. I'm going to I'm going to be
getting I'm going to be getting the mask ready.
I'm going to be getting the the mask ready.
I can't do it without the mask. Is it?
Look at the mask. Crazy.
Oh man. Right one second. I need to
brush my mashes.
I need to brush my nashes.
Oh, do you remember Monty? Um, do you
remember Monty? Um, Greavvesy. Monty,
why do people in this community call
people skin? Because they're skin.
Remember? Because they're skin.
Yeah. because they're remember.
So, we'll see who has a better takeaway today. Yeah,
we'll see who has a better takeaway.
You're not [ __ ] scary. No, brother.
Oh, bro, you're boring. You're [ __ ]
boring, bro. You're not. You are boring,
lad. Yeah, you don't You don't
intimidate no one. You're boring. Just
come with Timmy on Wednesday. Just come
with women. Just come. Listen.
Literally, listen. Listen. Just come
with Timmy on Wednesday, bro. You're
boring. Yeah. Stop trying to look good
on this community. You don't scare no
one. Yeah. You literally do not scare
nobody. You're just a homosexual
little non-slegs lover that needs to get
a life. Get a life. You need one, bro.
You don't scare no one. And stop telling
people, "No, no, no, no, no. Listen,
listen, listen, listen. This is I never
said come outside my house." I said,
"You knock on my door. You ring my
doorbell. You damage any of my
property." Yeah, that's going to be the
That's what I said. I didn't say come
out. And I said the same thing to Timmy.
Yeah, I said the same thing to Timmy.
And I bet you you will not be coming on
back on YouTube running up your mouth.
Yeah. Yeah. Simple as that.
Simple. Simple, bro. Simple as that.
Yeah. I never ever said I was stronger
than you, but I'm more mad than you. I'm
more mad than you. Trust me.
Yeah. Simple as that. You're just a
little low life. You ain't got nothing.
This is exactly why I said all of this.
You really have got nothing. Shouldn't
you be defending your boyfriend every
time I call him a virgin some more, bro?
Shouldn't you be doing that? Shouldn't
you really, really, really be doing that?
Shouldn't you be doing that some more,
bro? Get yourself a little life.
That's what you need to get. You need to
get yourself a little life, lad. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Of
course you will. Of course you will.
Yeah. Yeah. Of course you will, bro. Of
course you will, bro. Just knock on the
door so I can chef you up, bro. And
don't run away, bro. Just don't run
away. Don't run away, lad. Make sure you
don't run as well.
Yeah, bro. Make sure you don't run away
as well. Let me Let me Let me chef you
up so you don't come back on YouTube
after like the big man again. Yeah.
Simple. Yeah. Make sure you don't run
away. Make sure you go live doing it and
see what happens to you, big man. Make
sure Yeah. Go live pissing on my door.
Yeah. Yeah. Go live. Go live pissing on
the door, big man, and see what happens.
Come on, big man. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Come
on then, big man. Come on. And make sure
you don't run away. Let me let let make
make sure you don't run away as well.
You little jealous little nonslegs
lover. You noddlegs his boyfriend. Oh,
he's got a girlfriend, fam. Bro, make
sure you go live and do it. You can go
live on your channel as well. Yeah. And
make sure you don't run away as well.
Make sure you don't run away. No
problem. Make sure you don't run away.
Let me chef you up good and proper. Let
me give you the trouble that you wanted.
Let me give you Let me give you all the
trouble that you've always wanted on
this [ __ ] community. Let me give you
this trouble, bro. Let me give you this
trouble that you want. Yeah. Simple.
Simple. Yeah. Simple. Simple as that.
Yeah. Make sure you go live. I want to
give you as much trouble as you want.
Any trouble you want, I'll give it to
you today. And there's not going to be
no fair. There's not going to be no
fair. Simple as that. Yeah. It's as
simple as that. Simple as that. Simple
as that, bro. Yeah. You're saying, "Oh,
you make old women scream and no, that's
not going to be me, bro. That's not
going to be me."
Yeah, it's as simple as that. That's not
going to be me. Yeah. Well, you're going
to let Bro, I'll cut your dick off.
Like, who the [ __ ] do you [ __ ] think
you are? You're not bullying no one.
You're not scaring no one, bro. Do that
and don't run. I'm coming to you. I'll
just get some scissors and just cut your
dick off. Who the [ __ ] do you think you
are, bro? Who do you actually think you
are? Like, no. No, no, no, no. Come on,
come on, come on. Let's be so real right
now. Who do you actually think you are, bro?
Listen, listen, listen, listen, listen.
I wasn't in the house when that
happened. Yeah. I And your And your mate
knew never to do it again. Yeah. Your
mate knew never to do it again cuz he
knew what was good for him. Yeah. And
your mate knew to never ever do it
again. I leave the house every day. Your
mate is a [ __ ] hole. Yeah. Which is
why he never done it again cuz he knows
what's good for him. Every single time
you show up, you got weapons as well.
Every single time, don't ignore this
guy. Yeah. Every single time this guy
comes with weapons cuz he can't fight.
Don't ever try and tell you this guy
don't use weapons. Yeah. Don't ever try
and let this guy try. He uses weapons.
He can't fight. He's a [ __ ] He's an
internet gangster. I'm telling you right
now, bro. I'm telling you right, bro.
Yeah. This guy is an internet gangster.
He can't fight. No. No one he knows can
fight, bro. Trust me. You know that day
I emailed you. Yeah. Listen. You know
that day that I emailed you, I was
waiting for you to come. I was going to
p you up, bro, and put all over YouTube.
You wann to be gangster. I was going to
do it, bro. 100% I was going to do it. I
was going to do it. I swear to God.
Yeah. Yeah. Simple. You can come, bro,
and make sure you go live. Let me cut
your dick off, internet gangster. I'm
sick of you being this internet
gangster. Please do come, bro. You know
what? Actually, I think I've got a
lighter as well somewhere. Yeah, please
do come. Yeah, please do come. Yeah.
Yeah, please do come. Let me [ __ ] you
up, you little gay internet gangster.
You little nunch lover. You little gay
boy defending your boyfriend. Yeah.
Yeah, please do come. Please do come.
Yeah, please do come, lad. I've got a
lighter ready. I got blow all over your
face trying to act like a big man, bro.
Don't [ __ ] try and do it with me.
[ __ ] you. Don't intimidate me, you
stupid little [ __ ] Trying to look good
for women. You little s. Trying to look
good for women. Yeah, simple, bro. Yeah.
trying to look good for women. You're
not no big brother. You're not a big
man, BRO. YOU GOT BULLIED out of
Tottenham. THIS IS WHY YOU CAN'T STOP
GOING BACK TO THIS SECTOR. This is
exactly why you come back to this sector
cuz you're a bully victim. Tottenham
bullies you. London bullies you. You're
not known anywhere. That's why you come
back to this sector every time. Yeah.
Every single time you come back to
because you're a bully victim. You got
bullied out of Tottenham. You got
bullied out of London. And that's what
it IS. THAT IS EXACTLY WHAT it is.
You're nothing but a little bully
victim. That's what you are. Someone
that got bullied out of the ends. And
that's why you come here trying TO LOOK
BIG. I LIE. You're on here trying to
look big though. Aren't you just on here
trying to look big all the time? Aren't
you on it all the time trying to look big?
Aren't you on it all the time just
trying to look big despite leaving this
community? No. No. Come on, bro. Come
on. Come on. Come on. Are you not on it
all the time trying to look big for
YouTube? Trying to look good for women?
Are you not trying to do it though? Tell
Tell me you're not trying to do it, bro.
Cuz how does everyone know about your
channel when you said that you got away
from this place? Explain it to me.
Explain to me how everybody knows about
your channel. Come on, bro. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Bullied me out, bro.
Listen. You got bullied out of London,
bro. I listen listen.
Every single time you came with other
people and weapons, you're a coward.
You're a coward. That's what you are.
You're just a coward. You're a coward.
You're not about that life. You're not
psychotic. You don't pose a threat to
anybody, especially not to me. Yeah. And
that's and that is as simple as that.
Yeah. You're trying to look good for
women, bro. That's all you're trying to
do. And listen, I will go for Timmy when
I watch How I Please. Yeah. And another
thing, wasn't you trying to beat up
nons? One second. One second. One
second. Wasn't you trying to beat up
nons? Wasn't you trying to beat up
nonsexs? You little hypocrite. You
little hypocrite. [ __ ] special needs
[ __ ] You little disabled spacker.
Little gorilla. Wasn't you trying to
Wasn't you trying to beat him up? You
[ __ ] disabled [ __ ] Wasn't you
Wasn't you annoying at this guy multiple
multiple times? Yeah. Yeah. Simple as
that. Listen. Listen. Everybody heard
what I said. Yeah. Everybody heard what
I said. Yeah. It's as simple as that.
Wasn't you trying to be One second. One
second. Answer the video. Wasn't you
trying to have beef with this guy?
Wasn't you having Wasn't you having beef
with this guy? Yes or no? Wasn't you
having beef with this guy? Yes or no?
Oh, he's the weaker target. You [ __ ]
[ __ ] You tried meeting half of these
people yourself. You [ __ ] special
needs bully victim that ain't that ain't
finished school. You're another one
that's not finished school. You've been
bullied your whole life. You contradict
yourself. Everything you say, I swear
this guy contradicts himself. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Like I said, you break my
window, you even knock on the door, I
will be doing it. Don't go outside in in
your car with your little friends. Yeah.
Don't go outside in your car with your little friends.
I will tell you your thoughts about you
sucking nods dick. You little biased
bully victim. I'll tell you to your
face. I will tell you a biased little
bully victim to your face. You little
nonslegs loving [ __ ] I'll tell you
straight to your face. I'll tell you
straight to your face. Simple as that.
I'll tell you straight straight to your
face while smirking with my unbrushed
teeth. I [ __ ] will do it, bro. I will
do it. Simple. I will [ __ ] do it. You
little [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] You ain't
got no kids. This guy's got no children,
bro. The amount of times he's he he
spends stalking men. He's got no
children. He's another nonslegs. He's
This guy has got no family, bro. I'm
telling you, he's a bully victim.
someone that sits on here doing what he
does. Yeah. I will ever be allowed to go
to the shops. Oh, I will go to the shops
every day. No one's scared of your
little batty boy crew. No one is scared
of your little batty boy bully victim
crew. I guarantee you no one is scared
of you or your bully victim crew, lad.
No one's scared of you, bro. You [ __ ]
little gay little fatties. No one's
scared of you. You little [ __ ]
victim. I'll go out whenever the [ __ ] I
want to go out, you little [ __ ]
prick. You [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] I will
go out to any shops whenever I want to.
You don't [ __ ] tell me what I can and
can't do. You little [ __ ] bully
victim with no family. Shut up, bro.
Yeah. And everyone call this guy out
today if he doesn't smash windows. If
this guy don't smash windows and make my
mom scream. Yeah. If he doesn't make my
mom scream like he keeps bragging, he's
a [ __ ] I gave him full permission to
do it today. Him, his little walkup
boyfriend. Tell him to do it and see
what happens. This little nunchle legs
little bully victim. This little
nunchle's little bully victim lover.
Yeah, tell him. [ __ ] stupid little coward.
Yeah, that's what you are, bro. You're a
coward. Yeah, that's what you are.
You're a coward, bro. Yeah, that's what
you are. You got no kid. You got no
family. Simple as that. Yeah. Simple. Simple.
Yeah. If this guy does not ring the
doorbell today, knock the door or do
these windows in. He's not about that
life. Stop telling him to bring up stuff
from 5 years ago. Yeah. Yeah. It's as
simple as that. It's as simple as that.
Yeah. You're a coward, bro. That's what
you are. You're a [ __ ] coward. That's
what you are. You're a coward trying to
look good on YouTube, bro. That's all
you are. But you don't scare no one. You
don't intimidate no one.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's as simple as
that. You don't scare me. I'm not scared
of you, bro. You're not bullying me. You
are not bullying me. You will never
bully me, bro. Yeah. Do you understand?
You know, you little nonslegs lover. Oh,
he's got a girlfriend, fam. He's got a
girlfriend, fam. Calm down, you little
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying, bro?
Calm down, you little [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, simple as that, bro. You're a
little [ __ ] mong, bro. That's what
you are. And you know what's so mad is
Rick Mace didn't even spend more than 30
seconds more than 30 seconds talking
about you. Funny how you know everything
though. Ain't it? It's funny. Just Just
admit that you watch everything. Just
admit Just admit that you watch
everything. Yeah. Just admit that you watch everything.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Just admit that you watch
everything. Yeah. And stop saying that
you're leaving cuz you're never leaving.
Ant-Man left. You're not leaving. Just
admit that you watch this place 24/7.
It's embarrassing now, bro. It's
embarrassing now because think about it,
bro. If you wasn't on this sector. Yeah.
Listen, if you wasn't on this sector,
who are you trying to look good for?
Think about it, bro. You know that, bro.
You can't pull a wool over my eyes. You
know, if anyone gave you a challenge,
you would not meet them. This is why
you're addicted to this sector. This is
why you're addict. You watch this sector
every time you're a part of this sector.
You're a part of this toxic cuz you're
Why are you on it? Why are you on it,
bro? Why are you on it? You're on it all the time.
Yeah, bro. I've got a channel. Nobody
knows about my channel. How does
everybody know about your channel? How
does everybody know about your channel?
No one knows about my new channel. How
does everybody know your channel?
Because you [ __ ] commented and they
found you, you [ __ ] idiot. So, if you
was really done, why are you still here?
Why are you still here?
Why are you still here? It doesn't make
sense. None of it makes any sense. You
don't make no sense, bro. You don't make no sense.
Yes, they do know about your channel.
Yes, they do know about your [ __ ]
channel. Of course, they know about your
channel. You comment on other um comm
community on other people's channel on this community.
Yeah, they do know about your channel,
man. Shut up, man. Get a grip and get a
life. And do you know why I brought your
name into it with Timmy? You want to
know why I brought your name into it
with Timmy? Because I knew exactly what
you was going to do. And I was right.
That's why I brought your [ __ ] name
up cuz I know exactly. Right. If Timmy
comes here, you know exactly what's
going to happen. You know exactly what
you're going to come out with. Oh, you
only go for the weaker target, bro. You
tried to go for half these people
yourself. Not Timmy. You didn't never
try to go for Timmy, but you tried to go
for a lot of these people. So what are
they? Weaker target when I go for them
then. But they're not a weaker target
when you go for them. Come on, bro. It
doesn't make sense. Make it make sense
when you're going to say stuff. Yeah.
Yeah. Special needs, bro. You're calling
people special needs, but all you've
done was contradict yourself. All you've
done in that video, I swear to God, all
that, bro, you contradicted yourself in
that whole video. Nothing you said made
any sense. Okay? I'm special needs.
Okay, bro. But I don't contradict myself
like you do.
I don't contradict myself the way that you do.
You know, then you're trying to tell
people that they're bringing trouble to
Bro, people told you that you're being
biased and because you didn't like it.
Yeah. You come on this channel trying to
trying to be trying to be a little bully
boy. Yeah. Because I stated the fact
that you didn't like it. Then you
started coming on here saying that
you're going to do this and you're going
to do that and you're going to do this
and you're going to do that. First and
foremost, I don't know if you watched my
video. Uh I didn't pick on Timmy. Timmy
started mentioning my name and I said
that if he doesn't stop mentioning my
name, I'm gonna message his family.
Yeah. Because that's what I would done.
I message his family. Simple as that.
You keep going on about me, I message
your family. Simple. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Bro. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Just make sure
you go live as well when you're doing
it. Just make sure you go live and
you're putting your dick through that
through the through the post box and
I'll just cut your dick off, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You do that, bro.
Yeah. You do that.
Yeah. You do that, bro. Yeah. Yeah. You
do that and you see what happens. Is it?
It's as simple as that. You see what
happens? You sad sad pathetic. You know
you're just like these people. You know
that. You're just like these people,
bro. You're just literally like these people.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Whatever, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And I leave the
house every single day. Every day I
leave the house. Every single day I
leave the house, lad. So, I don't know
what time your people are coming, bro.
Cuz I leave the house every day. I leave
the house every day, bro. I left the
house yesterday. So, I don't understand
how you're saying that people can't go
hear people. You're cheeky. You know,
you're very, very, very cheeky. You are.
You're a very, very cheeky fellow.
You're a very, very, very, very Oh, I
[ __ ] will. I [ __ ] will leave my
house after tonight. And I'll do it on
camera. Oh, yes, I [ __ ] will. I will
do it on camera. Oh, yes, I will leave
my house after tonight. Yes, I will
leave my mom's house. Again, I'm not a
female, bro. Yeah, you need to remember
this. I'm not a scared little female.
Yeah. And am I stronger than you?
Probably not. But I know that you
wouldn't be You wouldn't win me, bro.
You wouldn't You wouldn't win against
me. I'm more psychotic than you, bro.
Trust me. People should have known with
the gambling [ __ ] how how mad I get
after losing 20. But bro, I'll do you
one better. Yeah. After tonight, after
tonight, I will leave the house and I
record it for you for your little
archive channel. Don't you trying to
tell people they can't leave their
house, bro? Who really are you, bro?
Like, who really do you think you are?
Yeah. Yeah. Like I said, you do the mad
things like smash windows or knock on
the doorbell. I will prove how mad I am.
Yeah. Try scare my mom like you said you
was going to do when I'm here and I'll
show you how mad I am. I'll show you how
mad I am, bro. I'll show you a Scream
eight. I will show you a Scream eight,
lad. Scream seven just come out. I'll
show you a scream eight. You show me how
mad you really are just like you was
back in the day. And and this do you
know why, bro? Because I don't I know
what you're going to do, bro. You're
going to try and run into the police. I
want to do you so bad that you can't
even try and snitch. That you can't even
try and snitch. You can't even try and
snitch. Yeah. That's what, bro? Yeah.
You can't even try and snitch. Yeah. I
want to do you so badly, bro, that I
don't want you to don't want no police
involved, no nothing. Yeah.
Yeah. You're cheeky. You're a cheeky
bastard. You're You think, bro, you
actually think Listen, bro, I don't I
don't think you live in a real world.
Yeah. You actually think that you're
going to knock on someone's door and
slap someone's mom? Bro, you really
really really think that's going to
happen? Like, bro, do you really really
what world do you live in, bro? Like,
can you tell me what world you live in?
cuz you don't live in you don't live in this world.
Like you really think that is actually
ever going to happen with anyone that
you know? You are crazy, bro. You're
very very very very very very crazy.
That's what you are. You're crazy.
I don't need to I Bro, listen listen. I
don't need to be live. I don't need to
do anything that you say. Yeah. I don't
need to do anything you say. I'm
bouncing in a bit. I'm not staying live
all day. I've got a life unlike you.
Yeah. I've got a life. I'm not staying
live. I'm not [ __ ] staying alive.
Staying alive for what? For you to say,
"I told you I'm not going out. I told
you as unless you ring the doorbell, you
knock the door, or you do any damage,
I'm not I'm not going outside. I've told
you this. The same thing with Timmy.
I've literally told you this. I have
literally told you this multiple multiple times."
Yeah, I am about to, bro. I've told you
this. The same thing as I said to Timmy.
Timmy can go anywhere in London. I'm not
meeting him. Yeah. He can go anywhere
down the road. I'm not meeting him. It's
as simple as that. Yeah. It goes to
anyone, shape, size, any skin color, including you.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. You
can do that then. Yeah. You can do that.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And you will see
what will happen. Yeah. And you will see
what will happen. And you will see what
will happen, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You will see what will
happen. You're just Do you know what?
Yeah. LT, you're just another little
nods legs. I'm glad these people are
biased about you. I'm so glad all of
these people Yeah. that um that done
this, you deserve it. You deserve it.
Every time people have told you that you
didn't meet anyone, that's why I went
along with it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Man, that Do you know what?
You deserved all of that [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. You You're just another launch
legs. You're his boyfriend. That's why I
said, "Yeah, you and Timmy You and Timmy
come together on Wednesday." I literally
Timmy is serious. I That's why I said
you and Timmy should come because I'll
do you both in. Not fairly. I never said
I'm going to do it fairly. I'm not going
to do it fairly. I've admitted I'm not
going to do it fairly. I'm not trained.
I've admitted I'm not going to do it
fairly. But I'll do I will do both of
you in both. I would have done both of
you in. Simple.
And you can tell me about how nonsense
he's not a virgin and cry about it some
more. [ __ ] little fanny, bro. You're
a fanny, bro. You're a top tier fanny. I
swear to God, you actually you actually
are a top tier fanny.
Yeah. You really really are.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Like I said, you
damage my property like you my mom's
property like you said and you will see
what will happen. You will see what will
happen if you try ringing the doorbell
going on the door. Yeah. You will see
what will happen. Yeah. You will see
what will happen. You little jealous
little nonsg lover. I'm going now
anyways cuz I can do what I want when I
want. See you later anyways, lad. Yeah.
See you in a bit. See you in a