[ __ ] little bastard.
I had a [ __ ] enough of this little sector.
I've had enough of this little sector.
Don't ask me a [ __ ] lifetime. Come on
then. I love you all. I love you all. Come on.
Love you all. You [ __ ] I love the
[ __ ] love you. Come on. I love the
[ __ ] lot of you [ __ ]
I love the [ __ ] lot of you. Got a
little something in my pocket. What I've
learned from a movie.
I love you all.
I love the [ __ ] lot of you. Come on.
I love the [ __ ] all of you.
I love the [ __ ] all of you [ __ ]
I've had enough. I've had enough.
Oh, here we go. What?
Okay. Okay. We can either do it the nice
way or we can do it dirty. It's up to
you. We can play nice.
You can come in for a cup of [ __ ] You
Or we can do it dirty.
It's up to you.
You coming for a cup of tea and
biscuits. Or we can do it dirty like a street fighter.
Yeah. Or we can Or we can do it dirty.
Or we can do Or we can do it dirty.
Simple as that. Or we can do it dirty.
It's up to grieving. All right.
You got selective memory, Joe.
Bro, how can you tell Joe that he's got
selective memory? You've got selective
memory as well. To be fair, this is what
I'm saying, bro. How can you moan, bro?
How are you You can't moan about Joseph
Ferrar being having a selective memory
when you're the [ __ ] same.
Does it matter?
Doesn't matter if he's got selective
memory. You do as well. [ __ ] you let
people call me virgins and all sorts.
[ __ ] hell, you silly goose.
All we can do is dirty. It's up to you.
I've got some biscuits in the cupboard.
In the cupboard.
You know, awaiting awaiting your
arrival. Yeah, awaiting your arrival.
Lovely cup of tea to get me in the mood.
O, why is he saying that you've got
selective memory though, man? He does as
well. He lets people call me a virgin and [ __ ]
You let people call me a [ __ ] virgin.
So, you got selective memory as well,
you silly goose.
I'm having a little dance.
Do you want to see my little dance
and show you if you like?
Oops. Here we Here we go. Got my little
tracksuit and ready. Probably not the
best color to wear.
I like this sector. This This sector is fun.
This sector is a laugh.
An actual laugh. I need to move this
video to Vick May soon.
Yep. I I need to do this video to Rick
Mason on how to work a washing machine.
You know, we've got more important
things to be doing. You know,
you got more important things to be doing.
A little dance. That's all right, ain't it?
No, it's a lovely little dance.
It's a lovely little dance.
This little sector. Yeah.
What is it? Is it this little sector? Grievy.
This little sector. You know,
this little sector. I'm sick of this
Yeah, that's [ __ ] [ __ ] That's what I'm
saying. That's [ __ ] [ __ ] No, just say
that you just do what you said you was
going to do. Just do what you said that
you was going to do, bro. Yeah, it's as
simple as that.
I love you all.
Simple as that. Yeah. Why are you always
mentioning other people? Other people.
Other people. What is that [ __ ] about, bro?
always other people like, bro, top
people fight their own battles or
something. This is some year 12 [ __ ]
This is some actual year 12 [ __ ] bro.
It actually is
[ __ ] embarrassing, man. It's actually
embarrassing. You know that?
Yeah. And it's not all me though, is it
Joe? It's not all me. He started it.
He started it. So what? He started it, lad.
He has started it. He started it. He's
[ __ ] st and he's and he's escalated it.
Even if I'm not innocent. So that's it.
Yeah. It's as simple as that. He has
escalated it. He knows exactly what he's
doing. Yeah. So that's it.
I don't understand what your problem is.
I don't know what your problem is. Jo,
I'm sorry. I don't know what your
problem is. LT, why don't you just be a nice fellow?
Why don't you just be a nice little
fellow for once?
You know, just be a nice fellow.
And then you said to me, wait, wait,
wait. You said to me, one second. You
said to me that you're going to give me
your address or your parents address. I
don't want your parent. Why would I want
your parents address? I don't I'm not
I'm not I'm not an I'm not Asbo, bro. I
don't I don't I don't want to go to
people's parents' addresses. But you
said you're going to give me your
address. You're a desk, bro. I'll just
come in a screen mask. Simple, bro. I'll
just come in a screen mask. Yeah, like
like in that picture. I've learned some new moves,
you know. I've learned some new moves, lad.
Yeah, exactly. Yeah, of course.
Uh Joe, I'm not you after.
You said that you wouldn't turn up to
people if they don't if they don't talk on camera.
people if they don't talk on camera.
Seriously, when are you going to stop
all of this [ __ ] It's really, really,
really boring. LT, this is really,
really, really boring. You know that?
When are you going to stop all of this [ __ ]
When are you really going to stop this
[ __ ] It's getting really boring
now. Like this is this is really really 2026.
No, no, seriously. You tell people No,
listen to me. Yeah. You tell people that
they're picking on Timmy. Why? Cuz I
messaged his family. I'm going for
weaker targets cuz I messaged his
family. When did I say that I'm going to
meet Timmy and beat him up? Never
happened, bro. It never ever ever ever
happened. He started talking about me
and I said the same thing to him as I
said to you.
He was talking about me on his channel
trying to draw me out. Yeah. The same as
he done with Monty. Yeah. So [ __ ] him.
Simple. Yeah. Simple.
Simple as that.
Joey, you're not going to meet anyone.
If you was going to meet anyone, you
would have you would have agreed to meet in Nottingham.
Come on, Joe. You're not going to meet
anyone, man. Come on. Come on. You know,
I've already heard what Greavvesy sounds
like. I've already heard what Greavvesy
sounds like. I've heard what we we me
and Greavvesy talk in private. So,
you're you you would you're not going to
meet even if I went to Lottingham.
Just stop it. It's boring, lad. All of
this is really boring now. really really
really really boring.
No, it actually is boring though. It
actually is boring. Can you just stop it
now? It's really boring,
you know. It actually No, no, it really
really is boring.
Seriously, it seriously is. It's really boring, you know.
You know, it's as simple as that.
Why are you making videos on me? I don't
understand why you're making videos on
me. All I said, all I said to Timmy was
you can bring LT with you because I knew
exactly what you was going to do. You
was going to get yourself involved
anyways. You was going to get yourself involved anyways.
O, you you was going to get yourself
involved anyways. Don't lie. Don't lie.
He was. And shut up, Gona. Listen, Gona.
Gona. Goona. Listen, mate. Yeah. Listen.
I I You're not turning up anywhere.
Goona, shut the [ __ ] up. Yeah. You
listen. What I don't understand with you
people. Yeah. Kevin Murphy, all of you
people. Yeah. Why are you Why are you
Why haven't you come to London and try
to meet anyone once? Skoona, you're a
fat old man. Yeah. You're a fat, ugly
old man. You're not doing nothing. This
is why I don't get into it with you.
Yeah. This is why I did not get into
with you. We told Timmy. Yeah. I told
him to I told Timmy to bring you because
I knew exactly what you was going to do.
Yeah. Okay. Okay. So, Timmy comes. Say,
say Timmy came in the cab the day where
he was supposed to come on the cab to
the front door where he was going to
knock on the door. Yeah. What would have
happened? What? Tell me exactly what
would have happened. You knew exactly
what would have happened. You would have
got yourself You would have got yourself
involved anyways cuz you're always
watching. You're always watching. you're
waiting for me to fight someone else or
whatever so you can get involved again.
So I thought, okay, [ __ ] it. Since
you're watching anyways, just say your
name. It's the truth. It's the truth. It
is literally the truth. That's why I
brought your name up. Yeah.
That's why I brought your [ __ ] name
up. It's the truth. Cuz you would have
got yourself involved. You would have.
And you know you would have as well. And
you know you would have. So why why does
it matter? You would have got yourself
involved anyways. I'm not the one doing
videos. I'm not the one doing videos,
right? Um, doing gambling vlog videos
and mentioning people's names purposely
trying to [ __ ] stir, which is what Timmy
was doing. Do I do videos about you
every day? No. I stated a fact, bro.
Yeah, that we know that you was just
going to get involved anyways. So,
it's as simple as that. Yeah,
it is as simple as that though, isn't it?
He mentioned me and he was trying to
draw me out on purpose. I don't make
videos of this guy. I don't try bullying
this guy. I leave this guy alone. I
clicked on his video because he was
doing a video about gambling. I was
like, "Oh, I want to I'm interested in
gam I'm interested in this gambling talk
because I gamble sometimes." Then he
started mentioning my name. Then he done
it again. Then he done it again. Then he
done it again. So I said to him, "Okay,
you you you me you you mention my name
again. I'm going to message your family.
I'm going to keep messaging your family
until you stop." That's what I said to
him. I'm going to keep messaging your
family, messing your family, messaging
your family. Oh, I'm going to come to
London. Oh, I'm going to come to London.
Come on, man. It's stupid. You know,
listen, Goua, listen. Stop trying to
[ __ ] stir. You don't meet anyone when
they come to [ __ ] Cardiff. You
haven't been to London once. So just
shut up. Stop trying to [ __ ] stir. Yeah.
Stop trying to [ __ ] stir. Stop trying to
get someone who you think is going to do
something to me cuz you never will and
you never can. Simple. So stop it. Stop
stop doing what you're trying to I know
what you're trying to do, bro, but it's
not going to work. So yeah.
Yeah. New Year's Eve as well. And also I
wasn't even trying to get Ricks to talk
smack about you. I just met I said, "Oh,
do you still talk to LT?" And then he
started saying that stuff. I didn't [ __ ]
stir. I didn't [ __ ] stir.
I didn't [ __ ] stir at all. I never I
just mentioned your name. I said, "Oh,
do you do you still talk to him and do
started going on this talking about you
and all of this stuff about oh, living
with your mom? I don't give a [ __ ] about
that [ __ ] I all I had to do was point
out the main things about what you're
saying doesn't make sense, you know?
Yeah, come on, Joe. You're not going to
meet anyone, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, that's fine. Yeah, that's
absolutely fine, bro. Yeah,
simple. Listen, GA. Go. Go. Go. Why
don't you This is the same argument. Why
don't you come to London next week? One
second. One second. Why don't you come
to London next week?
We're just having the same argument over
and over and over again, bro. We're just
having the same argument over and over
again. We're having the same argument.
We're just going around in circles.
Rezy, it's just the same argument over
and over again.
It's the same argument over and over again, lad.
Yeah. We're just having the same
argument over and over again. Yeah. Yep.
>> I didn't block you. You was never
blocked. Kitty in the gallivan. That's
how they talk in Cardiff. Oh, Kitty in
the gallivan, my mate.
You [ __ ] little sheep shagger.
You little sheep shagging bastard.
>> The same reason why you've never turned up anywhere.
>> You [ __ ] Welsh bastard.
A new UK asylum would have like that.
Oh, get in the caravan, my mate.
I'm working I'm working on the Welsh
accent. Is it any good?
Yeah, I bowled it, bro. The only one
that's bowled it is you. Yeah. The only
one that's bowled it is you. Yeah.
This is all I'm going to do. Yeah.
Yeah. I said, "Okay, so why don't you
come to London then and sort me out
then?" Duna, why don't you come to
London and sort it out then? Why don't
you come to London and sort it out?
I met a guy from Cardiff a couple of
weeks ago. He's a sound fellow.
Actually, he was actually a sound fellow.
No, no, no. I know. No, I know you
haven't. No, you haven't. But I'm asking
you, why don't you do it? You got all
this money. You haven't got anxiety. Why
don't you come and do it? Huh?
Do you know what I'm going to do in a
minute, Grevy? Do you know what I'm
going to [ __ ] do in a minute?
I'm going to go go out this front door
and I'll just be like this.
I love you all. Come in. I love you all.
I love a lot of you. Come on.
That's what I'll [ __ ] do. I love you all.
You stupid fannies.
I had enough of these little fannies.
Seriously. Yeah. Prime, bro. You can you
can keep talking about stuff that
happened years ago, lad. You can keep
talking about what happened in years
ago, bro. You're living in the past, lad.
Good morning, Vietnam.
Wasn't that the Tourette's? The the
Scottish people from Tourette's, Ly,
you know. Wasn't Wasn't Wasn't Wasn't it um
is it isn't that um isn't Wasn't that
Tourette's video with the Scottish lads?
Don't have you ever seen that program.
I'm sure it was. Wasn't it? I'm sure it
was. When he's like, "Good morning,
Vietnam." And he's got Tourette's.
I'm sure it was. Yeah.
Yeah. I remember them them Scottish
lads. Yeah. He was like Johnny Davidson.
I remember that. Yeah. Oh, bless. Did
you ever see that? Um, Grez.
Yeah, we can sort it.
Ah, Joe and LT having an argument, but
they're both biased. They both defend on
legs and they're both biased, but they're arguing.
Only on this disabled community could this happen.
I'll be waiting for your arrival. I know
I need to get a haircut and stuff. Just
drunk a cup of tea, but I'll be I'll be
waiting for your arrival with my little
Money Chip. I'll be waiting your arrival.
I'll be waiting your arrival, lad. Yeah.
I got a little present for you as well.
I'll be waiting all of your arrivals. Yeah.
You'll wait, Dusty. For what?
For what? I've had to unsub from Timmy,
by the way. Fire stick.
I had to unsub from him, lad.
I developed brain damage.
Yeah, sorry, man. I developed brain damage. you know.
>> Yeah, I had to unsub, lad. Sorry.
Too much brain damage.
Also, another thing. Why was you talking
[ __ ] about my dating video? Uh, uh, LT,
I was only saying that like they're
[ __ ] and stuff and what they do. I
don't care. I don't make videos every
day. I'm just stating facts. Somebody on
Instagram said, "I love the video. Make
sure you never delete it." I think it
was a lovely little video and it proves
I'm not a white knight and it proves I'm
not a s either.
No, I haven't done sub for Monty. Just Timmy, bro.
See, anyone can mention my name yet.
Launch legs. Um,
uh, anyone, literally anyone. But when
Timmy does it, it's annoying because you
know what he's trying to do? He's just
trying to draw you out. Yeah. To get
attention away from him. Yeah. That's
what And that's what in fact on sublad
he is a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. I don't
even know why I even stayed sub to that
guy. He's on [ __ ] minute.
See, he didn't get in the taxi and he's
still trying to make excuses. Oh,
Wednesday. Wednesday. Wednesday. Do you
know what here? I've never known that.
such a [ __ ] on YouTube trying to act
like a hard man. Like he's not. How come
someone like him Yeah. If you saw that
guy in public? Yeah. And he's trying to
act like he's some kind of hard man.
How are you How the [ __ ] can you look
like that? Yeah. Trying to come on
YouTube to act like you're some big man.
Bear in mind, he's lost every fight as
well. Every single fight he's got into,
he's lost. Even when it was a 2v one.
How How can you?
Doesn't make any sense.
Yeah, I'm full of anxiety, bro. Yeah,
you're right. I'm so anxious.
I'm not [ __ ] scared of no brother. Fire stick.
You're [ __ ] scaring no brother.
You're not scaring no brother.
You're not intimidating no [ __ ] Yep.
What if I get killed though, Greasy? And
then Christian Izzy's messaging me.
She's going to wonder what happened to me.
Then she's going to start wondering what
happened to me.
There'll be no reply,
Grevy. There'll be no reply. Oh, bless Greavesy. Leure
taking a baby away from its mama
by a stick.
taking a baby away from its mama.
Sig was never your mama.
Sig was never your mama. Grezy,
do you remember that one? Sig was never
your mama. for your belly.
You remember that account that was going
along with it, Grezy? Nope.
Oh, you're a nasty fellow.
You're a nasty little fellow.
I love you all. I love this. I hate this little sector.
I hate this little sector. So, if I lost
every fight, Peter, why did you run away
from me two years ago? And don't say you
didn't. It's all videos. Yes, you did. I
don't give a [ __ ] if you subbed or not.
I'm still coming. I'm still coming
Wednesday if you're sub or not. No, it's
not. Yeah. Yeah, it is. And you know it
is. That is why you're full of anxiety and [ __ ]
if I've lost every fight. Answer the
question, Mongol. Why did you run away
from me two years ago? No. No. Yes. GDP.
I can you ran away from a 12y old. You
ran away from a little 12year-old
with a pigeon. And shout out to London
Taylor twin. Go get him PJ. Go get him
You ran away.
You dick brain.
PJ. I'll upload it in the next [ __ ] 3
hours. Come back. I will upload it where
you ran away. PJ, if I killed you and
you left the gates of heaven, you still
say I've done nothing. You'll do a
Winchester and raise from the dead. No,
it's pointless that you're such a
[ __ ] spaz that you're such in denial.
It's untrue. PJ LT went around today and
put a stone through your window. You
still say PJ. You would still say LT is
a [ __ ] You will still say LT. Why did
your m phone?
No, no, no. So, why did mommy phone the
police when Okay, let's answer the question, Mr.
Why did your mommy phone the police
and she did? PJ
said, "Your mommy's going to phone the
police and we know it. Mommy's going to
phone the police."
Mommy's going to [ __ ] dude.
I'm not going to let him on anymore now.
Yeah, cuz he's giving me a headache,
bro. Yeah. Like I said, this star this
kind of attention until Wednesday and
that's it. That sounds like a plan,
isn't it, Greedy?
Because the excuse is going to be
exciting on Wednesday. I'm going to go
back on the channel on Wednesday and see
what the excuse is. Yeah.
Yeah. Let's see what the excuse is on
Wednesday then. Yeah.
Let's see what the excuse is on Wednesday.
That's only a couple of days away. Yeah,
let's wait. Let's wait until Wednesday. Grezy.
Yeah, I'll just wait until Wednesday.
Yeah, he can be on his way, bro. No one cares.
Uh, well, I'm not going to be knocking Timmy out.
That's not going to happen.
Well, that's never going to happen
because Timmy's never going anywhere. So
that's it. Uh you do realize I ordered a
taxi for him on um what day was it?
Can't even remember the day. A couple of
days ago. And he didn't get in the taxi.
He said if I ordered him a taxi, he
would get in the taxi. He never got in
the taxi. And he's still coming on
YouTube act like he's hard as [ __ ] when
he's a [ __ ]
When he's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
No. Why would I mention Cole? That was
just a copycat trend.
We're over that now, bro.
No, we don't need to mention it anymore,
bro. People used to say it to fit in
with the crowd,
bro. You will see what will happen. It's
simple as that.
You will. I already told you what will happen. Simple.
Yeah. Anyways, we'll wait until
Wednesday and see what the next excuse is.
And then I am literally done with this little sector.
My my Instagram should be unbanned by then. So
yeah, he and he still makes excuses.
This is what I'm saying. He still makes
excuses. So it's pointless with Timmy.
He's a spaz.
He's a spaz, bro. He's never going to meet anyone.
No, I did. I did used to mention
cheerful co by stick. No, no, I did all
the time. No, I have done, bro.
Um, yeah, because Non Legs used to say
she was good-looking to fit in.
Yeah, he used to say that I was gay cuz
I don't find her attractive cuz I don't
follow trends. I don't follow the crowd.
No, I did. I used to say it all the
time. I'm surprised you didn't hear it
kind of recently, too.
You just didn't want to feel left out in
it. Oh, [ __ ] Cuz he was getting
bullied and [ __ ] He was getting
bullied, so he used to just talk about
her. trying to look good for people.
That's where Miles McCoy comes into it. Rezy. Miles McCoy.
You're not [ __ ] scaring. No, brother. No, [ __ ]
Did you like that, Grezy?
Yeah, that's nice, bro. But no one cares. Bro,
you know the problem I've got with Timmy
yet is he tries to draw me out every
single time the attention is on him.
That's what I That's, you know.
Oh, yeah. Well, obviously. Yeah. No, my
issue with Timmy is he tries to draw
people out when the attention is on him.
And it's the way he does it. And it's
the way he does it as well.
Yeah. Oh, yeah. I used to mention Yeah,
cuz Nonlegs used to say she was
good-looking to fit in with the crowd.
He didn't want to feel left out in it. Poor [ __ ]
No, I just don't like the way Timmy was
trying to um draw me out.
on his gambling vlog as well.
But yeah, if Timmy comes and he not like
he said, I'm just going to rob him. I'm
gonna take his phone. I'm going to do
like real real bad like damage that
ain't even violence.
You know what I'm saying? I don't care,
bro. I really don't give a [ __ ] Simple.
Yeah. [ __ ] him in it.
Yeah, he can be on his way. I don't give a [ __ ]
He can be on his way. I don't really
care, bro. I honestly don't give a [ __ ]
Same thing with Timmy ain't going
anywhere, bro. Timmy ain't going nowhere.
I'll do worse than that, bro. I'll do
worse than that to this Timmy. Watch.
>> Right, Peter. What I said about
absolutely spot on. You are a gambling
skint virgin lowife mess who lives in your
But I don't PJ bills PJ pay bills. PJ
bills. You have to ask mommy for a
because you are not independent. Oh, mother.
There's no point. You can't win with
him, bro. You can't win with this
[ __ ] Just let him come on Wednesday
like he said he was going to do. Simple as that.
Yeah. Just let him just let him just let
him come on Wednesday like he said he
was going to do.
Just let him come on Wednesday like he
said he was going to do it. Yeah. I'm
not going to let him in now until until
uh Wednesday. Yeah. Is that all right, Grezy?
Is that right, Grezy? Is that okay with you, boss?
Is that okay with you, [ __ ] Huh, bro?
Yeah, just wait until Wednesday, ain't it?
Just wait until Wednesday, bro.
But I'm about to be done with this
autistic community, bro. It gives me
[ __ ] brain damage.
It actually Oh, my brain, bro.
My [ __ ] brain hurts, bro. It's such a
disabled community. Does it happen to
you as well, Fire Stick? When you're on
it, yeah, it gives you brain damage
or like, you know what I mean? Like,
you get what I mean, bro?
My [ __ ] head, bro.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
No, seriously, bro.
Do you know what's so weird about this
this this community, Stephen? How is
that you don't even know these people?
We don't even know these people. Like
you're actually arguing with people that
you don't even know.
It's mad when you actually think about
it. Like all jokes aside, if you
actually think about it, it's actually
weird, isn't it?
Do you not think it's really really weird?
Now imagine you told anyone outside this
community that you are
that you um you know yeah
fake leaving. Well, yeah. Obviously,
he's always here.
Obviously, he's always here.
Yeah, there is. Uh, Nlex's girlfriend is
a [ __ ] and Tiger's a [ __ ]
Oh, [ __ ] One sec. Yep. Yeah.
Yeah. Hey, there's two midgets. There's
two midgets that I know of, lad.
There's two midgets that I know of.
Don't know about you.
this little sector.
This little That's why I've unsubed from
Timmy now. I've unsubed from Timmy. Um, and
yeah, I'm going to go back on it
Wednesday. I think after Wednesday, I'm
going to be done with this shitty place,
bro. So, Steven Albert, you got my
email. We got Grezy Fire Stick. You need
to email me, lad, cuz I'm just going to
start a whole new channel. We need
Kieran as well, though.
Steven, Greavesy, Firest Stick. Um,
we need Kieran.
We need Ben whenever the [ __ ] he comes
back on, we just going to start our own community, bro.
Cuz you know the thing is with people
like Yeah. The thing is like with people
like this [ __ ] Ed Matthews and all of
these people, they get trolled. Yeah.
But most of it is not trolling. This
most of this comm majority of this is is
is trolling. Like it's negativity. Most
of it is. You understand? Like it's not
like the odd troll that it's it's
constant with these people.
And Triple H. Oh, yeah. As well. Triple
H, bro. If this Timmy doesn't um come on
Wednesday, then I'm done, bro. Simple as that. So,
cuz we only talk to a good couple of
people. We can we only talk to a good
couple of people, bro.
So, we might as well get the good people
from the community, drag it to another
and yeah, you might get an odd hater.
You're going to get that. But this is
ridiculous, bro. This is actually ridiculous.
And we're just going to talk about like
football bets and normal stuff cuz this
isn't normal, bro. This honestly is not
normal, bro. How can No, I'll just give
you my email. Everyone's got my email, bro.
But obviously or if you got like
Snapchat or I don't know, bro. We'll
find a way.
Yeah, he makes money. Yeah, at least he
makes money. Yeah, he makes money. And
most of it is not negative. Most of this
is negative. It's weird. A lot of the
people there were jealous. It's just
weird, bro. That's Yeah, exactly. But
it's what you're saying is true. Even if
you made money from this, even if you
made like400 a month, bro, then fair
enough. you know, £100 a week, you're
going to [ __ ] go on here and deal
with this [ __ ] Yeah. Like they say time
is money and you don't get no money from
being on here. And it's just [ __ ]
And it's [ __ ] It's not normal
people. This is what I'm saying, bro.
We'll start We'll start our own little sector.
How about that one?
No legs, no Red Star, no LT, no Timmy,
maybe unworthy clock. Yeah, Unworthy
Clock's cool, but what if he gives it to Timmy, bro?
He could possibly give it to Timmy, bro.
That's the thing. I don't think so. I've
met Unworthy Clock. I don't think he would. Yeah.
This is so weird, bro. It's not even
It's not even like you go live. Yeah.
and people are talking about football
bets or people are talking about their
day or they're just trying to meet up
with people they they don't even know.
Have you ever like stopped to think how
like [ __ ] it actually is?
We got Timmy a [ __ ] thinking he's the
big man on YouTube constantly calling
people out when he's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
I can understand if it was some musly
guy. I can understand if it was some big
hard man. Yeah. or some gangster coming
on here doing this. Yeah.
Yeah. But to be fair, you know, Charlie,
he's actually a cool guy. He doesn't
[ __ ] stir. He doesn't Charlie's actually
a cool guy, you know.
And to be fair, Tiger was. I never ever
had a problem with Tiger. And this is
how I know. Yeah. You know, when Timmy
came with Tiger,
uh Timmy was [ __ ] stirring it.
Timmy was [ __ ] stirring it because I've
never had a problem with Tiger.
Obviously, he's a bit weird and stuff,
but I mean, as far as like trolling and
[ __ ] stirring, he was never involved
with it. So, that's how you know that he
was just [ __ ] stoming cuz he never had
any problems with me ever. And that's
what Timmy does, bro. He will never
meet. He's a [ __ ] He needs to stop
acting hard on YouTube, bro.
He is embarrassing, bro. It's actually
embarrassing. It really, really, really
is. It seriously is embarrassing.
>> You know what I'm saying? It's like
[ __ ] John Cena topic. Seriously, bro.
That [ __ ] [ __ ] act big on YouTube.
[ __ ] off, man. Badness.
What a play. Remember that fire stick
with Chucky? Wanna play?
Do you remember that? Yeah. It's good, isn't it? Wanna play.
All listen, let's meet up. Let's meet up
tomorrow and go for a couple of drinks.
We'll do We'll do some football bets. Go
for a lovely little drink.
Have a little lovely laugh. A good old no that
I drinking for a long time.
I bet you I can make you laugh. Yeah,
I bet you I can make you laugh, right?
I bet I made you all laugh. >> Yeah,
I make you laugh. You see
Oh yeah, man. It was so dead yesterday.
These pubs around Romford. Not a soul in
them by a stick. Not a single soul.
Not a single soul in them,
Dusty. Not a single soul in any of them places.
Not a single soul. Oh,
you're very very sad, bro. You're very
very very you you know you got you got
too much time on your hands. You know this.
I don't know. Well, there's Weather
Spoons and it's like£3 pound something a pint.
It's actually£3 something a pint.
It's actually £3 something a pint in one
place and it's £5 in the other. Yeah.
So you're it's going to take So you're
going to drive over an hour.
Yo, you Bro, you really don't have
family, bro. It's so obvious you don't
have family if you've got all this time
in the world. Yeah, I told you what I
said. I told you I told you exactly what
I said and I mean it. It's exactly that.
It is exactly that.
>> You got Bro, I'm I don't think you have
family, bro. I really really don't.
No, I seriously seriously don't think you do.
Yeah, I don't think you do. There's no
way. There is literally no way. You got
too much time on your hands. There's no way.
No, no, no. You really, really don't,
man. You don't
guilt tripping you. I'm not guilt
tripping you. If you do what you said,
you're going to see what happens.
You will you will No, you could do what
you want. I'm just I'm telling you what
will happen if you do it. I'm not
[ __ ] scared of you. I just think it's
weird. People are allowed to not be
scared of you and think you're [ __ ]
weird, bro. You are weird. Same thing as
Timmy is weird.
Yeah, I will back up my talk. 100% I
will back up my talk. 100% I will back
up my [ __ ] talk. 1 million%.
Yeah, I will back up my talk.
I think you, bro, to be honest with you,
I think you're bisexual. I think you
really, really are.
You asked why I wasn't there because I
do not live. Yeah, it doesn't matter if
you live in London or not, to be honest with you.
Yeah, it doesn't matter if you live in
London or not. You shouldn't be getting
other people to fight your battles
whether you live in London or not.
That's even worse than doing nothing in
my opinion. Getting other people to
fight your battles is worse. That is 100% worse.
Yeah, that's worse than that. That's
even worse than doing nothing in my
opinion. So, yeah.
I think you're I think you're bisexual,
bro. I'm not even joking. I think you're actually by
Okay, bro. You You think that ain't it?
You think that?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You think that, bro?
You think that? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Whatever.
>> Yeah. I done nothing years ago. Yeah. I
done nothing when I wasn't living in the
house. That's why I said I beg you to do
it again. That's what I'm saying. I beg
you to do it again. You smashed an old
woman's house when I was at the police
station. Bro, stop flexing. Stop
flexing. You would never do that now.
You could never do that now. You're not
even going to knock on the door now, let
alone smash a window. So at the end of
the day, So at the end of the day, bro,
like you do it again and you will see
what he will do nothing as an update. So
it's as simple as that.
You're just a sad, gay, jealous bastard.
Just like the rest of them.
Just like the rest of them. You're just
a sad, gay, jealous bastard. I'm giving
it until Wednesday and I'm off this
sector, bro. I'm off this sector Wednesday anyways.
Yeah. Play the victim. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Of course. Of
course. Of course. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay, bro. Just do what you said you're
going to do. Yeah. And stop talking.
I'm off this sector anyways on
Wednesday. Um I'm going to do a video
beforehand and try to get people off of
it cuz this is really gay. It's very [ __ ]
And that's it. Yeah, that's it, bro. So,
yeah, do what you got to do anyways,
like you said, big man. And Timmy's
coming on Wednesday as well, so he said.
So, we'll see, bro. We'll see. I'm
leaving this place on Wednesday anyways.
So, that's it.
Yeah, it's as simple as that. It is as
simple as that. Yeah.
You weirdos need to know when to give it
a rest, bro. Like, you really really really do.
And it's obvious you're jealous of
something. You're obviously jealous of
something. You are. No, you generally
generally are. Like we can we can we can
get to the bottom of this right before I
[ __ ] off on Wednesday. You are clearly
jealous of something. For you to do this
every day. You've got to be jealous of
something. You've got to be. You
literally have got to be.
Yeah. You have got to be, bro. You
really, really have got to be jealous of something.
Yeah, you have to be. You have to be
jealous of something in life. It's too obvious, bro.
Yeah, I will. I will. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
You know, I might just stand outside the
front door to be honest with you. I
might just completely stand outside the
front door. To be fair, that's what I'm
I think I'm just going to stand outside
the front door. I'm not even going to
give you the chance to even knock.
Yeah. And if you come anywhere near my
personal space, you're going to see
exactly what's going to happen to you.
That's what I'm going to do. You know
what? I might do that, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Cuz this guy likes to try
and say that people are going to play
victim and all of this [ __ ] Do you
know what? I'm going to do one even
better, bro. I'm going to do one even
better. Yeah, that's what I'm going to do.
Yeah, I'm going to do one even better to
be honest. So, you have no So, you have
no excuses then? No excuses whatsoever.
How about that one?
Yeah. It's as simple as that.
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. All cuz you're
jealous of someone as well. This all
comes from jealousy with you people as
well. This all comes from complete and
utter jealousy. Like we have seen what
Timmy looks like. We have seen what a
lot of these people on this community
[ __ ] look like. You do it cuz you're
jealous. This is also the disabledness
about this community as well. You're
jealous of anyone that's better looking
than you. You're jealous of anyone
that's got more family than you. Like
you are. You know you are. That's why
you can't that's why you can't say
nothing because you know I'm right, bro.
This the only thing that would explain
why men that claim they're heterosexual
can do this every day for years. It's
got to be jealousy.
Like pretend I'm your therapist, bro.
Like, pretend that I'm actually your
therapist. You are jealous. You clearly
are jealous of something. Come on. You
can't pull the wool over my eyes, lad.
Come on. You can't. You really, really
can't. Come on.
You are, bro.
So, we got Wednesday as well. So that's
it, bro. It's It's not a problem. Yeah.
And that's it.
You do it cuz you're jealous of
something in life, bro. Like, it's
obvious. It's It's clear as day. It's
Could be as simple as like
circumstances, you know, someone living
with their mom. They have more money
than you. They're better looking than
you. They go out unlike you. They've got
a life. It could just be so many
different things. It's just a bit of everything.
And you know it as well. You know it as
well, bro. You know it is.
You know, especially Timmy. You know it is, lad.
Yeah. You know it is as well. Especially
with Timmy, bro. Especially with Timmy.
You know it is. Yeah.
And you know it is as well.
You [ __ ] know it is as well, lad. You
know it is. Yeah.
You know it is, bro.
It's [ __ ] It's utter [ __ ]
And after today, I'll be back on Wednesday.
Um, and see what the excuse is cuz I'm
going to need to have a brain rest until Wednesday.
And I'll be back um in the morning and
see what the excuses.
And we'll see what the excuses are.
Yeah. We'll see what the excuses are on
Wednesday after the brain west rest.
Yeah. We'll see what the excuses are. H
You know what I mean?
Simple as that, bro. It is as simple as that.
But no, I'm not I'm not saying I'm
stronger. There's a lot of people that
I'm not stronger than.
There's a lot of bouncers I've I've I've
tried it with and they're um they're
stronger than me, but I knew I would win
in the end.
I knew in the end I'd win. Trust me, I
knew in the end I'd win. There's a lot
of people that are stronger than me, bro.
But, you know, if you hit if you hit
someone in the right place, I'd expect
them not to get up
to get me, bro. I'd expect them just to
not get up.
And even if they did, I would never like
depends on the situation. Like, if I got
beat like fair and square and that and
it was a good fight, then yeah,
obviously I'm not one to like But you
know what I mean, bro.
And you know you've got an abnormal
temper. If you can lose 20 pound
gambling and be like that, you know
you've got a temper. It's as simple as that. Yeah.
Yeah. It's as simple as that, bro.
Got a problem with people messaging him.
No. So he's talking his name, but then
he's going to get involved anyways.
He would literally get involved anyways.
So why does why does it matter if
someone mentions your name? Because
you're going to get involved anyways.
You always do. You're always watching.
So when you go live, you always know
there's people watching. You feel the
vibe of people that's always watching.
Red Star L, you just know there's
certain people that are always watching,
just waiting to get involved, picking their moment.
You just know there's always people
watching. You just know there's always
people watching. people people that
aren't watch people that have left this
sector don't watch or people don't find
them like Ant-Man, like Big Henry, like
[ __ ] um you know Jake the Snake and
probably even Seaside Mark probably
doesn't even watch but people you know
people are always watching you know
that. So they're waiting to pick their
moment to pounce and get involved again
and you know it, bro. You know it.
You know what I'm saying? You know it as well.
This is [ __ ] bro. This is so
[ __ ] All of it. You know,
why don't you start doing some gambling
videos or start doing some content or something?
Go live and talk about something if you
want to change the community up, you
know? Um, why are you why is disbastic
Timmy trying to meet people when he is
not a hard man and he will never be a
hard man? He can't even like he could
punch you a million times and it
wouldn't even bruise you, bro.
Why is a [ __ ] acting the hard man on the internet?
I just don't understand why a [ __ ]
like him is trying to act big on YouTube.
Why? I don't He's never won a fight
ever. He's never beat anyone ever. He's
never took any W's ever.
Do you think everyone should just start ignoring Timmy? ignoring him?
ignoring him now?
Like after Wednesday? Well, after
Wednesday. Give him a chance, you know.
Do you do you think that Do you think
that everyone should just start ignoring him?
Do you think that everyone should start ignoring him?
Yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay, bro. Well, listen. Listen, LT.
I've said the same thing to Timmy. Hold
on one second. One second. One second.
Listen. Yeah. You're saying that I'm I'm
going for weaker people. Yeah. Then you
talk about nons even though you wanted
to beat him up yourself. But anyways,
you're saying that people are going for
weaker targets, bro. I said the same
thing to Timmy.
Even if Timmy went up the road, I'm not
meeting him. I'm not doing anything
until he does the same thing as what
you've done. So that you no bias list,
same rules and that's it. And that is literally it.
You you want to get involved. You're
saying that you're going to come on
people's doors. No one's asking you to
come on people's doors. You want to do
that. And I'm stating the fact that if
you do that, what is going to happen?
So, it's as simple as that. And it's the
same to Timmy. It's the same thing to
Timmy. When you're watching on
Wednesday, right? Watch. Listen. Listen.
It's the same thing with Timmy. If you
watch on Wednesday, even if he comes
outside, even if he goes outside the
door, I'm not going to do anything.
Doesn't matter what he says, what he
does. Unless he knocks or damages
anything, then I'll be coming out and
that's it. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. No one cares, bro. No one
cares. No one cares. I don't care. I
literally don't give a [ __ ] All of this
is gay, bro. All of this is bully boy
tactics. That doesn't bother no one.
This is 2026. It's bully boy tactic. You
need to get a life. You honestly do need
to get a life in 2026. I don't really
give a [ __ ] who turns up. I don't care.
I simply don't give a [ __ ] You're not
going to stop me going about my day.
Empty threats are not going to stop me
going about my day, bro. So, I really
don't give a [ __ ] Simple as that. You
need to get you need to get a life. And
if you're actually off this community,
bro, actually be off this community.
Yeah. When you're off when you say
you're off it. Yeah. Get off of it. Cuz
I'm not meeting anyone. I don't want to
meet anyone of this community. Kimmy any
I don't want to meet no one on this
community. Yeah. Well then he can make
my mom scream again then can't he? He
can make my mom scream again then can't
he? Simple as that.
Yeah. Simple as that then. Yeah. Well if
he's such a big man. He can make my mom
scream again then can't when I in my
presence. In my presence when I'm not at
the police station. When I'm at home.
Yeah. He can do something in my presence
then can't he? And see how far he gets.
Yeah. Go tell your boy that. Yeah. Yeah.
You go tell your boy that. Reinstate it
and see what happens. Yeah,
man. No one's going to bully me into
staying at home. Are you mad? I'm I'm
going out soon, bro. Going to bully me
into staying in my own house. Are you
mad? Are you [ __ ] mad, bro?
Please, bro. Please. Please.
And another thing is, and the reason to
answer your question, Dr. Eko, is
because I don't want to meet any of
these people. I don't want to meet
Timmy. I don't want to meet anyone. I
don't want to meet anyone. But I'm
saying if they do do this, they're
finished. Simple as that. That's the
best way. These people in this community
are not worth meeting. These jealous,
ugly people wasting your money. I don't
care who they are. Timmy. Timmy. I don't
care who the [ __ ] they are. What color
they are. I'm not meeting no one. It's
as simple as that. I'm not meeting no
one. Simple. Unless they actually come
and do what they said they're going to
do. Right. Then that's it.
Don't go shop. I'll go where I want when
I [ __ ] want. You don't [ __ ] tell
me what a [ __ ] cannon cop [ __ ] do.
I'll go where I want when I want. I will
go where I want when I [ __ ] want.
Yeah. No one bullies me, brother. You
[ __ ] mad. Not one person does. One
person does. Not one person ever will as well.
Yeah. And that's a fact. That is a fact,
bro. Not one person ever will, can, or
ever will. Yeah. It's as simple as that.
And that's it, bro.
No one [ __ ] intimidates me. Not one
person intimidates me.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I'm not
explaining this again. Anyways, I've
already told you whatever. Yeah, I've
already told you whatever. That's it. Yeah. Simple.
Simple. Anyways, I'll be back live in a
bit. Yeah. In about 20, 30 minutes, 40
minutes, I'm going to I'm going to come
back live in case you've got any more
excuses. Yeah. And we can do what you
both agreed to. I'll be back live in
about You're not anywhere near anyways.
So, I'll be back live in about 20 minutes. Yeah.
And we'll stick to the agreement cuz I'm
fed up with this. And I'm coming off of
here Wednesday as well. So, I'll be
back. Yeah. Yeah. I'm scared. I'll be
coming back in 20 minutes. Yeah. 30
minutes. Okay. Wait, bro. He's not even
here. I've got things to do. I've got I
I need to go and get some food. I'm
hungry, bro. What the [ __ ]
Yeah. 5:00 p.m. I'll be back live. Don't
you worry about it. Count me. I'm
coming. And this is what you people do
on this community. Please, LT, listen,
bro. Yeah. Please come on the door today
so I can end you once and for all.
Please. Please. I want to stop this big
man talk. Please just give me that
chance. Don't make excuses today. When I
come back, yeah, at 5:00 p.m., don't
make excuses. Please don't make excuses
cuz I'm coming back at 5 and I'm going
to the shop as well. So if you know
anyone Yeah. I'm going to the shop. So
I'm saying I'm going to the shop as
well. Yeah. So I'll be back at well4 two
maybe. So yeah. Yeah. You said that I
won't be going to the shop. I'm going to
the shop right now and I'm coming back
and I'm calling your bluff as well.
Yeah. In a