There you go. It's been proven wrong
once again to me. Yep.
Live with your hips hard.
That was delicious.
Well, it is delicious. I'm still eating
the [ __ ] up. Oh gosh.
I think I'll be falling asleep after
this fake beef. Yeah,
I just had to nip out to get some food.
Sorry about that, lads. Back now.
[ __ ] that hits different, bro. Today. Yeah.
out of 10
different chef or something. Yeah.
You want a bit you want a bit of a fire. >> Huh?
What about now?
You still waiting though it
>> how many mouths could you had before surrendering? >> No.
>> Nice man.
The tickle. You think it was weird? I
don't even cut the tickle. I just stop
it in my mouth. H.
>> Can you watch the next screen with me?
Eight. But more. Huh?
>> Okay. He has started it though. He's How
many years, Mom? Has this guy been
starting, bro? But seriously now, how
many years, Mom? Too many years, Mom?
He's been he's been starting and
starting and starting saying how he
scares you and stuff. Let him come. I've
said to him, if you come in the door
today, you'll see what happens to you.
Mr. S, because he keeps coming on my
[ __ ] You don't understand. He keeps
coming on my [ __ ] trying to be like
trying to be trying to be some sort of
bully boy. Do you get it?
I He's trying to tell to people how
they're not allowed to go to the shops.
Is this guy mad in his head? I swear he
thinks you're some disable I I swear he
thinks that people are some disabled
woman or something. It's got to be, bro.
It's got to be. And you can just tell
they're not about anything. When they're
trying to put fear into people like
that, you just know they're not about
it. Because who who who in their right
mind would be saying something like that, huh?
>> You're lucky I wasn't there that day,
mate. You're very lucky I wasn't there
that day. Huh? With the windows. You're
lucky, bro. You're very, very, very
lucky. Even if people might have ran in
the past or whatever, like, you know
what I mean?
It's weird. Like, do you know what's so
[ __ ] about this [ __ ] Yeah. You
don't even know these people. They don't
even know you, bro. And they're trying
to look good. Yeah. For a spasticated community.
It's so It's [ __ ] if you think about
it, is it?
How someone of that age Yeah. who claims
they've got this, claim they've got
that, is trying to act bad on on a
retardant community. What? How does that make sense?
>> It does not make no sense. at all.
[ __ ] is weird, man.
Very weird. They're weird, bro. They're
proper proper weird.
You try some of the curry, though.
You should try some of the curry. Do you?
I got two bottles, small bottles cuz I
want to cut down on the coing [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. Sometimes I buy two cans,
sometimes I buy two bottles. Yeah.
But it is proper. It is proper weirdo
[ __ ] though. Do you know? You see it
yourself though. Is it
>> And they do it because they're jealous.
They generally are jealous or something.
Mom, they are. Mom. Because for people
to sit online, right, every day from the
time they wake up to the time they go to
bed, bear in mind these people don't
know you. Yeah. They don't know you.
They might like to think they know you,
but they don't know you. They got They
have to be jealous of somebody, bro.
It's the only thing it can be.
Yeah. It's as simp as as simple as that.
It's as simple as that, bro. It really,
really is. All this trying to All this
bully boy tactic. This little bully boy
tactic. That's what it is with these
people. It's trying to act hard. I'll be
out there in a minute. Don't you worry.
I'm going to go out there in a minute,
man. About 10 minutes or so. I'm just
going to go out there. [ __ ] it. Yeah.
And I don't want him winging or crying
to the police what will happen. Yeah.
Simple as that. I'll be outside and if
he comes in my personal space, he's
going to see what will happen. Stop
trying to look a big man for YouTube.
You little wimp, you little s wimpy
[ __ ] Yeah. And it's as simple as that.
No, no, no. It's annoying. Every time
you go live, you got to deal with this
keyboard dangster for years and years
and years and years and years. Yeah.
Yeah. With these little with these
little keyboard warrior little tactics.
Am I lying, man? Am I lying? trying to
act big on YouTube. How many times have
you seen this, bro? How many times have
you seen this now? It's [ __ ] It's repetitive. Yeah,
it is though, man. It really is. You
know what I mean?
Trying to tell me how I can't go to the
shop. I'll go wherever I want, whenever
I want, however I want, in what fashion
I want. You get me? And this is always
going to be same with these jealous
people in this community. Do you not understand?
It's always going to be the same with
them. He's watching. He ain't got a
life. He ain't got a life. Yeah, he this
guy has not got no life. Trust me, he
has got no life. Not a life. He's
watching everything. Everything on
YouTube. Yeah, simple.
Tell him to do what he said he was going
to do. Ring bell, smash windows. You get
me. Let him see it, bro. Know. Let him
do it, Mom. Please let him do it.
Please. Huh? Simple.
Let this big man do it, bro. Let this
big man scare an old woman. Let's see
how bad he is. Let's see how brave he
is. Come on. Let's see how bad this
little keyboard warrior is. Come on.
Let's see how bad and brave he is.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Every
time with these people, I'm sick of it,
Mom. No, I am sick of their jealousy,
their stinking dirty jealousy every day.
You get me? You get what I'm saying?
I'm sick of them dirty, stinky jealousy
every day with this community.
Yeah. Simple as that.
It's as simple as that, bro. It actually
is as simple as that. Yeah.
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. That's what they
are. You're [ __ ] That's what you are. Yeah.
Knew what you said that I told Timmy was
going to do. Yeah. Same as what I was
going to I said to Timmy. Think you're
going to knock on my door and stand
there and see what happens. Think you're
No, I'm just going to [ __ ] it. Simple.
You're not going to do nothing, bro.
You're not going to do nothing. I advise
you to [ __ ] off cuz you're not going to
do nothing. You're a keyboard warrior.
Shut up. I advise you to stop acting
like the bad man cuz you're not a bad man.
Yeah, it's as simple as that. Don't
[ __ ] try and act the bully boy, bro.
Don't act like you're some bully boy.
You're not scaring no [ __ ] You're just
a jealous little non-legs lover. Little
jealous boy. That's all you are. You're
just like one of them. You're no
different. You're no different at all.
Yeah. You're not no different at all.
Yeah. Yeah. Simple as that. Yeah. It's
as simple as that.
And that's that. It's as simple as that.
Split it up. There's not going to be no
splitting up, bro. There's not going to
be no splitting up, you little weasel.
Yeah. Simple as that. There's not going
to be no splitting up. Who are you, bro?
Who do you really think you are? Huh?
H You're no one, bro. You're just a
bully boy on YouTube. Nothing more. Not
about anything. You don't pose no
threat. You do not pose no threat. It's
just bully boy tactics from a YouTube
keyboard warrior. That's all it is.
That's all it is. It's nothing more.
Just a bully boy tactic. Just a facade.
That's all it is.
That is literally all it is.
Nothing more. No posing threats, no nothing. Yeah.
That's it. Just bully boys actually to
try and look the bad man bad on YouTube.
Constantly trying to look good on
YouTube. It's embarrassing, bro. I swear
now. It is embarrassing. It really is.
Trying to look good for women on
YouTube. It's so embarrassing, bro.
It actually is so embarrassing.
It actually is. It actually is.
It actually is. Shouldn't you be
defending nonsense and crying when I
call him a virgin? But you've got better
things to do, bro.
You've got better things to be doing.
Surely, you have got better things to be doing.
Having a hustler of fuss when I call
someone a virgin with a disabled
girlfriend. There's so much more you
could be doing.
You know what I mean?
It's as simple as that. Trying to look
good for YouTube in 2026. Yeah.
You're not about it. It's bully boy
[ __ ] How many times have you done this?
This is school boy [ __ ] This is Bro,
this is school boy [ __ ] This is what
people do in year 10. It is, bro. This
is what people do in year 10. That is
This is literally what people do in year
10. I'm telling you, bro. That's what
they do in year 10. Try to look good on YouTube.
They try to look good for irrelevant.
That's what people do in year 10, bro.
Have you ever heard that saying, Booty
Boy? Yeah. It's the truth.
It is. It is the It's the truth though.
It is the truth though, isn't it? It is
the truth though. You're a little fanny bug. Yeah.