This is [ __ ] tragic, bro. This is the
same [ __ ] over and over and over again.
Yeah, I've just got on his channel. This
is [ __ ] funny, bro. About you're
going to be doing some criminal damage.
You're not going to be doing no criminal
damage. Shut up, man. Stop trying to
look bad on YouTube. Yeah.
Stop trying to look bad on YouTube about
you're going to be doing some criminal
damage. That's fine. I'll be up all
night anyways waiting, bro. I'll be up
all night waiting. That's all good.
Anyways, about you're going to be doing
some criminal damage. Ring the doorbell
now and I'll break your face and we'll
get it cracking. Come on, big man. Come
on, big man. Come on then.
Come on then, big man. Come on. Come on.
Let's see your body outside that door.
Come on, big man. [ __ ] this [ __ ] [ __ ]
this. Let's get it cracking now. Let's
Let's do some damage to your face. Come
on. Come on then. Let's get it cracking
right here, right now. Because we know
we all know that you're you're here. We
all know that you haven't just come
back. Let's get it cracking. Come on
about you're going to do some criminal damage.
You're going to do some criminal damage.
Oh, you [ __ ] bro. Let's get it cracking
now. That's what we need to do. Let's
get the ball cracking now, bro. About
you're going to do some criminal damage.
Come on. Chop chop. Big man, ring the
doorbell. Like you said, big man.
Stalker, bisexual. Come on. Come on.
Come on then. What are you waiting for?
What are you waiting for? You're still
here. Come on. Simple. Let's get it all
cracky dory. Come on. Come on, big man.
Come on. Come on, big man. Come on, big
Come on, big man. Come on. Come on.
You're going to do this. You're going to
do that. Let's get it cracking. Come on,
big man. We're giving you the chance.
Come on. Come on. You said you're going
to do this. You're going to do that.
You're going to start smashing people's
property. I've just shouted out the
window. Come on, then. Come on, bad man.
Come on, big man. Let's get it cracking.
Come on. What are you waiting for?
Come on, bro. What are you waiting for?
We all know you're still there. So, come
on, big man. The big man on YouTube, the
scary LT. Come on. Come on then. What
are you waiting for? Come on.
What are you waiting for? Now you can't.
I've gave you the same opportunity as I
gave Timmy. Yeah, I gave you the same
opportunity as I gave Timmy. So now you
can't say now you can't say people are
going for a weaker target. We already
established the rules and then you start
changing it. Yeah. Simple.
Come on. Come on. Come on. And do you
know what he's going to do? He's going
to change the rules. He's going to
change the rules. Yeah. He's going to
change the rules and then he's going to
try and do some criminal damage. He
always does this. This coward with no
life. I'm telling you. Come now then.
You know what the rules are? The same
rules are for Timmy. Come on. Come on.
Come on then. What are you waiting for?
You like bothering people every day on
YouTube. So, come on. Simple. Come on then. Simple.
Yeah. Don't start crying about, oh, you
go for weaker. We'll knock at the
doorbell and we'll see about weaker.
Come on. We'll see about weaker. Come
on. I'm here. I'm standing here. Come
Simple. What are you waiting for? Come on.
Yeah. I've just shouted through the
[ __ ] window. No one's there. Yeah.
Come on. Or just shut up. Or just shut
up. It's as simple as that. Or just shut
Yeah. But you're going to be doing some
criminal damage. You're going to be
doing some criminal damage. Yeah. Are
you big man? Let me tell you something.
I'll be up all night and I'll catch
anyone. I'll be up all night. Trust me.
Yeah. Trust me. Yeah. This is going to
stop today, bro. Yeah. You're so far up
my ass. You try to do these bully boy
tactics. Come on then. Come on then.
Simple as that. Come on then, big man.
You know what I'm saying? I'm sick of
this [ __ ] bro. No, no, no, no. I am. I
really, really, really, really, really,
really, really, really am. Then you
start trying to change the rules. Come
on. Make people cry. Make my mom cry.
Come on, my property. Come on, big man.
Let's do it in 2026. Come on, big man.
Let's do it in 2026. Come on. New
edition. Time for an update. Come on.
Come on then. And if you're not, then
just shut up and leave people alone on
YouTube, you idiot. Yeah, bro. He's not
outside. I've just looked outside and
he's not there, you [ __ ] idiot. Yeah,
same rules as I gave Timmy. It's the
same rules as I gave Timmy. Timmy got
exactly the same rules. Yeah, exactly
the same rules. Yeah, he's not outside.
I've just looked. Yeah, simple as that. Hm.
>> Come on, bro. Come on. Come on. Just let
me see that body on my premises. Let me
see that body on my mom's premises. Come
on. Come on. Come on, bro. Come on.
Let's just see my your body on my mom's
premises. Come on. Simple. Come on.
Come on then. Come on then.
Come on then. It's as simple as that.
And let me tell you something, girl. you
won't be doing no cowardly criminal
damage because let me tell you
something. There's cameras everywhere.
There's cameras everywhere. There's
people everywhere. Just so you can't do
your little cowardness. And I love that.
Just so you can't do your little
cowardness. Come on in the door. Let's
get it cracking. Come on, big man.
Come on. Come on, big man. Come on. Come
Come on. Let's get it cracking. What you
waiting for? But I do know. I don't like
glasses. [ __ ] all cameras and [ __ ]
We know that this will make sure you
can't do no cowardness.
>> And you won't get away from here
anyways. Trust me, you won't get away
from here. You're going to do some
criminal damage. Bro, knock the door and
I'll damage your face. Simple as that.
Come on. Knock on the door. Knock on the
door. You've met your mats now. Come on,
bro. Come on. You said that you make
people's moms cry. You do this. You do
that. You've met your psychotic match
now. Come on.
Yeah. You've met your psychotic match,
keyboard warrior. Come on.
Come on, bro. What you waiting for? Come on.
[ __ ] idiot, bro. And this is what I
mean with you people in this community
every time, bro. It's the same with you
every time. Yeah. Every single time.
It's the same with you people, bro. You understand?
Every time of you little weirdo jealous people. Yeah.
It's why it's not even worth coming on this [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying?
And trust me, don't think you're going
to be smashing people's windows later
and getting away with it.
Don't think you're going to be smashing
anyone's windows. Don't think you're
going to be smashing anyone windows and
getting away with it, bro. Trust me, if
you know what's good for you, you won't
even try it. Yeah. You won't even try
it. Yeah. Come knock on the doorbell
like you said. KNOCK ON THE DOORBELL
LIKE you said. Come on, big man. Come
on, big man. Knock on it like you said.
Come on. Knock on it like you said.
Knock on it like you said. Come on, big
man. Knock on it like you said.
Simple as that.
Shut the door.
No one's there, bro. That's what I'm
saying. They're not there. They're not
there. It's [ __ ] Yeah.
It's [ __ ] Just shut the door. Have
a sleep. He ain't coming. I've told him
to come on the door and what will
happen? He won't do it. He will not do
it. He will not do it. Shut the door. Go
on the couch. Trust me, love. When
you're here, none of these people are
going to be doing anything while I'm
here, mate. None of these people are
here. Trust me. Trust me. You are safe.
You are safe from the keyboard warriors
when I'm here. Yeah. The guy ain't even
outside. My mom just looked. Yeah.
Listen, you are safe. You are safe. When
these keyboard warriors are here, you
are safe. You are safe with me. You're
not by yourself. Yeah. You are safe.
You're safe. It's as simple as that.
Trust me. Trust me. He's not doing
nothing. He ain't doing anything, bro.
It's the same [ __ ] It's the same [ __ ]
with him. It's just bully boy tactics.
It's bully boy tactics. And listen, if
you are going to do some criminal damage
later, make sure you don't run. Make
sure you put on camera you don't run.
Yeah, we had a deal. We said what was
going to happen and that's it. Yeah,
there can be a car. I don't give a [ __ ]
See you later anyways, lad. Yeah.