There we go.
Uh, again and again and again. You know
what I find is so funny. Yeah.
One second. I let I let a couple of
people join. Right.
One second. I let a few people join. Yeah.
Do you know what I find so funny? What's up?
One second, bro.
One second. One sec. All
right. You know what I find so funny
right on this LT's channel. One second.
Let people let people join. Let more
people join. Yeah.
One second. I'm going to let more people
join, bro. I don't want to repeat the same thing.
You are pathetic. He didn't even do what
he said he was supposed to do. Lad, you
changed the rules as usual. Yeah, you
change the rules as usual. Anyways, I
don't give a [ __ ] about that. I want to
let more people join. Yeah, I want to
let more people join, bro. Yeah, one sec.
One second. Why didn't you go outside
when you That wasn't the deal. That
That wasn't the deal. Anyways, one
second. One second. [ __ ] all that. [ __ ]
all that. [ __ ] all that. [ __ ] all that.
[ __ ] all what he done, what he didn't
do. One second. Just wait. Wait. Wait.
Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
Do you know what I find strange? Why is
there so many people right? Bear with
me. Yeah. On this guy's channel. Listen,
listen, listen, listen. You've got
certain certain people on this guy's
channel telling him to do something that
they would never do themselves. The same
kind of people that will never say the
area that they live in, yet they can
come on YouTube for 4 years being
obsessed. I.e. i.e. Red Star, i.e. all
of these other people. How are they
going to come on here them them certain
obsessed people trying to get other
people to do something that they will
never do? That to me is funny, bro. That
to me, people like that is so funny to
you know. And they won't even say the
area, the fat little rejects.
Yeah, it's true, bro. Ain't it? It's true. Yeah.
Why are they Why are they trying to get
other people to do [ __ ] that they'll
never do? Can someone answer me that the
obsessed ones I'm talking about? Like
the the proper proper dedicated obsessed ones
telling people that they need to do this
that they need to do that when these
people will never even say what area
they live in.
[ __ ] little retards, bro.
Yeah, little retards.
Yeah, they're little retards. Why is
there people Hey, listen. Listen, LT.
One second. One second. One second. When
Red was commenting on your [ __ ] why
didn't you ask him to to do it when he
was telling you to come on the door? One
lesson. One one second. One second. One
second. One second. One second. Why
didn't you message him saying, "Oh, why
haven't you said where you are? Why
haven't you done anything?" That is the
first thing I would have been saying.
That is honestly the first thing I would
have been saying to two two of them
accounts. that Ess that Essex knots
account and that Red Star account. Why
are you replying to them like they
haven't tried getting you in trouble
multiple multiple multiple times?
That's another thing I don't understand.
They have tried to one second. Why
haven't you replied to them asking them
why haven't they done anything?
Cuz you know I'm right, bro. Yeah. You
know I'm right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You know I'm right. Yeah. You know it's
true, ain't it? Yeah.
These are all people on YouTube for four
or five years stalking that can't even
say where they live like the area or
telling other people. That is cheeky.
That is that is very very very very very cheeky.
No, that is cheeky, bro. That is [ __ ]
cheeky. Cuz you know what? Yeah. When
Monty and Timmy One second. Yeah,
brother. Don't let anyone call anyone
out, brother. Red Saw has never done
anything. All of these other cowards
will not even say where they live. Most
of these people won't even say where they live.
So that's it.
See, I never tried doing that. You know,
even with Monty and Timmy, I never [ __ ]
stirred. Ever. Ever ever ever ever tried
[ __ ] stirring. Even when they had beef.
Why are these people trying to [ __ ] stir
when they're more cowardly than anyone? What? Simple madness. Yeah.
Yeah. Well, I'm off here Wednesday
anyways. It's simple as that.
I'm off here Wednesday anyways. Simple
as that, lad.
Yeah. And then another thing another
thing as well, you don't you don't claim
to be about it. Well, when you're
stalking someone on YouTube every single
day acting like a big man, you kind of
are. People like Red Star. Well, you
kind of are. And if you're not about it,
then stop shiting. Then stop [ __ ]
throwing then. If you don't claim to be
No, no, no, no. We're not talking about
normal people. We're not talking about
normal people on here or anyone. We're
talking about people like we're we're
talking about specific people that have
been called out when they've called
other people cowards. Yeah.
It's as simple as that, bro. Like that
is mad. Yeah, you are a manta. You
little fat self-reflector. And you know
what? I'm going to do a video about this
community anyways. Do you know what? I'm
going to do a big big big video about
this community. And I've like and I've
lined up all the things I've got to say,
bro. Yeah. before I [ __ ] off. I'm gonna
wait until Wednesday anyways. We're
waiting for Timmy. Yeah. Yeah, we're waiting. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm going to line up all the [ __ ]
I got to say. And I'm put up all of the
video before I [ __ ] off. And I'm going
to give everyone my email as well. Yeah.
No, he didn't. No, he didn't stop me
leaving the house. I already went to I
already left the house earlier, lads.
No, he did not. I already left the house earlier.
Try again, lad. Try again. The coke is
full of the fridge is full of coke.
No, he [ __ ] did not. I left the house earlier.
Anyways, so okay, whatever.
Yeah. And this look and look at this
little s this guy as well. Oh, you can
only you can you can only what did he
say? He said you can only pick on people
that work. This is what I'm saying, bro.
You can't win with these people. Yeah, I
pick on men that work and I also picked
on them two guys with their girlfriends
that weren't at work. This is what I
mean. You people on here. Yeah, you're
actually so bitter. I'm going to I'm
going to save this for a video. No, I'm
I'm not going to talk about it now, bro.
I'll save it when I'm ready to talk about it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. No,
no, no, no, no. What was Red Star
telling you to do? Tell everybody what
Red Star was telling you to do. What was
Red Star telling you to do? Tell
everybody what he, the person that will
never ever tell anyone where he lives,
was telling you to do. Tell everybody.
Tell everybody what the obsessed gay man
on YouTube for three or four years that
will never say where he lives was
begging you to do. Tell him. Just tell everyone, bro.
Just tell everybody what he was telling
you to do.
>> Madness, bro. Madness. Yeah.
Yeah. Madness. Madness.
Absolute madness, lad.
Right. We'll see if um
this Timmy thing happens on Wednesday as well. Yeah.
Hiding with the lights off.
It doesn't matter, bro. You How do you
know that? How do you know? How do you
know that? I've traveled more of the
country. Have you ever trying to meet
these people? You don't know that? He's
never told me where he's lived. How is
some gay man on YouTube 24/7 who will
never meet anyone trying to tell you
what you should do? That is cheeky. If
anyone come on my channel and done that,
I would be like, "Why don't you do it
yourself, you obsessed little freak?"
That is literally what I would have done.
Yeah. No one cares.
And stop and stop with the L J thing.
Um, stop with the L J thing as well, LT.
He done absolutely nothing. Only in your
We're just going around in circles
again. It's the same [ __ ] with you
people. This is exactly why I'm getting
six, seven people off this community and
we and we're going on a new community.
Bro, you haven't ruined anyone's life.
You sad little bastard. You're a talker.
Begging LT to do this and that, but
you're a talker. You won't even talk on
panels. You won't tell anyone where you
live. You will not tell anyone where you
live and you're begging a man to knock
on someone's door. Get a grip, you
little loser. Right? If you put 1% of
that energy that you do stalking and
recording men that are better looking
than you, right, you would have actually
been able to do it yourself. Like you
would have actually done it yourself.
Yeah. Joe, if Yeah. Yeah. That's another
thing. You've got to meet LT now. That's
another thing, Joe.
One second. You've got to meet him now.
He done he done what he said he was
going to do. So now you've got to meet him. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You need to meet him now.
now, don't you? That's what the deal was. Yeah.
Well, apparently he did to you. Well,
according to you, he did. But you two
can meet each other now, can't you? Yeah.
No. No, he hasn't. But you think he has?
You're biging him up. Well, if he
hasn't, why are you biging him up then?
[ __ ] off, man.
[ __ ] off, man. You talk so much [ __ ]
Yeah, I I go for people at work. I also
go for two men with girlfriends that
weren't at work. Biased.
That's another thing with this. Hey,
don't worry, Steven Howard. Yeah, we're
bro. After Wednesday,
we're getting six people and we're
leaving this. We're leave. I'm deleting
the channel, bro. I'm deleting the channel.
I'm deleting the channel, bro. 100%. I'm
deleting this channel. I'm done.
And you know what I'm going to do? Yeah.
Listen, just so you don't feel left out,
LT. If this guy comes on Wednesday,
right, I'm going to wait until
Wednesday. I'm not running. If this guy
comes on Wednesday, right, I I will
travel to you. How about that one? I
will actually travel to you to stop this
going round and round and round in
circles again. Yeah. Cuz I know exactly
what you're going to do if Timmy comes
here. I know exactly what you was going
to do. And I know exactly what you're
going to do. If Timmy comes, if Timmy
comes on Wednesday. Yeah. I will travel
to you. Yeah. When you're when Well,
when you're back in London. How's that?
That's a good deal, is it? You don't
have to go anywhere. How about that?
That's a good deal. I think that's a
fair enough deal. Yeah. And if he
doesn't, then he doesn't in it. It's
simple as that. So, yeah, that's a good
deal. That's a That's a good deal.
I think that's a good deal to be fair. Yeah.
I'm going to get the scream mask. I'm
going to get the scream cape and I'm
going to start ringing your number. I'm
going to do it on YouTube as well, LT.
I'm going to start ringing your number
with the costume.
Trust me. Yeah. Yeah. I'll start ringing the number.
I will start I I will I will uh I will I
will start ringing you.
You know, with the voices. Yeah. That'll
be the start of it, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Whatever, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Whatever, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Whatever.
Bullies women and talk [ __ ] to bouncers
and other employees doing their job. H.
Also, two guys that have had girlfriends
who didn't even stand up. You people are
so full of excuses. Just like the virgin
thing, just like the women [ __ ] you are all biased.
That's what that's We've already
established that, bro. Like, let's just
leave that. You're giving me a headache. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, man. You really are.
You stick it on the man, they're at
work. Oh, you stick it on a man that's
not at work, they're laughing at you.
[ __ ] off, bro. You talk so much [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And also
what I'm going to do as well with you
people in this community. Yeah. I'm
going to talk about what you do on here
every day for years.
Yeah. Watch this video. It's going to be
a banger, bro. Trust me, it's going to
be a banger about what you people
actually what what you actually do on
here. Yeah. A video that can be uh a
video that can be remembered forever. Yeah.
I'm going to talk about the sh I've been
wanting to do this video since
yesterday, bro. The [ __ ] that it's the
[ __ ] that you people do on here. [ __ ]
how long you stay on here for
don't care about that, bro.
Look at what you what you actually
people what you people actually do on
here, lad. Put up a post about me.
That's good, man. Good for him.
Uh, one sec. It's actually what do you
know what it's what they actually do on
here is so weird. You know, I was just
actually saying this to my mom. Yeah.
You don't know. You don't know these people.
That's another thing. You don't know
these people. And And I I'll just save
it, bro. I'll just save it.
Yeah. Nobody cares about Longlegs. Go
suck his dick somewhere else. No one
cares. We're off this sector anyways.
Yeah, legs. The same one that made me
let me make posters about him and he
didn't do anything about it. Yeah. Yeah.
Good for him, bro. Give yourself a
little silver medal on top. And that's
what I mean. You'll never win with these
little pricks. But funny. Funny enough.
Yeah. It was Timmy that started it this
time. Oh, do you know it was Timmy that
started this this time? Yeah.
Yeah, it was Timmy that started it this
time. You know that?
It was Timmy that started it this time.
Yeah, it was Timmy that started it this
time, lad. Do you know that
if he if he comes on if he comes on on
Wednesday, right, I will go and meet a
London Taylor, bro. I will travel to
North London. 100%, bro. 100%. Because I
don't want him to feel left out. Yeah.
No, I will do it. I'll do it. I'll do
it. I'll do it. Yeah. And obviously if
he doesn't show up then I'm done
anyways. Simple as that. Cuz it's the
same [ __ ] with you people. Yeah. No. No.
It is. It is. It generally No, it is. It
generally is. Yeah.
It's the same [ __ ] with you people. Yeah.
I was a man, right, that ran to the
police because someone's put posters up
of them trying to call anyone a coward.
Do you see what I mean with these
people? You can't win.
You can't win. Come on, LT. Tell them, man.
Tell them. Tell them, LT. Tell them how
you're also biased as well. Tell Tell
them how you're biased as well.
Come on, man. Like, we should we should
have a discussion. Come on. We should
have a big discussion. Come on. Yeah.
That is cheeky, bro. The amount of
people that were [ __ ] throwing in the
comments, that is cheeky.
That is absolutely cheeky, bro. I would
go mad if that happened to me, bro. If I
was if I was if I was like if I was on
someone's door, Yeah. or outside
someone's door and somebody was egging
me on who's obsessed as Red Star, bro, I
would I would tell them to I would go mad.
I'd go mad. I'd be like, "Oh, one
second. You've been stalking this person
every day for years. Why haven't you
done anything? Why haven't you gave any
information about yourself so people can get you?"
[ __ ] hell. Yeah, I'm disabled, bro.
The only people that are disabled are
you people on this community. And that's
clear, lad. That's clear. Yeah.
That's like you people in this community
though, disabled, is it? Bit like you
people then, is it lad? So, we got
something in common.
Just like you little people in this
community then, is it on this little sector?
He didn't upset my mom. He didn't upset my mom,
you know. Yeah. But
yeah, pretty much. Mhm.
So, I've unsubed to him anyways. Um,
Timmy, but I'll go on the channel. But
I'll go back on the channel on Wednesday.
My own mom says I'm disabled. See you
later, lad. You get kicked for that.
You get kicked for that, lad.
Yeah, you get kicked for that, lad.
You get kicked for that, bro. Yep. Yeah.
No, he doesn't have respect for Laney
because he's the one that's actually
started it. No, no, no, no, no. Cuz he's
the one that's actually started it.
He is the one that's actually started
it. So, no, he hasn't.
And this is what it's always going to be
the same thing with you people.
It's always going to be the same thing
with you people.
It will always be the same thing with you people.
No, I didn't start it this time. No, I
didn't. Actually, you started it.
You started it. Timmy started it. And I
brought your name into it because I had
to bring your name into it cuz I know
exactly what was going to happen. You
actually started it this time.
So, and this is what's always going to
happen with these people on here,
Stephen Hard. That's always what's going
to happen. Timmy does his balls in. He
self swift. He self-reflects. These
weirdos self-reflect their skin life
onto you. You argue. LT gets involved.
It's always going to be the same old.
Honestly, it's always going to be the
same old on this disabled sector.
Yeah. It's always going to be the same
thing on here, lad.
It actually is always going to be the same thing.
It's always going to be the same thing.
No, Timmy started it.
It will always be the same thing on
here, bro. Always be the same thing. It
will always be the same with these
people in this community.
But no, actually LT started it. Timmy
did. It was Timmy first and then Yeah.
And I was thinking about what you people do.
actually do on here every day.
I'll save it for a video anyways, bro.
And I think I don't care how long you
are on here for or you know it's
actually what you people do on here. No,
it is, isn't it? It actually is what you
people do on here. So strange.
Very very strange what you people do on here. Yeah.
Yeah, the link's not working. So, yeah.
On there, bro.
You're all biased. You all [ __ ] talk.
It's the truth, isn't it?
Now, do you people think Yeah.