So yeah, that's that lad.
Yeah. No, I don't know what happened, bro. Um, yeah. So,
did you see on LT's channel Steven
Howard the amount of coward? Yeah. That
was trying to egg this dude on to do
something that they would never do.
These little cowards. Did you see it?
Obsessed little fat ugly old men that
don't even leave their house.
Like they were probably wanking off,
bro. Like they were actually pro They
were probably wanking off. Did you see
it? Did you see it, bro?
Always good to see Mauy people put put
in their place. You would never put You
would never put me in my place. You're a
little keyboard warrior who I've
discovered you right before Christmas,
right? I I discovered this account
before Christmas. Doesn't talk on the
panel. Doesn't show his face. I
discovered this. I've discover I covered, bro.
Malfy people, bro. I've put enough
mouthy people in their place, but Oh, it
doesn't count because they were at work.
Okay. And what about the men that I
stuck on in front of their women? Oh,
they just laughed at you. You're full of
excuses. When are you jealous people
going to get off of YouTube and get a life?
No. Honest question, bro. We should We
should ask this question.
No, no, no. We should ask this question,
bro. Come on.
Do you know what they do on here? Yeah.
Stephen Howard, I was thinking about
this. Yeah. When I come out the cinema
yesterday, the [ __ ] they do on it is so
disabled. Think about it. Yeah. These
people are older than me. Yeah. Let's
let's let's talk normal. Yeah. They're
older than me, right? this. So, they're
older than me, so they should know
better than me. Yeah. They're on YouTube
from the time they wake up to the time
they go to bed. Constantly talking about
other men that they don't know. Trying
to slag off other people that they don't
[ __ ] know, right? Trying to [ __ ]
slag off people, right? Trying to slag
off people that are better than them in
life. Bro, if they had a life, they
wouldn't be doing this.
They wouldn't be doing this, bro. If
they hadn't laughed these old wasters on
this little [ __ ] community, they
wouldn't be doing this, bro. 100%. I
thought about this when I come out the
cinema before all the LT thing.
It's the truth. Like, they come on here
every day talking about other men.
They're gay, bro. They're batty men. And
then they want to call other people
mters. If these people weren't such
munters, they'd actually be able to go
out and actually meet a woman and be
able to talk to a woman instead of
obsessing over [ __ ] men every day.
The [ __ ] mters themselves. [ __ ]
little muners. 5% of people in this
community show their face. Remember that
5% of people in this community show their face. Yep.
Yeah. Well, he didn't.
Yeah. Well, he didn't. And that's it. 5%
of the people in this community show
their faces. Why? Why? Why?
You get me, lad?
I never I wasn't forced to stay indoors.
I went out earlier, got my curry, got my
takeaway. No one forced me to stay
indoors. Not one little bit. I went out
earlier and got everything that I
needed. I wouldn't know, mate. I've
never been forced to stay indoors.
5% of the people in this community show
their faces because they are the real
life munters. That's why they're the
real life ugly people that don't fit into society.
They are [ __ ] but ugly. Right? I'm
telling you right now, all of the times
where I have had women and I've put and
I've put it on this community, these
people have been at nothing, bro. They
have been at nothing. Red Star, All
Night, all of these obsessed little gay weirdos. Yeah. Um, yeah.
And that's true, is it? Why is no one
backing themselves, bro? Cuz they know
I'm right. Look at Timmy, for example.
I've said this many times. I started
saying this the other day, bro. Yeah. I
started fully saying this the other day,
bro. Yeah. If
I look like a couple of people on this
community, I would kill myself.
If I looked like a couple of people on
this community, I would kill myself.
Timmy, Money, Mike, Tiger, LJ, I'd kill
myself, bro. And I'm not even lying. And
I'm not even joking, bro. So, think
about why they do what they do every day
on this [ __ ] shitty little community
along with the other people that are
probably even uglier, which is why they
don't show their faces. Pick them. They
want to pick big themselves up, bro.
You get me, bro? They want to big
themselves up when they are [ __ ] ugly
ass people. Ugly as [ __ ] bro.
I am out of all of the people that shown
their faces. I am
I am out of all the people that show
their that has shown their face on here, it's me.
Yeah. out of all of the people that
shown their faces. There's other people
that haven't shown their faces, but I
mean, they don't show their faces.
It's weird. Well, it's not weird because
there's a reason why they don't show
their faces cuz they're [ __ ] ugly.
And you're only And you're Yeah. I'm the
only one. I've already had a girlfriend.
Again, we've been over this multiple
times, lad. I've already had a
girlfriend. This is self projecting.
This is exactly what we're talking
about. You people don't have a
girlfriend. I have had a girlfriend. You
people don't. This is all part of
projecting again. Do you understand? Do
you understand the meaning of projecting? Yeah.
You understand the meaning of projecting?
That is literally what you're doing. You
people probably have never even had sex.
Half the people in this community. And
you're talking about a girlfriend. When
you start having sex, when you start
having sex, bro, then start telling
people that they ain't had a girlfriend.
Yeah. When you start getting sex, you
can start when you lose your virginity,
you can start telling people how they
don't have a girlfriend and and will and
will take you a bit seriously,
bro. Like again, you've lo you lose
every game. You lost the money game, you
lost the better looking game, you lost
the women game, you lost everything
game. you still come back and act like
you've won. Why are you doing this, bro? weirdo behavior?
But no, so seriously, bro, if I look
like some of these people in this
community, I would actually kill myself.
It's not even N. I would I generally
would if I was some of these people in
this community. Timmy, L J, Tiger,
Money, Mike, I'm I'd kill myself. I'd
actually kill myself, bro. It's not even a joke. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Literally,
yeah. Like I said, bro, when you people
start showing what you've got, money,
women, then come back to me. Yeah.
Yeah. Simple as that.
Then you start showing the [ __ ] that
you've got, then come back and criticize
me. Simple. But you can't
you can't prove the [ __ ] that you've
got. You talk about other people. Please, bro.
You know what I mean?
trying to tell people to go on the door
when you can't even say
where you live, the area that you live,
and you're trying to get people to knock
on people's doors.
Wow, bro. That is wild. That is very, very wild. Jeez. Anyways,
bro, let me ask you people a question on
this community. Yeah.
Do you think do you think um well the
normal people that are watching this do
you think Nando is a luxury? I me
personally call me call me stupid if you
want bro I think is a luxury you know I
don't know about anyone else and I'll
get on to why Gregy what do you think I
think Nando 100% is a luxury into in
today's standards I think so I think it
is cuz it's chicken is it and it's
expensive as [ __ ] What do you think? I
think it's I think I think it's a luxury. No.
You know what I think? You think I'm a
coward? That's nice, bro. You said that
behind the fake account and you didn't
show your face.
Yeah, that's nice, bro. Thank you. Thank
you for calling me a coward, lad.
Uh, basically it's a chicken shock.
Greavves and it's about450 for two
people for chicken
or £28 for yourself. Now to me I think that's luxury.
Yeah, I think I mean I think that's
luxury in this today's society, bro. For
chicken. I reckon it is. And the reason
I'm I'm I'm saying this is that there
were women out there that actually think
they're too good for Lando's.
Not even joking, bro. There's like
actual women that think they're too good
for Lando and they think that they
deserve better than a Nando.
[ __ ] What the [ __ ] bro? Nando is a
luxury, bro. Nando isn't cheap.
No matter how much money you have, I
don't think that's cheap for chicken.
There there's women out there that think
they're too good for Nandos Grezy. Mad.
There's actual single moms out there
that think that they're too good for Nandos.
Nandos, bro. Imagine that.
Imagine that, bro. Like, I can
understand if somebody had an
anniversary. Yeah. Because they was with
the person for a while and then they
tried taking them to Nando. Oh, you
could have put more effort into it. Say
it was someone's 5year anniversary, 10y year anniversary. You know
that is that is mad how people can think
they're too good for Nandos, bro.
Yeah, it was nice.
That's [ __ ] up, bro.
Yeah, that's [ __ ] up.
I'm going to put the link up. Hopefully,
it works this time.
I think I'm coming down with a flu.
No, I'm not funny. I'm being serious.
I'm being dead serious, bro.
People think they're too good for Nandos. [ __ ]
What the [ __ ] bro?
There's no point to this community, bro.
I don't see that. There's no point to
this community. No one even posts
gambling videos. It's just old men
talking [ __ ] about people that are
better than them.
From what I can see is mainly what is
this community is about.
What would you say Gre uh Steven Howard?
There's a lot of jealous ass people in
this community. Not everyone. Not
everyone. There's a lot of them though.
There's a lot of them.
Chipmunks. That was [ __ ] years ago,
bro. Yeah, he called the police.
Yeah, Chipmunks. Yeah, he called the police.
That was years ago. What the [ __ ] bro?
Yeah, he called the police.
I remember that.
That was years ago, lad.
I was just copying Ronnie.
No, all I said I think I said I was going to
You know what then? It begins with K.
They are slow backward bastards and the
more you engage with these people. I've
got a headache, bro. I'm sat here with a headache.
No, it wasn't nine years ago. Maybe
seven. No, six. It was six years ago.
I just said I'm going to K him.
That's what I said.
That's literally all I said, I think.
Yeah, you got the police involved.
He wanted me to go to prison as well. He
thought he was going to get me in
prison. He seemed to think that he was
better than he was because he was a streamer.
He seemed to think he was better than he
was because he was a streamer. He was
ready to get me in prison. and he was
ready for all of it, bro. If you watch
these uh Twitch streams, he was talking
about it. Uh
yeah, he was like he he put himself on a
pedestal because he was a Twitch streamer. Uh Chipmunks.
But I don't even know why I said that to
him. He didn't do anything to me. I just
said it, bro.
I just done it cuz Ronnie was doing it.
Yeah. Funny as [ __ ] bro.
Poor Laney. Lane. Lane.
I was saying to this I was saying to
this to Laney as well is that people
shouldn't even know where you live.
And I said to her multiple multiple
times, I said, "Oh, I'm not interested.
I'm not innocent. I'm not saying I'm
innocent." By the end of the day, people
shouldn't even know where you live
under the Privacy Act. No one should
even know where you live.
No one should even know where you
[ __ ] live. I'm not being funny.
Like seriously, no one should even know
where you live.
Like honestly, I know I'm not innocent.
I'm not acting like I'm innocent. I know
that. But I'm saying no one should even
know where you live to be fair.
Like they shouldn't even know where you live.
Like your address shouldn't be put out there publicly.
No, it isn't. No, that bit isn't my
fault. I never gave my mom's [ __ ]
address. That my that address shouldn't
be out there publicly. Even in them
nonstings. Yeah. Even in them nonsings,
right? Even in them nonsings when they
used to get them nons and they find out
where they live, they don't put their
address out there. No, I didn't do that.
No, I didn't do that. Trouble found out
where my mom lived. No, I didn't. No, I
[ __ ] did not.
No, I [ __ ] did not give my mom's
address. And even when they're when they
go to these people's addresses, their
address is not out there.
Yeah. No, it was Truman that put the
address out there. I didn't put the
address. So, realistically,
your address shouldn't even be out there publicly.
You know, to be honest with you,
your address shouldn't really be put out there, you know,
and that's it. I I reckon. Yeah.
Your address shouldn't even be out
there. Why is your address even out there?
Yeah, I do remember it.
The door getting glued. Yeah, I do.
Yeah. So, no one should even know where
my mom lives.
Yeah, they should even know that. Yeah. Nope.
No, I'm not bringing it all to my mom's
door because how do people know? Hold on
a minute. How do people know where my mom lives?
One second. Okay. Okay. Okay. How do
people know where my mom lives?
It doesn't matter if I'm here or not.
People should know where my mom lives.
And LT started it today. Anyways,
firstly, LT has started a lot of it.
Second of all, Secondly, they shouldn't
even know where my mom lives. No, I
didn't give the address out, you
[ __ ] I have never gave my mom's
address out, you [ __ ] Why would I
give my mom's address out? Use your
brain. No. No, I did not give my mom's
address out, you [ __ ] Who would give
that their address out where they're
staying? You clown.
No, I didn't. No, I [ __ ] did not.
So, why is this address even been put out there?
That's another thing. I don't know how
they got it.
Trouble got it. probably looked up the
name, went through the IP of the
broadband, so they shouldn't even know
where she lives to be honest.
They shouldn't shouldn't even know where
she lives to be fair.
Or if they did find out where or Okay.
Okay. Or if they did find out where
where she lived, they'd give it to one
person and if you was pissing them off,
they'd come. It shouldn't be public.
It shouldn't even be public.
People shouldn't know where other people are living.
You know what I'm saying? So, it's as
simple as that.
I never gave it. I never gave it. I
never gave the address.
I never gave the address. If I gave the
I never That address shouldn't even be public.
It's true though to be fair. So yeah.
Yeah. Simple as that.
Yeah. All of these people trying to egg
on this guy and they were all cowards.
That's all the people that was trying to
egg him on were cowards.
They're all cowards as well.
All of these people that was trying to
egg him on,
all of them were cowards as well. They
weren't even normal, impartial people.
They were all cowards. They were they
were like, "Yeah, this is it today. I'm
going to get my dick out. I'm going to
see Peter." Because they're so obsessed
with me. They've got a raging obsession
with me, right? They um they were
getting their dick out and think, "Oh
yeah, he's going to get smashed in
today." Yeah, it was never happening,
bro. They wished it was happening. They
wished They wished it was going to happen. Yeah.
I can't believe there's a single mom
that thinks she's still good. She's too
good for Nanos. [ __ ] That is
that is funny, bro.
It's full of old, ugly men that project
their life failures onto you.
Yeah, exactly, bro. And then they try to
talk about other people that are better than them.
I know, bro. I know. I know.
They sit on here every day obsessing
over other men. and they don't even
leave the house. It's a madness, isn't it?
It is strange, isn't it? It is strange.
They've been doing it for years as well.
These people have been doing it for
years. And you know, deep down a lot of
them are jealous. A lot of them are
jealous, bro. That's why they don't come
up on the panels and that.
A lot of these people on here were
jealous though, lol. Nons Red Star.
Um Jamie Thompson. There's another
[ __ ] as well. There's Oh, no. You
definitely definitely are jealous. You
definitely are jealous. For men to come
on the internet every day for years
stalking other men. Oh, you're
definitely definitely jealous. You
couldn't even pay me a million pound to
do that. No, you are definitely
definitely jealous. Cuz if you wasn't
jealous and you wasn't gay, you'd be
getting on with your own lives.
There's no getting out of it. So, you're
not jealous. Okay. Well, then you're
gay. So, which one is it? Are you
jealous or are you gay? Because or both.
You're either one or the other or you're both.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. You people,
listen to what I'm trying to say. Yeah.
You people come on the internet from the
time you wake up to the time you go to
bed stalking other men. Are you trying
to tell me that's normal?
Are you what? You know, are you really
No, no, no, no, no. It's not about No,
no, no, no, no. Listen, listen, listen,
listen. You don't come on here to annoy
people. You are your life is dedicated
to me. Do you not understand? There's a
big difference. Yeah. There's a big
difference between people coming on here
and trying to annoy people and what you
people do. You waste your whole life.
And it's jealousy. It is actually
jealousy. It has got to be jealousy. I
don't come on here annoying people. I
don't come on here stalking men because
I'm not a jealous ass bastard and I've
got a life. Do you understand? And you
know it is. And you know deep down it's
jealousy. To sit on here for four years
stalking a man you don't know. It's got
to be jealousy. It's got to be. It's got
to be, bro. There's nothing else it
could be, right? You you you know, you
wouldn't you should be out there with
your girlfriend, your life, all this
money that you people claim that you've
got. Uhhuh. No way. For someone to do
what they do for 4 years from the time
they wake up to the time they go to bed,
it's deep rooted jealousy. Even if
they're not aware of it, they might not
even know they are. But they are. But
they are though. But they are. What's my
life in the past 3 months? going out,
eating good food. Um, going out, eating
good food, going for drinks, went to a
couple of new places the past 3 months.
Had a good Christmas with family, which
you people was on YouTube on Christmas.
So, I mean, what was you people doing in
the in the past three months? Oh, one
sec. Let's say the last year. Yeah. What
was you people doing in the last year?
sat on YouTube calling people what you
are yourselves. Probably not leaving the
house. What were you people doing?
What you people do on here is so weird.
I don't know how you don't understand that.
what you people do on here is so weird.
It is so weird. And I don't even think
you understand it. I don't even think
you've got the brain capacity to
understand what you people do on here is weird.
It's weird. It's not even about how long
you're on it for actually. It's also how
weird you people actually are
on that LJ channel. It's full of freaks.
That's all it is on that channel. It's
full of self-projected little freaks
that ain't got no life.
I went out yesterday, went out the
today, went out the day before that just
don't have a life.
And that's it, bro.
Yeah, it's weird, bro. It's weird as
[ __ ] But your your brain is never going
to comprehend that
you're not jealous. You're not gay. Yet
you spend all day every day for 4 years
stalking a man that you don't know.
Yeah. Make that make sense.
Make it make sense.
That makes a lot of sense, isn't it? Yeah. Yeah. Not much.
I go out drinking. I go out to the
cinema. But okay. But what do you people
do? Okay. Okay. So, what do you people
do then? Tell us what you people do.
And like I said, I've done more than
four year in four years than you've
probably done in your whole life. A lot
of you people.
What do you people do then?
I'm going to make a tea in a minute.
Yeah, come on.
poverty eyed Joe
with the 200B phone
and then you call me a Mer in this
community. I'm better looking than all
of the people that try and call me a MT.
Even the people that show their faces.
Make it make sense, lad.
The same thing with LT, bro. I don't
really even give a [ __ ] if I won today,
lost today, he didn't turn up. I'm not
going to speak to him off here ever again.
Never ever again am I going to speak to
him off here. No way.
Trying to p me. Thank you. It's going to
end when you leave the community,
which is what I'm doing on Wednesday.
When this [ __ ] doesn't show up, I want
to hear his excuses for a laugh.
But I won't talk to him off here ever
again. I don't talk to biased people. Nah.
Yeah. Being called a M by people that
are actually ugly. I'm being called a m
by people that are actually too ugly to
ever get a woman. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm not speaking to LT off ever
again. [ __ ] that.
Yeah. Or or Yeah. It's simple.
Never again. I don't think I would. to be fair.
Yeah. Well, if it's speculate, like I
said, it's it's not until you show your
faces, I'm right. As simple as that.
Until you show you people are not the
muners, right? Then you are the muners.
Simple as that. If it's speculation,
prove me wrong. You can say it's
speculation all you like, but it isn't
speculation cuz you know I'm right.
That's why you people don't show your faces.
You don't show your faces cuz you're
[ __ ] ugly as [ __ ] And you know that
if you show your face, how are you going
to talk about anyone else?
Well, Timmy started it. Timmy started
the drama the other day. He started it
with his [ __ ] fat ugly mouth.
Bringing me into the his [ __ ]
Bringing me into his [ __ ] He's fat.
I'm leaving this community on Wednesday
anyways, bro. I'm deleting the channel
and everything. So that's it, bro. I'm
gone though. When I hear these when I
laugh at these excuses, I'm going to I'm leaving, bro.
Going to get as many people on this new
channel, normal people as possible. Then
I'm bouncing, lad.
Of course he's a real Mer. Look at him
and launch legs, bro. Why do you think
they do what they do? Just look at the
way they look. Just look at the way.
Okay, [ __ ] the people that don't show
their faces yet. Okay, say forget the
people that don't show their faces,
right? Look at Nons. Look at Timmy. Look
at Jamie Thompson. Look at these three
ugly bastards that try and talk about me. You know,
you know what I'm saying? Look at these
ugly bastards. You, bro, you'd kill
them. You'd kill yourself if you was
them. You would actually kill yourselves
if you was them.
Oh, he's just a little [ __ ] You'd
kill yourself if you was any of these people.
You'd kill yourselves. You would
actually kill yourselves.
I would, if I was Timmy, I'd kill myself.
If I was Timmy, bro, I would kill myself. Yeah,
if I was L J, I would kill myself.
These people, Could you imagine these
people go out? Could you imagine these
people going out approaching?
Could you imagine these people going out approaching? Never.
Yeah, that's not happening, lad. Well,
that's not going to be happening, is it? Yeah.
You're just all little weasels on this
community. Most of you,
you're just little weasels. That's what you are. Weasels.
It's a disabled community
cuz he's a spaz himself. That's why. Yeah,
I was going to put 500 pound on a double
both teams to score, but Joseph Fra
didn't let he wouldn't let me.
Yeah, I'm going to be meeting this
Christian Izzy very soon. So, I don't
need to be on here anyways. I'm not I
wouldn't be on here anyways even if I
wasn't speaking to someone. For [ __ ]
sake. Don't Let's not use that as an
excuse. Come on, bro. can't just leave
at the end of the day because you know
you're going to meet someone or you met
someone like at the end of the day. Even
if you haven't, you shouldn't even
really be on here.
Yeah, bro. I run my mouth. Okay, bro.
No, he ran his mouth on his video.
You people run your mouths all day,
every day. Timmy runs his mouth all day,
every day. Yeah.
Oh, it's a long story. I just don't like Dr. Pepper.
I just don't like Dr. Pepper. It's as
simple as that. Oh, [ __ ]
Oh, my leg, bro.
Laney's getting old. Bless her, Laney.
Yeah, post a link.
So weird. You gave me a headache today again.
I got a headache, bro. me.
I think I've got an overactive bladder.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I am uh about two or
three days. Yeah.
If you come off for like three or four
days, your your brain feels good. A
week, two weeks, your brain feels lush.
You come back on this little community,
after about two or three days, you get
brain damage again.
Every time, bro. It's cuz it's disabled.
It's dis you're you're engaging with
disabled people like Timmy and that
you're engaging with retards. You understand? So
I got a sore head now. Yeah.
I'm not gay.
Lo, I'm not gay, lad.
I'm not [ __ ] gay, mate.
But I still need to message that Miles McCoy.
Don't Stephen Hard music
you already know Lesie little copycat.
>> Oh bro, I need I need to message that Miles McCoy.
No, I haven't told it today. Would you
Would you like me to tell it?
Would you like me to tell it, dude?
Yeah, little copycat.
So, basically, yeah.
Um, I come across this thing where
people kept saying that, oh, Cheryl Cole
was attractive. Cheryl Cole was
attractive. So, I said to launch legs,
oh, I don't find her attractive. He
said, you're gay. He said that you're
gay. I said, I'm not gay. She's just not
my cup of tea. He's like, no, you got to
be gay. can't deny that she's
attractive, attractive, attractive.
Um, and then uh he started saying it in
college as well cuz uh Miles McCoy and
Jackary was [ __ ] bullying him for the
way that he he dresses. They basically
thought he was [ __ ] gay and then he
was like, "I'm not gay. I like I like I
like Sher Cole. I watch the X Factor.
She's not attractive. She's [ __ ]
ugly. She's got no tits. She's got no [ __ ] ass.
She looks like a [ __ ] transgender.
She is nowhere near as good as people
make out she is.
She is nowhere as good as people make
out. Not a chance, mate.
She's nowhere near as good as people
make out, lad.
Yep. You know, bro,
you already know, bro. Yeah,
I'm going to message that Miles, bro.
It's going to be weird though, is it?
Nah, she's [ __ ] not fit.
Not She is not fit. She's [ __ ]
stinking. Oh, gay. Homo,
what's the chances, lad? If you think
Okay. Okay. What's the chances that
everyone that doesn't find her
attractive gets called gay? It's
obviously a trend. It's obviously a
trend. How comes anyone that if you go
on the internet, people used to call
each other gay if they don't find her
attractive? Would they do that if their
name weren't Chevro Cole? No, they
wouldn't. So, it is a trend. Do you not
understand the point of a trend? A trend
doesn't have to be explained,
you know? And Rihanna, well, you could
go out and get a better looking woman
every time you went out. Well, not get
one, but like you would see one. It is
It is the It is literally It is to fit
in. It generally is to fit in.
It was It was generally a trend to fit in.
She's got no ass. She's got no tits.
She's not the best looking. She really isn't.
So, why people not allow preferences?
Well, people not allow preferences.
Yeah. He bullied him. Yeah. Him and
Jackie, they used to take turns bullying
him. And then when and then when he went
home, his mom used to throw the the
tilly the dalmatation on him. That's why
he's scared of dogs. You know, there's
always reasons why people are scared of dogs.
You get me?
Yeah. And that's where his fear of dogs
come from. His mom used to throw the dog on him.
He used to That's why he was put into care.
Oh, he was put into care at a very very
very young age because of it.
He was put into care at a very very very
young age. Why do you think he got his
his first place at 19? Well,
yeah, Sydney Sweeney. I like um
I like Sydney Sweeney, man. I discovered
her a couple of months ago. Yeah, I
think she's all right. Yeah,
but I wouldn't start saying, "Oh, if you
don't like her, you're gay. Cho,
everyone is gay." Yeah, I think she's
all right. Yeah. Wait, so does that mean
Wait, no, I'm not part of the trend.
Because I tell you why I'm not part of
the trend. One second.
The reason I'm not part of the trend is
because I saw her in a horror film. I
didn't even know her name before I even
knew her name.
with with nonspec it was easy. Oh, come
back. I didn't I didn't I didn't know her name.
I literally didn't know her name and I
didn't start talking about her.
I watched a horror film called The
Housemaid and there was some se there
was like some sex scenes and I saw like
a lot of her like nudes. I'm thinking,
"Oh yeah, that's good." Yeah. I didn't
even know her name until I until I
looked up the movie.
I never saw I I didn't know about her until then.
And I saw her like actually like there
was like sex scenes and [ __ ] So I'm
thinking, "Oh yeah."
But I didn't start calling people gay. I
didn't start talking about her. Do you
understand? Like what people used to do
with She Co. They used to actually talk
about her and look at you weird if you
didn't agree. That was part of the copycat train.
There's no sugar. [ __ ] There's a little
bit of sugar. No, completely completely
different. I didn't know I didn't know her name.
And now I don't even care. I don't ever
ever say anything.
And I only liked her cuz she had big boobies.
Those people just like God to fit in, you know.
I would cream. No, I wouldn't. I
literally wouldn't because she's not attractive.
She's not attractive. So, I really
wouldn't cream. She's not attractive.
She was never ever attractive.
And also, she hasn't got a body. So, if
someone doesn't have a body, then I
don't I don't want them.
And you wouldn't as well. If their name
wasn't Cheryl Cole, you wouldn't care.
It's copying. It's just It's just
copying the crowd.
What do you think, Mr. E? It's just to fit in.
That's it. Like, it is. It is though.
You didn't want to feel left out. But
no, I wouldn't cream. And do you know
why? I see better than that every time I
go out. Every time I go out, you see
better than her.
Every time you go out, you see better
than uh you see better than Cheryl Cole.
Every time you go out, you're telling me
you can't go into an O'Neal's on a Thursday and uh
and see and see a lovely little American.
And she a lovely little American that's
better looking than her.
No, she doesn't. Steven Howard,
she looks nothing like her.
How would you know that?
Yeah, but you're not Yeah, but you're
not going to get several Cole. So why
would people talk about Seel Cole?
You got more chance of getting out than Seel Cole.
Surely the most alpha thing you could do
is sear cold. No, because she's not
attractive. She's average.
She's average at best because she's not
attract she's average at best.
She's not good, bro.
You can get better than that in London
any day. You can go you can go into a
nightclub in London, right? And you can
find better than Cole. Why is if people
ask about Shel Cole? Because it's a
trend. It's to fit in. And Rihanna, she
looks even worse.
Rihanna looks even worse.
Yep. They bullied him rotten lad. They
used to take it They used to take it in
turns bullying him. Bullying him.
Sig wasn't that good looking.
Nah, not really, bro.
Do you remember when I was talking about
having babies with her and that and she
was going along with it?
Do you remember that, Leslie?
That was funny. Do you remember that little video?
You've never seen Christian, is he? Steven Howard,
do you remember that? Do you remember
that sick video? Um Leslie
because because Cheryl car was nowhere
near as good as people are making out
and if her name wasn't Cheryl Cole Dr.
Echo no one would care. Do you not understand?
No, I didn't get a blow I didn't get a
[ __ ] just sex.
He's like, "Oh, if you go down on me,
I'll give you a blowjob." I said, "I'm
not [ __ ] going down on you. [ __ ] off. No,
but yeah, what I'm trying to say is if
Shervel Cole wasn't called Sher Cole, no
one would care.
Think about it. That that Okay, let put
let's use this analogy. That date I went
on, that last date I went on with that
that one from Italy with the hair and
I'm wearing a gray top, she's better
than Cheryl Cole.
But why did why didn't someone say, "Oh,
if you don't find her attractive, you're
gay." Because it's the name. Do you not understand?
Yeah, I do, Leslie. Do you not
understand? It's the name. It's not the
person. It's the actual name. That
person that I went on that date with was
way better than Chev Cole.
But no one's going to say that because
they her name is not Shel Cole. Do you
get it? It's It's a trend. It's a bit like brands.
Yeah. It's a bit like brands, bro.
So if you don't find Cheryl Co
attractive, but you find Sydney Sweeney
attractive, that's that still means
you're gay. Do not understand the flawed
logic. Do not understand the flawed
Dr. Eko, do not understand the flawed logic.
So you're gay if you don't find chevel
attractive. But what if you liked
freckled women with big boobs and blue eyes?
Does would that still make you gay? So,
are men not allowed preferences then?
So, it's a trend.
It said on chat GBT, Leslie, that people
used to like Shel Cole to blend in with
the crowd to avoid being teased. It's on
chat GBT. And you know how accurate chat GBT is?
Yeah. Morgan, she was my mama. Leslie,
Yeah, she abandoned me. But anyways, um
yeah, you get me.
So, if I if I if I if I would get with
Sydney Sweeney, but I don't like Cheryl
Cole, would that still make me gay then?
By your logic, Dr. Echo,
he had big boobies. Leslie,
she had big boobies.
Lunch legs thought he had a chance with
her trying to message her. [ __ ] virgin
trying to get He was trying to get my
sloppy seconds. A little virgin.
Don Legs was He's a little virgin, man.
Nasty little virgin. He was trying to
get them boobs, but no, he got rejected.
Got rejected, didn't he?
So, does that mean I'm gay then, Dr. Echo?
Does that mean I'm gay?
So, does that mean I'm gay then?
I Because Dr. Echo, I'm just I just want
to know, lad, where the desire comes
from to want to copy another person. I
just want to know where that desire comes from.
I just want to know where that desire
comes from to want to copy another person, you know?
Because you have got no mind of your own.
So you want to fit in
anything to fit in. Eh Leslie,
I don't know who had bigger boobies.
Leslie Sigor USA is he I think they were
around the same size to be fair. Yep.
E I don't want to message that dwolf.
Yeah, I don't know who had bigger boobies.
No, I just typed car in Google images
and I don't see what the hype was all
about. Steven Howard
USA is Morgan lad.
Yeah, she had a nasty mini.
I sucked on her boobies the whole time
we was having sex. Leslie
for extra nutrients.
How cute is that?
Yep. Don't see the appeal.
Definitely wouldn't start questioning uh
someone's sexuality over.
Yeah, definitely. Uh
definitely definitely would wouldn't
start questioning someone's sexuality over, you know.
No, Cheryl Cole was definitely a trend.
It was Cheryl Cole, Megan Fox,
uh Rihanna, Beyonce,
and Justin Bieber for the girls. Uh they
went mad over Justin Bieber back in 2011
2012. Again, just a normal looking kid. Um
but they obviously it was the trend.
Justin Bieber was the trend
back in back in 2011. Oh bro, Justin
Bieber was the trend.
Yeah. They all used to copy each other.
Mhm. Mhm. Uh Justin Bieber, Harry Styles.
Yeah, that was a trend. That was
definitely a trend. I remember that.
Little copycats. Dr. Echo.
Do you not remember Justin Bieber?
Charles, his name was. Yep.
I can't believe my mommy abandoned me.
Morgan abandoned me. Leslie,
I got abandoned, bro.
It's quite sick when you think about it.
Yeah. How can you abandon your own your
own your own child?
You know what I mean? How can you
abandon your baby
and go back home like nothing's happened?
I actually messaged her ex uh like an
hour ago. I said, "Oh, bless you, Damon.
Oh, bless you, Damon."
She sure did.
She sure did. Les Leslie, she she said
the slower the better.
She said the slower the better.
She said, she said, "You'll be my 25th."
I'm thinking, "What have I walked into
here, Mr. Bean? What have I walked into?" Jesus Christ. D,
bro, I'm going to I'm going to get the
scream costume. Yeah. And I'm going to
start I'm going to start ringing LT. I'm
going to be like, I'm bad. I'm back.
I'm going to I'm going to I'm going to
leave him voice notes and then if he
doesn't answer, I'm going to go to Tottenham.
Then I'm going to go to Tottenham and be like
with the costume. Would you like to see
that, Mr. Bean? I'm back.
Want to play a game? Yeah.
Yes, I did.
Yes, I did. She had big boobies as well, Leslie. Yep.
Back when you could get one night stands, huh? Nope.
Nope. I haven't.
No, I just like [ __ ] Leslie.
I just like [ __ ] and boobies to be fair.
That's all I like.
I like what I like watching vintage [ __ ]
I love that kind of stuff. Yep. Yeah.
But mainly just uh boobies, Leslie, to
top up on my vitamins,
you know, to top up on my nutrients and stuff.
No, I don't think so. Nope.
Yeah. I don't know who had Imagine
Imagine Imagine Sig. Yeah.
Imagine Sig and USA Izzy. Yeah. Just like um
like just rubbing their tits on your dick. Imagine
them just like rubbing like their titch
on your dick.
Yeah, let's stop talking about this now
cuz I'm going to start getting horny.
So, let's change the subject. Football bets,
right? I've got a nice football bet for
tomorrow, everyone. If you want to copy. Yeah,
I've got a nice football bet if you want.
Did you see Sig when I was talking about
the babies and stuff? She loved it in
it, Leslie. She loved it.
No. Why would I want a hair? Why would I
want a hand job? I can give myself a hand job.
I don't want a hand job. I can do that
myself. I want a lovely warm mouth
around my dick.
You know, I want a lovely warm warm mouth.
Why I want a hand job? I can do that my [ __ ] self.
[ __ ] hand job, you know.
That's really silly
silly thing to ask.
If he waits for He can wait for me all
he wants. I don't give a [ __ ]
You can wait on me all you want. I don't
really care. I'm going out regardless.
Simple. So, I'm not scared of anyone,
bro. I'll go out. I don't give a [ __ ]
She meant it.
No, not all of them did.
They're so selfish.
They're just really selfish, some of these women.
I hope this Christian Izzy gives
[ __ ] or I'm [ __ ] basically.
You never know, bro. And I can't ask it,
can I? I don't even think when I meet
them soon, I can ask.
So, you can't ask. You're just going to
have to find out yourself in it.
No, they didn't. Not all of them did. No.
Sig wanted dick that day and she got my
number. Yeah, Leslie. And then she asked
me where I went.
She was like, "Oh, I don't I don't like
really touching people and stuff." And
I don't really like touching people and stuff.
I don't eat [ __ ] That's disgusting.
And then she next me and then she text
me saying, "Where have you upstairs?"
Then she starts kissing me and coming on
to me and stuff.
Starts coming on to me.
So yeah, Sig bought me chicken, you
know. She bought me chicken from the
chicken shop and I said we was going to
go to Nando's the next day and I never showed up.
Yep. I done a runner.
Yeah, I done a runner, bro.
I done a runner, lad.
She's an idiot, bro. She's like, "Oh,
I'm not going to have sex. We'll go back
and we'll do stuff, but we're not going
to have sex. We're not going to have sex."
She start I think she started wanking my
dick here and I was playing with her
tits and [ __ ] and she's like we're not
going to we're not going to have sex.
We're not going to have sex. All of a
sudden she just jumped on my dick. Leslie bless you.
We went back to watch some Alf Stewart.
I said it on the video.
I went back to watch some Alf Stewart.
Yep. To watch some elves do it.
We watch some Alves Stewart parodies.
Oh, did you like the little talk?
Who's messaging me?
Yeah, it was lovely.
You should have saw that [ __ ] I got
in Nottingham, Leslie.
That [ __ ] I got in Nottingham. I
don't even think I lasted like 30 seconds
cuz we was kissing. She I couldn't [ __ ]
her. She was on her period. So, we was
making out right in the hotel room. We
were drinking wine and then she just
started like rubbing like rubbing my dick.
And then like she'd move her hand off my
dick and then I'd move her hand back
onto my dick and then we started kissing
and then she just went down on me. I
can't remember how long I lasted but she
went down on me. Yeah. Yep.
A lot come out as well.
Yeah. a lot come out and then I kicked
her out after I was done. I just I just
kicked her out.
Yeah, I just kicked her out. I wanted
the bed to myself.
She went home. She went home with a load
of like come in her mouth. Leslie,
that is absolutely delicious. Lovely.
Yeah, she went home with a load of [ __ ]
in her mouth.
Yeah, that's funny as [ __ ] bro. And
then she probably say to her parents
like, "Where have you been?"
Never you mind,
you know? Never you mind. You know?
Yeah. She had big boobies as well, Leslie. Yep.
No, I didn't pay her. I met her in a
nightclub, de lads.
I met her in a nightclub, de lads. It
wasn't an escort. It was a It was a I
met her in a nightclub and then we met
the next day.
We met on a Sunday. Ant-Man went home. I stayed.
No, she was um she was Colombian, but
she was born here.
I was telling her all about USA. Is he
Leslie? I was telling her all about USA. Izzy,
it was fun.
I was telling her all about it.
I used to tell these women all about it and stuff. Oh gosh. Yep. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
And then I got And then I got a [ __ ]
in the alleyway from an American Leslie.
She said, "I really want you, but I
don't think you want me."
But I don't think you want me.
See, I have all of these experiences
that Nons legs don't have cuz he just
don't have the looks.
He don't have the looks. He don't have
the clothes. And he most certainly
don't have any money.
Now, it's quite normal talking about sexual stuff.
That's how we was brought into the world
through sex. We need to normalize it and
not make it sound weird cuz there's
nothing weird about it.
I really want you, but I don't think you want me. Yeah, Oh gosh. Oh gosh,
the one in Manchester swallowed my um
my sperm and stuff.
Oh, Laney knows about all the women I've been with.
I'm sure Laney knows all of the
Yeah, I showed my mom a video before. I
was holding this American's hand and we
was talking and I sent it to my mother.
I was pissed.
No, not the details,
not the exact details, but you know,
there's the, you know,
I don't know who my favorite one was. Um,
no. I don't think she saw that. No, I
don't think she did.
That she never ever did see. No one from
my family did.
No one from my family ever saw that. Funny enough,
actually. They never did. Um,
yeah, the 19year-old was okay, Leslie,
but she didn't have any boobies.
I You know what? I reckon if I had a
baby with a Scottish person, I'd
probably call it Miles.
Yep, I'd call it Miles.
Probably call it Miles
if it was from Scotland. I like that name.
I like that name. [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. the the the the the
19year-old was all right and stuff. She
used to give good [ __ ] Leslie,
but I did used to I used to treat her
like [ __ ] and that, bro. I can actually
I can actually see why she actually
turned out to be a [ __ ] like in the end.
No, I don't really watch Paul. Not
really. Sometimes. Sometimes I watch vintage porn
sometimes, but not really.
It's always vintage as well.
Ant-Man. I'll never forget Ant-Man. I'll
I'll never forget Ant-Man, bro. You
watch porn from the 70s? That's [ __ ]
weird. I've known I've known a lot of
people that watch porn. Yeah. He says,
"I know a lot of people that watch porn.
porn, but not from the 70s. He said,
"Nope." I never got I remember the first
time we sat down on the sofa, actually.
She was showing me her little tattoos and stuff.
Then I started stroking her breasticles.
I started squeezing her breasticles, Leslie.
Breasticles as as as Tony Holly would call them.
But you're not a lovely fellow.
A little fellow.
You lovely little fellow.
Then she just pulled her top out. Uh,
pulled her top up, Blessie, and they
come out. She pulled her little Calvin
climb bra up
and out they came.
Yeah, she pulled her little top up and
out they dangled. Leslie, what a lovely sight.
that's what you call a lovely site.
I'm not telling you what I done. That's personal.
All I'm going to tell you is I got my I
got my vitamins
that day and then I got abandoned and I
was suppressed for like two years after
that and then I got depressed for like 2 years after.
Then I had to try to find a new mama
which they put me into care, didn't
they? So obviously when I was abandoned
they they tried to give me a few other
different mummies, tried getting them
vitamins from them. Never worked. So, I
was basically just thrown from pillar to
post, pillar to post, pillar to post,
basically. That's probably why I'm so
bloody [ __ ] up in my head.
Why you Why would you have a child if
you don't want them?
Ah, the alleyway.
That alleyway one. Oh my [ __ ] god, I
almost passed out.
I'm not sure.
Uh, Crash knows about USA, is he? She's
a nasty nasty nasty fellow. Yeah,
it was the alleyway one. I reckon
the Somalian one. She was kind of biting
my dick, so it kind of hurt. Ouch. Ouch. I said,
"Yeah, it was the Alleyway one, I
reckon." Or the Nottingham one. I don't
know, bro. May I think it's the Alleyway one?
The Alleyway one. Oh my god. I thought I
was going to pass out.
Bear in mind, we was both drunk and that.
I just took my I just took my I just
took my pants down.
I thought I was going to I thought I was
I thought my dick died and went to [ __ ] heaven. Leslie,
the 19year-old was good at giving
[ __ ] though. She used to come
around the old house after I finished
work sometimes and give me a lovely [ __ ]
Then we'd have a lovely Chinese and I'd
go to bed.
Le uh Leslie and then I'd go to bed. sometimes. Yep.
Have a nice Chinese and then go to sleep. Yep.
No, she went back to America, bro. I had
her number and then she went back to America.
She wasn't from here. She was American.
Bro, it was not last summer, the summer before that. Uh-uh.
They were skanks. And they're the best
kind of women. Skanks. Dr. Echo.
They were skanks. Most of them.
I remember that 19year-old. Yeah. She
was pissed off at me. Yeah. She was
like, "Oh, yeah. We're not doing
anything until you change. I'm sick of
you." Where? I took her back to the
house and that in it. Bear in mind, I
got stuff before and that. She come
back. She said, "I'm not giving you
anything. I'm not giving you anything
where I said, "What if I give you
money?" I'll never forget this.
She was like, she was like, "Um,
she was like, I'll never forget this."
Yeah. I'm not a prostitute, but but how much?
And it was £50 on the side. Yeah. And um
Yeah. I just had I just said, "Have the
50 on the side, isn't it?"
And then she then she done it and then
she swallowed it.
Yeah. That was one time though, bro.
I remember that. That was that was the
old house. She has done it for we have
[ __ ] and that and she's done it for
free before that obviously but that's
like I don't think she really like doing it
and that. So I just thought yeah there
was £50 on the side and that. So yeah,
there you go. I'm not I'm not a
prostitute but how much? Oh gosh.
And she swallowed it as well.
I think she swallowed it one time, too.
Yeah, man. But the thing is when I was
meeting her and stuff, Leslie, like
she's not ugly. She was really nice and
stuff, but I was always I was always
looking for somebody with bigger like
breasticles and stuff cuz I had to think
of like the future,
you know, of like me getting vitamins
and obviously baby Peter.
You know what I mean?
I always had to think of like the future
and stuff and you know if you don't
think if you don't see a future with
someone and stuff
but she was like good at like sucking
dick and stuff but like there was no boobies. So that's
it's not no good for me. It's not
something I would be interested in. Oh gosh. Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
Peter belly does. Yeah,
cuz when if I got someone like pregnant
and stuff, I'd want to see like the the
the the progress of the pregnancy and stuff,
like how big their boobs get and stuff
and whatever. I'd like to see the progress.
I'd see I'd need to see like the
progress and whatnot. So yeah, basically
I still don't know whose was bigger
though, USA is or Sigs. I think they
were both as big as each other.
Yeah, I think they were both as big as
each other to be fair. Yeah. Yes.
I went on her profile a couple of months
ago and she was wearing like a little top
Leslie and and you could see like she's
got big boobs and stuff and I was
thinking I had them once upon a time.
They were mine.
I had them.
They were mine at one point.
I told Scott all about it.
I said, "I've already had your daughter
and her body. Thank you very much, you silly goose."
Oh, Christian is just messaged me.
I remember I remember that USA is these kisses.
I love them kisses.
I like to be kissed. I like to be hugged. Seriously,
it felt so nice them kisses, Leslie.
Yeah, Christian is talking to me now.
No, he didn't. I was just talking about
all of the women that I've been with.
Fire stick, you know. I think she's all
right. Christine, is he? She doesn't
ignore, man. I think she's all right, bro.
She actually seems all right, bro.
Seriously, I've had no [ __ ] behavior so far.
Nothing so far, lad.
I don't blame you. We was just talking
about some of the women that I've been
with in the past. Fire Stick, it's
always nice to look back on your collection.
Fire Stick, it's always nice to look
back on your little collection. So yeah,
so if you think if me and Sig had a
baby, Lesie, Lesie, would a baby be cute? Oh [ __ ]
At least you stayed off the gambling
fire stick lad.
At least you stayed off the gambling,
bro. I do the football.
I don't like this LT. He's such a nasty fellow.
Was it hot? Not really, bro.
Bro, nothing's hot for me except the reaper burger.
No, some of the [ __ ] some of the
single mama yet with three kids. Yeah.
You know what I said to her as a joke,
Leslie? I said, "All right, five sick."
Yeah. The only single mama.
Yeah, it is.
They think they're too these women think
they're too good for Nando now, Leslie.
I said, "Oh, we should go Nando sometime
just to see what she say." Yeah,
cuz I like like
I can't explain it. Yeah, she said she
doesn't she thought she was too good for
Nando. Nando is a luxury nowadays, mate.
This country is in poverty.
This country is in poverty, lad.
Do you know
Scream 7 is? Yeah, I'm talking to her. I
don't think I can watch horror films
anymore. D Fire Stick after that, lad.
It's too sick. It's disgusting, bro.
Maybe I will, bro. Maybe I'll get over
it after a couple of months, but
it's a bit too much now, bro.
It's a bit um
It's a bit [ __ ] up, is it? Fire stick.
I can I can remember this scene. Yeah.
This guy, he had they put a knife
through his neck and he started spilling
blood out of his mouth. That's
definitely 18 for a reason, bro. Um,
no, I haven't ordered it yet. I just get
a whole chicken at Nando's whole chicken and rice.
No, I didn't, bro. I said if he knocks
the door, he breaks the window, then I
then I'll do something.
Oh no, not this bastic again.
I hate this little toxic sector.
Remember Leslie, you're not my mama.
Yuck. Yuck. You're not my mommy. Yuck.
You're not my mama.
They tried to con me into thinking that
they were my mama.
I've only got one mama
and they weren't any of you women.
There were none of you.
There were none of you cheeky chappies. Ah, [ __ ] All right.
USA is my mama.
One second. I'm trying to message. Yeah.
How sweet. What do you mean? Oh, yeah.
It is sweet. And have you noticed,
Leslie? She looks like me as well.
That was the most weirdest part about it.
She looked exactly like me.
Same hair, same eyes.
waiting for me tomorrow. Well, you'll be
waiting a very long time, bro.
Be waiting a very long time. Yeah. Of
course I'm going to put a bet on
sniff around who? Oh mate, that virgin
ain't getting no one. He's a s. He's a
proper s that nonsle legs. Of course I'm
putting a bet on tomorrow, bro. What do
you think? I'm going to stay in. How am
I [ __ ] going to stay in? I'm going out
tomorrow. Of course,
cuz I'm not scared of No, brother.
You're not intimidating no [ __ ]
They get me. Yeah.
Oh my gosh. Yep.
Can you believe that? They abandoned me though, Leslie.
She actually abandoned me. How sick is that?
She had She took my money. She took my
stake and then she abandoned me.
You should be put into prison for that.
Should be sent to the death penalty. Sentenced.
Sentenced to to
So this is the death penalty. I'll show you tomorrow.
I used to have dreams, Leslie, about her and stuff.
How cute is that? Little dreams. They
were cute little dreams
about my mama. Yeah.
That's so cute. Really?
Because he's already found his mama.
That's what someone wrote before,
Leslie. Peter belly can't get attached anymore.
Yeah, it took me about two and a half years.
I remember one time I was in Manchester
and I was in the hotel and I was crying.
I was crying my little eyes out and she didn't care.
She didn't care.
I was crying my little eyes out.
I remember one time I was in Manchester.
I was I remember I went to see if my
friend would come out. He didn't come
Yeah, bro. I was
I was bad for about two and a half years. Two years.
Yeah, I know. Yep.
I got left.
She is horrible what she done to me.
Nothing but a coward.
That's what you are.
Do you reckon if if if she was outside
with LT today, do you reckon I would
have went out then? Uh Leslie. Nah.
No. I would have had to. That's your
mama, isn't it? It's family.
No, I probably would, to be honest. It's
your mama, isn't it?
How can you not? Yeah.
Where And where would I bring my mama?
Where would I Where would I bring my mama?
Inside the house.
Inside the house. Isn't it?
Peter Belly can't get attached anymore
because he's already found his mama.
I'll never forget that comment, bro.
Somebody just wrote it out of nowhere
cuz you've already found your mama.
Sign not Peter Belly's mama.
Sig not Peter Belly's mama. Oh,
hey, Fire Stick. You can't get attached
anymore because you've already found your mama.
Uh, it's not sing when the person's your
mama, Joe. That's literally my mama.
You know that's not sing. That's being
an opportunist. I tell you what sing is.
Yeah. Simp is what notchs does.
That's what No, sing is like when
you're, how do I explain it? Simp is is
kissing women's asses
on the internet defending them and
putting them on a pedestal like what
nonslegs does with Autumn.
If my mama was outside, of course I'm
going to go outside
to bring my mommy back in the house.
I don't give a [ __ ]
I'm interested and that's all it and
that's all that counts. So
that's it. I'm interested and that's all that counts. So,
no. Honestly, on a real on a real,
what would I do? Honestly, like all in all seriousness, um
I don't know. Probably nothing to be honest.
Probably nothing to be fair.
Maybe like a year ago I would have maybe
just told him about them myself, but now
probably nothing to be honest. Even if
they walk past me, I don't think I would, bro.
It's too It's gone on too long now, bro. You know?
No, I don't think I would do anything.
I already had her body, Joe.
I already had her body, lad.
I told her dad I already had her body.
No, I probably do nothing to be fair, bro.
I've already got a new mama anyways,
Joe. So, it's fine by me.
Do you remember the 19year-old Joe?
She said, "I treat her like shit." And that
because he didn't do what he was
supposed to do and he was giving me a headache.
But I don't regret messaging family and
stuff. No. All seriousness, I don't
forget me. I don't I don't I don't
regret messaging her family and [ __ ]
with her and that. She deserved it for
being a little [ __ ]
She deserved it for being a little [ __ ]
She deserved everything she got. I told
my mom this as well when we weren't talking.
How did How do you remember that?
Uh, no. I don't regret that. I don't
regret that. I don't regret that. To be fair,
if you want to be a [ __ ] I'll be a
[ __ ] I don't regret that. I said this
to my mom when I was living at the old
house as well when all that [ __ ] was
going on. I don't regret it.
Not one little bit.
Simple. I don't regret any of it.
You're not scaring. No, brother.
Oh, LT, you're not scary. No, brother.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay. How about this, Joe? Right. What
if I wear the Scream What if I wear the Scream costume?
Um, and I go to Tottenham and try and meet LT,
will you then will you then give me a W?
Will you then big me up then? If I order this costume
and I go there on Wednesday
and I walk around, will you will will
you will you big me up?
Oh, she just said, "Oh, it was a bad
thing to do." I said, "Yeah, well, they
led me on and stuff and they didn't give
me closure, so [ __ ] them in it."
So, if I go to Tottenham in a in that in
a screen costume,
but I'm going to have to start the calls first, though.
in it. Fire stick. I'm I'll call him and
be like I'll have to call LT a few times
and leave him some voicemails saying, "I'm back.
I've got to get you." And then I have to
leave a couple of voice notes and then
I'm going to have to just pull up,
make a make a make a make a scream,
mate. Is it fine stick? Make a make a
scream. Isn't it?
Why would I expect him to, bro? Why
would I expect him to go? How many times
has he done this? He's been doing this for years.
He must love driving his little car.
Yeah. I'll ring him first in it. Being
like, "You want to play a little game?" Yeah.
I'll be like, "You're going to have to
get USA Izzy in back back in touch with
me or else
I'm going to go for you." Yeah, that's
what I'm going to do. Like like the
claws of that, is it? Yeah. Oh gosh.
He must love driving in his little car.
He said he left. Yeah. cuz he was he was
shouting and the neighbors got kids or something.
How many years? About five.
Yeah, about five.
About 5 years. He's broke into the house
before, bro. And um he tried killing me,
but I wasn't there.
Yeah, he I think he was going to kill
me, but I wasn't there.
Yeah. And that was over YouTube. Uh
who I started talking to first? Uh I
come on this community through Timmy. I
started talking to Timmy first and then
Pat Mustard was on here and then I come
across LT through Rick's Mace and I
don't even know where the [ __ ] this Red
Star came from.
Yeah, well, when it happens, it happens,
don't it? And I don't know where the
[ __ ] this Red Star come from, bro, to be
fair. But Timmy and LT would um
LT I met LT from Rick's
and I thought, "Oh, he's he's a he's a
London lad like me."
So, uh yeah.
Yeah, he's a he's a London lad like me.
But yeah, this has been going on
absolutely absolutely years. Yeah.
Yeah. This has been going on for absolutely years. Absolutely years.
Yeah. I think I said some racist stuff
to him and I said stuff about his kid years ago. But
I think baking into someone's house is
still a bit too far.
I don't think I would smash I wouldn't
smash someone's I wouldn't do that, bro.
I wouldn't do that.
I don't think so, bro. The only time I
would do that, yeah, is if someone
The only time I think I would do that,
yeah, is if someone stopped my money
or I had a child and they touched my kid.
I think that's the only time I could do
that. I was speaking to my friend in
Amsterdam about this and he said the
same thing. He said that
he knows about the YouTube thing and he
said he would never he would never do
that. He'd come on the door
and that he said that he would never
ever break and like unless someone done
something to his family.
I would I don't think I would do that, bro.
I don't think I could ever do that, bro.
I don't think so. Unless someone done
something like that affected me
personally in my real life or something
to do with just talking about a kid. Nah,
that is that is a bit um it is a bit
weird, isn't it?
It is a bit weird. Yeah,
I'm talking to Christian. Izzy Joe,
we'll be meeting soon.
She would never abandon me.
She would never abandoned me.
You never abandon Peter Belly.
She'll never abandon Peter Belly. Never.
Only Nasty Morgan does that, Joe.
Only M. Only Nasty Morgan. I just
I don't know. I don't know. Would
you do it, Joseph Farah?
Would you break into someone's house
if they live by themselves?
One second. I need to message this woman
on a voice note to explain something
properly. Give me two seconds. And yeah,
I'll be back. Yo,
sorry about that.
Yeah, but how would you catch them when
you weren't expecting it? Joseph,
you haven't seen her hair,
Stephen. Now what you haven't seen?
You haven't seen her hair? Not possible.
You like my little women stories. Joseph Ferrar.
Who's your favorite one?
I liked I liked USA and I also liked Sig
before I got [ __ ] over
by one of them.
I got [ __ ] bro. Absolutely [ __ ]
He hasn't seen her hair. He doesn't know
what she looks like. No one does. Oh man,
how was Sig the best, Joe?
She wouldn't even give me a [ __ ]
unless I licked her out. That's selfish.
Yeah, it's just a shame about her, Mini.
It's just a shame about her miniature
Joe in it.
She had a really nasty mini. That's the only thing.
I brush my teeth three times a day. I
wash my clothes every day.
My dick never stinks, matey. Yeah,
that USA was a horrible old [ __ ] ain't it, Joe?
I just think she was I I think she was
just leading me on.
Why? Why did she want me to go to her
birthday party, lad?
But no, Sig would have been good. You
could have just carried on meet and see
and just told her to like wash herself and stuff. Ricky Millington,
that's a funny account.
You could have got her to go to the gym and wash.
She would have been all right in it.
I don't know what happened to that
Selissa. She I didn't go to her party in it.
She invited me to her birthday party.
Yeah, I approached her at the train station, bro.
She also had big boobies as well, Joe. Yep.
Yeah, I forgot about that solicitor. Yeah.
Yeah. I wonder what happened
cuz she obviously didn't watch it in it.
Yeah. That solicitor. That solicitor.
I think that's another one I [ __ ] up
though. I reckon I could have been in there. >> Yeah.
I love how you know I know how I love
how Joe you say that you [ __ ] up this
one, you [ __ ] up that one, but there's
certain ones you don't list because you know
cuz you know that it was them. I love
that in it. I absolutely love that
you don't list other ones because you
know it was them.
cuz you know it was them in it. That's
why that's why you don't list the other
ones because you know it was them in it.
That's why you always go to Sig and just
solicitor and that one in the in the in
on the date and that cuz you know cuz
you know it was a lot of the time it was them.
No, I didn't.
No, I didn't. that Italian one. The last
date I went on, we was holding hands, we
was rubbing hands, we was vibing. I
tried to kiss her. She didn't want to
kiss. What the [ __ ]
We was vaping and everything. So, no, I
There isn't ones I [ __ ] up. Uh-uh.
There was ones where I went There was
ones where I went on dates, perfect
dates, fire stick, and they come up with
some bogus excuse.
It happened a lot of times, bro. It
happened a lot of times.
But uh it happened a lot of times, bro. Trust me.
Like it was like before New Year's Eve
and stuff, like around the December
time, and they'd come up with these mad
excuses when I didn't even do anything wrong. So yeah, [ __ ]
I haven't had any chances for a very
long time. Well, except from this
Christian, bro. Yeah, that was years
ago. But you're talking years ago, lad.
And I went on a date with went to the
casino. Perfect date and stuff. Fire
stick. Um, and at the end of the date,
we're talking about like New Year's
resolutions. I said, "I'm going to go
here. I'm going to go there. Rare, rare,
rare." And then she says to me, "Oh, she
doesn't feel the connection." Which
doesn't make any sense because I look
smacked. I learned everything right.
What are you expecting?
They I went on within 20 minutes. Didn't
say anything. Didn't do anything wrong.
They don't feel the vibe. You approached
me. This is the same person that
approached me. So there's been loads of
times where they have they have wasted time, bro.
There's been a lot of time, bro, where
where they have and there's been a lot
of times where it's been me as well.
It doesn't matter if I went, "Okay, I
can list you one where I didn't go to the casino."
Bro, come on. You can't keep blaming me.
You can't keep blame. There was ones
where I didn't go to the casino.
where they were just [ __ ] So, no, it
was them a lot of the time.
It was them a lot of the time.
70% of the time. So, no, it was them a
lot. It was them a lot.
Trust me. I don't know how many dates
you've been on Fire Stick, but No,
there was a lot. So that's how these
people in relationships. You see, when
you see people that are in
relationships, they just got lucky and
stayed with a person,
but it might not ever happen again.
It probably will never happen again. Oh, [ __ ]
The dating game's gotten worse, Fire
Stick. It hasn't got any easier. It's
gotten worse, lad. So
yeah, do you remember when I ditched a 19year-old?
My mood swings used to be really bad. Fire stick.
I remember I lost like I think it was
150 one time. Yeah. in the casino and I
wanted to get the glass and smash it
over the casino manager's head. I was
going mad. I just ditched her, bro. I
just I just went to the yard, bro. I
just went home.
I literally ditched her, bro.
Madness, bro. I used to get really mad,
bro. Like really, really mad. Trust me.
And I just I just went home, bro.
Yeah. I used to like ditch people and [ __ ] Yeah.
But it was easier then because I was
drinking when I was doing it. So I just
calm down after a while to get me fired.
I just calm down after a while.
So obviously you calm down when you're
drinking in it.
But obviously if you're not drinking
it's harder to calm down. So
yeah, that's what happened basically. Oh, well,
you're not scaring. No, brother.
You're not intimidating. No, [ __ ] Do you remember? Oh,
yeah. Do you remember? Do you remember
the first Isabelle Joe?
Do you remember the first Isabelle?
Yeah. Do you remember the little video
with me and little Isabelle holding hands?
That got the virgin jealous, didn't it, Joe?
That got the virgin jealous. Do you
remember the Weather Spoons? No.
Isabelli. Isabella was my first kiss.
She was my first kiss. But that was my own fault.
She was She was my first kiss, Joseph Farra.
She was my first kiss. She started
stripping in front of me and stuff. I
said, "What are you doing, Isabelle? Put
your clothes back on right now
before I tell your mother."
She also done my makeup, too.
She done my little makeup, too. Yeah.
The first Isabella. But do you remember
the virgin though, Joe? The virgin got.
Do you not remember that Joseph Ferrar?
when Pat Mustard was on here? Everyone
was on here. Do you not? Oh my god.
Craig Goodston, everything. You know,
do you remember when they were all on
here? Yeah. Do you remember when they
were all on here? Yeah. They were all on
here, right? And
bear in mind, these people were trolling
the [ __ ] out of me, bro. Every day. And
Isabelli was playing games and then she
saw my little roulette win ring, Joe. My
little 300 pound roulette win. So she
hit me up saying, "Do you want to meet?
Do you want to meet?" I said, "Why do
you want to meet me, Isabelle? You've
been really nasty to me. You've been
trolling me over YouTube." But okay. So
then we met and then we done some videos
and everybody was biging it up. Pat,
Craig, Mr. G, Triple H, the absolute
[ __ ] lot. Yeah, the absolute lot. And
then you got [ __ ] virgin boy saying,
"No, you didn't sleep with her. There's
no proof. There's no proof."
He's always been a little virgin like
that though, Joe.
He's a miserable old virgin, but we love
him. You know, he's a nasty, nasty
little virgin. Oh, you're telling me you
don't You're telling me you don't
remember that, Joe?
You're telling me you don't remember that?
No, I definitely remember that.
Those were the really skint days.
Those were the really skint days, Joseph.
I remember I had her number like four or
five years ago, bro.
She was playing games and stuff.
Yeah. I went on her door.
You're not scaring. No, brother. Fire
stick. You're not intimidating. No, [ __ ]
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
No, I see I seen someone say that
before. I just copied it. LT calls this
the toxic sector.
He calls O. He calls this the little toxic sector.
Did you think the solicitor looked good? Joe,
do you think the solicitor looked good?
You could have sex with all three of
them at once, in it.
That would be lush.
Stop it. You're trying You're trying to
turn me on.
Yeah, she had big boobies as well, Joe.
Plenty of vitamins for Peter Belly.
I said we should get in a hotel room.
We should be in a hotel room.
Oh, [ __ ] me, bro.
Okay, she's messaging me. One second,
bro. Right. Sorry. This person's sending
me voice notes.