Yep.
Back on this little sector. This is how
you know. Yeah. This is how you know
this community is so so so so toxic,
bro. Cuz like whenever you lose a
football bet or or on the roulette or
whatever, you're straight back on here.
I swear. Like that's the first thing you
want to do is come back on here, bro.
This that's how you know it's a toxic community.
That's how I, bro. I swear to God. This
is how you know it's actually toxic.
This is how you actually know it's toxic, bro.
Yeah. This is how you know it's toxic.
That is literally how you know. Yeah. I
just done a 20 pound football bet loss, bro.
The mood swings are coming again.
Thoughts on what I want to do to people
is coming again, bro. Oh, just 20 pound
on the football. I feel like getting a
screwdriver and shoving up someone's anus.
Yeah. I feel like just getting a
screwdriver and just ramming up
someone's anus, bro. Their pal anus.
Yeah. It's so depressing, is it, bro? I
swear to God. This is how you land back
on this [ __ ] community, bro. With these losers.
This is how you [ __ ] come back on
this community with these losers. I
swear this is how you end up back on
here, bro. I just want to get a
screwdriver and just ram it up someone's
ass. And a lot more as well. And a lot
more. is [ __ ] annoying, bro. It's so [ __ ] annoying.
I don't I don't know how it doesn't
annoy people. How they just how they're
just fine with it. I just told Ant-Man
about it. Oh, he says, "Oh, you still
got more money than me, though. At least
you're not skin." It doesn't matter if
I'm skin, not skin, millionaire, broke.
It doesn't matter what I am. I'm playing
to win. I'm not playing to lose. Do you
understand, Dusty? I'm playing a game
and I'm playing to [ __ ] win. Yeah. Do
you understand? I'm not playing to lose.
I don't want to lose. Doesn't matter if
it's 10p, 20 p,5.
I don't give a [ __ ] I'm playing to win.
I'm not playing to lose. Just like a
football team, right? The players in a
football team are playing to win.
They're not playing to lose, are they?
They're not happy with losing a football
match. It's the same thing with a
football bet or when you're playing
roulette. I don't give a [ __ ] It is too
bad. It's annoying. It is too bad. It's
It is bad. It's annoying. Losing any
amount of money is annoying. Doesn't
matter how much money you got left.
Doesn't matter how much food you got in
your fridge. It's as simple as that. It
is as simple as that.
No, it's annoying, bro. It is actually annoying.
Oh, there's a new saying, by the way.
Um, Gre there's a new saying as well,
Grezy. Um, always
on the roulette. It's rigged. Yeah. Um,
and stop trying to blame the house
heads, poor [ __ ] It's only 2.7%.
That's where that guy got that saying from. Oh
yeah, poor [ __ ]
Yeah, it's only 2.7. The poor [ __ ]
gets the blame for everything. That's
where we got it. He copied me. Always
blaming the heads, poor [ __ ] It's
only 2 months and seven days old. The
poor [ __ ] gets the blame for
everything. You know,
the poor [ __ ] gets the blame for everything.
Listen to me right now. I could lose
right now £500 on roulette and I'd be
exactly the same as I was to lose 20
pound on football. It's not the amount.
It's not the amount you got left. Just
losing is is annoying. Losing is
annoying. Simple as that. Yeah,
I bet I can I I bet I can make you laugh, Greasy.
So, Peter the penis hasn't entered a
woman's mouth for over a year. Poor [ __ ]
Got you, didn't I? Got you. [ __ ]
I don't know. I like that one. I thought
that one was cool.
Did you Did you like that? Poor [ __ ]
No, it hasn't even It hasn't been a
year, but I don't know why I said that. Poor [ __ ]
Uh, only 20 pound. I only done 20 pound
in the football.
No, it was only 20 pound on the football.
>> Yep. 20 on a football, lad.
I just feel like dressing up as
screaming. Just just just just doing
someone in their [ __ ] ass with a screwdriver.
Like just doing someone in the backside
with a screwdriver, bro. I swear. Yeah. Seriously.
You still got more money than me though,
Lee. You're not skin. Does it matter?
Does it matter? Does it matter if people
are skinn or they're not skinn? Why does
that make a difference?
Why does that make a difference?
I could be in a Weber spoon. Yeah. And I
could put 2030 pound in fishing frenzy.
I could have thousands in the bank,
could have money coming in. It doesn't
really really matter, bro. And if I
lose, I'd want to smash the glass over
that o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o o
o o o over over that machine. Um
and stuff like that. So it doesn't it
doesn't matter. That's that doesn't mean
anything how much money people have. I
don't know why people bring it up.
So when you don't react the way that
these people want you to react,
apparently you've got problems. No. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It could be£10, it could be£20, it could
be any amount of money and you could
have any amount of money left. It
wouldn't make a difference.
Well, he's the Mong. if you can't even
use if you can't even use a washing machine. So yeah.
Uh well, I actually come back because I
lost a football bet. And this is how you
know this community is toxic cuz every
time I lose a football bet, I feel like
coming back on here and just ranting and
ranting because I'm psychotic, you see.
So that's what happens. Yeah.
Just really feel like doing some
[ __ ] Oh, I'm not having a takeaway
today, Greavves. I've got steak and
onion rings for dinner. I went out
earlier. I went to the arcade, done a football bet,
and I'm back in the old homeland. So, yeah.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Yeah,
I just chilling today, bro. Yeah, basically.
Yeah, but that's not what the rules was.
The rules was he said that he was going
to knock the door and he never. So
anyways, we're not getting into this
because this is how it goes in circles
again, bro. Yeah, we're not going around
in circles again. I'm not going around
in circles again. This is how you avoid
going around in circles, Grezy.
I told you I unsubed yesterday from
Timmy. I'll be back on his channel on
Wednesday. This is how you avoid going
around in circles. You see, if Timmy
comes, I I I'll leave you with this.
Yeah. If Timmy comes on Wednesday, I
will I will travel to Tottenham myself
and call out this LT. No coming to me.
No, nothing. How about that?
How How you How Well, did I lose money
yesterday? Did I gamble yesterday? No, I
didn't. But I g I will do it. I will
actually do it. If Timmy comes, like he
said, then I will I will I will travel.
I don't give a [ __ ] I will actually do
it as well
cuz I'll be I'll be in the mood. So
yeah, I will do it. No one has to travel
anywhere. I'll be doing it.
And if they if he doesn't come, then
we're finished. Simple.
That's it. So yeah. Okay. My word means
nothing. Okay, lad. Whatever. You're the
one that's had people's addresses for
years and you ain't done [ __ ] So
whatever. That's nice, bro. Good for you.
And you're actually obsessed. Like every
comment you make is about me, but you've
never ever tried to come on my door
before. The LT [ __ ] when I live by
myself. So, bro, at the end of the day,
you telling me that my word doesn't mean
anything means nothing.
It means nothing. Coming from you, it
literally means nothing. You understand?
It means absolutely nothing, lad. Like,
you've had chances to get me. I've been
up north multiple times. You kept your
mouth shut. So, anyways, we we'll just
see in Wednesday anyways what Timmy's
doing and we'll go and we'll go from
there. It's as simple as that.
What do What do you get? You get what?
Uh only 20. But it is dojo. You comment
every day about me, but you're never
going to come on my door. You're never
going to come to London. Even before
this LT [ __ ] even when I've traveled up
north by myself, um, you haven't tried
meeting anyone. So, at the end of the
day, you're not LT. So, if you want to
keep bringing up LT, you're not LT. So,
yeah. So, yeah, you're not going to
you're never going to do anything.
If someone damaged this property and
someone come in the door, you would have
saw what would have happened. Anyway,
stop trying to [ __ ] stir.
Uh cuz I've already met Timmy before
when he's come so you can't even you
can't even use that excuse.
Yeah. It's your turn now to meet London
Taylor as well. Yeah. That's another
thing. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He's it's your
turn now to meet him like you said.
Yeah. That's another thing. Yeah. It's
your turn now to meet London Taylor.
Yeah. It's your turn.
It's your turn next. Yeah, that's another thing.
Yeah, it's your turn. You done what he
said according to you. Yeah, that's
good, man. Now it's your turn to meet him.
Yeah. So, if he comes if he comes to
Leeds, are you going to meet him
anyway? So, if he goes to Leeds, are you
going to meet him? Yeah.
Okay. I'm a weasel. That's good, bro.
Yeah. So if if he comes to you, are you
gonna meet him?
If he comes to you and he calls your
name out, are you gonna meet him?
Yeah, I'm a [ __ ] bro. Yeah, I know,
man. He beats me. Yeah. So when he comes
to you, are you going to meet him? Yeah.
How you going to get your way out of this one?
How are you going to get your way out of
this one, lad? Huh?
You can't play two sides of a coin, lad.
You can't play two sides of a coin. You
need to show me how it's done, bro. I'm
terrified of London Taylor.
I'm scared of London Taylor, bro. He
scares me, bro. Yeah, I admit it, man.
So now you have to show me how it's
done. You have to be the first one to defeat him.
And I don't know why you're saying about
Timmy cuz I've already met Timmy when
he's comed with Tiger. So, I don't know
how you can say that when I've literally
met Timmy when he's coming on the door.
And what's the point of Timmy coming on
the door? Cuz he said that he's coming
on the door. Hey, bro. I was watching
Timmy yesterday. Yeah. When he was going
mad at Monty like videos from like 10
months ago, I fell asleep watching it. I
was pissing myself laughing. I was
pissing myself laughing. I was watching
it, bro, for a good 20 minutes in
Weather Spoons outside outside of Iceland.
You've just got to laugh at him, is it?
Yeah, I know. So, if he goes to leads,
are you going to meet him then? Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, I know, bro. Yeah. So, when
he goes to leads, are you going to meet him?
Yeah, I know, bro. When I'm I'm I'm
terrified. My word means nothing. Yeah.
Okay. So, are you going to meet him when
he goes to leads or Harriet? Yeah.
Are you going to Are you going to Are
you going to meet him? Yeah.
So, if he comes to you, you're going to
meet him. Yeah.
So, you're backing out of it now. So,
you're backing out of it. So, you're
backing out of it now. Yeah. So, there
you go. There you [ __ ] go.
There you go.
Oh, so so you're backing out then. Oh,
so you're backing out again then. So
you're backing out again then. Oh, okay.
So you're backing out again then.
You're backing out again then. Oh, okay.
So you can't talk about anyone then cuz
your word means nothing cuz you said you
was going to meet him.
Uh, we're just going around and around
in circles. You're a [ __ ] house, bro.
Stop it. Stop trying to act big, man.
You're just a windup. Come on. You're
never going to meet anyone,
whether it's me or anyone else. Like,
just stop it. Yeah. My word means
nothing at all.
Yeah. Says the guy that can't even talk
on a panel. Congratulations, bro.
on a panel. Yeah. Congratulations. Anyways,
I tried to win Patrick Star today
with£10. It never worked.
Yeah. And you proved that you're a [ __ ]
house as well when I agreed to go to
Nottingham and you wouldn't agree to it.
You proved you're a [ __ ] house when you
had two different addresses where I
lived, but you would never dare come to
London even before all the LT [ __ ] So,
I mean, you're in the same boat as me
then, aren't you?
I tried to win Patrick Star. Never worked. Yep.
Both the games were 1-1.
Oh, I think you find I will because I am
and I just did all your You're you're
just terrified. You know, the thing is
with you, what it is with you and Red
Star and stuff. Yeah. you you are so
you're so excited to see me get beaten
up, but you can't do it yourselves.
You're scared to do it yourselves. And
you know the only one the only one that
will uh do it or has a chance of doing
it is LT. And that's what drives you
mad. You ain't got the balls to do it.
Red Star ain't got the balls to do it.
So what you do is you cling on to
someone else and when it doesn't go your
way, it it drives you mad. And the thing
is, yeah, Mr. lot. Yeah. All of them
people that was that was golden LT
yesterday. These are all the same people
that have been obsessed for years,
right? That will not even say where they
live. That's the bit I found funny. And
it was all of them doing it. It weren't
like people that have tried to meet me
before or people that don't get involved
in the drama or someone that doesn't
really say much. is all it was all of
the people that had channels dedicated
to me who I called out multiple times
before the whole LT [ __ ] would not say
where they lived will not meet anyone
and they're trying to go someone else
what the [ __ ] bro don't go watch don't
go people it's the same thing with t
it's the same thing with Timmy and Monty
I never goed the beef ever I've never
ever [ __ ] stirred people into doing
something that I would do myself I never
have done it bro never ever ever have
and And I never will.
Never have. And I never will. I never
did, bro. Trust me. You'll notice all of
the people that are [ __ ] stirring and
golden are the biggest cowards.
That's what you That's what I found out
on LT's channel. I found that out.
I found that out right now. Cuz we all
know that if I if I fought LT and he
beat me or I beat him or it was a draw,
whatever, and then I go and say, "Okay,
Red Star, you meet me." It would never
happen. It would never happen.
it would never happen. Do you
understand? It doesn't matter what the
result of it was. These are the same
people that will never meet anyone. Trust me.
So, I don't know why they're going to
other people when they're never going to
do anything themselves.
You know what I'm saying?
And you can't an LT can't say you can't
say that. Oh, well, if you're not going
to meet me, you're not going to meet
them. But you said I go for the weaker
target. So, which one is it then? Do I
go for weaker people or do I not go for
weaker? I don't go for weaker people.
Timmy's got the same It's the same rules
with with Timmy. Unless he knocks on the
door or he damages something, I'm not
meeting him. He has is exactly the same rules.
It's exactly the same rules for anyone. Um Yeah. So, yeah.
Oh, you don't dis you don't meet
disabled men. Yeah, you never took any
of my money, mate. I've got plenty of
money and plenty of savings, but keep
telling yourself that. Anyways, so you
don't meet you don't want to meet
disabled men, but you want somebody else
to beat a disabled person up. Make it
make sense, lad. Um, that's another
excuse they use that they won't meet
anyone because they're disabled. I
assure you, lad, that the only disabled
person is yourself and you never got
anyone's money stopped. So, see you
later, lad. There you go. So,
uh, see you later, lad. And you've never
got anyone stop letting money stopped.
I've got more money than you and more
savings than you'll ever have. And this
is what I'm saying. These are the same
people that are trying to go the man to
do something that they will never do themselves.
Do you understand what I'm saying? To
me, that's a big problem. You know,
to me, that's a big problem. And you've
never got anyone's money stopped. But at
the end of the day, if that helps you
sleep at night, keep telling yourself
that. Doesn't wind me up. Doesn't bother me.
I had your boy went, bro. I'm not even
going to repeat this again. So, yeah,
we're not going around in circles again.
Anyways, so anyways, are you going to
meet LT or what?
No, I'm saying to you. One second. I'm
saying I'm saying I'm saying that you
said Joe said that he was going to meet
you. Yeah. If you come and you done what
you done yesterday. So you done what you
done. So I'm asking Joe if he's going to
meet you now if you go to if you go to leads.
Yeah. That's what I'm talking cuz this
guy's trying to [ __ ] snow again. So I'm
thinking, okay. So, are you going to
stick to your agreement then? Okay. Yep.
LT owned me. I'm scared of LT. Yep. Yep.
Yep. Yep. He done everything he said he
was going to do. Yeah. That's good, man.
So, are you are you going to meet him
now if he goes to leads?
You know, that's good. Yeah.
Are you going to stick to your
agreement, Joe? Are you going to stick
to your agreement?
Are you going to stick to your agreement?
Come on, LT.
Listen. Listen. No. No. One second. One
second. One second. Listen to me. Yeah.
You know, you said that you showed me up
yesterday and whatever. Yeah, that's
good. That's good. Now, can you go to
leads now when you're ready and show
that this guy's never going to meet
anyone? Like, you two agreed.
Well, they were bringing you up. So,
listen. Listen. So, you showed me up.
Yeah. I'm scared. Okay, whatever, bro.
So, can you go to leads eventually then
and show this Joe up? Like, you two
agreed. Yeah. Can you do him now when
you're ready when you're back in London?
cuz he wants to act the big man. He
wants to act the big man. So like could
you just go like there for like a couple
of days or something or one day please
to show that this guy is not ever going
to meet anyone himself, you know?
Can you can you do that?
Cuz you two did have an agreement and he
agreed to it. So at the end of the day,
stick to your agreement, man. Just get
the train there from King's Cross. It's
very easy. Simple.
Yeah, bro. Okay, man. That's good. But
are you going to go to Are you going to
go to Leads, though?
Okay. Are you going to go to Leads and
and and meet this Jo like you said?
Yeah. Yeah. But no, no, no, no, no. I
don't care. Listen to me. Listen to me.
Listen to me. Yeah. I don't care about
people ridiculing me. I don't care about
like people like Griezy and all of these
other people. I care about the people
that will never ever meet anyone
themselves that have been obsessed with
people for years. That's the people I've
got a problem with.
That's the problem I don't give a [ __ ]
Like, okay, give me give me an example.
Okay, let me give you an example, right?
If how hard can it be when on your
channel talking [ __ ] I wouldn't care if
[ __ ] if anyone even the people that
like me come on your channel talking
[ __ ] I wouldn't give a [ __ ] It's the
people that were doing it. Red Star
coward. Uh Pooh, coward. UK biggest
nonser coward. Every single one of these
people are more cowards than you could
ever call me. And they're trying to go
you to do something that they never
would. I've never tried going people to
do stuff if I wouldn't do it myself. I
wouldn't. I [ __ ] wouldn't. Yeah. You
see that time that before Mont uh Monty
met Timmy, right? I said, "Do what you
want to do, bro. I'm not involved.
I never ever once tried to go anyone
into doing [ __ ] like these people like
these cowards. Do you understand the
problem with that? Do you It's the It's
the people doing it. It's the people. It
is actually the people that are doing
it. Cuz let's face it, right? If I went
outside yesterday and you beat me or
whatever, whatever the case, whatever
the weather, we all know that these
people that come on your channel would
never meet me.
Would never meet me. Am I lying? Tell me
I'm lying. Am I lying?
It's the people that was trying to go
you. They're the biggest cowards ever.
And LT, you can't say as well that, oh,
I'm there's no point them coming because
I'm not going to meet them because you
said that I go for weaker people. So,
you can't play two sides of a coin. You
can't play two sides of a coin to be
honest with you. Cuz you said that, oh,
like I I go for weaker people. So you
can't use that, you know.
It's mad. It's actually m It's actually mental, bro.
That is actually mental.
The people that was trying to go you is
bad. It was the people that was doing
it. It's under the fact they were trying
to go to like bro. It's like
you know this like you know you know
this anyway. So yeah,
you know this anyways. So yeah,
the same people that was
um the same people that are trying to go
Jew are people that would never ever say
the area they live.
It's strange, isn't it?
You know, and you can't say that I
wouldn't meet them because you say I go
for weaker people. So, you can't play
two sides of a coin.
But listen, LT, anyways, if Timmy comes
on Wednesday, Yeah. and he comes on the
door, unless he comes, unless he knocks
on the door, I'm not meeting him
anywhere. He can be outside, whatever.
And if he does, and he actually does, I
will travel to you.
That's a deal. I I will do it. I will do
it. So you don't have to go anywhere. Whatever. Yeah.
I haven't been going you. I haven't been
Yeah. Okay. I wasn't going you. I told I
told Timmy to bring you cuz I knew
exactly what you was going to do. Bro,
bro, bro, bro. I know exactly what you
was going to do. If I if Timmy comes
here, I know exactly what you was going
to do. So that's why I said bring you
because I know exactly what you're going
to do. You're going to get involved cuz
you're always watching. So what? You
would have got involved anyways. That's
why I mentioned your name and nobody was
going for Timmy either. He was making
videos not shutting up about my [ __ ]
name. So then I said, "Oh, I'm going to
message your Auntie Rose. I never
mentioned me in this plastic for a
fight." He's the one that brought it up. Yeah, simple.
This guy's been running his mouth now
for too long. So that's why Yeah, I
might as well have brought you up
because you would have you would have
got involved anyways. You would have
come back and said, "Oh, oh, you go for
Timmy, but you don't go for me." That's
exactly what would have happened.
Bet, bro. 100% bet.
So why it made sense, isn't it? really
bringing your name up, you know.
So, yeah, man.
Here we go. >> Hello.
>> Listen, anyone that's listening, do not
go to this guy's door. It's all a setup.
I saw everything yesterday for myself. I
saw I saw it last time, but I forgot.
This guy's got
>> Listen to what I'm saying.
>> Camera, but Okay. Yeah. Listen, all him
and his neighbors, they all got the Ring
doorbell cameras right outside your
outside the house.
>> Okay. My mom don't have a camera.
>> Number one. And then he informs his mom
before you come. He tells her
>> Bro, my mom was watching the whole thing.
>> Okay. Well, she's watching the whole
thing. Why don't you be mad enough and
just walk outside the house? Then
>> I was I didn't tell my mom nothing. She
knows everything, mate. She didn't know
anything. My mom listen people around me
don't know everything.
>> She subscribe to YouTube cuz she watches
my YouTube. Yeah. Whose fault's that?
>> Well, she knows my channel, isn't it?
>> Yeah. How would she know your channel if
you didn't give it to her?
>> Cuz she's been going on for years, obviously.
>> No, no, no, no. This is a new channel
that you're on right now.
>> Because Laur put it up.
>> So, she watches all Well, but all I'm
saying is if you know that, if you know that.
>> Yeah. Why don't you be quiet about stuff
and why don't you come outside your
house and walk around the corner then so
she don't have to Why are you trying to
put your mom through trauma? You ain't got no
>> No one's asking. No one's No one asked
you to drive all that miles and go out.
>> No, no. Listen, listen. No one You've
been talking about me. You've been
talking about me for the longest. You've
been talking about me for the longest.
My problem is I'm trying to tell you as
a man, if you're going to talk about
someone for ages and gossip and talk
[ __ ] Yeah. Be willing to say it to
their face. Be willing to stand up to
them. That's what my problem
and you keep telling Timmy.
>> I've not been around. You keep telling
Timmy that he should bring me getting me
involved for no reason. Timmy get involved anyways.
>> Who told you anything? Yeah. What's
wrong with you anyway? So,
>> well, why don't you be a man for once
then and step out then let's just get
this over and done with then. Yeah. You
know what you've said about me in the
past about my children, about all this.
You keep mentioning talking about my
children. I've told you to stop. Keep
doing it. But notice children. No one talks about
>> But listen listen but listen listen
notice notice when you when you was last
in Stratford and I left you alone in
when he was in Statford. He was denying
it the whole time. Notice that he wasn't
coming with all this mouthy [ __ ] And when you
>> spoke about your children in years,
listen to what I'm saying. Listen to
what I'm saying. Yeah. When you was last
in Stratford and you was denying it to
everybody that you was there,
>> you was not being this mouthy whilst you
was there. Whilst you know that your mom
wasn't there cuz you know I would have
just came there and I would and you know
I would have terrorized that place just
like how I did before. Just like how my
cousin did before. Yeah. So so now that
you know that you're in a safe haven
with your mom and you know I don't
really want to bother your mother like
that because out of what's the point?
That's a mad charge. Anyways, if I if I
get caught doing that,
it is a mad charge. It's a mad charge.
All she has to say, all she has to say,
all your mother has to say is I'm an old
woman and she has to say that you're
disabled. It's a wrap.
>> Oh my god. The other house was worse,
bro. There was five people living there.
You wouldn't go.
>> Yeah, I didn't mind that though. Bro,
listen. What do you mean I wouldn't go
away? Because that mean I broke into a
house when these people are talking
about because Are you going to let me
talk, bro? If there was if there was
four or five people when you broke in,
you wouldn't have got away.
>> What do you mean I wouldn't have got
away? You're 10.
>> You're gonna beat five people. So, you
got to beat five people.
>> Well, you think I was by myself all the
time. So, shut your mouth then.
>> So, you're going to beat four or five people.
>> You don't know what's going on. You
don't know. You don't know who I was
with or anything. All them terms. You
don't know. So, stop talking [ __ ] about
why was they begging me then? Why did
you give them my my number or whatever?
And they was begging me. Am I lying about that?
>> Because one of them might have been
scared. Because one of them might have been scared.
>> No, it wasn't one of them that I spoke
to, though. There's about three of them.
Bro, simple as that, bro.
>> That other house was worse. That other
>> Yes. So then why are they scared? And
why are they begging me to allow it?
Then why are they begging me to not come
back and to leave you alone? And why are
they begging me? Am I challenged?
>> No, it wasn't one. It was It was three
people that was asking me to allow you.
And one of them saw my cousin face to
face and he didn't want none with my
cousin. Nothing. My cousin stuck it on
him. I was on the phone when it was
going on. So don't come on here trying
to make out anything like, "Yes, it was
even better when you had five tenants
living at there. At least it's not your
mom. Your mom's an old woman. What type
of charge is someone going to get for
doing something at your door? It's going
to be aggravated assault, aggravated
this, aggravated burgy, aggravated
harassment. I I don't want those type of
charges. I've got [ __ ] to lose. Do you
not understand that?" >> Well,
no. But if you're going to be running up
your mouth, listen. as a man. As a man,
if you're going to be running your mouth
online as a man, right, and knowing full
well that I know where you live, you
keep talking about [ __ ] You keep
talking about people kids. I've told you
to stop mention my kids at all.
>> Oh, it's not your kids.
>> Just the other day. Just the other day.
What do you mean?
>> What did I say? What? You didn't have kids. [ __ ]
>> What did I say? My cousin has heard you.
My cousin has heard you himself saying I
say what did I say recently? Tell me
what Listen. Listen.
>> Tell me what I said.
>> You said a lot. I don't need to recite.
What? Yeah, cuz nothing's been said. You
You're making stuff up.
>> You said that people been racist
recently. No, they have not. You're
making that up.
>> Yes, they have. Did you call me a gorilla yesterday? >> Yeah.
>> That's not racist.
>> That's not racist. Or would you call
your nephew? That's not racist. Would
you call your racist?
>> Would you call the the the Shim's
youngest a gorilla? Cuz he looks more of
a gorilla than I do.
>> Would you call him one?
>> No. If you if you call him that, you
call him that.
>> Yeah. Well, I'm saying would you call him one?
Well, I've I've called him something else before.
>> Oh, is it? Yeah. Okay. But yeah, not
racist, but Yeah.
>> Oh, okay. But anyways, yeah. So, what
I'm saying is to anybody out there, do
not knock on this guy's door. Yeah. It's
clear as day.
>> Another thing is another thing doesn't
want to fight. It's okay. Can you answer
Can you answer me? Can you answer me
this then? Can you listen? I need to ask
you nothing, man, because you didn't
want to come out. We didn't want to come
out to you.
You were silent yesterday. Just remember
that trying to just remember that when I
was outside your house yesterday, you
were silent. You were silent. You had no
talk for me. Your your lights were
turned off. Everything like you had no
>> All of the people that commented on your
channel were more cowards than I could
ever be. That's the joke about it.
That's what made me laugh. My
>> Okay, okay, okay. They may not turn up,
right? But is this it?
>> No, no, it's not about turning up. They
won't even say where they live. [ __ ]
turning up anywhere. They won't even
give a location.
>> Okay. And you see with you, you run your
mouth and tell people to come and do
this and you you you yesterday you was
giving me all this talk how you fight
dirty and all this nonsense and you're
so mad and you will do this and do that
to me and you will chef me up, chef
anyone that I bring up all of this
nonsense, right? And what happened to
all of that? So if anything, you're
worse than all of them because you've
been talking about the biggest talk on
here for a very long time. And then and
then when some and then even when you
get what you want, even if someone
knocks on your door, I've done more than
knock on your door. I don't know why
this person's in your chat talking
about, "I'm scared to knock on your
door." No, I'm not. And you know, I'm
not scared to knock on your door. But
it's out. It's It's cuz your mom's
there. Really? Realistically, if you're
this bad enough, all you have to do is
step outside. I don't mind smacking you
up in front of your mom. Yeah. But but
the thing is, I I ain't going to knock
on I ain't going to knock on a door
because I know what them charges are. I
know what that that is. That's
aggravated. The minute I do that, that's
aggravated. You think I'm stupid? You
think I don't know what what's going on here?
>> This is pathetic, bro.
>> Everything that you do here is
calculated. That's why you're telling
people to do it. And even if I did knock
on the door, you think you're you're not
going to come outside? Why did you leave
your mom to come and look outside when I
was in a cop?
>> Yeah. Okay, bro. Whatever.
>> Did I What? Am I Am I lying?
>> Yeah. Okay. Whatever, bro.
>> Oh, I'm lying about
>> I told my mom to go out the door and
look out. No, I didn't.
>> Why did your Yes, you did. And then you
said close the door. You said close the
door. So, you were stuck inside the
house where your mom's there looking up.
Why are you doing that? That's what I'm
trying to I would never in a million
years hide behind any female and tell
her to go and look at anything. I'm
doing the looking myself.
>> And I told you I was outside. I told you
to put the link in and you did not want
to put it out there for me. Not at all.
>> Yeah. Okay.
>> The truth though.
>> Why can't you even
>> Yeah, whatever, man.
>> You're full of [ __ ] man. You're the big
You're the biggest, strongest guy on
YouTube. Are you happy now, bro?
Oh, we left. Are you happy or what?
Like, is that is that what you want?
Is that what you want? I can say a load
of [ __ ] but I just can't be bothered
getting into this again. It's just
[ __ ] bro. All of it is just
[ __ ] That's why I can't be bothered
getting into it again. I just like,
"Yep, yep, yeah, whatever. Yeah, yeah,
yeah, whatever." Cuz the whole thing is
just so pointless. Pointless, stupid,
gay, all of it. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Whatever, man. So,
Not good, man. I lost 20 pound.
Was thinking of doing some mad stuff
earlier, you know.
Was thinking of doing some really crazy mad stuff.
Yeah, I lost 20 pound on a football bat.
Uh, sick stuff, bro. Really sick stuff.
Like stabbing someone in the ass
with a screen mask. Yeah. Really like
sick stuff, bro. Yeah. Yep.
Yeah, like really really really really
sick stuff, bro. Really really sick stuff.
These people don't understand, Fire
Stick. My mate Ant-Man don't understand.
He says, "Oh, well, you're not skinned.
You got more money to be." Uh, okay.
Uh, okay. And your point is what? Is
that all good? Is that all hunky dory then?
Is that all good then? Yeah.
So yeah, you got money. So is that good?
Is that all good?
Okay. So So what what's your point?
[ __ ] mad bastard, man.
[ __ ] [ __ ] in it. Yeah.
You're not out today drinking Fire Stick.
I piss in the sink, but I don't piss in bottles. Yeah.
I would have went on I would have come
on um uh I would have come on I would
have come on um
I couldn't um
I couldn't come um I wouldn't come on
YouTube today if I didn't lose that
football bet. Bro, you go straight back
to this toxic place. It's a toxic
sector. This is the toxic sector. Grezy. Yeah.
[ __ ] annoying, bro.
Sad sad times, bro.
No, just a football bet, lad.
Had to take some pills to calm me down, bro. Yeah.
No, I can't be bothered either, lad.
I'm just fed up, to be honest.
Yeah, proper fed up.
Maybe next month. I don't know, bro.
It's depressing, isn't it, bro?
I done a double both teams to score on
the teams to win and they were they both
ended in 1-1. Yep.
I'd even be happy to win like a 100
pound. This sounds crazy, bro, but I've
got money and stuff, so I I'm not
skilled. But even if I even if you win
like a £100 on top of what you've got,
150 on top of what what you've got, bro,
it'd be all right, you know?
Yeah. I I just wanted to go on the
street, bro, and just spit on someone.
Yeah, I know. It was only 20.
Even if you won like 150. Yeah,
bro. But like obviously cuz you still
got money and stuff. If you even if you
just won 150, bro, it would be good,
you know? You can't even win anything
anymore, bro. It's depressing, isn't it?
Yeah. If you won sometimes, it'd be
different. If you won sometimes, I
wouldn't mind losing.
I wouldn't mind losing.
I wouldn't mind losing, bro. If you won
sometimes and you lost, then I wouldn't
mind losing, bro. To be fair, if there
was a fighting chance of winning, I
wouldn't mind losing sometimes. As long
as you won sometimes, too. You know,
the odds have got really [ __ ] as well.
Yeah. 100 pound on a double. Both teams
to score returns 210. It's It's
finished, bro. betting on betting on two
teams and lumping on is finished.
£210 for [ __ ]
No, that is mad.
That is mad, bro.
Yeah. Got worse and worse and worse and
worse and worse. Even the both teams
just got no draws or [ __ ]
Mad it mad depressing, bro.
It's mad depressing, is it?
Do you think you're as bad as me, Fire
Stick? I don't think you're as bad as me.
I don't think you're as bad as me, bro. Yeah.
Yep. It feels like they're watching us
in it, bro. Because it does it does feel
that way, is it? Because how comes all
of a sudden, you know? Yeah.
I don't think you can win anymore, bro.
I really don't think you can. Oh man,
I don't think you can win anymore. Fire
stick. I generally don't think you can, bro.
I don't think you can, bro.
It's hard nowadays to win it. Yeah.
Yeah, pretty much.
Why did you used to watch TGF? Fire
stick. Did you watch You used to watch TGF.
I was watching some podcast
yesterday. He [ __ ] cemented a [ __ ]
microwave in the to his head, bro.
He cemented a [ __ ] microwave to his
head, bro. Almost died. That's mad, bro. [ __ ] that.
Oh, it's a YouTube channel, bro.
He cemented a microwave to his head.
TGF, bro. That's the channel. Sure people know.
It was for like a video. He almost died
in it. Oh, [ __ ] I couldn't even imagine
being in that position, bro.
[ __ ] that. [ __ ] that, bro. I couldn't
even I just think I would just die of a heart attack
of the thought of like suffocating in
it. [ __ ] that. Yeah,
you should try 500 pound on roulette.
Um, fire stick online.
You should try £500.
You should try 500 pound, bro. See if
you can win.
You should give it a try.
You should try Fire Stick, lad.
Why don't you try? You never know till you try.
You never know. Chill.
No, I'm cooking myself some steak today
with onion rings and mushrooms. No. Yeah.
Cost me £7.75.
So, I'll do that in a bit, I think. Yeah,
that's what they do in it. That's what
they do. These casinos, lad. Yeah,
later on. I will. I had a bacon and
cheese wrap earlier from Greg. It just come out.
No, I'm putting it under the grill.
I'm going to have to quit damning, I reckon.
Well, I've already basically given up. I
put 20 on the football. I'm just going
to have to stop doing it completely. Is it? Yeah,
I reckon so. Yeah.
Just can't win anymore, bro.
You just cannot win anymore.
Why? Why? Why? Why? Why?
Good old Frankie.
I would had more money, you know, if I
didn't [ __ ] gamble um last month
or if they just paid me my [ __ ] 150.
Know what I mean? Bastards.
How about 100 pound versus global draw roulette?
Is that a video you'd like to see? Fire stick.
Nah, bro. [ __ ] that. No, no,
no, man. I'm done with that [ __ ]
You're talking about yourself, Lad. You
don't have a woman. You don't have no
money. You don't have no friends. You're
talking about yourself, lad.
Oh, [ __ ] I got that wrong there, bro.
All you're doing is talking about
yourself, lad. Not me.
Which is what most of you 40year-old odd
projectors do on here. Only talking
about yourself, lad.
Or else you wouldn't be on here. Simple
as that. I mean, like I said, I told you
why I'm on here today.
I told you why I'm on here today. So, yeah.
Yeah, that's nice, bro. I believe it
when I see it.
Timmy Timmy's words means nothing, bro.
Timmy's word means nothing.
So, I was right about the uni thing
then, wasn't I, Greasy? I was right
about it, was I?
Yes, I [ __ ] was.
Yes, I [ __ ] was, man.
Yeah. What you're saying about that?
Like Shakur and a woman lose her bets.
You people are worse than anyone you're
talking about in this community.
These people from L J's channel, um,
Steven Hour, they're worse than anyone
they're talking about.
Anyone they try to talk about, they're
worse than that person.
Money, looks, whatever it is, they are
worse than anyone they're calling.
You understand, lad? There's a reason
why they're on here every day doing the
[ __ ] they do every day. You get me, lad?
So, you always need to bear that in mind
with these people.
You say, bro, did I? Oh yeah. Yeah.
Bless you then greasy if you get 200 if
you get 1,200 power a month. Bless Hey. Yeah,
but they say
they say if you lose money you can
afford to lose. It's okay. Steven Howard.
Yeah. They say if you if you lose money
you can afford to lose. It's okay.
don't know. Don't care.
He's irrelevant, bro.
You know, when you actually look at at
this community, bro, do you know the
thing that makes it funny, bro? Yeah.
Well, it's not funny. It's [ __ ]
is that you know you don't actually know these people.
You don't actually know any of these these people.
You know like people on lav the lavry
mongs, right? That sit every day and
talk about people that they don't know.
They literally don't know you. They
actually don't know you. They don't know
what you have.
But they but they talk about people that
they know them. It's so weird, lad.
So weird, bro. So weird.
They were trying to get LT to do me in
yesterday, bro. They were probably
wanking. They thought, "Oh, hit this is
going to be the day. This is going to be
the day." Knowing how obsessed these
jealous losers are. If you read the comments,
they thought it was their lucky day,
mate. Yeah, of course they're all
backwards. They're retards. The worst is
Timmy, bro. Like I said, I unsubscribe
to Timmy. I'm going to go back on the
channel Wednesday and then that's it.
I'm done. Even watching him, you lose brain cells.
If you watch these people long enough,
you lose brain cells, lad. Give it a
couple of days. Yeah.
Timmy pretends he's meeting people. He
never does. You argue with him. It's
just the same argument, bro. You get me?
Very, very disabled place. It really is,
bro. It really is. Oh yeah,
I'll stop, bro.
could have cooked my steak in a minute. Yeah,
cook my steak in a minute.
I'll prepare it in a minute, Robert. Yeah, man.
Yeah, that betting on a football is
[ __ ] depressing, is it? That
[ __ ] is not better than [ __ ] roulette.
That's not any better than roulette,
bro, if you think about it.
Doesn't matter if you don't do your
balls in the mood, your mood's still the
same, isn't it?
Oh yeah, bro.
I'll put on later. Later, bro.
Or some cans of Coke. Data.
What do you think of Reddit moderator Steven Howard? Yo. >> Yo.
>> Did you hear a football bat today?
>> No, I didn't. [ __ ] that.
>> Why not?
>> It's just long, isn't it? When they
lose, just it's just similar like you're
saying. It's just similar to roulette. I
know roulette you'd lose [ __ ]
quicker, but football bets. I know it's
only a little bit of money, but it's
still just [ __ ] long. And you've got
to go in and actually place the bets and
that as well. >> Yeah. >> Huh?
>> You're not doing football bits no more, are you?
>> No, I say that, but do you know what it
is? I only put 10 20 a week. So, I just
do it in it. Even though I say I don't,
I just end up doing it cuz what else is there?
>> It's still It's still frustrating
though, is it? When you get close to
like the other night, bro. It is
annoying. Like the other night when you
needed SL was it?
>> I needed I I should have just put 150 on
the global draw roulette today.
>> Why try it? Huh?
>> Why? Why? Roulet's horrible.
>> I can win it. Huh?
>> Roulette's horrible though, is it? I hate it.
>> Do you reckon I could have won on that
global draw if I played today? Nah.
>> No, probably not.
>> You probably would have lost in it.
>> Yeah, more than likely. It's [ __ ]
>> So, how can you win now? You literally
can't, is it?
>> No. You since they changed it to this
two pound spin bar thing, you can't win.
Not anymore. Not these days. You can't
win. And if you do get lucky or online, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Um I don't know. I don't play
online, but I imagine that's just the same. >> Yeah.
>> But in the bookings, even if you do win,
the very most you're winning is a grand.
Ain't like when you could win three or
four grand that ain't happening no more.
>> Nah. And when I win, I'm trying to win.
I don't know about you, but I'd want to
win life changing money.
>> Yeah, we all want that. Do it just don't happen.
>> You know what I'm saying? There's no
Because then that then I would, like I
said, if you won 50, 60 grand, I would
quill it forever, bro. Until I down to
my last like 10k, maybe. Then I'd try
again in it.
>> Yeah, I'd probably do the same to be
fair. I'd make sure that like I'd all
like I' I'd start my own business and
[ __ ] bro. Like I I wouldn't just lose
it all. You get me? You get me?
>> Yeah. You would invest it?
>> Yeah. Something like that. That's what
I'm saying. Yeah.
>> What steak did you get?
>> Nice. Where from?
>> You like the ribeye in it? M&S.
>> I like all of them. How long do you cook
it for? How when you go to a restaurant,
how do you have it?
>> Oh, bro. Every time I go to the
restaurant. Yeah. I tell them I have it
and they've got to change it like two or
three times. I like it pink a little bit
pink but no blood.
>> Yeah, I've had that when they bring it
out. Have you ever What? You've gone up
three times and said this is [ __ ]
>> Like to Normally it's two times. I say
that I want it bloody but no. I said I
want it pink but no blood. I don't want
blood on it.
>> Yeah. What? You've had to tell him three
times. That's still not how I want it. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. That's annoying, isn't it?
>> If you could win the bookies would be
out of business. Simple. Yeah.
Obviously, but you would think that you
could still win. You know what I'm
saying? Like, you get what I mean?
Shortterm. Obviously, long term, you
won't win. But
>> even when the bookmakers online or in
the shop pay out a massive humongous win
every now and again, you see in like the
local newspaper, somebody won 70 grand
on a really rare bet, that's nothing to them. >> Yeah.
>> That's [ __ ] all them. And you never see
you never see a port book makers.
>> You reckon you reckon if you won you
reckon if you won Yeah. 200 grand in the
casino. They they'd um they'd pay you
out in cash. Nah,
>> I ain't got a clue, mate.
>> I think I think the max would be like 50
60 grand in it.
>> Yeah, they might have to give you so
much in cash
>> or something. Yeah, I think they'd give
you 60 grand in cash, though.
>> And the rest thingy. >> Yeah.
>> You know, PJ, you know that Indian that
you posted yesterday? Yeah.
>> That start that you had that chicken
taker. Oh my god, that looks so nice.
>> It was banging, bro. It was banging.
>> How much was that just for the starter?
That was £2250 in it.
>> No, probably like£6 something £7. No,
it's not that much for a starter, bro.
If it's a main, it is. It's a starter,
not a main, is it? So,
>> I know, but it looks quite big.
>> Yeah, I don't even I don't even cut it.
I just stick in my mouth, bro. I don't
know about you.
>> Well, you just You don't chew it. You
just swallow it. No, I chew it, but I
don't cut it like in in half to get it.
>> Yeah, you just put the whole chunk in.
>> I hate that. Don't you hate that when
you're in a restaurant, you look over
and there's a man there with his wife or
his girlfriend and he's like eating all
day gay and that like trying to eat all
tiny bits and
>> Yeah. [ __ ] That's why I don't go on
dates to Nandos, bro. Cuz I will finish
it off with my hands and I I know what
I'm like. You have to finish off chicken
with your hands if it's boned in it. You have to.
>> Yeah. It's messy. Messy, isn't it?
>> Yeah. So, that's why I try to avoid like
You know what I mean? Whereas if you
have like an Indian, you don't need to
eat with your hands in it. >> Yeah.
>> Or like a steak, you don't need to eat
with your hands. Unless it's a T-Bo,
then you have to finish it with
>> I was so pleased yesterday that you got
like pillow rice. Yeah. Not that weird
what Timmy was telling you to get. What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Where was Timmy's takeaway?
>> Oh, he's I don't know. He said he was on
a poster, isn't it? He said he was at
his mom's. Yeah. So he couldn't he
couldn't come up on your panel last
night and all that, but then he was on
um you know [ __ ] uh Shauny 97.
>> He he was on his channel last night. >> Really?
>> That's Sha9. Is that is that non Is that
how you call nons?
>> No, that's another one.
>> Oh, do you get on with that sh listen
when you get paid your money again? I
reckon when you get paid again, I reckon
you're going to gamble when you get paid again.
>> Hopefully not. I've got money now.
>> You you
>> No, I've got money now. I just I don't
want to. It makes put makes me feel
[ __ ] [ __ ] when I lose. I don't like
it. So, I'd rather stay away from them.
>> You're like me in it. >> Yeah.
>> Are you worse or what you think?
>> I don't know. When I lose hundreds of pounds,
>> I think so. It
>> When I lose hundreds of pounds, it just
[ __ ] makes me feel like [ __ ] And
then all I want to do is just lay in bed
for days watching.
>> Even me, it doesn't matter the money.
Like if I lost £500 on roulette today,
>> I would have just been the same.
>> That's mad to say to be fair.
>> I wouldn't have been any different than the 20.
>> Would you not?
>> Not really.
>> Why? It's a big difference though, is it?
>> It's a big diff. But that's what I'm
trying to say to you. It's not about the
money. This is what I mean.
>> That's what I said earlier. It's not the
money. It's just the principle, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> It depend. It also depends like like if
you was up or if you wasn't up or if you
won recently. It all dep all these
things like factor into like how how you
will feel if you lose. You get me?
>> Well, did you just want to [ __ ] kill yourself earlier?
>> No, just like stay in bed and just not
do anything. I'll just go and beat someone up.
>> When I lose, that's what I want to do.
Just stay in bed. You just want to go.
>> Have you ever been on a night out yet
and you've lost and you just want to go back home?
>> What happened? I heard someone saying
yesterday in the chat. Yeah. What
happened with you and this bird in the
casino? Did you leave a bird and go to the casino?
>> You know, I ditched her in the casino
cuz I lost.
>> Yeah. What? Tell me what happened. You funny [ __ ]
>> No, I just lost 150 and I was going mad
and I wanted to like beat the manager
up. Like I wanted to throw the glass
over his head and that in it. I just I
just left in the end. I just walked I
just ditched her. She said, "What the
fuck?" But then I went back in it. She's
like, "What the fuck?" So I I was I was
three stops away and then I come back and it
What' she say?
>> I felt bad in it. I felt bad in it.
>> You blocked her in it. I know you
blocked her, man.
>> No, I went back there.
>> I went back to see that in it.
>> Yeah. You reckon you [ __ ] that one up in it?
>> Bro, this is what I'm saying. It doesn't
matter what position you are in life.
Money, no money, woman, no woman. You're
always going to feel the same. This is
what I'm saying with gambling. It doesn't matter.
>> Bro, you need to go to Thailand, bro.
Yeah, cuz it's [ __ ]
>> But do you get what I'm saying though?
But do you get what I mean though?
>> Well, you're just what you saying that
you're never ever happy.
>> Yeah. No, like you'll always No, no.
What I'm saying is like you'll always
feel the same if you lose gambling.
Doesn't matter what position you're in.
>> Yeah. Of course it's going to feel the
same. It's horrible.
>> Doesn't matter if you get more money. If
you got It doesn't matter if you have no
money, you got more money, you get more
money, you get less money. It doesn't
matter, bro. It's always going to be
that same feeling. You get it? When Tim
come on that Sean's panel last night, I
think Dusty was Dusty Showiz was in
there as well. I see him in the chat. He
was joining, but he was whispering. He
was saying he was at his mom's and that.
>> When you need to try to imagine the
happiness you bring to But you know
what? Yeah, I I got one over them
casinos. When I used to go to landbased
casinos, I won more than I ever gave
them. I know that for a fact.
>> Do you reckon?
>> 100%, bro. I took him to the cleaners,
bro. Every week. Well, we say the
cleaners. It's not the cleanest to them cuz >> PJ
>> PJ, have you ever actually said to
anybody in the bookies or in a casino
any of the staff once you've lost Yeah.
when you've been so angry, even if you
didn't mean it, have you ever actually
looked at any of the staff face to face
and said, "I'm going to smash you up in it."
>> No, I've just lassed out at them. But I
don't think I've said I'm going to [ __ ]
you. No, I don't think so.
>> Don't the security in the [ __ ] casino
beat you up?
>> Oh, no. They don't beat you up. They
just tried to calm stuff down and like
they don't know. >> Yeah.
>> No, they wouldn't do that, bro. Unless
you like started like fighting them or
you know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> They come straight over though. As soon
as you're a bit loud, as soon as you're
a bit loud, they come straight over.
>> Who did you say that guy was who called
the casino like telling them bare [ __ ]
about you, saying that you're going to
kill their kids and that? Who? Who was
that? Whose voice was that?
>> That voice
of reason. Is that him?
>> M saying
>> we should we should meet up today. Me and you.
>> No, I can't bo to go out. Not today.
>> We going for a fist off in it.
>> Why are you going out today? I can't be bothered.
>> No, only Only if you want it in it.
>> I can't to go out. He when he rang up
that casino, he said to them, "Oh, Peter
said he's going to kill and rape."
>> I went into that arcade today that he
said I was banned from. Do you remember
he said I'm banned from the arcade? I
went in it today. I thought you was I
thought you was banned for life.
>> I don't know, bro. But I went into No, I
went into the arcade, you know, with the
grabbing machines, the amusements. I
went there today. Nothing.
>> I heard that I heard that you was bred
from there for life.
>> No, I went in there today.
>> Well, they never chucked you out. >> Nope.
>> Cuz don't forget, bro, they they
probably forgot after a while. They send
you stuff. They're not seeing you. They
don't know you. So after a while, that
you know what I mean? >> Yeah.
Yeah, it's fine.
>> Are you ordering this screen mask
regardless of what you said you was
going to do with it? Yeah, you should
just get it. That's good film merch.
That's good movie merchandise. Yeah, you
should get that [ __ ]
>> Should I do it and make a make a scream
eight on this community in it and just
do madness with the mask.
>> Just made me laugh when you said you'll
put the mask on and record it and slap someone
>> and start and start calling them saying
I remember you in it. Yeah, with the mask. Yeah.
What do you think, Grezy? Should we make
a Should we make a scream eight on this
community and start calling people out
with a mask?
>> Greavvesy, yes or no? Shall they order
the mask? Shall they order the mask or
not off of Amazon?
Delivery. You can get a mask and a
>> You ain't watch You ain't watched the
news yet, have you?
>> No, I haven't. Is it any good?
>> Yeah, man. It's good, bro.
>> You told me you couldn't stop thinking
about some of the violent scenes. That's
what you said.
>> It was [ __ ] Yeah, some of it was [ __ ]
up to be fair, bro. Was you thinking
about walking out when you was in there?
>> No, obviously not. No, obviously not.
>> I don't know.
>> Some people can't deal with blood in it. >> Huh?
>> Some people can't deal with blood and that.
>> Yeah. Know, it weren't the blood. It was
just the way they were being killed.
>> Yeah. Even Grezy said order it.
>> Yeah. There was one bit. Yeah. You know,
you know the play, bro. Yeah. You know,
like a play, like a theater play when
someone's in the air where they where
they put them in the air on strings. >> Yeah.
>> Basically, the scream um took over and
as she was going back and forth, he was
just like slashing it with a knife.
Slash, splash, slash, bro. It's [ __ ]
up, bro. [ __ ] hell. You You need to
watch it, bro. You You need to watch it.
I see that new Jason Stathithm film in
the cinema like two weeks ago. It was [ __ ] crap.
Did you did you do do you get popcorn
and coke at the cinema?
>> Um sometimes [ __ ] bear deer in the
cinema though. Is it when you buy the [ __ ] there?
>> Yeah, I always buy the popcorn and
picking mix there ain't it?
>> Yeah, I normally get one of them ice
blast things. Yeah, but they're [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I used to love them in the summer,
bro. The tango ice blast in it.
>> Yeah, but now they never had the tango
machine. They have some shitty copy one
and they're sugarfree now, so they just taste crap.
>> Oh gosh, that's not good.
That's what you need to have. You got Amazon Prime.
>> Yeah, bro.
>> Order a screen mask.
>> Okay, I will. I will. I will.
>> Trust me, they're not even I'm looking.
I'm looking right now. They're not even expensive. >> Yeah.
>> I just I want you to get one in it cuz I
I know for a fact that you'll do videos
with the mask on and I know you'll go on
camera with the mask on. Well, and try
and try and meet people that is it.
>> Yeah. Don't laugh on that. Just casually
be like, "Yo, what you up to? What are you saying?
>> Would that be okay with you, Greasy Boss?"
>> Oh, [ __ ] One sec, bro. Need to get out,
man. Need to do my steak in a bit, bro.
I'm hungry. Are you hungry?
>> No, I've already eaten. What did you eat, Captain?
>> No, I got kebab in it.
>> Yeah. Which one?
>> Lambish. Was right. Lamb. That's the
best one. That's the best one, bro.
>> Got a lamb shish with garlic and chili
sauce. And I got a cheesy chips and
couple of extra p breads. It was actually quite
>> You know, you know what I get? Do you
know what I get with this [ __ ] I always
get a mix because I like them both and I
can't decide. So, I just get chicken and
lamb. [ __ ] it,
>> chicken. That's a combination of two.
It's well known. I don't know how people
eat that lamb dollar. It's so greasy, isn't it?
>> Yeah. That is bad. That [ __ ] If you if
you have a lamb. Yeah. If you look at in
the in the morning, look in the bin.
Yeah. Look in the corner of the packet
that it comes in. Yeah, there's a big
puddle of white fat. >> Yeah,
>> the chicken one is all No, but you know,
I like that chicken chicken tickon is is
nice, but it's very very hard to get.
It's so nice.
>> What's it called?
>> It's called chicken tickadona, but I've
only had I've only ever seen it in
Wales. When I went to Wales, I can't
find it. So, there's lamb. So, there's
lamb. There's lamb. There's chicken. But
this one was lamb chicken. And then
there was a chicken ticker and I got the
chicken ticker one. You got it.
>> [ __ ] hell. I've never heard of that.
Is it any good?
>> I You can't get it in London. I looked.
I looked cuz I really fancied it in it,
but I couldn't find it.
>> Yeah. Oh, yeah. I've never even heard of that.
>> You know, I had it in Cardiff in it when
I went in Cardiff.
>> How much was your hotel in Cardiff?
>> They were all different, bro. I've been
there a few times.
>> Is it really expensive?
>> Nah, like 100 maybe.
>> Yeah, that ain't too bad.
>> The most I've ever paid was 170 in
leads. That was expensive, right?
>> Yeah, that's too much. You get two
nights for that. >> Yeah.
>> Oh. Oh gosh. Fire stick. Oh gosh.
>> Do you reckon he's going to come?
>> I need [ __ ] He's going to come on. Do
you reckon he's going to come Wednesday?
I don't think he will, bro.
[ __ ] Willy monkeys. [ __ ] man.
Apparently, now he's saying, Yeah, now
he's saying that he's not going to do
any videos or anything on the way. He's
just going to go bang and surprise you.
That's what he said he's doing. Bro,
>> it's always you know, is it the Be
honest yet? Is it the same argument
every day, isn't it?
>> Yeah, it gets boring, man.
>> Well, how like even like with Do you
know when Monty and Timmy used to go
out? Yeah. Was that the same argument?
>> Yeah, of course. Just the same [ __ ] for years.
>> It's the same argument every day. Yeah.
But you know Mr. B, he writes the same
comments every day as well. Is it that Mr. B? >> Yeah,
it's the same. That's why I think you
stopped coming on it for a bit, is it?
Cuz it's the same repeating people now.
>> Um, it does get boring, but it does get
boring. But at the same time, this
community is funny. Otherwise, we all
people say, "Oh, yeah, it's this, it's
that." But it is funny at the same time. That's why
>> you see my video. Did you see my video
to Rick's mates?
>> No, it's in it.
>> You didn't see it? I don't I don't know
how to use a washing machine. You did see it.
>> Oh, yeah. I see that. Yeah, I did see
>> Yeah, I was laughing. No, I did see that one. Yeah.
>> Do you know how to use a washing machine?
>> Yeah, of course.
>> That's how that is, man. How can you be
38 yet washing machine?
>> He's back in He's back in hospital, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, he's in hospital. I'll show you my
steak, lad. I'll show you my steak, lad.
>> Yeah. Show it. One set, brother.
>> How much was it?
>> £7, bro. From M&S.
>> You should have got two. >> Huh?
>> Yeah, true, bro.
>> Why are you having
>> I'm going to have it with mushroom and onion rings.
>> Yeah, nice. I do like onion rings.
They're [ __ ] nice, isn't it?
>> Yeah, they are nice.
my favorite t-bone steak. But obviously
I didn't go to the butcher, didn't it?
There's not a butcher uh near me anymore
that serves it.
>> You told me you pay like 12 or 13 quid
for them in it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. But it's not I don't get it
often, is it? >> Why?
>> Um cuz I have to really fancy it, bro.
Like a nice t- it Well, if I go gym, I
would, I guess. But
>> wait, you live you live with like your
mom and your family and that, don't you? Yeah.
>> No, just my mom.
>> Oh, just your mom. I thought you had
like brother or sister from here.
>> I live on my own. I got my own place.
But you know what? The reason I'm asking
is Yeah. What you know every day like do
you never have the same dinner as your
mom? Like does your mom never say to
you, "Oh, I'm making so and so. Do you want some?"
>> You know, occasion sometimes maybe like
three times out of like the week, but
not us. How do you have your How do you
have your own place then?
>> Well, you just Well, so you just [ __ ]
What? Most of the time you just make
your own thing.
I just I normally just get takeaways
actually like like£10 takeaways to be fair.
You get me? Oh,
I need to make these mushrooms. I need
to flash these mushrooms. So,
Grezy, I was on um a shovel coin
yesterday. sorry earlier and they were
saying she's hot. She's hot. And then
there was people saying, "Oh, she's
average." And then they were getting
[ __ ] for it.
They were getting [ __ ] for it, bro. They
were getting absolute [ __ ] for it, lad.
Yeah. I said, "You little copycats."
Yeah, little copycats.
What are they, Grezy? Are they little copycats?
Are they little copycats? Squeezed.
Are they little copycats, Leslie? Oh,
she's hot. She's hot. She's hot. She's
They were saying she's hot and [ __ ]
Leslie, I'll [ __ ] chase you. You little copycats.
They're copycats, man.
Right. I don't think I can put all of
these mushrooms. I'm going to have to ask ladies. Mom,
uh, I'm only Sorry. Sorry I scared you.
I'm going to have half the mushrooms now
because there's so many. What do I do
with the other half?
Yeah. Are you right? I scared I scare you.
I'm not gay.
I'm not going to be gay. That's what
you're saying, bro. You're a weird creature.
I'm not [ __ ] gay.
Stop saying I'm gay. I'm not [ __ ] Attractive. attractive.
>> Oh, do we have lemon? Please tell me we got lemon.
Miles of jackary. Yeah,
there's no bloody lemon, lady. Oh, there is.
Yeah, there is lemon chery.
Miles and Jackie. Oh, bless Jackery.
Right, I'm going to show you. One second, lads.
[ __ ] hate cooking, bro. What is the date, [ __ ]
It's opened. Let me ask lady.
This level's not going to be any good. How long?
Are you sure? He said,
"What the damian?" Yeah.
Put some pepper, some salt, some lemon.
There we go, man.
And then obviously we're going have to
put the onion rings on as well. [ __ ] multi.
I need to focus. One second, lad. No,
she isn't. But I am.
You can if you want.
Why you put it there?
You can if you want. I want to be there.
You can if you like. One second.
You said she's hot.
He said that she's hot.
He's a little cat with no mind of his own.
With no mind with no mind of his own.
Why? Why are all of these people in the
comments saying that she'd hot?
Leslie, why are they all saying that she'd hot?
They were all saying that she's hot and [ __ ]
I'm preparing this. One sec.
Going to take a while to cook. I'm multitasking.
Why are they saying that? Yeah, most of
the butter is going on the mushrooms.
You need quite a lot of butter for
mushrooms, you see. Why were they saying that attractive?
Oh [ __ ] It's [ __ ] gold.
Yeah, at least I put some more pepper.
But black pepper, salt, lemon. Yeah.
>> What's wrong with you, boy? Sick. What's happening? Where it's
Why is the oven on? What's that?
One second, please.
>> Yeah, it's not working, is it?
It's cut up, isn't it?
>> It's not working properly, is it?
Something wrong with it, mate.
What's wrong with it?
What is it? What's wrong with it?
>> Yeah. Go on.
Is that what you got to do now?
Would I put on seven? Yeah. >> Yeah. Yeah,
they take like 20 minutes, don't they? I
know they tend to pop out on you means it. >> Yeah,
I'm crooked now.
>> Yeah, I'm I I am
I was talking to someone. Huh?
And I was speaking to someone lane.
Yeah. Most of the butter is for the
mushroom, isn't it? Yeah. We're cooking. Okay. So,
this one doesn't even turn on, bro. We
need a We need a new cooker by
another year. Yeah, we're going to need
a new cooker.
I reckon in another year, mate, we'll
need a new cooker.
No, I'm not posting the link for this
[ __ ] I'll see him on Wednesday.
He's just trying to get attention on my
channel. [ __ ] him. There's
I'll give you
I'll give you a power.
Oh, I'll give you a bowl of steak.
You need your vitamins.
I have one piece of quiet as well. And I
want some vitamins in my tummy.
I need I'm topping up on my vitamins.
Turn it over
to the side now. Sorry that's not
Oh, this dude is going to be nice. But
we add some more bottom above I'm okay. Oh, right.
Oh man, I scared a lot. Oh [ __ ]
bro. I got the Look, I got the mushrooms. Yeah. Oh, steak.
Steak cooking. I got the onion rings
cooking a lot. One second. That's not
high. Is it multi?
That's enough. You
need quite a bit of butter when you're
doing mushroom as you see, bro.
May need the mushrooms that need
the most butter. It's mushrooms in it.
It needs a
[ __ ] got hardly any butter left.
[ __ ] virgin [ __ ]
Yeah, I know, bro. I got enough butter.
There's enough butter, bro.
Look, there's enough.
Trust me. I'll put some more there, too.
Oh, you sick of it. Getting you down. Bless you.
Oh, you there. A
is it getting you down?
Keep adding more mushrooms in it.
That's enough anyways. Yeah.
I'm going to do you a little play
whether you like it or not. Yeah,
I wash it up. I wash up that wash up version.
They can go back.
They can go back in these rings again.
You only have to turn them over on. Yeah. One twist.
I'm going to do a roll.
I'm going to cut I'm going to cut Laney
some steak now. She likes it quite
bloody. I don't
cut the lady a nice bit.
I don't like mine steak, but I don't like mine.
One second, bro.
I like mine. I don't like mine. Bloody.
She does. So, put her some down.
One piece here.
Kind of feel like a penis. You come to
I don't like air fires, lad.
Yeah, I I left it bloody for Laney.
That's how Laney likes it.
I have it medium well done. I don't like blood.
I don't like blood on a steak. Yeah,
that's the baby.
Snake will be done soon.
I like it a little bit pink, but I don't
like it bloody, lad.
You get me?
Right. And it's annoying. The only
annoying thing with this is the onion rings.
The onion rooms are annoying, bro. Do anything.
Oh, you dirty bastard.
Hurt me, man.
I don't know if they
always [ __ ] everything up. They take long.
Two seconds. I need to concentrate here. Oh, [ __ ] They said
first time doing any business Sorry, bro.
One second, bro.
We're going to need the We need a
mushroom. We need to move the mushrooms now.
Not me, lad. I need cook quick.
They need you, but they don't.
>> Oh yeah.
I'm making the bulb a little lame lane.
I don't like it bloody.
I like my snake bloody, bro.
Yeah, there was I was on a show call
with and they were saying that she was hot again.
They were saying hottest woman in the
world or something.
What's your opinion on that?
What's your opinion on that greeting?
A little copycat almost done.
I don't think the onion loses
they take the longest
one more time on this day. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, he can come with him Wednesday.
I'll [ __ ] him both up. Simple as that.
Oh, I didn't shut that [ __ ] I didn't
shut the [ __ ] oven, bro. Oh,
let me try a bit of that smoke here.
Not bloody, is it?
That's the business, boy.
That is the business.
Stink will be ready in a minute.
Okay, these can't be ones, but they're
the best thing, you know,
and they should be ready. that I need wins.
>> I think it's done.
>> Yeah, I think it's done, man. Yeah. Two seconds. No.
No. It's just not that.
for this article. Yeah.
I'm such a double on this.
Maybe they're not. Maybe they are.
There they are.
One second, bro.
>> Yeah, that's on the flyer. I used to
have a fire at the old house.
There we go. Let's try them.
that one lady greedy.
No, they're fine, ma'am. They're fine. There's
That's how I like my steak. Look
red. Kind of red but no blood.
Red but no blood. You see,
that's how I like my steak, bro. I like
it like a bit red but no blood like
similar to this.
That's how I like it. Um,
it's better than USA's boobies. Yummy. M
I want to take it No.
Why did I watch them [ __ ]
All right. Bet. Why was people saying that
go was hot? Was they saying it to fit in?
But I decided to fit in that.
No, people used to say that if you don't
find her attractive, you're gay.
Must be must be focusing. Um 7.5. Yeah,
I have enough stuff. I'm eating enough.
I just put a lot of steak in my mouth.
I are so nice on a on a on a fryer. I
used to have a fryer, bro. I used to do
chips on it. Chips for pork chops.
My Muslim tenants used to hate me. Mhm.
They were saying that she was the best
Muslim woman in the world.
Tell me that's not copying.
Tell me that's not copying that.
Yeah, it has. Mhm. Finished. Hey, mama.
How was your food, mama?
You didn't like it.
What was your favorite bit?
You like the steak? I cut it up before I
finished mine cuz I knew you'd like
yours less done, mama.
That's all right, ma.
Was it just how you like the steak?
I put some black pepper and lemon and stuff. >> Yeah.
So yeah, Greasy, why would they say that
she's the why would they say that she's
the best looking woman in the world?
They used to make comments and stuff. Um
I don't know, man.
All different types of restaurant. Nando
usually. Usually if you have Nando, you
just go straight through you.
Usually nine does. Yeah.
Yeah. Just trying to fit in.
just trying to fit in
cuz people that wouldn't want to fit in
they would just say average.
Is that right? I like oh what do you
think of her then like average? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I have had food poisoning. Well, I
told you we last spoke two times. Yeah,
I have had food poisoning. Both times it
was from Dixie Chicken.
Yeah, I have had food poisoning.
From Dixie Chicken, lad. We darling.
I'm making a cup of [ __ ]
I wanted a cup of [ __ ] in the morning then.
Crazy. But there was no sugar.
There was no sugar. So I didn't I didn't
have one until I bought sugar.
Wow, that was nice. Whenever I eat a big
meal, I always fancy a cup of tea after it.
God knows why, but I always do, bro.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
That was nice, bro.
I need to get some more vitamins tomorrow.
Yeah, I pissed out the window. I used to
piss on the floor eight years ago. You
know when there was carpet I used to
just piss on the floor.
Yeah, I used to piss on the floor
and then it started stinking a piss so I
stopped doing it. So yeah. Yeah.
I love peeing.
I love waking up and having to pee. It's
like an obsession. You know when you
need to pee?
You know when you just need to pee? Have
you ever peed before having sex?
I've actually peed before before getting
a [ __ ] Greavesy.
About to go in. I had to pee. That's funny. Oh gosh.
We Oh gosh.
This was years ago.
It was years and years ago. We got some sweets here. attractive.
So what you're basically saying, Groovy.
So what you're basically saying is no
sex is a big fat stinking copycat.
Is that what you're trying to say? Yeah. 15 [ __ ]
Oh, we cracked him. We cracked him.
trying to make me feel [ __ ] about
myself, Grezy, because I didn't want to
fit in with the crowd.
He tried to make me feel [ __ ] about myself, Grezy.
He tried making me feel bad and make me
feel like I was gay and stuff. He tried
making me feel [ __ ] dusty,
cuz I didn't want to fit in. Wanted to
do my own thing.
That's not good, is it?
trying to make me question my sexuality
or cuz I don't follow trends.
Get me now.
I think you're a troll fire stick. I
think you're an undercover troll lad.
Fukum, you love that. You're skinnier
than a [ __ ] skin flim.
Skinner than a [ __ ] skin flim.
What do you think of that, Briy? Skint fing.
So, what's the chance I would go out
today drinking greed and not even get a
number? Is that possible? No. No.
No. That's not possible, lad.
You go to central London drinking. Of
course you you will get someone's number. Yeah.
You just wouldn't get a date.
You would find you you would
But I don't need to do that. Do I agree
with you? Why is that?
Because I already found my mama. No.
No. It's not a high chance. There's no
way I can go out and not get a number,
bro. It's impossible.
It's not possible, bro. It's never
happened before. Ever.
That's never happened.
It'll never happen. No.
Do you remember?
Sig not Peter Belly's mama.
Sign not Peter Belly's mama.
I love these little sayings. Yeah.
God bless. Right. What's the latest on Instagram?
Yeah. But Reddit says it's me though, Leslie.
Reddit says that it's me and they ignore
my little evidence pack.
They say it's me and then they ignore my
little evidence pack. Leslie. A
I just had my lovely steak.
I just had mine. Oh, I had to wipe the
camera. Oh god, I'm starting to look a
bit like Waggy. I might have to go to
the barbers or something cuz I'm
starting to look like Waggy.
You know the troll Waggy. Oh gosh.
That went down the right hole, man. Oh gosh. Oh gosh,
drinking a nice can of Coke.
You didn't answer me, Leslie. If it's
not me, why do people on Reddit say it's
me then? Why does Nons say it's me and stuff?
Yeah, bro. When you show your face, I'll
get on the scales, lad.
Self projecting, bro. You people are obese.
You're not going to self-reflect your
life and make me feel like you fat ugly
people, lad. You're pointless even
wasting your time. You people don't show
your faces cuz you're fat and ugly and
you can't prove me wrong.
I'm not being funny, but most of you
people in this community are fat and
ugly. That's why you don't show your
faces. Um, and you know I'm right as
well. So anyways, why don't anyone why
doesn't anyone say any why does Reddit
say about it being me then? Nesly,
I can't think of one thing that anyone
on this community says that isn't self-
projecting. Skin, they're skin. Ugly,
they're ugly. Fat, they're obese. I
swear down five stick. I can't think of
one thing these people say that isn't
about their own ugly lives. I can't
think of one thing in the whole of 10
years that any of these people have said
that's never been about their own vibes.
That is mad, bro.
They're fat. They're ugly. They're
miserable. They're lonely. And they try
and talk about [ __ ] me. People that
are better than them. These 40y old
spastics little losers.
That's why we call it a disabled sector, right?
Oh, these people are so fat they
probably can't even leave their house, lad.
They're fat. They're ugly as [ __ ] That's why
That's why um
That's why they uh
that's why um Yeah, basically
most of these people in this community
have been bullied, bro.
Most of the people in this community
that go on like L's and that, they've been bullied
every day. They've been bullied. So
that's why they're on here. Be there.
Just bully victims.
They're just bully victims, lad.
Oh, I'm under the blanket now.
I'm under the electric blanket now.
Greasy. Oh gosh.
There's a reason only 5% of the people
in this community show their faces.
There's a reason for that, Leslie.
Never forget. There's always a reason for that.
These people on this community are ugly as [ __ ]
That's why they come here and try to
talk about other people's looks and
other people's this and other people's
that, cuz they're ugly as [ __ ] They got
nothing better to do, bro.
What life could the Lavy Mongs possibly
have if they're on here from the time
they wake up to the time they go to bed?
What life could they possibly have? Ask
yourself this question.
What life could they possibly have on
YouTube all day, every day? Ask Ask it,
bro. Ask Ask yourself Ask yourself the question, man. Hey. Hey. B
still. Is Timmy still pretending he's
going to fight people?
Is he still pretending that he's going
to fight people?
Oh yeah, Timmy's just done a video. I've
just clicked on his channel. Let me see. One second.
He's not going nowhere.
Oh, what did he say? He's coming with
Mike. I told you he always needs backup.
I told you this, bro. Every I told you
this, bro. I told you this. If he ever
comes, right, if Timmy if there's a if
there's a very small percent chance
Timmy would ever come, he will come with
backup. I told you he does this, bro.
He's so predictable. Didn't I say all of
this, bro? Didn't I not tell you all of
this? It's the same with the [ __ ]
acting hard on YouTube when he's not
hard. He's just some fat [ __ ] trying
to act the big man on YouTube. And then
crunch [ __ ] comes to crunch then he
doesn't meet anyone. He will never meet
anyone or he'll turn up with backup.
It's the same thing with him bro. Every
time it's the same thing with this [ __ ]
all night. Mike, are you still doing
this? [ __ ] hell.
You know, you know these people in here
have been doing this for years. You know
that Fire Stick,
they're just proper proper bully victim
wasters. That's the only thing I can say
about these people.
These people have really been bullied in
their life, lad.
Right. Let me see.
Right. One second, bro. I'm listening to this [ __ ]
Well, I'm just listening to this video, lads.
Timmy's calling me a m when I'm
literally 100 times better looking than him. Madness.
Now he's already making excuses.
This Timmy is a proper proper [ __ ]
This is why I'm subscribed from him,
bro. He's a [ __ ] proper [ __ ]
How How is this ugly man with four eyes
calling me a M?
And this is what the most of them are.
Even though Timmy like shows their
faces, they're ugly. They're ugly old
men calling people that are better than
them in life tragic. That's the
definition of tragedy, bro. Anyways,
I'm just listening to this Timmy's
video. gives it.
Oh, he's not going anywhere. Is he still
doing? You know, all of this like trying
to act the big man, Grezy. Yeah. Yeah.
It It's all for attention. You do
realize this. No, like you do realize
this is all for attention. I was
listening to this uh yesterday before I
went to sleep when he was going at Timmy
when he was going at Timmy uh when he
was going at Bonty for like 20 30
minutes straight like old videos. And
just look at this guy, bro. He's a
[ __ ] [ __ ] He's not a hard man. I
don't know why [ __ ] on YouTube is
trying to act like a hard man. It's
embarrassing, you know? He's literally a
[ __ ] bro. And he's trying to act
like a hard man. I'm just on his video
now. He's a [ __ ]
Your brother's saying it's not worth it.
Bro, all you're trying to do is look
good for YouTube and you're going to get
seriously seriously hurt. Seriously,
bro. He's going to get seriously
seriously seriously seriously hurt. He
doesn't understand, bro. He will. He
will get seriously hurt, bro. Trust me.
His brother said this. He's What the
[ __ ] is this guy talking about? He's
going to get himself seriously seriously injured, bro.
Seriously, if he knocks on the door or
rings a doorbell, he's going to get
injured, bro. Trust me. You better tell
him that, Mr. B. You better tell him that.
But that'll probably teach him a lesson,
to be honest. Stop trying to look good
for YouTube. Stop trying to show off for
YouTube. Simple as that, is it?
He says, "I'll never have friends. I'll
never have a close family." The guy
doesn't even know me, Mr. I mean, the
guy literally doesn't even know anything
about me, bro. What I do every day, who
I'm friends with, who my who are my enemies.
He literally doesn't even know me, bro.
And he and he's talking about me,
someone that's better than him. This is
what 90% of the people on here do, bro.
You get me, bro? This is what 90% of
these people do. They talk about people
that they don't know that's better than them.
It's true, though, isn't it, bro? Yeah.
Everyone knows I'm You don't know me.
You don't know how much money people
have. See, this is all self-projecting.
When you're watching these people,
right? It's the same thing as these
Lavry Mongs, Timmy. They're all self-projecting.
Ugly fat people. Timmy, all the rest of
them, bro. They're all They're all the
same on here. Yeah.
Nice. Oh yeah. Apparently he's coming
with Money Mike on uh Wednesday. Dusty
chicken madress. I think lamb tastes
better than the chicken.
Don't know about you. I think lamb
tastes better than chicken. Oh,
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Why does he do all of this? Why does he
go on like he's some kind of hard man, bro?
When he's just a [ __ ] Why? Why does
someone that's disabled, that's never
won a fight, still keep going on like
they're bad every day on YouTube?
I've never come across more of a
disabled person than Timmy.
So if Timmy comes right and there's a fight, Grezy,
Monty's not going to see it, is he?
Yeah. Yeah. Monty's not going to see it
though, is it? I don't think so.
Yeah, exactly. He does it every time,
bro. He deflects. So, I hope he does
come cuz I'll knock him out and I'll
knock Money Mike out as well. I want him
as well, bro. He's he he was trolling me
on YouTube on Nons's um thing. So, yeah.
Bring who you like, bro. No one's scared
of the Birmingham the Birmingham
waistman crew. They're soft as [ __ ]
bro. Trust me, they're they're soft. Proper soft.
You wouldn't even need a weapon. Even if
it was like threeon-one, they're [ __ ]
He does it all the time. or or Dusty. He
does it when he does his balls in as
well. When he does his balls in cuz he's
ugly and I'm better looking than him.
Timmy's Timmy's a jealous individual
just like his non-slegs boyfriend who
thinks that he's got money when he
doesn't. Um he does he does this every
time. He does it when he does his balls
in as well. When he does his balls in
Dusty, he also reflects onto me cuz he
knows I'm better looking than him. I got
more money than him. So what he tries
doing is he tries putting me in a mood.
This is what he does. He self-reflects
and then tries putting me into a mood.
Do you get it? Does that make sense?
Because he does his ballsing and he
knows that his life's over at 40. He
tries making me feel the way that he
does. Similar to like non legs. It's all
self-p projecting from these spastics.
Said it once, said it twice, say it
again. Bro, there's a reason why most of
these people don't show their face. the
people that have come on here for years
like hating on people that they don't
know. There's a reason they've been
doing it for years and there's a reason
they don't show their faces.
Do you get it, lad?
Do you get it?
Do you get it, bro?
I could beat I could I could beat Timmy
at the money game right now, bro. I
could pull out [ __ ] well over a grand
and and and prove that I've got more
money than him, but what's the point?
He's going to run away again. It just
goes around in circles again with this
little self projector. What it is, every
single time Timmy does his balls in, he
has no money, so he wants people to show
him money. Money that he doesn't have
himself. And then when people show him
money, he runs away
every single time. Has he shown me Has
he showed me £2,600 yet? Has he showed
No, didn't think so.
No, I didn't think he did. No. Yeah.
Do you remember in the pub when I showed
39, he ran away?
He [ __ ] ran away, bro. Hey, baby. Hey baby.
Yeah, they're not going anywhere, lad.
They're not going anywhere.
We've seen it all before. We've heard it
These spastics need to stop acting like
they can fight.
They need to stop acting like they can fight,
you know. And I'm going to be the one to
teach them on Wednesday, bro. I'm going
to be the one to teach them. Yeah.
It is the same old [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah. Right, bro. Yeah, right.
And I I I hope he does come on Wednesday
cuz I'm going to smash his face in. If
he does, I'm going to smash his face in,
bro. And he's never going to bother
anyone on this community ever again.
He's never ever going to bother anybody
on this community ever, ever, ever again.
Little fat, jealous, self-projecting [ __ ]
Jealous little bastard. Yeah,
trust me, bro. Trust me.
It's because he done his balls in. It's
because he's a compulsive gambler. Do
you not understand? I've already
explained this. When Timmy does his
balls in, he self-reflects. When the
attend when people are going for Timmy,
he self-reflects. This is what he does.
He does this every time
cuz he knows that he's fat, he's old,
he's ugly, he knows I'm better looking
than him. He knows I'm younger than him.
He knows I've got more than him. So
that's why like he he does this, bro.
It's all deflecting.
It's deflecting cuz he's done his balls
in and because people are going for him.
So what he does is he starts fake
YouTube beef. So people So he looks good
for people and I wouldn't mind. He's a
[ __ ] [ __ ] that's lost every single
fight. He's lost every single fight that
he has got into. He's not a fighter.
He's never going to meet anyone ever.
People should People should know all of
this by now with this [ __ ] He's been
doing it for years. How How many years
has this guy been on this community? 15 years.
Is it 15 years?
He's coming out with me because he wants
a day out.
Oh, mate. Listen. He's coming out
because he wants a day out. Yeah, bro.
because you're just going to go to
London on all places on a Wednesday
because no, you need to turn up with
backup cuz you know that's the only way
you've got a chance of beating someone.
But you won't win. Even both of them
wouldn't beat me, bro. Even both of them
is not going to beat me. Trust me. Trust
me. They didn't last time, so they're
not going to this time. Simple as that.
I'll tell you this. Yeah. I'll tell you
this, right? I'll tell you this. Yeah.
If he gets involved, Yeah. If he gets
involved, I'm doing it dirty. It's as
simple as that. Yeah. I'm going to keep
something. I'm going to keep something,
right? Not going to tell you what. I'm
not going to tell you where it's
concealed. But if he tries to even get
involved, I'm going to just pull it in
his face. It's as simple as that.
So, it's it's as simple as that, bro. If
you want to watch, if you want to
record, but yeah, bro, like you you get
involved. You even try to even go near
me or even break it up. I'm doing you in
your eye. Simple as that. I'm doing you
in your eye. Simple as that, bro. Simple
as that. Simple as that. So, yeah.
I'm going to respond to this [ __ ]
anyways, bro. Yeah.
Oh, he's going to stay in the pub.
He's going to stay in the pub. Okay.
He's going to go on my mom's door by on
his own. Yeah, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Of
course you are. Yeah. Of course you are to me.
Of course you are.
What do you mean don't stupid to them
losers? If someone's coming on my mom's
door, I will do what I want. I will use
what I want and I'll do what I want. You
want to come to someone's mum's door
over YouTube and at the big man cuz
you've done your balls in. You don't
call the shots. You don't call the
shots. I will stoop to lower than that.
If you think you're going to come on
people's If you think you're going to
come on someone's mom's door to try to
look good for YouTube, I will stoop to
whatever low I want. I will play dirty
as much as I want. I'll go through any
kind of low. You know, it's it's a
different if you if someone sees you on
the street or you arrange a meet up.
Yeah. That's different. But oh no, I
will definitely step to them lows. 100%.
100%. There's no rules, lad. There are
no rules. Simple.
Yeah. No. If someone if someone comes
and knocks and knocks on your bum's door
of YouTube, bro, there it's it's not
going to be it's not going to be a fist fight. Yeah.
You know what I mean?
You're not going anywhere to me. Shut
up. You know what he's going to do?
Yeah. On Wednesday, he's going to say,
"Oh, he's going to say, oh, um, he's
going to say, oh, um, you're not, uh,
you're not, uh, you're not going to come
out." That's exactly what he's going to do.
He's going to be like, "Oh, I'm not
going to go anyway because he's not
going to." Just watch the excuses on
Wednesday, bro. Just watch the excuses.
It's all for attention. That's all it
is. It's all for attention.
I'm going to meet you here. Oh, I'm
going to meet you next. It's all It's
all hosting fights that are never going
to happen with this attention seeker.
That's all it is, bro. That's all it is.
The guy can't even fight. Why is he
offering people one-on- ones when he can't fight?
He literally cannot fight. He can't
fight anyone. Why is he right?
Do you know what I might do with this
guy, bro? I might just embarrass him one
more time at the money game. But I
should No, I'm not doing that because he
needs to he needs to show me he needs to
show me 2,600 pound. I want to prove to
everyone that he's self projecting, bro. Yeah.
No, he won't turn up Wednesday cuz
that'll be the last thing he does. And
I'm going to do a video talking about
this jealous fat [ __ ] as well.
I'm going to I'm literally going to be
I'm going to be talking, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, mate. I can fight better than him.
I can fight better. And I'm not the one
acting hard on YouTube every day. I'm
not the one acting hard on YouTube every
day, bro. This guy's got a history of
this. [ __ ] come here. [ __ ] come
here. You can't fight. You're [ __ ]
You couldn't even beat me with two
people. Why are you still acting the big
man on YouTube? You literally cannot
fight. Even when it's a twoon-one.
Like, bro, you can't fight anyone. You
fat self-reflecting fat skin bastard.
Yeah, it's as simple as that.
I'm going to ask him to show me £500 as
well. Show me £500 and I'll double it.
No problem. Simple. Or show me £1,000.
I'll double it. No problem. Whatever.
Yeah. Let's embarrass you before Let's
embarrass you before Wednesday.
Oh, that's irrelevant. But it's just
like a dig. You know what I'm saying, bro? Yeah.
You're [ __ ] All you're trying to do
is act big on YouTube. You're not
meeting no one. You're not meeting
nobody. You're just an ugly munter with
a [ __ ] gambling addiction. Yeah. And
I might gamble sometimes, but I can
afford to gamble. I've got the money to
gamble. I don't leave myself broke. I'm
not gambling every day, unlike him. Do
you get it, bro?
You're not meeting anyone. You're not
going to fight anyone. You You would
never be able to knock anyone out. Yeah.
You fat ugly [ __ ]
Just like your non-slegs boyfriend. All
the same, bro.
Yeah. He ain't going anywhere, bro. He
ain't going anywhere.
This is all for attention, lad. All for attention.
And he goes for me, bro, because I'm
younger than him. I got more than him.
And I'm younger than him, bro. I'm I'm
younger than him and I've got more than
him in life. And I'm younger than him,
bro. He's a fat spaz. And I'm going to
mention as well, if I look like half of
you people in this community, I'd
[ __ ] kill myself. No wonder you go
for people that are better looking than
you. You was dealt You was dealt a
[ __ ] bad card in life, bro.
You was dealt a bad card in life.
Literally, like you actually was You are
[ __ ] [ __ ] You're [ __ ] ugly as
Yeah. You know what I'm saying? You're
ugly as [ __ ] You are [ __ ]
It's true though, isn't it? It's true.
Yeah, it's the truth.
Videos, videos, videos, videos. But no
one's stepping on a train and doing anything.
No one's No one's stepping on on a train
and doing anything. Do you know what I'm
saying? It's all talking, but no one's doing anything.
It's all talking. It's all trying to put
people in a bad mood, but no one's doing
anything. Do you get it? Yeah.
Timmy will never ever go anywhere by
himself. He's a [ __ ] He will never
ever ever go anywhere by himself.
You're old. You're overweight. You're
ugly as [ __ ] No wonder you go for me
someone better than you when you've done
your balls in. And I beaten you at the
money game as well, which I could have
embarrassed you again, but I mean,
you've got you've got 2,600 pound to
still show me from last February and you
still haven't shown it because you're
just a self projector.
You know what I'm saying? The thing is
Fire Stick. Yeah. I don't know about
your how you gamble, bro. I don't know
what what your situation is, but bro, I
always have money. Whether I gamble
every two weeks, whether I don't, I
don't gamble every day.
This guy gamles all day, every day. He
drinks every day as well.
He drinks every day.
Yeah, he drinks every day as well.
Imagine that. Drinking every day. Like
he's an alcoholic. He's basically like
an alcoholic, bro.
He's a [ __ ] alcoholic
if you think about it.
He's an alcoholic. He's a gambling
addict. He's [ __ ] ugly. Yeah, just
like Money Mike. No wonder you're making
videos about me, bro.
Yeah, you [ __ ] Mong
loses every And I could understand, bro,
if someone like The Rock come on here
trying to act the big man. Yeah. Someone
like The Rock, someone like John Cena
calling every come out. I could see it.
I could understand it. Yeah. Yeah.
You're trying to act the big man, bro.
We get it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But yet
when someone But when someone like him
is trying to like the big man, it's just
laughable, isn't it? It's just something
to laugh at. I'm going to bring up that
bread and water thing as well. I'm going
to bring up that bread and water thing.
I'm going to also bring up that he
drinks every day. Like, you're an
alcoholic bum with with disabilities.
Not to be rude, but you are. You're an
alcoholic bum with disabilities and a
chronic gambling problem.
It's the truth though, isn't it? I
haven't drunk for over a month now. I
don't even drink, bro. Rarely. I rarely [ __ ] drink.
Just cuz your life is at the pits. Yeah,
I am. Yeah. Just cuz your life at the
pits, bro. Don't Don't Don't start [ __ ] self-projecting. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm doing a video, bro. I'm going
to talk about the bread and flour as well.
Yeah, simple as that.
[ __ ] little clown.
Yeah, I'm going to do it in a bit, bro.
I'm going to do it in a bit.
So, in this in this in this
circumstances, you started it and I'll
finish it. It's as simple as that. Yeah,
he's a proper proper self projector, bro. proper
proper skin self-p projecting fat ugly mess.
And if this guy doesn't show up
Wednesday, just everybody ignore him.
Everybody ignore him. If you want to
watch the videos, yeah, watch like the
gambler videos and stuff, but if he
doesn't turn up anytime he starts
talking about like meeting people, just
laugh at him. Just just laugh at him, bro.
You know, just laugh at him. That's what
I'm I just laugh at him, bro. Every time
now he tries to act big after Wednesday.
Just just laugh at him.
Yeah. Just laugh at him.
Yeah. Oh, I'm going to bring that up as well.
I'm going to bring that up as well, lad.
Oh, yeah. That's another thing. You call
people a virgin even though you're a virgin yourself.
Hey, let me do this video anyways. I'll
be back, bro. I'll be back. Let me do
this video cuz this [ __ ] has done like
two, three videos on me. One sec.