Don't want to see anybody on this platform. watching me.
I don't want to see anybody watching me.
I don't want to see anything. I just
want the number to stay at zero. Please
don't want anybody watching me. Don't
want anybody commenting.
Yep. Don't want anyone watching me and I
don't want anybody commenting if that's
okay with you. Thank you very much.
Don't want anyone watching me. Don't
want anyone. Nope. Don't want anyone
doing any of this stuff. Why are you not
at work today? You're the first person
on it. Why are you not at work? Why are
you on YouTube?
I'd like a I'd like a response. Why are
you on YouTube and you're not at work?
Don't tell me it's Sunday cuz you'll be
on YouTube again tomorrow. Don't tell me
it's [ __ ] Sunday. They'll go live
again tomorrow. Why are you not at work?
Why are you straight on YouTube?
That's what I want to start asking these people.
You know what the [ __ ] they doing on
YouTube? I'm broke. I've got no uh
money. I've got no job. Okie do. So,
what are you people doing on YouTube
then? Yeah, that's a good that's a good question.
Oh [ __ ] man. Yeah.
How are we doing, Greavvesy? Did you see
what I sent you? Jamie Gillis. Top fella.
Top fella. Jamie Gillis.
Yeah. Top porn store. Jamie Gillis, lad.
Did you see it? Top uh top porn star lad. Yeah.
That's so old. You're watching these
these vintage porter. These people
aren't even They're either really old or they're dead.
It's so weird, isn't it, Greasy?
They're very old and they're dead, isn't it?
That man made me that man made me laugh.
He said, "You need to come out here,
lad." He says, "You need to come out
here, Grezy. There's literally vermin.
There's mold on the ceiling
that's got more of a sex life than you."
I was dead.
I was I was dead when he said that. There's
There's W on the concrete that's got
more of a sex life than you, Grezy.
Oh, I don't mind the wind up, bro. I
don't mind the wind up.
And man said, I told you about Vietnam.
It's westernized as [ __ ] Creepy. Crazy
is westernized as [ __ ]
Have you heard of that? Three men, one
hammer. Apparently, they just smashed
this guy to to death with a hammer and
it's apparently really sick.
No, I've never seen that. I've heard
about it. And man's talking about it. I think you
Hey, you know that's I think that's the
best way you could you could you could
defeat someone, you know, Greavvesy. A
chainsaw. What do you think?
Not a knife. None of that. Like a chainsaw.
Yeah. It' be [ __ ] then, is it? Like a chainsaw.
Yeah. Three men, one hammer. Yeah, I
have heard about it, but I I didn't
watch it. Smash this in innocent guy to
death with a hammer or something, was it?
He said it was proper sick. He said it
weren't even funny. It was sick.
Apparently it was really sick.
Yeah, apparently it was really sick, man.
Christian Izzy messaged me yesterday at
almost 1:00 in the morning.
Yeah, we was messaging. We was texting Greasy.
Oh, you got a new message from Christian. Izzy,
how cute is that? Yeah.
Well, you've seen that where they where
they smashed the guy to death with a hammer.
Yeah, Antman's told me about it, but
I've never I've never been able to access it.
But I've never I've never been able to
access it, bro.
Well, they just smash him to death with
a hammer. I think it's called three two
men and one hammer was it? Three men and
one hammer or something.
Yeah. Three men, one hammer. Yeah.
Three men, one hammer. I'm going to He
said, "Don't watch it. It will [ __ ] you
up." Maybe I want to watch it. I'm second.
Yeah, Antman's told me about it.
But you can't watch it though, can you?
Did you watch it? Where do you watch it?
They done it for no reason as well, didn't they?
I swear they done it for no reason as well.
They do it for no reason. They done it
for no reason, I think.
At least Timmy's been quiet today. Is it?
That's good. Now we can leave people
alone, can't he? Yeah.
I had a pie for I had a pie today, Grezy.
I had a pie today, lad. A pie. A minced
My body aches, bro.
Minced pie be my body's aching, man.
My body is aching.
My back. My back hurts.
I don't need a diet, lad. I'm not fat
like you people. You people need a diet.
Stop self projecting.
Stop self-reflecting your [ __ ] onto me,
bro. Don't do that on this channel. A
lot of you do it, bro. A lot of you
people do it on other channels as well. Yeah.
Yeah. So, why would I need a diet, bro?
There's nothing wrong with my um nothing
wrong with my body. Nothing wrong with
the way I look. One sec. Damn.
Yeah, my back aches, lad. My [ __ ] backachches.
My [ __ ] backaches, lad.
Three guys, one hammer griev. It's about
a guy. Yeah. that was riding home from
work on his bike and he just got killed
for no reason. Imagine that.
I want to watch it. He said Antman said
you'll find it somewhere.
Three guys, one hammer.
That's [ __ ] sick, isn't it?
That's sick, is it, bro?
Where do you watch it though?
Yeah. Where do you watch it, bro?
But I don't think you can, bro.
I can't find it. So what? You're saying
you watched it, Grezy? Yeah,
you actually watched it. You actually
watched that video.
Adman watched it.
Let me see.
Yeah, it's on Reddit.
In my time in my entire life, this is
the most disturbing thing I've ever
seen. I watched it years ago. It still
haunts me truly evil.
You can't watch it anymore.
There be a middle-aged man to death of a
hammer wrapped in plastic.
Yeah, there must have been nothing that it Yeah. Um
That's sick, is it, Grezy? That's sick, lad.
That's pretty sick, isn't it? Wow.
Yeah, I'm just looking it up.
Yeah. Anyways, I want to jump off.
Anyways, yeah. See you in a bit.