[ __ ] hell. Yo. Jesus Christ.
The worst to be honest. Jesus Christ.
I'm not sure about 5 hours sleep. Jesus [ __ ] Christ.
Jesus Christ, bro. I got 5 hours [ __ ] sleep, man.
I couldn't fall asleep yesterday, bro. Some reason.
Uh, I have a repo.
Probably him sleeping, but I did to be fair. Oh yeah,
man. Might still be in bed.
[sighs and gasps] [ __ ]
I doubt it though, bro.
He's just messaging me on Instagram. I
don't know what time he messaged me. I
didn't look at the time to be fair, but
I did get a message yeah.
Oh my god, bro.
Someone sent me something. Hold on. Snapchat.
One second. Back.
Jesus Christ, bro.
Why was that?
What did I think? No, maybe around 6:00.
I went to bed, I think.
I couldn't sleep, bro.
I was thinking about too much [ __ ] last
night. I couldn't even sleep.
Yeah, there's not going to be no slug
fight. He's not going anywhere, mate. Yeah. Yes.
You ain't going anywhere, bro. You still
believe he's meeting people. [ __ ] me,
man. [clears throat]
You ain't going anywhere that nowhere. lower. Cool. Nothing.
This person's changed the photo.
Come on, Luigi. Where the hell are you?
We know you're awake, man. Jesus Christ.
Oh, [ __ ] sake, man.
I'm hungry. Where are you, mate? We know you're awake. [snorts]
We know you're [ __ ] awake.
You're always watching like the virgin [ __ ]
Like the virgin [ __ ] [clears throat]
>> No, he won't, bro. He won't.
I fell asleep at [ __ ] like 6:00 in
the morning, bro.
Yeah. 6:00 in the morning. So, I got
like 3 hours and a half sleep. Wow, bro. That's insane.
Anyways, I've already unsubscribed from
Timmy anyways, bro. I don't know about anyone else.
No, officially the only person I'm
subscribed to is Monty. Officially, bro.
that's it, bro. Yeah.
[ __ ] constipated as [ __ ] bro.
Hate that, bro. Like, being constipated
is annoying as [ __ ] man.
Come on, Greasy, man. [ __ ] hell.
You know, I know you're awake, bro. Come on.
No, I don't play code more. I'm just I'm conc
You should just saw this [ __ ]
uh Christian is yesterday, bro. Mr.
Bean, she was crying on voice notes and
stuff trying to play the victim. I'm
thinking, "Oh [ __ ] I'm dealing with
[ __ ] crazy here, bro.
Proper proper crazy mad.
Bro, it's [ __ ] mental, isn't it? No,
I don't say anything anymore. UK signing
cuz you just say that I'm a troll.
So, what's the point of me saying
anything anymore and you tell me I'm
trolling, but I never troll. Yeah.
She started trying to get go in on me
yesterday, bro. So, I had to [ __ ] not
like that in that way, but I had to tell
her about herself. So,
like, you're the one asking me how many
people I've had sex with. What the [ __ ] bro?
Yeah, it was just madness, bro. Just
mad. It was just madness. So, yeah.
No, I'm not a troll, lad. Never tr
my life. Never have. Never will. [ __ ]
I need to book this person. I forgot to book him.
But yeah, UK signing. That's basically it, lad.
So, as I said, as I said, if you do get
someone's number, you want to try
meeting them ASAP.
Wasn't right about that UK asylum. Like
I stated in both of them videos, my man,
people had problems with that. People
have problems with you trying to meet
people as soon as possible. Why? So
stuff like this happens
and then it just ends up worse.
No, I'm not. You're not allowed to try
to meet people within a week
or even a week and a half.
See what you see what I'm saying, bro? I
was going to add more stuff on it, but I
couldn't be popping, bro. To be fair,
there's a reason. There's a reason for it, lad.
Do you understand?
There's a reason why people try to meet
people quicker. There's that for this
exact reason. Do you understand?
For that exact reason, bro. For that exact reason. [clears throat]
I just couldn't sleep yesterday, bro.
I was watching some gory stuff in UK
side. I was watching some gory stuff. Yeah,
it's kind of [ __ ] gross if you ask me.
Well, watch a gory video. I got did
loads of gory stuff. Yeah, bro.
Yesterday was such a weird day, bro. I'm
not going to lie, man.
Well, I watched one. Yeah,
I watched three. I watched three guys, one hammer. Pretty sick.
Have you watched that? I'm sure someone
has watched that. It's [ __ ] disgusting, bro.
It's kind of It's disgusting, isn't it?
Yeah. It's [ __ ] disgusting, man.
You know, I don't need to do any more
positive things. I've given up with the
dating, bro. And like I told you, man,
you know, once bitten, twice shy. End of
that, bro. I'm done with that, bro. With
the dating, I'm done with it.
But I don't think you meant that
anyways. No, I'm done with it, bro.
That was a [ __ ] piss take yesterday.
And I'm not trolling, bro. You can call
me a troll all you want. I don't care,
bro. Yeah, I'm not [ __ ] trolling.
That was annoying yesterday, bro. So, yeah.
No. Well, it does end when you give up,
which is what I done. These are not
people. You know when I tell you I'm
speaking to people, lad. I'm speaking to
I'm pe I'm speaking to people from
months like [snorts] like a month to
months ago, bro. They're not like new
people. I don't speak to new people. I
rarely drink. I really go out.
So, they're just like old people, bro.
They're not like people I'm constantly
going out and meeting. So, yeah. No.
know usually on video as well.
That's depressing yesterday, bro. I'm
not going to lie. That was depressing as [ __ ]
And that's why you try and that's why
you tried to meet people as soon as
possible. There shouldn't be no problems with that.
So then I was going to start talking
about people and the way people are
nowadays, but I thought just save that
for another video. You know, [clears throat]
you save that for another video. [clears throat]
You just save it for another video. Mia,
having a child, you need to be able to
get a date first, lad, which is
impossible in 2026. So, you might want
to actually uh thinking about think
about getting a date first before
thinking about any children.
Yeah, that might be that might be a start.
No, I've completely given up on dating, bro.
Even whilst I was speaking to this
person, that was the last straw.
That was the last straw, bro.
And yeah, that's it.
You know how many times you have to keep
getting slapped in the face before you
fall on the floor, bro? You understand?
Like, you got you got to think about it
logically. How many times
you have to keep getting slapped in the
face? Been on Tinder doesn't work. Being
on hinge doesn't work. Try again, lad.
And that annoyed that actually did annoy
me yesterday, bro.
That did annoy me yesterday. I'm not
going to lie. It did w me up.
So, I couldn't even sleep as well. It
was just a weird day yesterday, bro.
No, I'm done, bro. I'm absolutely done.
I'm finished. Benito, bro. Absolutely.
Oh, just this Christian Izzy, bro.
Yeah, it's turned out to be like a [ __ ]
bro. To be fair, after like a month of
speaking to him and that and Yeah.
Why am I Why am I trying to Why am I
trying to uh chs at it? Um because the
reason I'm trying to chirps at it,
there's two reasons, which I already
explained in the video, is that a none
of her exes had any of these things. So
why is it why is it required from me?
They never went college. They didn't
finish university. So why do I need to?
And second of second of all, that
doesn't make or break a relationship.
What what difference does that make to a
relationship and what somebody could be
in a relationship and what what somebody
could provide in a relationship?
So, I mean, it's just [ __ ] excuses,
isn't it? If you think about it. So,
there is there's a problem with it when
the other people that you've dealt with
haven't had to have the same thing that
you're requiring from me.
That wound me up the first time, you
know, but I didn't say anything. I
thought, "Oh, [ __ ] it. People just make
mistakes." Whatever. Cool. I Yeah. But I
brought it up when we were arguing.
Yeah. 100% I brought it up. There's no
way these Albanian people had had had a
degree. There's no way they went church
and just cheated on you.
So don't ask me, don't require that from
me. It's as simple as that. So,
and then yeah, it's it's that, bro. And
then, you know, even if people even if
people didn't have that stuff, so what
does that mean? They'd be any less good
of a partner than any they'd be any less
good of of of of a candidate?
I think about it, it just sounds silly,
isn't it? You know, so
yeah, that that was all I was thinking
when I first heard that. The the number
one I was thinking, but I didn't say anything.
And she was like, "Oh, yeah, they did."
No, they [ __ ] did not. No, they
I'm not getting into it with you, lad.
I'm not getting into it, bro. I'm not
I'm not getting into it. I ain't getting
into it with idiots, bro. Um I done my
video. I said what I've had to say and that's it.
You know my opinion. I've said
everything I've had to say. So that's
it. And just the way she was telling me
about like her two exes, you just know
they never had any of these things. You
just know it's straight,
you know? Whereas when you when you
could see Izzy's boyfriend, you can kind
of be like, "Okay, yeah, we went uni.
Yeah, okay. Whatever." you know that's
you know you just know bro is it like
it's it's as simple as that.
Sorry bro I just don't feel like getting
into it bro it's just a waste of time
um you know I've said all I've had to
say now and that's that is in it. So yeah,
it's bad. Really bad, bro.
Really, really, really, really bad.
I said, I woke up to 23 messages the
other day, bro. Like 23 messages at
Well, no, actually, I was half asleep at
2:00 in the morning and then bam, 23
messages. I'm thinking, what the hell's bells?
asking people's body count and T.
So yeah, the point I'm trying to make is
this is a perfect example of why you
should try to meet people as soon as you
can. This is a perfect example. And you
know what? It's so mad that I'm never
the I can show the conversation and
people would agree with me. They'd have
no choice. I I can safely put all of
these messages out there saying that
people would still find excuses, but you
know, deep down they'd know that like
yeah, it was fine. So, you know what I
mean, bro? Like, yeah. Um Yeah.
Yeah. It's depressing, bro. That
actually is proper depressing, you know.
Whereas if you speak to someone for a
day, 2 days, it doesn't really matter,
does it? 3 days, it doesn't really
matter. Someone on the street, it
doesn't really matter. You know what I
mean? But that is that is a slap in the
face with a knuckle dust duster. And
you're going to keep having these
experiences. The longer you do this,
yeah, the longer you date or you try to
date, you know what I mean? Like the
longer you're in the game, this is
what's going to keep happening. It's
just going to get worse and worse and
worse and worse and worse.
And you just you just you you might just
end up losing it one day. You know,
people you don't know people's temper.
You know, you might just end up going
out drinking one day and just smashing
some [ __ ] headon. You don't know. This
is what I'm trying to say. You don't know, bro.
Oh, no. I've been trying for years and
years and years. I'm not trying again.
Yeah. And I've tried again and tried
again and tried again. I'm finished,
bro. It's over.
So, yeah. What did you think of it,
Grezy? Bro, it was proper proper [ __ ] up.
I think I messaged you at like 5:30 in
the morning. It's so [ __ ] up, bro.
Okay, I'm scared of everyone, bro. Good for you.
Um, bro, it's like [ __ ] up, man.
It's bad, bro. It's really, really bad.
Yeah. When you get yourself a little
job, lad. Um, I'll get myself one. Same
to you. You get a job instead of being
on YouTube 24/7.
And I said to him, "Oh, like if you've
got a problem, if it's this and that,
just tell me." Like, I'm I'm the kind of
person, mate, that like I'd rather the
truth, you know?
Bloody watched a man's h head get
hammered in. I've seen a man [ __ ]
drop dead in front of me with blood
pissing from his face. Like, nothing's
going to nothing's going to phase me. Do
you get it? Crazy. Did you actually get
it? I'm the kind of person that, bro, I'
I'd rather the truth.
I'd rather people to be cruel, to be
kind. You get Do you get it, bro? Like,
you know what I'm saying? I'd rather it
me. I'd actually rather it.
I don't know about you or anyone else,
but I'd rather the truth.
That's me personally. I don't know who
else is like that, but you know, I I am.
And that's why I don't deal with them,
bro. You know, as much as I like to
laugh, I I would love to laugh, but I
can't laugh at something that's not funny, bro.
And something that's just It's just
depressing, isn't it?
What? What? What? What else is it?
No. No. No. Greasy, grievy, greasy,
greasy, greasy. Listen, listen, listen.
A, none of her exes had a career. None
of her exes went to church. That's the
first thing. And second of all, she
doesn't know who I live with. She
doesn't know what I got. She doesn't
know anything. She knows of me. She
knows me as a [ __ ] landlord. And when
it comes to it, it comes to it, you know.
So, no, no, no, no, no, no. The thing
is, Greasy, that would be fine. But the
problem is is none of these exes had
them requirements. These Albanian
cheaters. Do you understand what I'm
saying, bro? That's the thing that made
it worse. That's the thing that made it
Do you understand? That's the thing that
made it worse. And the fact that they're
that they're more they're similar to me.
Cuz at first she thought that I was
Albanian. She thought at first that I
was Albanian, right? Um, she thought
that I was Albanian because like the way
I look, you know, some people think that
I'm Albanian. I said, "Oh, no. I'm not
Albanian. This is what I am." So, the
fact that they're so similar to you, but
they had none of these requirements, you
know, and I doubt that any of these
people were better looking than me. I
doubt they were any better of a person
than me. So, why all of these
requirements for me? That's the That's
the first thing I'm thinking of. And she
doesn't know who I live with. She
doesn't. And again, like I've said,
Greasy, bro, like you can have your
opinion, you know, but what about when I
was living by myself? What about when I
had all of that this what what about
when I had more money than I do? What
about when I was going to the gym? What
about when I was working? What changed?
What changed then till now? Nothing.
You know, I was living by myself. I went
to the gym. [ __ ] the money. You had a
job. Doesn't matter what the job was.
What changed? Nothing changed over that whole summer.
I'm not being awkward. I'm telling you
the truth, bro. I've lived all kinds of
different lives. I'm really not telling
I'm really not lying now, bro. So,
what what what changed? What what what
actually changed? I mean, I can tell you
many different positions that I've been
with in in my life. Then she starts
crying on these voice messages. Greasy,
what the [ __ ]
just go back to your ex and just stop
wasting people's time. You're not
serious about meeting me anyways. So, I
mean, just go back to your ex. And they
definitely did. They definitely def and
you know now they act the the way
they're acting now, Greezy, it just
proves that they deleted the lumber.
They did they they've added me back now.
They've added me back now. But it just
shows that the way that they're acting
now, it proves that they deleted the
number. Because when someone deletes you
on on WhatsApp, their picture and their
and their status goes, "Oh, I deleted my
picture. Fair enough. Why did your
status disappear?" So, it just now proves
it proves it. Now, it now it actually
proves that now the way they're acting
now that is that you you might have not
thought it at the time, but now you can
just tell. You know what I mean? So,
you can't respect people that don't help
themselves. You get it, bro.
So, I'm not being funny, bro. Like,
okay, your exams are finished now.
There's no reason why you can't meet
unless you don't want to. That was that
that was a problem. Unless you don't
want to. No, they didn't block me, bro.
It still come up as two ticks. No,
that's what I'm saying. They didn't block me.
No, they didn't. No, no, because it
still come up as two ticks.
Sad. It's that that actually did that
actually did depress me. But I'm not
going to lie to you. That actually did depress me.
If it wasn't for the X's and the other
things, then I wouldn't have cared. I
don't think I would have been bothered.
No, they deleted my number because I
thought at first they blocked me, but
then I messaged them and then it was two ticks. um
that they said that they just removed
their picture, but their status removed
as well. So, I was like, nah. But then I
just didn't pay I just didn't pay I just
didn't pay um much attention to. But it
just shows now that they they did do
that because of the way that they're acting. So, yeah,
I was just sat upstairs, bro, like 5:00
in the morning, speechless.
I don't know, bro. And to be honest with
you, I really don't care.
I don't care about that obsessed,
jealous buffoon, bro.
I really don't give a flying [ __ ] to be
honest with you, lad.
Yeah, this dating thing is pissed me off
again, Ben. Proper piss me off, bro.
Cuz you're talking [ __ ] See you later.
This just gets worse, Ben. I'm going to
have to go to Thailand, bro. In all in
all seriousness, bro, now like this guy
has been saying to me, um, Ant-Man's
been saying to me, "Oh, you should you
should come meet me. You should come
meet me, bro. I feel like, bro, you you
need to go, bro, before it's too late." Seriously,
going to keep getting worse and worse
and worse and worse and worse.
But how many how many times are you
going to keep getting slapped in the face?
>> Yeah. Do you watch my video then?
Well, actually, funny enough, this
person actually had Iraq in them.
Yeah. See you later, lad.
This person actually had Iraq in them.
You watch I guess you watched the video
then, didn't you? Ben,
I don't know, bro. Don't know if he did or not.
Depressing, is it, bro? So, yeah.
You want me to do you want me to explain it then?
Oh, I gave up a long time ago, bro. I've
100% gave up. That's depressing, bro. I
didn't go to bed yesterday until 6:00 in
the morning, Ben. So, I only had 3 hours sleep, lad.
3 hours? No, I'm done, lad. I'm 100% I
am finished, bro. I am done.
So, you know, the last time I went out,
uh, Ben, a month ago on the Thursday
when I got my haircut and that, uh, went
out a month ago. It's got to be like a
month ago now. Yeah, it was a month ago.
Well, when where that month went, I
don't know, bro. It seemed like a week
ago. Met this person. They were talking
about how like they're a Christian and t
and they want somebody that's that um
goes to church and has a degree in uni,
but then they said, "Oh, as long as you
go to church, whatever." Spoke to them
for a whole month. They were asking me
my body count, this, that, and the
other. I said, "Oh, let's meet up." Oh,
uh, yeah, I've got exams where, uh,
wait, waiting until their exams
finished, right? Then they come up with
a lover excuses. Bear in mind, I spoke
to this person every single day, Ben,
for like a month basically. And um, this
come out with this bogus excuse, then
starts like trying to turn it on me. And
I'm thinking, what about these exes that
these two exes that cheated on you? Do
they do they have to go to church? Cuz I
can't imagine these people going to
church, mate, to be honest with you. And
then just the whole thing just wound me up, bro.
I already had a bad day yesterday as it was.
So, it's just a slap in the face, bro.
It's just a slap in the face, in it.
And this is what I mean, Ben. It's like
it was always going to be the same here.
It's always going to be the same here,
bro. And it'll get worse. That's the
thing is it will get worse. That's the thing, you know.
It's bad. Really bad.
I think they're not mentally stable to
be honest with you. They started sending
me voice notes crying and stuff
and they did say they were going to meet.
No, my friend said talk. I've got
nothing to say to them.
I'm not apologizing, lad. I didn't do
anything wrong. So why am I apologizing?
I'm not [ __ ] apologizing. No way.
For what? Speaking the truth. Why am I
saying sorry for speaking the truth,
Ben? I meant exactly what I said. So,
you know, whether [clears throat] it
takes you 10, 15 years
to um to to to to figure it out, then
takes 10, 15 years, bro. Like, I was
right. So, you know, that's it. So, yeah. So, yeah,
it's bad then. It really is bad, lad. It
really is bad.
Um, Vietnam, they're stuck up as well.
So yeah, Grezy, do do you generally
think that that like
do you generally think that if you went
um if you live by yourself and you had a
job that all of a sudden your dating
life's going to get better.
You're sadly sadly mistaken.
Yeah, I know. I know. I wouldn't mind if
they're expecting it from all of the
people, but no. And why you why did you
delete my number as well and then add me back?
That's a weird one, isn't it?
I watched some pretty glory [ __ ]
yesterday. My friend told me some scary
stories and then I had this [ __ ] happen.
Yeah. No [ __ ] bro.
No [ __ ] Did you just realize that? No
And I I imagine I look
And I imagine I look I look I look
similar to these guys as well cuz
they're Albanian. So I I'd assume that
I'm I'm I look similar to them.
So what what the [ __ ] What's going on,
man? you know. So,
that pissed me off, bro. I'm not going
to lie. That pissed me off. But I didn't
say anything at the start cuz I just
thought, oh, maybe like they just don't
want to get cheated on or something.
What video, bro? This one.
No, they basically a man was cycling
home from work. Yeah. And they just
attacked him randomly. They smashed him
off his bike. They pulled him into the
uh into the forest and just smashed his
head in and cut him open for no reason.
They didn't even know the guy.
It's like a plastic Yeah. Like a yellow
plastic It's like a yellow plastic bag.
Yeah. [ __ ] disgusting, bro.
Yeah, it's disgusting.
They didn't even know the person as
well. They just done it for no reason.
Well, that never happened. So, it's all
hypothetical, isn't it?
It's all hypothetical.
You must have heard about it, Greavvesy.
You must have heard about it.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] It is vile, bro. It
is vile. Really vile.
There's some people that's watched it
and they they still think about it every day. Bro,
Ant-Man said that it affected him and he
watched it when he was 17.
Cuz that could be anyone, bro. Think
about it. That could be anyone.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It happened in 2007, bro.
Yeah, but even if you say them stuff,
they're still not going to get with you.
It's just excuses.
But you can say that, but they're still
not going to get with you.
So why why why is the matter? It's just
excuses. If that was really it, then all
of them exes would have had to go to
church, wouldn't they?
>> So I'm just done with the whole thing,
bro, to be honest with you. So yeah,
so when they talk about men, they can't
talk about men anymore.
They have had ample full of chances um
to meet people that won't cheat on them,
to meet people that are down to earth,
and they don't want to. So I mean, don't
just don't feel sympathy for them. It's
their loss at the end of the day. So at
the end of the day, people shouldn't
feel sorry for them.
Now they are purposely going for these
people. At the end of the day, right, I
before I used to think, oh, like maybe
they're not. But no, it's clear as day
they are. It's it's clear as day they
are purposely going on people that that
cheat for them and cheat on them. It's
got to be. It's too obvious now.
You know, there's there's there's people
where they're [ __ ] dating people in
prison. Like they're actually dating
people they've got with them whilst
they're in prison. Explain that one. you know,
you know, start explaining that one.
What's the score, bro? So, yeah. So,
I'm just fed up of it to be honest, bro.
It's just so depressing. It's depressing as [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm I'm I'm not happy JN at all, bro.
I'm pissed off.
I'm not going to lie, bro. I'm actually pissed off.
I felt like getting on one yesterday,
bro, but it was Sunday, so I didn't bother.
Yeah, I'm actually annoyed, bro. And
that's why you don't speak to people for
a month. Point proving,
you know, I can put all of these
messages up as well.
That's depressing, bro. Depressing.
I swear I just got I swear I just got
like a [ __ ] dopamine low, bro. I
can't even lie. That is depressing as [ __ ]
>> Seriously, that is depressing, bro.
It gets bad to worse.
It goes from bad to worse.
It'll never change, bro. Never change.
No, I'm good, bro.
No, I'm good, lad.
Yeah, I'll never change, JNA.
Never change, lad.
What do you mean? Try not to overthink
it. That's exactly what you should do,
bro. Why are you being treated different?
You're not different than these. These
Albanian people would have looked
similar to you. 100%. They would have
looked similar to you. They probably
weren't better looking than you. They
probably weren't had they they're
probably similar to you and looks and
obviously not the same personality but
they they Albanian people are probably
probably some of them look similar to me
cuz I'm not fully white.
Like if it was like um a black guy then
obviously you I don't look anything like
a black guy or you know I don't know an
Indian guy or whatever then it's like
okay but when these people must be so
similar to you.
Yeah, like Ricky, I've already shown
messages, lad. You're not going to rage
bait me, brother. I've already shown
messages of people leading me on. Um,
and I'm not getting into it with you,
lad. I already showed my messages. I
showed what happened. Um, so yeah,
that's it, bro. I'm not going to waste
my time anymore explaining something to
you. You keep white nighting. You keep
sing. That's if that's how you want to
live your life, bro. Then live your life
like that, bro.
Um, but yeah, I I know how it is. I know
what I've been through. I know exactly
what this person was saying to me. And
that's that, bro. Like, it's fine, bro.
I'm not going to get into pointless arguments.
Like I said, JNA, it's not it's not the
requirements that they're asking for,
bro. It's did any of their exes needed
any of these needed any of these requirements?
Did they need did they need any of these requirements?
I mean, if you listen to I mean, this
particular Ricky, there's there's no
arguing with this one. Even even though
you will argue with it, you would always
argue with it. You'll always defend a
woman no matter what she's done. So
that's why someone like you it's
pointless because when people like you
are even shown different experiences
um when a woman is shown different experiences.
So when you're when you're shown these
things you still deny it bro. So the
whole the whole thing is pointless.
You was telling me that I'm not allowed
to put lover hearts on voice notes. You
was making all kinds of excuses
for the women that was doing the same
thing, but it was okay for them to do
it. Ricky, I hate to break it to you,
but you're a white knight. It's that
it's it's as simple as that, bro.
Whether you get [ __ ] whether you don't
get [ __ ] I don't know. And I really
don't care to be honest with you, lad. Um,
you know what I'm saying? Um, I really
don't know. And I really don't care. I
don't know you, but I do know you're
100% a white knight, bro. Cuz this
person done me wrong. Properly wrong.
And there's loads of videos I put up
like approaching videos as well that you
just dismiss. So, I'm not sure what's
the point of anything or even having a
having a discussion.
Yeah. It's funny how they always make
mistakes with the bad guys, isn't it?
Huh? I find that funny, isn't it? Isn't
it how they always make mistakes with
the bad guys?
Yeah. [ __ ] off.
And the requirements are so silly as
well. Like they don't make or break a
person. If they said, "Oh, they want
somebody with money or they want someone
that like isn't addicted to something or
they don't want somebody with an ST
[ __ ] D," you know, then I'd be like,
"Oh, well, these these requirements make
sense in a relationship." They don't
make sense in a relationship, you know?
Cuz what if somebody was making money
from YouTube? Yeah. and they had all the
free time in the world or they or they
won the lottery and they didn't need to
get a degree and they like you know do
you understand what I'm trying to say?
Would that mean that they're any less um
what's the word I'm looking for? Is does
that mean they're any less of a person
when it comes to a relationship? Say you
won the lottery tomorrow. Say for
example you won £200,000 or you won a
million and you never had to work again,
right? And whatever. Do you get what I'm saying?
Do you get me, bro?
It doesn't make sense to me how their
how their exes never had didn't need any
of these requirements,
you know, and and obviously you've got
all the time in the world. You've got
money now. I've still got money. That
should be enough, you know.
That should be enough. Yeah.
Yeah, it just annoyed me. She wasn't my
type type. She was like she had big
boobs, but like she was kind of too
short for me. But it doesn't matter
anyways, bro. It doesn't matter really.
It doesn't make it any less. It's just
annoying. All of it is annoying.
All of it is. That's why I gave up.
That's why I got away from it, bro.
That's why I got away from this, you know.
So yeah, that's why I got away from this
dusty. That's why you never see me go
out nothing anymore like when it comes
to that because I know it what it's
always going to be.
I know it's always going to be in this
country now. It's too obvious, bro. Is it?
And then you're crying on a voice note, you know,
trying to make me feel bad. Go away,
man. Simple go away. [snorts]
Not good, bro. Not good.
Not funny, Grezy. It really isn't funny.
That's actually w me up, bro.
And I watched Three Guys, one hammer yesterday. Dusty,
don't watch it. Don't watch it.
I was going to show it to Laney, but
nah, that would scare the [ __ ] out, bro.
Trust me. Yeah, I watched that yesterday. [gasps]
Yeah, [ __ ] vile, bro. Vile. Not sure
you've already seen it, but yeah, I
thought I'd see what What is this all
about? Ant-Man's talking about
Jesus Christ, bro.
I mean, I think I'm sometimes [ __ ] up
and I've got a temper.
But that is sick, bro. That is sick.
Have you Have you watched it? Have you
watched it, Dusty?
I might screen record and put on my channel, Greasy.
And she kind of was leading me on as
well, Grezy, because she was asking me,
okay, she was giving me mixed messages
because she was asking me what my body count is.
Now, unless you see somebody as a as as
a as a potential uh partner, you're not
asking their body count. That is a weird
thing to ask somebody that you've just
met. How many people have you had sex with, you know,
like and so yeah, they they were given
mixed messages. They they were given
mixed messages. Definitely given mixed
messages. Even if they wasn't leading
you on, they would definitely because
you don't ask someone's body count.
And they said they would meet you
anyways. It doesn't matter what it was
for friends or what. They said they were
going to meet you anyways. So it doesn't
really matter. So
they said that they were going to meet
you anyways, didn't they? So yeah.
So it's regardless whatever happened. So
you know what I mean?
I always get dragged into this [ __ ]
loop again, bro.
You know what I mean? So, yeah,
it's always going to be the same here,
brother. It's always I mean I mean, you
got people with three kids thinking
they're better than you now, Dusty. I
was speaking to somebody the other day.
They thought they were better than me.
And they had three [ __ ] kids
and they thought they were better than
me. Three [ __ ] kids and they thought
they were better than me. Bro, come on
now. It gets worse and worse and worse
and worse and worse. You know, I was
watching approaching videos in Vietnam.
In Vietnam and they were saying they had
they were stuck up that attitude.
I don't know, bro, who the dads were,
but all I know is that they thought they
were better than me.
So, it's always going to be the same
here, JNA. It's always going to be the same here.
It will never change. It will never
No, one kid's all right. If you're in
your 30s, one kid's right, bro. [ __ ] Yeah,
we're just born in the wrong day and
age. Just as simple as that, is it? Like,
so when these women are met with people,
JNA, that won't cheat, that won't do
this, that won't do that, they don't
want it. But then continuously moaning
about men, do you want you see the
problem with that? That's like me going
out having good experiences with women
and then moaning about women. It doesn't
make sense. It does not make no sense.
You get it? Whereas they will come even
if it's just me cuz I can say I've met a
lot of people you know so they must like
this behavior they must like this
degenerate behavior you know they must
like degenerates it's you know what I mean so
starts crying to me like what the [ __ ] Yeah,
if it was Saturday, I probably would
have went out today, bro. If this
happened, I probably would have to be fair.
Just to get your mind off of it, bro.
It's bad, isn't it?
It gets worse and worse and worse, J. It
just gets worse and worse and worse.
So yeah, even if you speak to someone
for a month, lad, they've got no problem. Nope.
No one has ever done that.
And then the same thing will happen
again. JNA, you go out, you get numbers,
they lead you on, they play games. The end,
you know, and that's it. And that's what
we will always be here. That's what it
will always be in this country, you know.
You know, please for the lover for the
love of God, if you do meet someone, try
to meet them within four to seven days.
No one is that busy. You know, I only
gave them the benefit of the doubt
because they had exams and they were
stressed and they and they used to
almost cry messaging me. So, I thought,
okay, whatever. They're clearly they are
clearly busy and the fact that they're
still typing. But, father of God, trust
me, no one is too busy, bro. Trust me.
Like say they say they if they ain't got
exams or whatever they bro no one is too busy
you know you're no one is too busy trust
me Thursday to the Thursday the latest
there's no excuse trust me
there is no excuse.
Yeah that's what Timmy calls it. There's no excuse.
Trust me I've spoke to people before for
ages. They still on me over.
Um, I don't know why you think they
wouldn't, you know. Nah,
you know what I would personally do,
bro? If you did go out approaching
someone, just try to stay with them as
long as possible.
Stay with them as long as possible and
try to meet them as soon as possible
when it's via text.
Obviously, you do what you want to do. I
don't but I'm saying that's from my
experiences that's what I would do
[snorts] if I ever was to try again. I
don't think I will be but you know yeah
it makes perfect sense. Perfect perfect
You know at the end of the day bro
you've got to rule out time wasters at
the end of the day.
Oh yeah on next Saturday you can be
there if you like but I won't be there.
Go to waxis. You can if you want, but I
won't be there.
Yeah, you can if you like. Yeah. Well,
believe it or not, I used to get a lot of dates.
Maybe, but then if you try but then
here's the thing, doctor. If you speak
to them for a month, they will still
[ __ ] you over.
So, I'd rather take the gamble.
I mean, what what would you rather do?
Speak to someone for two, three months
and them still have no intentions of
meeting you? I know which one I'd pick.
I know exactly which one I'd pick.
Trying to meet them ASAP cuz no one's
too busy. If it wasn't from them saying
that they had exams, I would have
stopped talking to them. No one is that.
I said to them, this is what I said to
them Greavves. I said, "Oh, do you want
to go for some food? Like, I'm a train
I'm a train away from them. do you want
to just go for some food or whatever? I
didn't even expect anything. I just just
I was just bored like next week, which
is this week. So then they started
coming out with all the and then she
started saying like, "Oh yeah, and like
I said, JNA, even speaking even speaking
to them for a month doesn't work cuz
they still they still don't meet you."
So, would you rather speak to someone
for a week and then not meet you and
then oh, you just move on or speak to
someone for a month and two months and
they're still not going to meet you? I
know which one I'd pick. So,
so yeah, then they were making up these
mad like kind of like excuses.
Soon as someone says to grey, I'll let
you know it's over. Done.
Trust me, it's done. Soon as someone
says to you that they will let you know
unless there's a [ __ ] good reason,
it's over. Simple. There's no I'll let
you know about it. You know, like they
people people are not too busy, bro, to
be able to meet someone a day of the week,
you know, unless they're in another
country. Like there are some exceptions,
but nah, [gasps]
it's done. Soon as I saw that, bro, I
was like, it's done. So
I was speaking to her every day, all
day, every day. Voice notes. So I just
thought I just assumed that they were
just going to be decent and normal
because didn't bring up sex. Didn't talk
about any weirdness, which I I might as
well have really to be honest because
they still [ __ ] you over. All the things
that you avoid doing, you might have
just you might as well just done it
anyways cuz they're still going to treat
you the same. They're still going to
treat you like [ __ ] and treat you
differently. So, you know, yeah,
she didn't Google me cuz if she Googled
me, she would have blocked me. Dusty,
she would have blocked me. Think about it.
There's no may. They're just [ __ ] bro.
That's That's what they are. They're just [ __ ]
It's as simple as that.
They're just [ __ ] bro.
If they Googled my name, they would have
just blocked me.
They would have told me. They would have blocked me.
his excuses. They're just [ __ ]
So when they come across somebody that
is actually normal, but all joking
aside, all trolling aside,
um I can't feel sorry for them
pretty much. Yeah, bro. But I mean I
mean if they've been meet Yeah. But the
thing is Echo if they've been meeting
you for 6 months it's different. If they
if they if they if they see it straight
away then you know if they see it
straight away then obviously yeah you're
[ __ ] or even but if they've been if
they've been meeting you for months and
months and months there's a higher
chance that they're just not going to
leave you because it was ages ago. They
know what you like what you're like and
stuff. So, I mean,
I think if he was meeting them long
enough, then um
I don't think it would matter.
Do you get what I'm trying to say? Like,
if it was like four to 6 months, I don't
think they would just leave you. If
you've been meeting them loads and loads
and loads and loads and loads,
you know, there's a high They could
still leave you obviously, but I'm
saying there's a high chance that they
wouldn't cuz obviously they've got to
sort of know you. And that's not even
that bad, bro. When I watch that three
guys with one hammer, right, that's what
you call sick. That's what you call
sick. Greavves. When And when you
compare it, right, to things that I've
said in the past, it really ain't that bad.
It really, really, really, really ain't that bad.
Think about it, bro. Like, if you
actually think about it, okay, you might
have said mad stuff in the past. You're
saying stuff, but there's actual sick
people out there. actual really really
really sick sick people out there
like like that. And there's other things
as well which I'm not watching but you
know I've heard about it. That's what
you call really really sick. That would
warrant someone not speaking to you
forever again. You know when you
actually see proper [ __ ] up
psychopaths and that bro you know that
really the [ __ ] you said really isn't
that bad in comparison bro. Really?
I'm sorry. It really isn't, you know.
Sorry, bro. That's that's one thing I
thought of as well.
I was thinking, oh, like there's there's
somebody I don't speak to. My there's
one person I don't speak to in my
family. Shouldn't have been saying it.
There's one person I don't speak to.
Okay, but think about it. You got guy.
Did you do something like that? Did you
smash a man's face in the in the [ __ ]
woods so his brains were coming out? No,
you barely you didn't really do
anything. You just said mad stuff,
you know? Like if you That's what I was
thinking about. Like if you done
something like that, yeah, then I could
I could understand it, bro. Like I could
understand it. But even though it's
still not good, you know, the things you
saying that, but bro, compared to that
and other [ __ ] people have done, that's
that's really nothing, bro. That's really nothing.
I can understand if you done something
like that, right, and you got trolled on
the internet forever.
Yeah, I know. I saw all about it. It's
disgusting, bro. It was w It was winding
me up watching it. It was winding me up
watching it, bro.
It's not like It's not like it was gang
related and someone just got shot and
they died. Oh well, people die. [ __ ]
happens. They actually like done it for
no reason as well.
It's disgusting, bro. People like that.
Yeah. People that do [ __ ] like that.
Yeah. They need to be [ __ ]
they need to be stoned to death. Like
whipped whipped and and and crippled and
then put into prison. That's disgusting,
bro. people. But you know the death
penalty, you know, when people say stuff
about the death penalty, no, the death
penalty is not enough for certain crimes
like that because the death penalty,
think about it. They inject you, you're
dead. You You're still looking good in
that casket. Unlike someone that's been
smashed to [ __ ] bits,
you know what I mean, bro? That wound me
up. That actually annoyed me that, bro.
That wound me up watching that.
It's sick, bro. It's sick. So, you know
exactly what I'm talking about, ain't
it, Dr. Eko? Yeah, you know what I'm
talking about. So, if someone just kills
someone, they just kill someone.
Um, and that's it. Like, there's is the
dead death penalty. Okay, fair enough. A
life or life. But that is, bro, [snorts]
I'm never going to Russia. I'm never
going to Ukraine.
But then they wonder why people go
outside with knives.
This is the contradictory of it. This is
And then they wonder why people go out
with knives, bro.
Because what if something happens? What
if something like that happens? You know,
you know what I'm saying? What what if
that happens, bro? You know, it's happened before.
I started getting laded and stuff.
[clears throat] All I could think about
was my head, bro. That's probably why I
couldn't sleep properly. Like, it's not
going to affect me for ages like he did
Ant-Man. I've seen someone die in front
of me, but like it's still [ __ ] up.
It's still [ __ ] up, bro.
So, yeah, if you done something like
that, I could understand it, you know?
They've done it to animals as well.
Yeah, they done it to animals as well.
Don't know how they could do something
like that to someone, bro. I really don't.
I couldn't even do it to somebody so
somebody that I hate.
Seriously, bro. It's [ __ ] vile.
It is vile, bro. It is vile. It is sick,
bro. It is sick. And then you're more
bothered about what someone said about
children ages ago on YouTube when
there's [ __ ] like that going on in the world.
Sorry, bro. I'm not even making excuses
for myself, but come on now. really
really really really really you know
I'm scared of Laney going outside now me
not me not me as as much but I'm kind of
scared I'm kind of scared of Laney going
out cuz whatever happens to Laney
you know that's what I was thinking bro
I was bro I was I was about to stop
sleeping with a knife and [ __ ] it's
[ __ ] disgusting bro
it's not good Bro, it's vile.
It's [ __ ] vile, bro. It's disgusting.
No, I just watched um Three Men One
Hammer yesterday. Fire stick. It was sick.
Very, very sick. Very disgusting.
Disturbing. I don't know if you ever
watched it, but
we was just basically saying that, you
know, people have got such a problem
with mad stuff you've said years ago or
whatever. Yeah, you might not be
perfect, but look at people that are
doing that stuff in the world.
Think about it in comparison to just
[ __ ] you sell online ages ago. You know
what I mean?
Yeah, it's viral. It's disgusting.
Nah, it's called Three Guys, One Hammer.
I don't advise you watch it.
Don't watch it. I was going to show
Laney it, but I wouldn't do that to the P [ __ ]
Grezy. I wouldn't do that to the P [ __ ]
He's bad enough with just like horror
movies. So something in real life would
just You know what I mean?
No, it's called Three Guys, One Hammer.
Yeah, it's really bad. It's really bad.
It's basically there's the these two
guys are waiting in like the they're
waiting in like the woods for someone to
kill. This guy comes with his bike and
just starts hammering him to death for no reason.
smashed his face in, cut his abdomen
open for no reason. They don't even know
the guy. It's just some guy cycling home
from work. They didn't know him and they
just killed him. They tortured him and
everything. Like madness, bro. It was sick.
Yeah. Don't watch it. [clears throat]
Yeah. You shouldn't watch it, bro. It's bad.
It's [clears throat] really bad, bro.
Really bad. Really, really bad.
Yeah, they killed 21 people. They kill
people every day.
They killed people every day. They
killed 21 people, bro. [clears throat]
It's vile, is it? Very vile.
So, that's what when you look at stuff
like that and the people and there's
worse. I'm sure there's worse out there,
but you know, then when they want to try
and talk about things that you've said
online, come on. You wouldn't even know
evil if it hit you around the [ __ ] head.
You really wouldn't, mate. You really
wouldn't. What I've said is like,
I was just talking to this [ __ ] Christian. Izzy,
she's a [ __ ] bro.
Anyways, you can watch the video.
Anyways, I'm not repeating it. So,
did you see the full video, Dr. Echo?
There's a bit where they actually knock
him off the bike.
Imagine that, bro. You're coming home
from work as a normal person. You've
just been at work and someone just
[ __ ] hammers you to death. Imagine
that, bro. Imagine you've just survived
cancer yet. You've just survived cancer.
You're just on your way back home from
work and then in broad daylight, mind you, [clears throat]
and then someone just literally hammers
you to death.
Imagine that. That is [ __ ] up, bro.
No, he was an innocent. No, he was an
innocent person. He was an old man.
No, it was two young kids, two young
boys just done it for no reason. It was
an old man.
No, it was just it was an old man. They
didn't know him.
No, it was a completely innocent person.
They didn't know him. They didn't know
He was just an old man, bro. They were
just two 20 year olds.
They didn't know the guy, bro. They
didn't know him. They' never saw him
before. They just waited for anyone to
murder. They just murdered innocent people.
Obviously, cars drove past, but they
can't stop a car, can they? So,
yeah. It's not hilarious. It's sick.
I won't be going to Russia. I won't be
going to Ukraine. [ __ ] that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I wouldn't even do that if someone
cheated on me, bro. Let alone an
innocent person who didn't even
um do anything to me. I don't No, I
wouldn't do that. I wouldn't do that, bro.
That's [ __ ] vile. Oh god. Imagine
that like hammering someone's face and
the thought of it isn't it mad.
Do they actually think they was never
going to get caught though doing killing 21 people?
Do they really think they were never
going to get caught? >> [snorts]
>> That is madness. Madness
doesn't feel like a Monday today, does
it? Yeah, I watched all of it.
It didn't bother me as much as Ant-Man.
It's just the whole principle of it. I
think you know the whole principle of
it. I watched it in subtitles as well.
Have you watched it in subtitles?
They're like to him, "Oh, how you
feeling when the guy is like you can't
even talk his head smashed in and
they're like they're mocking him and
stuff." Did you watch it in like subtitles? >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, it's 30 minutes long, the full
one, isn't it?
[snorts] Yeah, but I don't think I could get it. Um,
I'm not um Yeah, but I've I've seen a
guy die in front of me, bro. So I seen a
guy get banged, got hit in front of me.
Yeah, they took a screwdriver to his
eye. Yeah, that never gave me PTSD.
So I don't think that will. It's just [ __ ] up.
Yeah, it's just [ __ ] up.
>> poor [ __ ]
When stuff like that has been seen, it
can't be unseen. So, you best not
showing it to older people. You know, [snorts]
you're sick for watching that, you echo.
You're sick for watching that, lad.
really sick for watching that.
You're a [snorts] sick can.
I'm surprised it's still on the internet,
Echo. I'm surprised it's still on the internet.
Yeah, you're a sick bastard. G, man.
Yeah, that's how Ant-Man watched it. He
said that they just played it.
Yeah, Ant-Man. That's how Ant-Man saw
it. They just played it basically.
And um Yeah.
Yeah, she asked me what my body count
was. I just told her it was three. Even
though it's seven, I just told her I
just told her it was three.
Could you imagine you asked a woman's
body count the day after meeting her Dr. Echo,
I think white lights would have a lot to
say about that.
Yeah, if you asked a woman her body count
so soon, I think people have a lot to
say about that. Dr. Echo,
that's one to add into the double
standards, isn't it, Greavvesy?
Pretty sure they would. Yeah.
No, she doesn't want a low. She doesn't
want She doesn't want a low, but she
doesn't want a high body count. That's
why she was asking me. I just said three.
That is I think that's double standards,
isn't it, Grezy? Literally the double
standards folder. That's a good one,
bro. When it comes to meeting, when they
moan about uh when they moan about dating, um
when um yeah, the body count thing would
definitely been a brought up.
It would have definitely been brought up.
Yeah, that would have definitely been brought up.
Didn't agree with you. Yeah,
they'd come after me with a hammer if I
asked a woman her body count the day
after meeting her.
for them. Well,
they're allowed to do that, aren't they?
No questions asked.
hit the double standards folder.
So, Grezy, you know, you're you're going
to have to wait, right?
I'm I'm going to have to wait. Yes.
Until it's been made.
The double sanders folder. That's a good one, bro. Yeah.
You're just going to have to wait until
it's been made, Grezy.
And then what if and what if someone
else has a double standards folder? Greavves it.
What would that make them? Yeah. Yep.
You know what you should do? Yeah. Every
new person you meet, Greavves. Yeah.
Have him as is he number one, is he
number two, is he number three, is he
number four. [laughter]
Grezy, is that funny?
That's funny, bro.
All [snorts] I wanted was to do was be
your friend. All
right, Greasy. I just wanted to be your friend.
Don't get [ __ ] sassy with me.
Yeah, I just message her now.
I just messaged her now saying, "Do you hate me?"
That's a lovely little message, isn't it?
I can do what you're doing as well. If you want,
I'm just going to start trolling her
now. [ __ ] it in it, lad. Yeah, I'm going
to start trolling, bro.
But no, seriously, she started being a [ __ ] yesterday.
Yeah, pretty much dusty. Back to square one.
Pretty much, lad.
And the thing is, the only [ __ ] up
thing about it, Dusty, is we can't use
that. We can't use dating apps. We'd
have to go out approaching
[ __ ] retards, isn't it? But people on
Reddit say it will be different, Dusty.
People on Reddit say it will be different. Greasy.
Uh, Dusty, sorry. Oh, [ __ ]
Um, basically I tried to meet basically
I tried to uh I said yesterday um
I said basically yesterday uh fire stick
because they're um
because they're fire um because they're Um
um because their exams finished, I said,
"Oh, do you want to meet up next Friday?" Um
um I said, "Oh, do you want to meet up
Friday?" Then she says, "Oh, I'm busy
Friday. I'll I'll let you know." T
When obviously when someone says they
let you know, it's over.
No, I one second, bro. And then she was
just starting to get like really rude
and stuff and then like started playing
the victim and [ __ ]
Like she didn't ask me my body count.
Like she didn't say this to me like just
proper started being a [ __ ] cuz I'm not
I weren't born yesterday, bro. I'm 28.
How long have I been in this game now, bro?
Someone says they let you know it's it's
over, lad. Simple. In my experiences,
even when I was 17, it's over. You know,
and this is why I said to you, Fire
Stick, well, you already know all of
this stuff anyways, bro. But you need to
try to meet people ASAP
when you approach them within a week maximum.
The only reason I gave them the benefit
of the doubt was cuz they had exams and
they showed me their exams and so I
thought, "Fuck it. Why not?" They're
talking every day. So, but remember,
bro, no one's ever too busy. Fire stick.
Remember that, lad. Work. No work. No
one is ever too busy.
No, I said I was going to go to church,
Dusty. That's what I said. I wasn't
going to study. I said I I would have
went to church because why not? Is it?
But it doesn't matter. They're all
excuses anyways. It's just an excuse
anyways. So, it's, you know,
it's always they'll just find another excuse.
Whether it's age, whether it's religion,
they'll always find an excuse, bro. Too
old, too young. You You know how it is, lad.
[snorts] No, I don't think they care
about your body, bro. I don't think they
care about your body.
I don't believe that.
But yeah, basically, and I brought up
Fire Stick. Why is none of your exes
have to have these requirements? Why did
none of your exes have to go to church?
Why did none of your exes have to um study?
I find it weird how they make mistakes
with the wrong guy, but not the right
guy. I find that to be funny, but yeah.
And funny how they're fast enough to
respond when you're arguing with them.
Rezy. Well, when they when they've got
something to argue. Yeah.
But then even but the thing is Dusty,
even if you did go get into it, they'd
find another excuse and another excuse
and another excuse and another excuse.
I know I know all of this stuff. I know
all of this stuff. But Fire Stick, she
said that she was going to meet me. She
said she said that she was going to meet
me. So when someone tells me something
and they've been speaking to me for a
month, I thought, you know, you know
what it is. Yeah. So
yeah, exactly. No one's ever too busy,
bro. No one's ever too busy.
Yeah, exactly. Yeah.
And I brought up to her as well, well,
how comes none of your exes had to go to
church? Why did none of your exes have to study?
truth. That was annoying me from the
get- go, but I just didn't say anything
because it is what it is, isn't it?
That was annoying me, bro. That's And
they were Albanian as well. So, you
know, they were similar to me. You know,
they look similar to me, these people.
So, why why is there different rules for me now?
[ __ ] off, [ __ ] Yeah.
And yeah, so what I'm saying is this is
always going to go around in circles.
Fire stick. This is always going to be
the problem in this country trying to
date. It's always going to be some [ __ ]
As you know, bro, as as as you know. So,
it's always going to be an excuse.
You know, you got people with three kids
thinking they're better than you
nowadays. So, good luck, lad. That's all
I can say to you. Good luck.
I might have went out today. I'm not
sure. But obviously it's Monday so no
[snorts] maybe it was like a Friday
Saturday I might have gave out went out
give it a while
but I don't know lad for a while so I
don't know I don't know
if I knew this I would have went out
last week you see if I knew this I would
have went out last week.
I would have went out on the 28th. You
see, if I knew this uh bick, I would
have went out last week. You get me? So yeah,
now. What she's saying doesn't make any sense.
You is Yeah,
Oh, what do you reckon Reddit would have
to say about this, Grezy?
What do you think Reddit would have to
say about this, Grezy? Huh?
[ __ ] hell. I need to bring these cops down, bro. Yeah,
I'm going to jump off. I'll be back later. Yeah,
hopefully some more people will be on. and see.