Yo, I hope the Wi-Fi works in here now.
Just s having a coke. I want to go on a [ __ ] mission.
>> It's [ __ ] Monday. It's [ __ ]
to do on a Monday. It's [ __ ] boring, man.
It's [ __ ] dead on Monday, bro. Even
later on, it's [ __ ]
Just went for a walking up here. Oh, [ __ ]
this nice cloak. Oh, bit of lemon and ice.
>> Yeah, man. Like I said, you people can't
take a day off of YouTube, lad. You
don't need to You don't need to welcome
me back anywhere, mate.
You need to worry. You need to worry
about taking a day off of YouTube before
you talk about anyone. basically
I would drink but there's no point in this Monday
it's [ __ ] dead bro
the Wednesday I could have went and hit
a madness but Yeah,
get some [ __ ] chicken. But no, I'm stay man
and [ __ ] You know what I mean? Yeah.
Yeah, it's a madness, bro.
This should have happened on a [ __ ]
Thursday, bro, or Friday or even a
Wednesday would have went on a madness.
But there's no point. Monday's dead, bro.
Yesterday would have been right. It's dead today. do anything.
>> But to be fair, it doesn't feel like a
Monday. To be fair,
>> it doesn't feel like a Monday.
broke for a little bit. Oh,
doesn't even feel like a bastard Monday,
does it? Monday is dead.
I need to do some exercise, you know.
No, I'm just having Coke. There's no
point drinking. It's a Monday,
so there's no point. No one's out. No
one's going to be out. So, it's a
Monday, ain't it? So it's pointless.
I have to go out for a walk and just Yeah.
Sad sad sad times e bro
all right today as well. It would have
been nice if it was a Thursday Friday or Saturday.
I was drinking coke.
I need a good piss up, mate. That's what
I need. But [ __ ] It's not It's not
not busy, is it? It's quiet.
There's no point drinking today. It just
ruined the detox. Yeah, mom.
activity. He [ __ ] drinks every day,
but [ __ ] that.
I have drunk couple months. Yeah,
it's just dead, isn't it? Yeah, man.
Pointing the stranger, bro. Pointless as [ __ ]
like damn, but I'm not going to do it.
Obviously, I'm not going to do it
because it's not [ __ ] Thursday,
Friday. I would have just got smashed.
I would have just got smashed, bro.
Yo, we just got smashed, bro. And I mean
smashed, mass, bro.
[ __ ] whiskey everything, man.
Probably would have started on the
Guinness on a whiskey to be fair. Up, man.
Fed up, bro. Fed up.
I needed like a [ __ ] dopamine rush
from some [ __ ] but
I'm not drinking. I ain't drinking. pointless.
Probably there's some people that just
wait until pubs open and they drink from
the time they wake up to the time the
time it opens to the time it closes.
That's mad. Imagine doing that on a Monday.
Yeah, I'm just chilling with a coke, bro.
Just went for a stroll where my little
legs took me. I had to clear my head. So,
just drinking some normal coke. Yeah. Oh, yeah.
No point drinking cuz it's Monday. I
want to go on a madness today. But I
want to do I want to go on a mission.
But like I said, you can't. It's Monday. It's [ __ ]
I feel this way on a Monday, is it?
All that [ __ ] that happened yesterday, man. Huh?
I don't really care to be honest with
you, mate. I don't want to hear about
it. I've had enough of it to be honest with you.
I've had enough of it to be fair. Don't care.
I'm my name. I'm a man on name mission.
I get another Coke. Maybe
not drinking that.
Maybe I can have one Guinness, right?
One won't hurt. Nah,
I'm not drinking. But
we'll save ourselves. We'll save
ourselves. Don't worry.
Yeah, I was going to be honest. Mhm. Oh, [ __ ]
I just met just um said to her yesterday
since her exams and all that's finished,
I said, "Oh, do you want to meet? Do you
want to meet up on Do you want to meet
up next Friday?"
Um, and she said, "Oh, I'm busy next
Friday." I said, "What about Saturday?"
She's like, "Oh, I'll let you know." I
was like, "What do you mean you let me
know? We've been speaking for a month.
We've had plans to meet. You said you
wanted to meet. Now you're making
excuses. Now she just coming out with
mad [ __ ] contradicting herself,
[ __ ] had it all [ __ ] morning as
well with a [ __ ] Bad, bad, bad, bad."
And that that just proves my point all
along that even if you speak to someone,
you know, for a month, they'll still
[ __ ] your ass over and feel no two ways
about it. I said this all along before I
had a pure prime example. Like I knew
all of this cuz
cuz it's simp it's it's obvious, bro.
You know what I mean?
It's so obvious, isn't it? It's [ __ ] obvious, bro. Well,
just being a [ __ ] basically. Excuse my
French. Not really.
No, I'm good, bro. I'm good. No, I'm all right, bro.
Yesterday was so weird, bro. It was a
weird day yesterday.
I'll find someone soon. Yeah. Thank you,
bro. You keep telling yourself that. I'd
rather you have the hope than me, brother.
And to be honest with you, I did see it
coming, but at the same time, I didn't.
Yeah. I mean, he's not coming anyways.
I'm not talking about this because it's
not happening, bro. I'm not talking
about something that's never going to
happen. It's pointless. I believe it
when I see it.
Same analogy goes to Timmy. I believe it
And that's it. No energy is going to go
into that until it happens. Until I see
that come from that train. I'm not
talking about it. Simple.
Want to go on a madness today, bro. But
it's [ __ ] Monday, so I can't [ __ ]
this Monday. [ __ ] bro.
I thought that people was just about to
come in, bro.
Five, six, seven, eight. N
goodness. [ __ ] it, bro.
Oh, [ __ ] I just got one in it.
This is where the badness stop. Think about
Can I get Guinness, please?
Did you get my message on um Instagram?
You hear what I said?
Oh, it's only £3.95 here to Guinness.
Dirt cheap, bro. Dirt cheap, bro. Of course,
>> what I was basically saying, Grez, is
them army [ __ ] were laughing at us, mocking you.
I don't know why it makes me laugh, but
mocking you. Green. Mocking you.
Should we go see the mommy comes today?
Gy, I don't think they're out on Monday.
I don't think they're out on one day. Greasy.
I want to be on a mission.
Say I'm on a mission.
No, I can't be doing it on Monday. Can't
be doing that on Monday. But thank you.
Lovely pine again. Yay.
You start feeding it with one could be [ __ ] bad.
I got my haircut on or anything. But
it's [ __ ] Monday. Who's going to be
out on a Monday, man? [ __ ] me.
Not worth going out on a Monday.
That's the thing, Grezy, is that no
one's going to be out on the Monday.
It's [ __ ] bro.
Let's end the day with some lovely roulette.
Remember when that account said that?
Let's end the day with some lovely roulette. that.
No, you can't do that, bro. I'm not
doing that [ __ ]
Anyone would actually be out on there.
think they actually would.
Let's hit it.
No, bro. Can't.
I don't think so, bro. I don't think so.
Maybe like a Wednesday, but I don't
think people will be out on a Monday.
>> I don't think they will be, but
3.95. It's a bargain, bro.
You like this kind of content, don't you, Grezy?
Yeah, Grezy, this is more your content,
isn't it, Captain?
Breezy loves this loves this [ __ ] Yeah,
I'm just going to have one
and that's it.
You know what I'm like on the phone
though when I've had a few drinks.
Greasy. I'm a maniac.
You know this, don't you, Grezy?
You know that, don't you, Grezy?
So, I've started the d I've double I've
started the double standards folder. Grezy.
I'm going to be You're going to have to
wait for it to be made. It should be
with you today at about 900 p.m. Really? Yes.
Yeah. It should be with you at about 9:00 p.m.
You'll see. Captain. Um,
I'm going to say that a woman's allowed
to ask you your body count straight
away, but you're not allowed to ask her
her body count straight away.
You get me, bro?
It's uh and the fact that they can try
to meet you straight away and you can't
meet them straight away. Bit bias, isn't
it? Bit sexist. Yeah.
I want to stay out, but it's [ __ ] Monday, bro.
What am I going to be doing on a [ __ ] Monday?
Dead, bro. Absolutely dead.
My phone's on 17% as well. [ __ ] man.
A couple of sips and Peter Bell is
already tipsy greasy on the good old Guinness.
With you, boss.
Okay. With you, boss. me.
What do you reckon? Do you reckon the
pubs will be busy on a Monday? I don't
think so. What do you think?
I don't think so. No,
it'll be [ __ ] bro.
I think people do this every day. Agrees.
They actually do this every day. Yeah,
but it's dead, bro. It's a Monday. No
one's going to be out. I want to stay
out. I want to do a madness, bro. But
I haven't got my haircut and
well, that doesn't even matter anyways
to be fair.
But the thing is, yeah,
you know what? I might go out, you know,
but I'll have to go home and then go back out.
But obviously has to be all right with Grezy Perth.
What you saying, Greavves? Got hit.
What do you reckon, lad? [ __ ] descendant.
I have to run about gry first.
Yeah. You want you want to do it? Yeah.
Go out. [ __ ] it. Fine.
Pick up a couple of here. Go back and
then [ __ ] off somewhere more further.
But what kind of trouble you're going to
be getting into today, Greasy?
Let's see what kind of trouble. I just
feel like going madness, bro. I feel
like going out [ __ ] madness, bro.
I can't lie to you, bro. [ __ ] it in it.
That pissed me off, bro. That actually
proper pissed me off, bro.
Right, I'm going have a couple here then.
And then goes from here.
One second, bro.
I'm just drinking dinner. It I'll just
drink when I'm out.
We're going to go on a [ __ ] madness.
I haven't got my hair down or anything,
but doesn't matter.
look nicely groomed and stuff. You know
what I mean?
Now, I'm not filming everything, bro.
I wonder how many numbers you'll get on
the [ __ ] Monday. That'll be interesting, bro.
I'm thinking maybe three. I need to go
back home and then go from there.
Where's my phone and that?
It's going to be a madness. That person
on the on the phone were an absolute
[ __ ] today, bro. They were an absolute
I have to agree. They were an absolute
[ __ ] in it.
Absolute [ __ ] mate.
Oh, the account's back. Greasy. The
The account's back, lad. Yeah. One time,
I'm going to have a couple here. I need
to go home and then go into central
London. It's going to be a long day, bro.
It's going to be a long day, though,
because I've already found my mama, Annie.
I knew you'd come back after that video.
I knew it. Hey, bro. I swear I said
after that video, this guy's going to come back.
I knew 100% he was going to come back, bro.
>> Yeah, exactly, bro. 100%. Stick your
middle finger up and it Yeah, I would
give it a whirl. I would [ __ ] give it
a little whirl.
I'm going to have a couple here. Give a
good price. Go home. Charge a phone. [ __ ] off.
You want my opinion, Annie? Yeah, we're all [ __ ]
They are absolutely all [ __ ] They are.
Watch. I'm going to go [ __ ] I'm on a
mad list today, bro. Trust me. I'm so
[ __ ] mad today, bro. Trust me. Watch.
Yeah. He hasn't even started, bro.
Has not even started by the slightest.
Someone some con playing the slot. [ __ ] bro.
Because you already found your mama and
you already found your mama.
That's funny, bro.
No, I'm never letting them win. Never.
I know it's a women. They're [ __ ]
conscious. Oh, yeah. You're good
looking. You're handsome. You'll find
someone at the right place, the right
time. Oh, really? So, why isn't that
person you then? That's what I said,
Annie. Why is that person not you then?
Why is that person not you then, mate?
You know what I'm saying?
You got me, lad.
Never going to win, bro. Never going to
win. We're going to fend it hard, bro.
I'm on the piss, Mr. Bean.
I'm not even get my hair cut my bad.
Looks fine, bro.
Looks fine. Anyways, yeah, of course,
Mr. Bean, we're going on a [ __ ]
madness today. Let's hit it. Let's hit
it. Isn't that right, Boozy? I'm all showered up
in it, bro. Let's hit it, bro.
All right, Mr. Beam, we're going to hit it.
We're going to hit it, bro.
So, why couldn't I get attached anymore
then? Uh, Annie,
why couldn't I get attached anymore then, Annie?
Do you remember a reason or what?
Probably have to get some food when I
get to the other side. To be fair, my
phone's on 14%. [ __ ] Poor [ __ ]
Did you watch that three guys one
hammer? Annie, it was sick, bro.
Did you watch it? It's proper sick, bro.
You already found your mama.
Because you've already found your mama.
Now, there's no one that's dead.
It's [ __ ] dead, right?
I don't even know if I can. No, I am
going out. I am going out. I have to go
out. I said I'm going to go out. I need
a new collection.
I need a new collection. Is that right, GZ?
Probably just stick to Guinness to be fair.
Yeah, I need to get another one and then
I need to get out. I need to hit the
city in a bit, bro.
Messed up. Yeah.
Hey, who's that Indonesian fellow? Ali,
who's the Indonesian fell off?
We're going to send it off today. Don't
worry about it. Send it on.
Who's the Indonesian fellow?
Let me get another one and then dip.
Got the beard. Got the beard going. Got
the hair going. Bro, I ain't got my
haircut. I don't give a [ __ ] bro. That
makes a [ __ ] indifference.
That's never going to happen, Ghost. So,
you got more chance of winning the lottery, mate. Yeah. [ __ ] horrible. Hello.
Stop it. Stop it with your comments.
Stop it with your comments, bro. Stop
it. Please stop it. Bless.
Well, I've got people looking at me.
Bless the Indonesian fellow.
The Indonesian fellow.
Yeah, you can come out to the No, I'm
not going out with him. He comes to my style.
That's the Indonesian fellow.
I'm going to find my number. Annie,
why can't I deprive you of content then? Annie,
why can't I deprive him of content?
Am I not allowed to deprive him of
content then? Is that not allowed?
What's the time? 3:35, right? Okay,
I might. Let me get another Guinness.
Can I get another Guinness, please?
down this, bro.
Oh, you over. Yeah, thanks. I'm just
going to down the skin this, bro.
I'm going to down it. I'm just going to
down the [ __ ]
I'm going to down it because we don't
have no time to start uh
[ __ ] around and stuff like the location.
Yeah, I'm going to completely get on it, bro.
Because he's already found. He's my
about seven quid. But I'm in a place
now. I'm not in central London yet. I'll
be in central London later
because he's already found his mama. Now
there's a H on it now. Greavesy.
Now there's a H on it. Oh, Guinness is coming now. Come in. Thank you.
I'm going to sound the skin.
Let's see if I still got it. Yeah.
Give me 10 seconds for that one. 1 2 3 4
5 6 7 8 9 10
Oh my god.
Jesus Christ. I see that.
They didn't speak to her. They don't
know who she is. What's
They don't speak to her. They don't know
who she is.
Oh god. What's that? Chill. Chill. This no, bro. Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Oh, [ __ ] me. Probably
Jesus Christ, bro. That is a [ __ ] nuts.
Anyway, I'm going to go back to the
house. I'm going to [ __ ] charge the
phone up. I'm going to charge the phone
up and then
I'm going to charge the phone up and
then uh Yeah. Get going, bro. I'm going
to blow up. I'm going to send it hard.
Look at this.
[ __ ] hell. [ __ ] gobbled a lot,
mate. Jesus Christ.
Well, I'm going to go now anyways.
Drive back to the house, charge up the
phone, and just get on it. Get on the
be back in about 3 hours, 4 hours. I
think some [ __ ] numbers. Yeah, in a
bit. I'll be back later.