Yep.
There we go, bro. Okay. Now,
I just want to say something. UK silent. Yeah.
Before you talk about buying tickets, bro,
I I booked to go to America and I didn't go.
How much money do you think that cost? I
mean, I booked to go to America. I
didn't go. I booked to go to Nottingham
and I didn't go. So, I mean, that
doesn't mean anything, bro. Anybody can
buy a ticket and then get a refund. And
unless you're actually in London, then
people will actually believe it.
then people will actually believe it,
bro. You get what I'm saying? Like, do
you actually get what I'm saying, bro?
Like, I've just I've just gave you two analogies.
That doesn't mean anything, bro. Buying
a ticket. We'll actually see you when
you're in London. One thing buying a
ticket, bro, and there's one thing
getting on that train and coming all the
way here. Big difference. Big
difference. Yeah. He's not going to be
outside. He's not going to be outside my mind, bro.
So yeah, it's not going to happen
because it will be the last thing he
does. Trust me, bro. So yeah, I'm not
talking about it no more till it happens
anyways, bro. I don't want to hear about
I've been hearing this, hearing this,
hearing this, hearing this, hearing
this. I will see it when it happens.
I'll believe it when it happens, bro.
Simple as that. Yeah.
And that's it. I had I see someone on L
J saying that I'm out of I'm out of
shape. Nothing out of shape about me,
bro. My weight is completely completely normal.
Maybe I'm not muscly at the minute cuz I
don't go gym, bro. Seriously, I'm out of
shape. Please. Okay, bro. You can This
is what I'm trying to say, bro. Yeah,
this is exactly what I'm trying to say
with this community, bro. Is that they
big themselves up, right? And they talk
[ __ ] about other people, but they will
not they will not show themselves
because they're the fat ones. They're
the obese ones. You don't understand.
All of this on this community is self-p
projecting from these people. It's
self-p projectors. Why do you think it's
the only community where only 5% people
show their face? Cuz it's cuz it's the
truth. Because it's cuz it's right, bro.
If they're biging themselves up, they'd
show themselves just like I would. But
they can't because they're fat and ugly.
Simple as that. So it doesn't matter
what fat, ugly self-p projectors say
with no life, lad. These people are so
fat, bro. They probably can't even leave
the house and walk. It's self
projection. It's self- projecting. Just
like Timmy self-p projects. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying, bro? And it's
fine, bro. It's fine. Yeah. It is self-p
projecting and you know it is. And you
know I'm right as well, bro. You can laugh. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
But yeah, if this fat comes coming, if
this fat comes on the door tomorrow, I'm
finishing him, bro. I'm finishing him
worse than anyone else, bro. cuz he need
he needs to learn. He can't keep coming
back. He can't keep coming on YouTube
trying to [ __ ] at the big man. I'm
going to finish him, bro. Trust me, I
will finish him. Trust me.
That'll teach him to try to be the big
man for YouTube. Yeah. Self-protting
jealous little [ __ ] And I'll say it as
well, bro. He is He is a self-projecting
little jealous [ __ ] He is. He is, bro.
Trust me, he is.
He literally is a self-proing jealous
little [ __ ] He is. Yeah. Thinks he's
going to come on people's doors. Him of
all people. Okay. We'll see you tomorrow then.
I was just saying Greg that I booked to
go to America. I didn't go. I booked to
go to Nottingham. I didn't go. So
booking a ticket doesn't mean anything. Yeah.
So simple as that. And I'll tell my mom
anyways if this [ __ ] comes. I'll tell my
mom why. This little jealous [ __ ] Am I
going to be able to sleep tonight? 100%
100% I'm I'm going to be able to sleep
because I've already beaten Timmy and
Timmy's not coming anywhere anyways. So,
like I said, there's a difference
between buying a ticket and then actually coming.
There's a big big big big difference.
Yeah, I'll be able to sleep just
perfect. I've already beaten Timmy and
Timmy's not coming anyways, even if I
couldn't beat him. So, I'll sleep
completely fine. This is what you people
do on this community. You all talk talk
talk, but none of you is going to do anything.
Well, no. I I I didn't go to America
when I booked it the first time.
Everyone knew that. The first time I
booked it. No, I didn't go. Everyone
knew I didn't go. Yeah. And that was two
grand down the drain. Yeah. So, so if
someone's bought a ticket to go
somewhere, there's every chance that
they're not going to go either. Do you
get it? Especially someone like him.
Anyways, bro, I'm not talking until I
see this come in London. I'm not
talking. I'm not talking anymore, bro.
Simple as that. I'm not saying anything
until I see this [ __ ] in London. I'm not saying nothing.
Yeah. And I'll tell all she wants to
know, bro. I'll tell everything that
this little jealous [ __ ] keeps drawing
me out on YouTube. And I'm about to
message his family. He started on me. I
can safely say it. I'm Am I lying when
I'm saying that? No, Grezy. This guy
actually started just in case, you know,
it does cause problems. I can literally
tell you straight, bro, that he started
it. I'll finish it. Simple. He wanted to
be a little jealous showoff on YouTube,
then he got it. Simple. That's it. He
wants to be a jealous [ __ ] And I'm not
doing it. And I'm not playing fair with
him. I'm going to batter him. I am going
to batter him. I don't care if he's a
[ __ ] If he's he can't be that
disabled when he's mentioning people's
names on YouTube, you know, time and
time and time and time and time again, bro.
Yeah. I am going to batter the [ __ ]
Trust me. Yeah. Ser simple as that, bro.
and he started it. Read down my line by
him me saying he started it just like a
lot of these jealous self-p projectors
want to self project their life onto
other people trying to draw people out
and put people and trying to put people
in a bad mood. Do you understand, bro?
Am I lying?
All cuz he's jealous. Cuz he's a
gambling addict. This is all this is.
This is jealousy. This and I'm not the
first person to say it with these people, bro.
I mean this is jealousy. I'm sure it is,
bro. This is so it is jealousy. When you
look at the the way these people look
their lives, it's jealousy. There's a
reason why all eyes are on you because
they're jealous of you. They can keep
saying that you ain't got nothing. They
can keep saying that that you ain't got
anything to be jealous of. Look at them.
Look at these people. Yeah. Even the
ones that show themselves. What have
they got? Nothing, bro. You get me? Yeah.
Simple as that, bro. You ain't going
nowhere. [ __ ] fat [ __ ]
[ __ ] fat little showoff. I'm I I'll
show him tomorrow, bro. Watch. I'll show
the little [ __ ] tomorrow. Bro, he
couldn't even beat me last time, bro.
And there was two of them.
There was two of the [ __ ]
There was [ __ ] two of the [ __ ]
There was two of the [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
And they still could have beat me. And
how many years ago was that?
He ain't going to get a draw, bro. He
ain't going to get a draw. Yeah, bro.
But do you see what I mean, Grezy? With
the people in this community and their jealousy.
Do you see what I mean, bro? You draw me
out. I told you about yourself and now
you're saying that you're going to come
on my door. Oh, we'll see you tomorrow
then, won't we? We'll see you tomorrow
We will see tomorrow. Yeah.
Anyways, I'm not talking about this now
until I actually see the [ __ ] in London.
One second, bro. The [ __ ] phone's gone again. Yeah. Anyways,
I'm not talking about it anyways until I
Sorry, my phone. I had to reset my
phone, bro. Anyways, I'm not talking
about this now until I see the [ __ ] in London,
right? I'm not talking about this now anyways
because there's no point getting excited
for something that's not going to
happen. I believe it when I see it. I
think that's fair enough, isn't it, Greavesy?
Yeah. And that's as simple as that.
Yeah, that's that lad. I'm not talking
about it no more. So, yeah,
I'm changing the subject, lad. Yeah.
Hold on a second. Oh, did you like my
collection of mummas? Um, Grezy,
did you like my collection of mummas?
But yeah, all of these people that are
bigger themselves up in large A's and
stuff, they can never show themselves.
Remember that. They can never show their
faces cuz they're fat and ugly, bro.
They're probably so fat they can't even
leave the house. That's how bad it is.
Self projectors and not one person can
prove me wrong. Unlike I could I could
do it. I could do it if I jumped on a
community talking [ __ ] about people. I
could I could prove I could prove them
wrong. I could prove they were
speculating. Everything that they say
about me, Grezy, I could prove that they
were speculating. Do you get it? They
can't because they know they're fat and
ugly. And they knew if they come on
camera, they know they can't never talk
about. They can't talk about anyone
anyways, but they know for sure they
could never ever come back on here
without being picked on by other people.
That's why none of them show their faces.
It's not because of this doxing stuff.
It's not. It's cuz they're ugly as [ __ ]
bro. Fat and ugly, bro. That's what they
are in this community. They're more than
out of shape. I'm not even out of shape,
you [ __ ] [ __ ] I walked about
[ __ ] 10 miles yesterday. Show
yourself on camera, Mr. big man and they
can never do that and that's one you'll
always have over them and all the ones
that haven't in the past when they've
been seen to be what they look like
they've always been fat and ugly. So
yeah, that's all I wanted to say about
that basically. Yeah, bro. So yeah, they
can never show themselves. They can
never show their faces.
Horrible looking people in this
community, bro. Horrible looking people
in this community.
Doesn't matter where I went.
Doesn't matter where I went, lad.
About out of shape, you [ __ ]
self-reflectctor. I ain't even got a
beer belly, you [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah,
like I said, it's just self projecting
from these people,
just like it has and it will always be. Yep.
Let it get to me. These people don't get
to me. These people are
self-reflectctors. I laugh at them.
These fat ugly people don't get to me. I
laugh at him, lad. I still show my face.
I still come on camera. They don't They
don't get to me. Oh, bless you. You
think these little weasels on this
community, these [ __ ] fat ugly self
projectors get to me? Oh, bless.
Oh, bless. You think these people know?
It doesn't get to me. That's why I so
that's why I put myself on camera.
Something that these people can't do. It
doesn't get to me because when they say
stuff about me, I could put myself on
camera. They can't put themselves on
camera due to their ugliness. That's the
big That's the big difference, you know?
That's the big difference, you know.
They don't stop me showing my face. I
stop them showing their face. Remember
that because they're self-reflectors.
Talk about themselves every day.
That's their life, isn't it? Is on
YouTube talking about themselves.
I was busy yesterday. I was busy today.
Do you get it, lad?
No. No. No. No. No. Bro, like I said,
Mr. B, I'll see it when it happens, bro.
When I see that [ __ ] in London, then
I'll start talking and getting excited,
but until then, I mean, yeah, I'm not
I'm not talking about it, bro,
cuz it's not going to happen.
I boo I booked tickets to go to
Nottingham. I think it was Was it last
year? Maybe the year before. I didn't even go.
This couldn't be bothered.
So, I'll believe it when I see it, lad.
When I see somebody in my city, bro,
then I believe it. I think that's fair
enough, is it?
You get me, bro? Yeah, bro.
Yeah, we'll see anyways, bro. We'll see.
Yeah, there's no point in talking about
something, bro, and then and you getting
disappointed. Did you get me, lad? Nope. No, lad.
I see Joseph [ __ ] is going on about me
again. Another one that's obsessed.
Well, at least I know I'm doing
something right when you've got all of
these old men obsessed with you, I
guess, isn't it?
You still there, Grezy?
I've never been anyone's wingman, bro.
Never have, never will. Yeah.
So, if this [ __ ] don't come tomorrow,
anytime now he talks about meeting people, whatever,
that's like, bro, you you you just laugh
at it. Well, we laugh at it anyways cuz
he's not about it, but we just laugh at
it, bro. Is it?
We'll just laugh about it in it. Yeah.
We will just laugh about it, lads.
We will just laugh about it.
Which we laugh about it now, but we can
definitely laugh about it even more. Yeah,
he's really got proper disabilities if
he actually thinks he's going to come on
someone's door and start making a scene.
It didn't work the last time. See, it
never happened last time when he come
three years ago.
I beat him and I beat Tiger three years
ago. He didn't even win with another
person. And that was three years ago.
You know what I'm saying? He's a proper
[ __ ] I can tell he's a [ __ ] lad.
He is going to get proper hurt, bro.
Trust me. Proper proper hurt.
Cheeky. He's a cheeky [ __ ] bro. He's a
cheeky cheeky bastard. Yeah.
I'm not even going to tell you what I'm
going to do as well. Yeah, simple.
Duh. All because Yeah, this is all
because Tibby's done these balls in and
he's a little jealous self-reflector.
Tell me I'm not telling the truth, bro.
Tell me I'm not telling the truth.
Am I lying, bro? Like, be honest. Like,
honestly, am I lying, Greg? Am I lying
or am I telling the truth? Anyone else?
Am I lying? I'm telling the truth. I'm
spitting facts, bro. I'm spitting
[ __ ] facts. Every time this guy does
his balls in, he likes to try to put
other people in a bad mood. Tries to
draw people out. He tries to draw people
the [ __ ] out every time, bro. of his
jealousy which is which I'm the first
person he goes for. So I said, "Okay,
you keep messaging me. You keep
messaging me. I'll message your family."
Simple as that.
So what is he really going to say
tomorrow? Why he's If he came on if he
comes on the door, what are you really
What are they really going to say? Well,
that I brought them here. You can't even
say that. You wanted to try to show off
YouTube. You won't keep my name out your
fat something jealous mouth just like a
lot of other people on here. So you're
going to get battered and it's sure. So
don't start crying when you get
battered. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
And this is what they're like on here,
bro. They're just jealous, jealous ass
people. And it's the truth. And you know
it is. You know it is as well. That's
why you laugh at it when I say it
because it's the truth. Yeah.
It's the absolute truth, lad. Yeah.
Yeah. I sound scared. No. Oh, I really
really don't sound scared. There's
nothing scared about me whatsoever. I'm
just a bit hung over cuz of the drink.
Scared? Scared of a [ __ ] No, I don't think so. Yeah.
No, no, no.
So yeah, they're just self-reflectors on
this community, bro. Proper proper
self-reflectors on this community, including Timmy.
Anyone that's younger and better looking
than these people,
they don't like it. I noticed that from
ages ago, bro. But when I said it,
people didn't believe me. Literally,
honestly, people didn't believe me, bro.
Anyone that's younger and better looking
than these people, they don't like. Have
you noticed why most of the people in
this community look the same? Fat,
[ __ ] ugly. Have you noticed, bro?
It's jealousy. It is absolute 100%
jealousy. You know, the amount I've
asked people I've asked these people
several times, come on camera. Yeah. and
put their um put their face on, they
won't do it. Yeah, that's it, bro.
Weirdo. I'm I'm I'm agree with you. I'm
I'm I'm um going to come off this
channel, bro, in a couple of days.
Anyways, bro, I'm going to link you my
new one later on, bro. Yeah,
we need Triple H and um a couple of
other people, but they'll get it just
another way, bro.
I'm going to start putting some more
content on that channel, bro. There's
already some good videos on there, to be
honest. After I beat this [ __ ] clown
tomorrow, I'm I'm going, bro. Maybe a
couple days to be honest. Yeah, really.
I won't leave. Yes, I will leave, mate.
Watch me do it. I [ __ ] will.
I [ __ ] will, mate. And another thing,
greasy. Yeah. Like, um, cuz we only
speak to like six, seven people.
So, and the rest were just stalking
weirdo little jealous haters. So, we
might as well just get them six, seven
people and just [ __ ] off, bro.
Yeah. No one cares, bro. See you later.
Yeah. So, um, I got Steven Howard's
email. I got your Instagram. That's two.
We're going to have to wait for Triple H
to come back
and yeah, bro. We'll just have our own
little community and add some more other
people to it.
Did you like my collection of M's music?
You didn't get any responses back, but
it was a Monday in it. Yeah. So,
did you like them? Did you like the
eyes, Grezy? the western eyes.
Oh, look at these people. They're so
sad. Someone clone Triple H and get PJ's
new channel. You're never going to get
my new channel, lad. Never.
Never. It's never going to happen. You
sad little bastards. And I mean it. I
swear to God, Greavves. I mean it, bro.
Are you serious about it, bro?
Are you serious? Like, I'm done, bro. Honestly. Yeah.
Nah, mate. I messaged all of them, lad.
Boy, that Christian Izzy thingy was
[ __ ] up, bro. [ __ ] up.
And it I agree with you. Was it actually
[ __ ] up? It was [ __ ] up in it, bro.
So, yeah. No one's going to find a new
channel, lad. No, just starve these
[ __ ] We'll just go on like we usually
will, but we'll just be on another
channel doing it.
Yeah. And I'll give some of my like
friends the channel as well
cuz these people are weird, lad. They're [ __ ] weirdos.
To be honest, I haven't really been on.
I wasn't on most today.
Yesterday I was only on for a little bit.
Yeah, bro. Cuz
the same thing is just going to go round
and round and round in circles and gives
everyone a headache again.
You get me, bro?
I might talk about this community before
I [ __ ] off, bro.
Because obviously I need to give people
the new channel, isn't it?
Just I just think this whole community is weird.
I just think all of it is just weird. I
don't know about you, bro. I just think
all of it is weird.
Like from start to finish. Not I don't
know about you, bro. You know,
then they ask, look, I'm reading the
chat right now. Yeah. Why does he think
everyone is jealous of him? You're
asking questions that people have
answered already multiple times. Why ask
a question when someone answers the
question? When somebody answers the question,
you you ask the same question.
What What's the point of asking
something, then when someone answers it,
you ask the same question again?
That doesn't make any sense.
You ask the question, someone's already
answered the question.
Yeah, I've asked these people multiple
times to come on camera. They will not
do it. They will not show their faces.
They will not show their weight. They
will not show anything that they claim
that they've got. Am I lying? Like, am I
lying? They won't show anything that
they claim that they've got. They won't
show what they look like yet. They big
up themselves every day, talk [ __ ] about
other people. It's the truth. It is the
truth, lad. And you know it. You can
laugh all you want, but you know it's the truth.
people. Most of these people in this
community, they haven't even got a life, bro.
Most of these people just have not got a
life. That their life is just sat on
YouTube talking and hating on people
24/7 that they don't know. Being jealous
of being jealous of people that they
don't know. That's their life from the
time they wake up to the time they go to
bed. Most of these people
and they try to talk about people that
are better than them. Huh? Please, bro.
It's laughable. Actually, it's laughable, bro. Yeah.
So, yeah. Um,
I can't trust you with a new channel, UK Asylum.
I can't uh
I can't trust you with a new channel, lad.
I've unsubed from Timmy as well. I just
go on it manually. I've just been
clicking on it manually, so I'm not even
sub to him. Yeah.
And obviously tomorrow then obviously
I'll just never go on the channel again.
It's as simple as that. Whatever happens
tomorrow, I just will never go back on
the channel ever again.
Simple, isn't it, lad?
There's not really any good horror films.
And I sound scared. Not scared or
anything, bro. I'm just I'm just
stressed about other stuff. Not some fat
[ __ ] that's never going to come to
London. Thank you very much. if that's
what you think it is. No, I just I'm
[ __ ] a bit hung over to be fair.
Just got a lot of [ __ ] to think about,
you know? It's [ __ ] bro. Not some [ __ ] [ __ ]
I didn't go to bed the other day until
7:00 in the [ __ ] morning.
The [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, that's what Timmy does. Yeah, to
be fair, what will happen is they will
go meet up, have a drink, PJ will buy
the cheap buds for them. All that last
time will make up lies that he done this.
Yeah, pretty much. That's exactly what
Timmy does. Yeah. Yep.
So what you got an off peak ticket and
this is the kind of [ __ ] these are the
kind of people that you're dealing with
buying off peak tickets at [ __ ] 43 44
years of age lad. These are the kind of
people that you're dealing with on this community bro.
Yeah. Oh wait, brother, you're another
self-reflector. You was live on YouTube
on Christmas. You're bald. You've got no
girlfriend. You're fat. You're ugly.
Yeah, you're talking about yourself,
lad. And you will not come on camera and
prove me otherwise. Remember that. That
there's a reason why the law the Lavy
Mongs don't come on camera and they
don't talk. Most of them don't even talk
on the Streamyards. Brother, it's self
projecting with you losers. Give it up
in 2026. Nothing you say has any effect
on me. I'm the one that still comes on
camera. I still show my faces. Something
that you old, ugly, defeated men can
never do. Facts. That's all I got to say.
There you go, bro.
If you see how many people right go on
LJ's, none of them join the Streamyards,
none of them show their faces, and only
on this community that this happens. Why
do you think that is? Yeah, you be the
judge. I know the answer. So, there we go.
You know the answer. I know the answer.
And that's that.
And now you're making jokes that people
are bored, brother. I've got my hair.
The only reason you people say that I'm
bored is cuz you're bored yourselves.
Since you don't like showing your faces
because apparently people going to dox
you, people going to do this, people
going to do that. So, how about this?
Show us your hairline. Show us your hair.
Come on. Show us your hairline and show
us your hair. That's another self-p
projecting thing that you do because if
you done that, it would show that
majority of the people on here are [ __ ] bored.
So, again, self projecting.
Yeah. Yeah. These people should show their hairline.
Okay. If I'm not correct, if I'm not
correct, come on camera and show us what
you look like, then. Show us what you
look like. Show us what you've got. Come
on, bro. I'll come I'll jump on camera.
You're trying to be sarcastic. Okay,
that's nice. Bro, you was live on
Christmas, by the way. This was the
same. This was the guy that was live on
my live stream on Christmas day when I
was doing that experiment. That's cute.
Anyways, just come on the camera and
show us what you look like. Show us what
you got. If you got nothing to hide,
bro, jump on camera. It's not a big deal.
You can't do that cuz you know you'd be
[ __ ] if you done that. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, bro. That's good, man. So,
join the join the Streamyard and show us
what you look like.
up. Here we go. Timmy's needing backup
now. Up. Here we go, bro.
Yep. Here we go, bro.
Here we [ __ ] go.
This is hilarious, bro.
This is exactly why in a couple of days
I'm coming off of this [ __ ] 100%, bro. 100%.
[ __ ] little [ __ ] It's just such a
disabled community. But to be fair, bro,
at least we found a couple of people
that are decent on this community, bro.
At least we actually found a couple of
people in this community, which is um,
you know, five, six people, whatever.
Where's Fire Stick, bro? Yeah.
Again, players number, you're self projecting.
You're self projecting. Similar to what
Timmy does, similar to what everyone
else does on this, most people do in
this community. It's all self-reflecting.
You still hasn't You still ain't clicked
that link. You still ain't showing us
what you look like.
That's where you people always lose.
Yeah. That's where you people always lose.
And that's that, bro.
Who the [ __ ] is that, man?
Yeah. And I'll warn anyone about this
community as well. When I do this
leaving video, I will warn everyone as well.
Anyone who's younger than these people,
anyone that's better looking than these
people, stay away.
100%, bro. I will literally I say,
no, do you know what it is, Ja? It's Do
you know the thing is, bro, as well,
it's the jealousy on this community as
well. They'll sit there and point blank
and deny, bro. Yeah, they they'll deny
it, but bro, you ask them several times,
come on camera, show your face. Come on
camera, show us what you got. They can't
do it, bro. Only 5% of the people in
this community show their faces.
Yeah, they've got nothing. They're just
self They're just self projectors. I got
a new channel, bro. In a couple days,
I'm I'm on that channel, bro. And I'm
just taking a few people that are good
on it onto that channel, and we'll just
carry on as normal.
I've already got like videos on there.
We'll just carry on as normal, bro. Yeah.
It comes to jealousy on this community,
bro. How many How many [ __ ] men have
got channels dedicated to other men?
It's weird. They're weirdos, bro.
Yeah. No, it doesn't matter, bro. It
doesn't matter. But what I'm saying is
they just self-reflect their life. Yeah.
I'll have a great day tomorrow. Oh,
another one. Oh, another one that can't
show their face. Do you see what I'm
saying, bro? The people in this
community will not show what they look
like cuz they're ugly as [ __ ] This is
exactly what I'm saying, bro. But then
they tried to talk about other people.
You get what I'm saying?
You're not coming in, you [ __ ] [ __ ] Bye-bye.
You absolute [ __ ] See you later.
You're not coming in.
Yeah, JNA. Like I said, anyone anyone
that's younger, anyone that's better
looking than these people, they start. I
don't know how long you've been on this
community, bro. I don't know how long
you've been on this community. I'm not
sure. But yeah,
it's true though. It literally is. No,
no, no. But it's the truth. We laugh at
everything, bro. But no, no, no. It's
seriously, seriously, it's just the
truth though. Isn't it seriously just
the truth? Like, all jokes aside for one
second, it is the truth though, isn't
it? It generally generally generally is. Mhm.
>> I'll see you tomorrow, Timmy. You're not
getting attention on this channel.
You're not coming up. Anyone that's
younger and better looking than them,
they don't like. It's the truth. I'm
telling you, it's the truth, bro. They
don't like anyone better looking than
them. Think about it, bro. These are the
same people that are sat on YouTube
24/7, bro. 24/7 sat on YouTube trying to
talk about other people, talking about
other people that they don't know.
Imagine that, bro. Literally imagine
that for one second. Yeah.
Anyways, yeah, it won't come on as
normal. So, yeah, Jay and I went out yesterday, bro.
I got free numbers. Messaged them. They
didn't reply. None of them's replied
yet. It's typical in the West, isn't it,
bro? Was on Monday, to be fair. Quite
good. Free numbers for Monday, isn't it?
Yeah, I know you like to talk about
dating and [ __ ] so I thought I brought
it up, bro.
Yeah, I was pissed off yesterday, bro,
so I just drunk in it. Yeah, see you
later, Timmy. You're not coming in. See
you later, lad.
You ain't coming in, lad. See you later.
Stop talking and get on that train for
[ __ ] sake. Yeah.
Yeah, I was just pissed off yesterday.
Um, JNA, bro, so I thought [ __ ] it. Yeah, bro.
I know. It drinks on a Monday, man. Did
it? It didn't feel like a Monday, bro.
You know what? It didn't feel It didn't
even feel like a Monday.
No, it didn't even feel like a Monday to
be fair, bro. But yeah,
there we go.
>> Why won't you let Oh, you've let me in it.
>> I'll I'll see you tomorrow.
>> So, yeah, tomorrow, Peter. No flapping
around. It's not going to be like a whole nice
donations. Make sure doesn't phone the
police cuz you'll see tomorrow.
>> You can't see tomorrow. You won't me.
You call yourself an ambulance as well.
>> Okay, we'll see. We'll see about that.
>> Make sure you call yourself you call
yourself a [ __ ] ambulance as well.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] I'm battering him,
Ben. I swear to God, I'm battering him,
bro. And not just with my fist. I don't
give a [ __ ] This [ __ ] needs to learn.
This jealous fat [ __ ] needs to learn. He
needs to get a good [ __ ] around his
mouth. I swear to God, bro. He needs to
learn. Trust me, bro. He will learn as
well, bro. Trust me, he will learn.
Because it seems like all of the other
people that has done [ __ ] to him, he hasn't learned.
He hasn't learned, bro. Yeah.
All you be needing is an ambulance. I
know, but this JNA, this is what I'm
saying. It's jealousy with these people.
It's it's it's jealousy with them. You
do you understand the point I'm trying
to make now? Yeah. This guy is going to
get battered tomorrow, bro, if he comes.
And it's his own fault. All cuz he's a
jealous [ __ ] like the rest of them. And
this is what it is. It's jealousy with
these people. Joe, Red Star. It's
jealousy. I swear my life on it, bro. It
is 100%. It is, bro. It is. This guy
done his balls in because he's a skin
gambling addict. Then he mentions my
name trying to put me in a bad mood.
Okay. You want to keep mentioning my
name? I'll message your family. Now we
saying that he's going to come on
people's doors, bro. I'm going to make
sure he goes back in an ambulance. If he
if he comes tomorrow, I'm going to make
sure he goes in an ambulance and he
won't come back on YouTube acting a big
[ __ ] I promise you, bro. On on on
anything you want. Yeah. Simple. 100%,
bro. I'm sick to [ __ ] death of this
[ __ ] This [ __ ] jealousy on this
community over people that they don't
know. I'm sick of it. Laugh all you
want. You know it's the truth. You can
laugh, but you can't you can't disagree
with it cuz you know it's the truth.
Yeah. Cuz you know it's the [ __ ] truth. Yeah.
Don't mention me on your little gay
little gambling videosing
your skintess onto me just like what
your boyfriend Nons does. a [ __ ]
little weasel. And that's why I'm coming
off of this [ __ ] 100%. I'm coming off of
this [ __ ] after tomorrow when I finish
this [ __ ] I might be around I might be
round for I might I might laugh for a
couple of days and then we are
definitely done, bro. 100%.
Yeah, it's jealousy with these people in
this community, Ben, bro. All of it's
weird. They're jealous. They're weirdos.
They're weird, bro. They're [ __ ]
proper weirdos on this community, lad.
I'll give you my new channel as well,
Ben. I don't know if you got my email,
but email if you've got it, bro. Email
me. I'll give you the new channel as
well. We're all going to that channel,
bro. We're all going to that channel. Um yeah, basically,
we're all going to that channel um
in um in a couple of days, bro. Yeah.
Nope. Cuz you're going to give it away, lad.
No, sir. They're never going to find it.
These people in this community are never
going to find it. They haven't found it
yet and they never will. So, there is a
point because they're never going to
find it. How are they going to find it,
bro? This channel has been made a couple
of months ago. No one's found it.
They're never going to find it. What are
they, God? How are they going to find
it? There's millions of channels on
YouTube, I'm guessing. What are you, God
or something? How How are you going to
How are you going to find it? You'll
never find it.
Well, he would have found it by now.
Yeah, they're never going to find it,
bro. Once I batter this [ __ ] tomorrow,
I'm off of it. Fire stick, bro. Uh,
we're going on this new channel on
Thursday, bro. Yeah, my new channel. So,
if you want it, bro, uh, email me or
whatever, bro. I'm going to have
Greavesy, Steven Howard, you. We need
Triple H. We got Ben. Like, I'm off of
this place, bro. And just starting fresh
on another channel. Just taking a few of
the good people off of here
cuz that's basically just what I go live
for, is it?
So, yeah, man.
Yeah. Uh, it's it tzpjx@yahoo.com.
And anyway, any any people that's
thinking of cloning [ __ ] don't even
try, bro, cuz I'm going to know who it
is. So, there's no point you even trying
to clone anything because you're not
getting that channel. Simple as that.
And unlike LT, I'm not going to know
what's going on in the future.
basically six, seven people. I'm going
to give my friends it as well. Yeah.
Yeah, exactly, bro. Yeah. Oh, she just
turned out to be a [ __ ] bro.
Pip smoker. Yeah, I messaged her drunk
yesterday and I sent her voice notes
saying, "Oh, meet me now." It not
swearing and then Yeah, she just blocked
me, but she was being a [ __ ] anyways.
She was playing games anyways, bro.
No, they won't find it. They definitely
definitely definitely won't find it. And
I'll put money on that right now. They
won't find it.
They definitely definitely definitely
will not find it. He says he is, bro.
Yeah. So, we'll see. But yeah, Pips, she
was being a [ __ ] anyways.
[ __ ] sake, man.
Yeah, I went out yesterday five stick
got three numbers. None of them replied.
I mean, it wasn't Monday, is it? I went
on a I went on a piss. Monero. Yeah, she
was playing like mad games. Pip, I think
she's like mentally unstable or some [ __ ]
Not good, bro. It's
It's quite depressing, actually, lad.
It's quite bad to be honest with you, bro.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
I could show the I could show the whole
conversation one day, bro. But there's
loads and loads of messages.
I think it's virtually impossible now
here in Fire Stick. I think it's
virtually impossible now to even get a date.
Yeah, they're not going to find it.
They're not going to find it. They would
have found it already. Fire Stick. If
they were going to find it, they would
have found it already. But yeah, anyways, um,
I think it's virtually impossible now,
bro. I had uh came across um uh a couple
of toxic people yesterday. Bro, it's gotten worse.
Five stick. It's getting worse, lad.
Probably about 20, bro. I can tell you.
I can tell you some of the ones I done.
I done one by the train station, said I
had a boyfriend. Another one said had a
boyfriend. Another one weren't having
it. Then I done one in the shop, got her
number, and then Yeah, I done about 20, bro.
Uh, I done about 20, maybe more, bro. I
can't even remember to be fair. A
[ __ ] shitload, basically. done some
sober, done some drunk. Now I was
talking I I approached this person, bro.
I thought [ __ ] it, why not? Because I
was on a mad one yesterday because I was
pissed off because that Christian Izzy
thing that's the reason I started
drinking so I thought [ __ ] it. Just
[ __ ] go out, bro. What else is there
to do? Yeah. Now I approached this
person, bro, and she was kind of be like
trying to be like a bit rude, trying to
be like a bit sarcastic. I can't explain
it. And I said, "Oh, um, there's not
going to be no fight tomorrow anyway
because he's not coming." But yeah. And
I said, "Oh, you don't need to be rude."
Yeah. I said, "I'm being rude, but if
you want me to be rude, I will be rude."
I said, "You what?" I said, "If you got
anything to say, come outside. Do it
away from people so no one can get
involved and whatever. If you really are
that brave to think that you can get
rude, just do it outside then just to
test the waters. Just just as a little
test." And I said, "Oh, that's what I
thought. So, [ __ ] off." And they didn't
even they didn't even try anything. They
even try to walk past me several times.
A lot of these people uh five stick they
need telling about themselves lad. Yeah.
A lot of these people need telling them
about themselves. Like their egos are so
inflated that you know what I mean.
Yeah. Well, it doesn't matter.
Yeah. I told him I told her about herself, bro.
>> Yeah. I told her [ __ ] off, bro. I said,
"If you've got anything to say, let's go
outside." That's what I'll do now. If
anyone ever gets rude, I'll just say,
"If you got anything to say, you can
stay outside, can't you?"
Yeah. No one cares, bro. He's never
going to find it ever.
So, it's as simple as that. He's never
ever ever going to find it.
It's not possible. They never found The
only time they found my channel before
is when I linked it to them cuz I
thought it was a woman. Other than that,
they never find it and they never will, you know.
But yeah, I'm coming off this disabled place anyways
by like Thursday. So yeah.
Yeah. If you stay on this community, it
will always go back and forth. It will
always go back and forth on this community, Grezy.
Do you know Do you know how the cycle?
Do you know the cycle that will happen?
Do you want Do you want me to explain
the cycle if you stay on this community?
Yeah. Do you do you want to know what
will happen? I can tell you exactly what will happen.
see the correct way it will happen as well,
right? Do you want me to tell you
exactly what will happen?
How this happens on YouTube? So, you go
live, right? And you show that you're
not gambling and you show you ain't done
your balls in ter then you get a [ __ ]
called Timmy that studies balls in and
tries to rule you out, tries to mention
your name. You argue back, he argues
back, you argue back, LT gets involved,
you argue with him, and it just goes
round. It's actually quite boring to be
honest, you know, and I'm sure like most
people are bored of it. And it always
and it just goes round and round in circles.
He will not find it, bro. Simple. He
will not find it. And he doesn't find my
Reddit accounts. He All he does is stalk
subreddits that I go on. There's one
subreddit I go on. There's one subreddit
that I go on. Um, there's one subreddit
I go on and he just sits on it all day,
bro. He doesn't find my accounts. He
doesn't, I quote, find them. He sits
there and waits for somebody to post on
a subreddit and then he just thinks
everyone's me. He's a sad bastard.
Sad, stalking, jealous bastard. That's
all they are in there, bro. So, we're
getting away from it anyways. Simple.
Yeah. Oh, just approaching for now, but
we'll do some food videos as well. It's
just approaching basically. And there's
no point looking up approaching cuz
you're not going to find it. If that's
what you're thinking, you're going to
type approaching. You're not going to find it.
Now, he doesn't get bored. Jealous.
Jealous. Mentally disabled. Well,
disabled, mentally jealous people don't
get bored. That's what I'm saying. And
it's not about being bored. You don't
understand. When someone's got a mental
obsession with someone, they they'll do
it for years and years and years till
they drop dead. It's jealousy. When they
when you are what they wish they were,
right? And they will never be that. They
will never stop. Never ever ever stop.
10 years, 20 years, 25 years, it will
never stop. They're jealous ass people
with no life. Simple as that. So they're
not going to stop. Why are they going to
get bored? Bored of what? They ain't got
a life to live.
They haven't got a life to live. You get
me, bro? But yeah, you I know what
you're saying. Yeah. Like even with that
USA easy thing, I got bored. I got bored
after a couple of months and I never
done it every day. So yeah, but it is a
good compar It is a good comparison that
you're using. Yeah. I said it to you in
that video. Yeah. If you're obsessed
with a woman, think about it, Leslie. If
you're obsessed with a woman, you
wouldn't stalk them the way they stalk you.
You get it? So,
so do you understand what I'm saying?
Like this [ __ ] Christian Izzy has
pissed me off, bro. I'm not going to lie
to you. I'm still pissed off over it.
But I don't keep calling them. I'm not
trying to find them. I'm not trying to
find their Facebook. And even if I did,
I wouldn't do it. And the point that you
just made, even if you was to do
something, you'd get bored of it
eventually. But these people don't.
So, they must be really jealous of
something. You must hit a nerve really
for these people to do what they do for
years. You must hit some nerve. Probably
just being better looking than them and
younger than them. That's enough with
these people, I think. Yeah, I think
that's enough. But yeah, you'd get bored
of it. Even if it was somebody you was
in love with, even if you was obsessed
and in love with someone, I don't you
would no one would do what these people
do for years and years. That's that's
the point that makes it weird as well.
It's jealousy. It's deep rooted
It's deep, deep, deep rooted hate and
jealousy. And that's what it is, lad.
They can deny it all they want, but we
know the truth.
You can never pay me to sit on YouTube
all day stalking a man. To me, that's
weird. To me, that's weird.
Sit online for three, four years
stalking men every day. No thanks. No
thanks, Jeff. You see what I'm saying?
When you when you put it that way, it's
it's weird. Do you understand? When you
see it as that, when you see it that
way, it's weird. Do you get you get Do
you get what I'm trying to say?
Yeah. That's nice. He can slag me off
all he wants. He's irrelevant. I don't
care. The only person I'm sub to now is Monty.
You know what I mean?
You get me, bro? So, yeah. Yeah,
you get me, Dad.
But yeah, anyways, back onto your dating
[ __ ] Fire stick, bro. Yeah, it's really like
it's like virtually impossible now, bro.
Yeah, I feel [ __ ] today because of the
drinking yesterday. Fire stick.
I feel really bad today, bro. Really bad.
I feel bad today, bro. I had some curry
and that, but I feel really bad
[ __ ] drinking and [ __ ] in it. [ __ ]
Yeah, 100%, bro. Yeah. Uh-huh. Yeah.
Yeah, they would, man.
I feel like [ __ ] today, bro. Like,
[ __ ] Yeah. I'm not even going to say
what, but yeah, cuz I I felt bad
yesterday before I drunk. So,
yeah. I thought I'd be I I thought I'd
be [ __ ] safe just drinking beer, but
no way. This is how people become
alcoholics, you see? cuz they drink and
then the next day they feel worse. So
then they drink again, you see? And then
it's a cycle. That's how people become alcoholics.
Yeah, I had a big session yesterday,
bro. Got three numbers. None of them
replied. Done [ __ ] loads of approaches.
Don't really care anyways.
No. Why' I sniff, bro? I don't do drugs.
I'm kind of scared, bro. I'm not going
to lie to I'm kind of scared for the
future to be honest with you. Fire stick.
Yeah. The more you know, the more like
bad experiences you get and the more
they do these [ __ ] up things, these
women, it's kind of scary, bro.
Like if it's only getting worse now,
it's kind of like scary, you know?
Yeah. I messaged that Christian Izzy. I was like
I sent her voice notes and that ain't
it. They weren't abusive. And then she
started like trying to play the victim again.
To be honest, Leslie, I was I was Bro, I
was I'm used to it to be honest. It's
just it's never going to change you. It
doesn't do my heading because there's no
hope. Ultimately, there's no hope. Oh, I
just said, "Oh, yeah. You want an
apology?" Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Why don't
you meet me now then? Let's talk. Yeah.
Let's have a chat and stuff. You know,
I'm not far from you. I was in central
London, so I wasn't far from Elen. I
said, "Oh, let's talk then. Why not?"
It's all I said literally, bro, in the
space of like a couple of voice notes.
But no, it doesn't do my head in B
because the thing is Leslie will always
it will always be the same,
you know. So it's like what I'd be more
surprised if they didn't reply meet you.
I'd be very very surprised. So it's like
it's you expect it in it like it will
never change in it, bro.
It's proper [ __ ] up as well, Leslie,
bro. And some of them that won't even
talk. Like some of them, you'll approach
them and they won't even talk.
Um, he won't even talk. They're sorry.
They won't even talk. Some of them are a
bit rude. Some of them just said they
have boyfriends. It's bad, bro. London
is very westernized.
It's a very, very westernized place.
It's a horrible place, bro, with the
people. It's No, the city's good and the
restaurants, but the people are just unbearable, bro.
You know them balls like Fire Stick.
Yeah. Like Simmons and [ __ ] It's so
westernized. You can smell the
westernity, bro. It's just Bro, you
can't even explain it. It's so westernized, bro.
Yeah. He's not going to be knocking
anyone's head in, Ricky. Yeah, it's
very, very westernized, bro.
Yeah, it doesn't matter, bro. That was years ago,
not now. So yeah, that Christian Izzy
thing [ __ ] with my head, bro. I can't
lie to you, bro. Now I feel worse today
cuz I was drinking yesterday.
Yeah, it's not good, bro. That's not good, man.
Yeah, it doesn't matter if you saw me
with women, bro. It doesn't matter.
Oh, and Fire Stick, you can get kicked
out of places for approaching, by the
way, as well. Yeah.
Yeah. Do you know what they said to me
yesterday? Bro, went into this bar.
Yeah. The one that I met Christian Izzy
and you remember that thing that
happened months ago.
It's very westernized. I had this gay
guy come up to me, bro. Like the manager
trusted to be a gay person just to just
to rub it in your face a little bit
more. Yeah. Right. And he says, "Oh, we
don't allow tracksuits." Cuz I was
wearing a tracksuit. I said, "Oh, okay.
I'll change my jeans. I've got jeans in
my bag." Right. Cuz I have I wear
tracksuit. I put jeans in my bag. Um,
you know, and what happened was is uh
then he's made me wear them. Literally
just about to order the drink. Yeah.
He's like, "Oh, well, yeah, your face.
Come on recognition."
Uh, you can't uh you can't uh you can't
come in here. And remember I told you I
got banned for approaching them three
people months ago. Yeah. It come up
again. So, he said, "Oh, thanks for
understanding." I said, "Oh, I don't
understand. It doesn't make any sense,
right? It's a bar that serves alcohol
with people in there. You're free to
talk to who you want. You're free to do
like you're free to talk to who you
want. You're single. You can you can
make friends with men. You can speak to
women. You know what I'm saying? It's
things like this country. It's like it's
it's little things like this about this
country that annoys me. That's why I
don't really go out drinking much, bro.
To be honest, bro. It was only because I
was so depressed yesterday. I couldn't
even bear it, bro. That's one of the
reasons why I went out.
So like, yeah, I just felt like I was
just bored and depressed and [ __ ] like
proper depressed, bro. So I just I just
went out drunk. But that's one of the
reasons I don't really go out, bro, cuz
it's just a whole like you you got them
you got people trying to tell you what
you can and can't do, right? People
trying to tell you what you can and
can't do. Okay? So you go through hoops
with that. So then when you go and do
that, you still have to deal with [ __ ]
with women. I'm good, bro. You know what
I'm saying? I'm good. Just chilling. You get me?
Yeah. Well, they let me in last week.
Uh, well, the month. They let me in last
No, but it should have been. And then,
yeah, the bouncer tried snatching the
drink out of my hand. You remember that
happened? That was months ago. Yeah.
Yeah. So, yeah, I approached three
people that never complained about me.
And your point is it's a free country.
Like, it just doesn't make no sense,
bro. It's just this country just annoys
me, bro. Simple as that. Um
I think I got home about like 12, I
think it was. Yeah.
So, yeah, don't speak to people in a bar
where you're supposed to speak to people.
Yeah. No, there is no hope. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. There is no hope.
There literally is no hope, bro. Yeah,
there is no hope. That's why I'm not
pissed off because there is no hope.
That's why I'm not angry because I know
that there legitimately is no hope.
There is no hope. You try to speak to
people, they're not interested. They
pretend they got boyfriends. Even if you
get a number, they lead you on. Yeah.
There's no hope. That's why if I go out
and people don't reply, I'm like, "Oh,
okay." Yeah. It's literally the same old
until you leave this country will always
be the same old. I expect it. Like, you
don't expect anything different.
Yeah, there is no faith and there is
literally no hope. Look what happened to
that Christian Izzy,
you know. Look at what happened to that
Christian isy, bro. That was [ __ ] up.
That still annoys me even now. There is
generally there is no hope. There's
generally generally generally no hope.
There is no hope. And anyone that says
there is, bro, they're lying to your
ass. There's no hope.
There is no hope, bro. And I'm not even
trying to be awkward.
So, uh, yeah.
Haven't been on a date since April. Um,
yeah. And I've got so many numbers.
There is no hope. I would say now it's
like a 1% chance. I think now I was
saying to Antman earlier, I reckon even
trying to get a date now, 1% chance,
bro. People are so cold and they're so
stuck up and they're so [ __ ] that I
don't think so, bro.
Nah, bro. I done a video on it. You can
watch the video if you want, bro.
Nah, we're not sound, bro. We're not sound.
I explained it on the video.
She blocked me yesterday as well.
No, I'm not worried about I'm not
worried about any of that stuff.
It's on my main channel. Do you want me
to link it to you?
Yeah, it's on my main, bro. You want me
Yeah, it's called another slap in the
face. Go watch it, bro, and come back.
It's long repeating it all again.
Yeah, go watch it. It's called another
slap in the face.
Yeah, what better way to put it, bro? So yeah,
but I wouldn't even entertain going out
now that I got money and everything, but
I I wouldn't even I would even bother
with it, bro. For the most part. Like
seriously, it's always going to be the
same here, bro.
Everyone knows that.
So there's not much left to say, you know.
They just say that. Yeah, they just say
that they got boyfriends or they just
act like they're better than you.
So that's all that ever happens. Fire stick.
Trust me, you won't I'll be very
surprised if you even get another date
in this country. By you, I mean me. I
don't know about you. I don't know what you're doing.
It's bad. It's really bad, bro. And
that's it. It didn't even depress me,
bro. Is that Christian Izzy thing?
That's depressing, bro. That is so
depressing, bro. Seriously, that's so
depressing because then a lot of these
women, what they like to do is they like
to lead you on and make you feel like
[ __ ] And they know exactly how to do it
as well. You get it?
That is so depressing, bro.
That is madness, man.
Have I had that, bro? Of course I've had that.
Of course I've had that, bro. You know I
have. I've had everything. Everything
you've had, I've had.
I've had people try to cause arguments
and try to get rude. Bro, I've had everything.
But that doesn't piss me off worse than
the leading someone on and giving them false hope
like what this Christian Izzy did.
And and she deleted my number. I knew
she deleted my number the other day. She
was trying to deny it.
Uh yeah, I did have it last night. Yeah,
they said I had a boyfriend before I
even finished my sentence. Yeah, people
say they go for personality. Make it make sense.
[ __ ] uh I knew they deleted my number
the other day. I knew it. Fire stick.
I knew it, bro. Just mind games in it
the other day.
The other day when I told her, oh, I
asked her, "Why did you delete my
number?" She said, "I didn't delete my
number. I just removed my picture." I
didn't believe her because her symbol
disappeared as well. So, she added me
back, right? But then she deleted my
number again yesterday.
Oh, it was two ticks.
It was two ticks, but now it's one tick.
She's blocked me now. Yeah. But it was
one It was two ticks like a week ago, a
few days. A week ago. Then she's like,
"Oh, I didn't delete your number." I
said, "You must have because your your
your symbol is not there. Your status is not there."
So, she deleted my number. Then, she
added me back. Then, she added me back
Fire Stick. And then she delete my
number again. So, what's the point in
giving your number just to delete my
number? Pointless. You get me? Um, do
you get me Fire Stick?
It's not good, bro. Not good.
Yeah, I had Indian, bro.
Yeah. So, I wonder why she deleted my
number the other day and then didn't
block but then didn't block me. That's weird. That's [ __ ]
Yep. But I knew she deleted my number
the other day as well. I knew it anyways
because the status disappeared as well.
I thought they blocked me, but they never.
Proper mind games. Proper proper proper
mind games, bro. What the [ __ ]
Then she sent me a load of messages
yesterday. Then she deleted it. She
said, "You're actually scary."
I'm scary. What the [ __ ] bro?
I'm [ __ ] Holy [ __ ] brother.
Yo, I done some approaches in Oxford Circus, Lad. Yeah,
he's just trying to play the victim, is it, lad?
It all Do you know how it all started
when I asked to meet her?
By stick, that's when it all started.
That's when it all started when when
when I said, "Oh, like, do you want to
meet up next week?"
Then she start coming out with all these
excuses. That's what started it, bro.
That's what started it kind of. Yeah.
Yeah. No, basically I said to her, "Oh,
let's meet up next week." So, I'm busy
next week. Oh, I'll let you know. And
that and obviously I know that means no.
So, I'm thinking like, if you don't want
to meet, just saying it. Like, it's
cool, man. Like, and then it just
started from there, basically.
It literally just started like that as
quick as that. Yeah.
Oh, you're good looking. You're this. You're that.
But you know what I'm saying? I'm
[ __ ] sick of this [ __ ] But I'm sick
of this [ __ ] brother.
No, I just said to her, "Oh, let's meet
now." I just let's let's meet now and
talk in it. That's literally all I said.
I said, "I'm in central London. Let's
just meet up and talk." That's all I said, literally.
That's literally all I said.
Nothing more, bro. Nothing less. That's
literally all I said. Yeah.
Then she delete my number. Then she
blocked me. So yeah, literally, bro.
But all of that's irrelevant, isn't it?
It's just mind games and she had no
intentions of meeting anyways. So all of
that's irrelevant. So yeah. Yeah.
And I was telling some guys in waxies
about it and they were basically saying
that some women just get off on leading
people on fire stick. So say they feel
insecure. Yeah. They will get off on
like leading you on
basically and like giving you false hope
and [ __ ] They basically get off on
that. You get me?
Yeah. It's not good, bro. It's sick. It
really is sick.
They're sick in their head, bro.
Yeah, just like most of them do.
But yeah, Fire Stick, bro. It's like uh
I told you anyways what to do, bro.
No, but do you know why I thought it was
genuine though? Fire stick. Because they
were messaging all day, every day, and
it went on for so long. Do you know what
I mean? Fire stick where it went on for
so long. Normally you get a number.
Normally you'll get a number. Yeah. And
they don't reply. Um you'll get a number
and then they
um they they reply then they stop very
quickly or stop the next day to get it.
They don't normally continue it for that long.
Yeah. They're messed up, bro. They're messed.
And I just told her, why are you asking
people's body counts?
Depressive, is it?
Yeah, it is depressing, isn't it, lad?
But yeah, that delete and the number was
dodgy, bro. I just think I think they're unstable.
So tired, bro.
While it isn't while it isn't normal if
you've got no intentions of dating a per
the person. I don't think that's normal.
I think that's [ __ ] weird.
I don't think that's normal. I think
that's weird, lad.
To ask a friend that you've just met to
ask someone that you just met. That's weird, bro.
So yeah, JNA, it's proper [ __ ] up now, isn't it? Yeah. Basically, bro.
Yeah. People are just cold nowadays,
JNA. They're just cold, lad.
They're just cold, bro. Very cold. Uh,
people on Reddit make dating sound easy. Uh, JMA
Reddit's Reddit. Real life's real life,
lad. You know what I mean? O
I really get escorts cuz I don't really
just I don't really just care. I don't
care about the sex that much. Fire stick.
I don't really care about sex much anymore, bro.
Do you get me?
Yeah. The me the anxiety subreddit is
good, but when it's to do with dating,
it's [ __ ] because they make dating
sound so easy. But I don't know anything
harder in life than dating, bro. I can't
think of one thing that's harder. Like
money, you can make money, you can you
can get money, you know, going to the
gym, you go gym, [ __ ] I personally
cannot find anything harder than dating JNA.
Like I would say now you got more chance
of being a [ __ ] millionaire than
finding someone, bro.
Like it generally feels that way. Like
it generally generally does like feel
that way, bro. Everyone's the same now
because of Tik Tok, cuz of Instagram.
Everyone's the same, bro.
And it doesn't matter. The maddest thing
is I didn't even get a haircut
yesterday. Do you know why I didn't get
a haircut yesterday, JNA? Cuz it doesn't
make a difference. Even if I looks maxed
and I made myself a seven, eight out of
10 again, went to the gym, whatever, it
would be the same result. Like that
might sound excuses like excuses, but no
matter what you do, bro, it will always
be the same result. Haircut, no haircut,
looks max, fat, in shape, it will always
be the same.
It would always be the same, bro. So,
I'd rather go not having a haircut and
saying, "Oh, just just do it in a
tracksuit." You know what I mean?
Nah, there's no hope, bro.
Nah, there's no hope. Especially after
that Christian Izzy thing, bro. No,
that's [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah, you should go
gym. No, no, yeah. Everyone should go to
the gym, bro. Everyone should stop doing
unhealthy things and do healthy things.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, bro. I'm not saying
that, but I'm saying that like even if
you do go to the gym and you was the
best version of yourself, you made the
best of your situation, you're still not
going to find anyone. So that's what
people need to make clear. Like don't
make people believe that if they do all
of these things that they're going to
find someone, bro, cuz they're not. But
they should just do it anyways cuz yeah,
there's other reasons to do it. Like you
said, that's not the point I'm trying to
make, bro. You get it?
But yeah, J, that's the
that's the thing, lad. That Christian
Izzy thing, bro. No, bro. I'm [ __ ]
I'm defeated, bro.
I'm actually defeated, bro. I can't even lie, lad.
Yeah, she's just playing games, bro. I
didn't say anything wrong. never brought
up sex once. I done everything perfect,
bro. And they still done me dirty.
Nothing's going to help you getting
someone. You probably got about a 1%
chance of finding someone.
Probably, I'd say about 1% in this
country, especially London.
I spoke to an American yesterday, JNA. I
asked for a WhatsApp. Guess what she
said? I I don't know what WhatsApp is.
Nope. didn't say any weird stuff at all.
Not once on any day. I was just taking
things slow and asking how they were and
was talking about things we liked. Not
even once, lad. Not even once.
So, this is what I'm saying, Ja. This is
what we're dealing with, lad.
This is what we're dealing with in 2026.
There's a lot of [ __ ] in this country, bro.
Um, so yeah. Yeah, man.
I got one number. One was from Italy.
She lives there. Doesn't matter. Italy
is not far. The other one lives here.
And then the other one lives here. One I
got in a shop in Oxford Circus. cuz I
got that number at Oxford Circus
uh in the shop. So yeah,
pump the [ __ ] up, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. London's very westernized there. Very westernized.
There's a place there's like a bar
called Simmons and you That's why I met
Christian Izzy and you will never get
anywhere in this these places, bro.
They're just too stuck up. Especially
like the Indian ones that were born
here. They're just nah.
No way, bro. You have literally no
chance. Like, no chance, bro. No chance.
I think Italy is really bad for dating as well.
Rome, I wouldn't like to be in Italy
trying to date. Oh, no way. No, no, no,
no, no way.
Italyy's really bad as well.
Italy, New York, London. [ __ ] that, bro.
I can't. Yeah,
I've never been with Italian woman ever.
I think they're they're the hardest to
get. I think
I've been on a date with one, but
they're very hard to get.
And then French are even harder.
Yeah. Yeah. There's certain like races
They're just impossible.
I mean, JA like French impossible to
get, Italian impossible to get, and
Polish impossible to get. But that
doesn't surprise me cuz a lot of Polish
people are racist. So, I know that for a
fact. So, there's certain like people
that you just can't get Indian as well.
Can't get them
anything like that. You got no shots.
You got no chance, mate. No chance. You
know what I mean?
Maybe Indian and Italian is the worst
as far as entitled women go.
Yeah, they're racist, bro. Um, Polish
people, I've seen videos, bro. They're racist.
There was this black guy and then they
kept following him and [ __ ] Weird, bro.
It's a weird country. I see it on
Instagram. You probably saw it yourself, man.
What do you reckon is more harder,
though? Seriously, America or England?
I was talking to this American guy about
this yesterday, bro. And I I I said the
same thing as I said here. I was
basically think I feel like if you was
in America long enough,
you'd find someone in maybe 6 months to a year.
Maybe after a long time you might. But I
don't think anywhere's worse than London, bro.
Cuz they're bad in different ways. Like,
oh, I can't explain it, bro. We were
basically talking about it, bro. Is it
like with these guys and [ __ ] but um
I don't know.
Yeah. Like in in America, they're more
like fake sarcastic.
Like how I can't explain it, bro. Like
it's a vibe that they give off. Like
American people are very like fake and
they they're very patronizing.
Does that make sense? Whereas like
obviously English people are just cold
and stuck up. I can't explain it, bro.
Like it's a vibe that you can't explain.
Oh, you watched it, did you, man? What
did you think?
They're different in But they're both
They're both bad in different ways. You
get it? You know what I mean?
They're very fake American people.
That's the that's that's the only thing
I think of, bro. When I speak to a lot
of them, they're just fake. You know
what I mean? But yeah,
I used to I used to meet a lot of
Americans, so I kind of like I met loads
and loads and loads and loads and loads
and loads. They just [ __ ] like the
English, bro. You know what I mean? Um yeah.
Yeah. Canada's brutal for dating, isn't it? Canada.
Yeah. Canada's brutal for dating.
Uh Toronto in it. Oh, [ __ ] that, mate.
To be fair, you don't really meet a lot
of Can Canadians here. You do get them, but
you don't really um
you don't really meet them.
You do you do come across them, but yeah.
Yeah. So I'd have no chance in Canada
either. See day and day like back in
like when I used to go out approaching
and stuff like it used to be one in
seven on the street. If I approached
seven people sober on the street I get
one number but it was always hard but
not like it is now. Now it just seems
impossible. Nothing's changed with me,
bro. I've still got the same confidence.
I still look the same. I've still got
money, you know. So, it's like um
I've still got money and stuff, but it's
just I don't know why it just seems it
just seems impossible now, bro.
That [ __ ] Christian Izzy, bro. [ __ ]
me royally, bro.
That's why I'll never speak to anyone
for a month again before we meet. It's bad that
And then the thing is they make you they
make you feel [ __ ] about yourself cuz
then they start questioning the way that
you look. But there isn't anything wrong
with the way that you look. Like you can
even be like above average looking.
There isn't anything wrong with the way
that you look.
You know what I'm saying? Like and I was
saying it to these guys. I was saying it
to these guys, bro. Um you know how it
comes up in conversation is that like
bro like mad ass, bro. I told him like,
"I've never been insecure about the way
that I look. I don't I don't have any
insecurities or nothing." But when
people play enough games with you, you
actually think you're thinking like,
"Bro, is there something wrong with
you?" And then you realize that there isn't.
To be fair, bro, I used to think it was
because I didn't look like fully white
and I've got a beard. But obviously I
always get my beard trimmed. Well,
usually I get my beard trimmed before
going out. I used to think it was that,
but it isn't, bro.
They're just it's just even other people
in London that approach they seem to get
the same thing. [ __ ] you know what uh
other guys like black people or or other
people like white people the same they
seem to get the same [ __ ] [ __ ] like
it's crazy is it
is bad at JNA bro like but you know if
you was if you was like fat and ugly
then you could kind of understand it in
it or if you was in a wheelchair you
could kind of understand it Bro, similar
to what I said in the video, bro. If you
was if you look like that, but then when
you're normal looking or decent looking,
whatever, it shouldn't be happening,
bro. Is it? But unfortunately, it does
and it will always happen and it will
never change on the flip side of that. So, yeah,
that's just the way it is, bro. Like, yeah,
it's not good, bro.
The more bad experiences you get, the
more you lose hope as well. That's the
thing, JNA. The more you'll lose hope.
So, I'm sure years ago when I used to
approach people on the street, I'm sure
more used to stop and talk.
I'm sure like there used to be a lot
more that used to stop and talk. Now, nah.
But yeah, no one has time or Yeah. It's
bad, isn't it? It's scary, bro. It is
quite scary when you think about it.
Yeah. To be honest, and I don't really
have much of a sex drive anymore, JNA.
I don't really care about it like with
this Christian is I just wanted to meet
someone and just vibe and that, bro. You
get it? I don't, bro. I don't I Bro, I
got some money yesterday. I got some
money today as well, bro. I was I had to
get some money off something, bro. But
uh I'm not gambling it, bro. Like the
only thing I'll probably do, bro, is
probably 10 pound a week on the football if that.
If that, bro.
But yeah, I am, bro. I'm going to I am
going to start doing stuff.
Don't worry, bro.
Probably, bro, I'll probably just do
like£10 a week on the football if you'd
even class as gambling. But that's about it.
Yeah, I like
as far as roulette and [ __ ] goes, I
didn't gamble. Yeah, to be fair, I was
tempted yesterday to gamble, bro, cuz I
was pissed off cuz of this Christian
Izzy [ __ ] I was like, I really need
like a dopamine rush.
I really need like a dopamine rush, but
everything happens for a reason, bro.
He says he's coming, but we'll see in
it. Uh, I needed this dopamine rush, but
I said, "Oh, but you know, if you lose
and stuff and whatever." So, I never
done it. Came back home and I got the
money I was expecting. So, everything
happens for a reason. You know what I
mean, bro? Like, but I wasn't going to
do it, but I was I was tempted, bro, cuz
I wanted like a dopamine rush from somewhere
cuz I was on a dopamine low, you see?
So, I was like, "Let me just get pissed."
Yeah. And I was like, "Oh, let me just
get pissed." You know what I mean?
You know, and then now I [ __ ] I'm
anxious today cuz they're drinking yesterday, JNA.
I'm a bit I'm a bit anxious now cuz
they're drinking, bro. You know when you
get like [ __ ] depressed the next day
and [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] when I woke up,
bro. It's [ __ ] Oh, it's mad.
You feel it in your body and that, is it,
bro? It's bad. You know,
anxiety sucks. I didn't think I was
going to get it cuz I only snuck a beer.
But where I'm stressed about other
things as well. Um,
yeah. And that's how people become
alcoholics. You see, that's how people
become alcoholics. You see, JNA,
that's that's how people become alcoholics.
You see, fun fact, if you didn't know.
Yeah. Here you go.
But yeah, the Lego thing was good, bro.
I need to do the Lego. I've got two I've
got one big set. I ain't touched it yet.
I originally bought it to stop the two stock gambling.
Does that make sense?
I didn't even do it, bro. So,
but yeah, don't rely on anyone. Like, if
you ever want to go back to the dating
game, JNA, I don't know what you where
you at, bro. Don't expect anything from
anyone because you're just going to get disappointed.
You will be disappointed. If you have
any faith and you have any hope in
anyone that you approach, bro, you um
you um you're going to be sadly sadly disappointed.
That's all I can say, you know.
Yeah, I don't drink much, bro. Like
every month, if that, maybe once a
month. Normally, it's every two months,
but I was just pissed off yesterday. But
yeah, if you're stressed about other
stuff and you go out drinking, you just
feel worse the next day. So, it's just a
Cats 22, bro.
I don't really like drinking that much,
bro. I used to just go out approach and
sober, but don't need to approach
anyone, bro. Like, we get the point now.
We know what it is.
We know what it is in this country. So,
and the amount of times J I used to go
out for like 8:00 in the morning
like Well, I used to do it because I had
a high sex drive. JNA, I was a mad
bastard back then. Like when I was
younger, 23, 24, you're a mad bastard,
isn't it? Like when you've got a sex
drive and obviously, but now I'm older,
I've already had experiences. I've
already been with [ __ ] women and it's
just not worth it. I know it's a waste
of time. But when you're younger, like
23, 24, like 25 even, bro, like Yeah.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. with this Christian Izzy, bro.
Like, I didn't even care about sex. I
don't care about sex, bro. I don't give
a [ __ ] about any of that that [ __ ] bro.
I used to, but I don't care about it anymore.
But, um, you just want to find someone
to vibe with, bro. You know, as you get
older, but no one can be normal. No
one's normal in this society, J. No
one's normal, lad.
Um, you know what I mean? People
are [ __ ] liabilities. So,
it's not good.
It's not good, bro.
But I went to the cinema the other day,
J. I watched Scream 7. I've gone to I'm
looking to see if there's any more
horror films in a cinema, but there isn't.
Yeah, Ghost cinema is a good thing to
do, but there's not always.
Yeah, I watch Scream 7.
but if something but then obviously some
of the some of the graphic stuff is
quite depressing that happens in these
horror films, but now I know they're not
they're not real anyways. Oh, I know
they're not real, but they're not real
is it? So, it doesn't matter. Some of
the scenes are disgusting, but it's not
real, is it?
It's not real anyways. So,
yeah, it's a good experience, bro.
Seeing couples used to bother me, but it
doesn't bother me anymore. Like couples
at the cinema, JNA. Nah, that doesn't
really bother me. You You notice as
well, I don't know if this this is the
same in Canada, but you'll notice Yeah.
that when you go out, there's a lot of
like average looking men, normal looking
men with some ugly fat women. That's how
you know the game's down bad, bro.
That's how you know the game's down bad.
That's how you know the the game's down bad.
And even even when you're on break share
and you're not even approaching, you
just watch other people do it and they
get the same [ __ ]
Tick streamers, people on Instagram,
they get the same [ __ ] It's bad.
It is bad, bro.
But so what happens in Canada then? Like
when when you go on um when you go on a
dating app, what happens? You just get no matches.
I don't get matches, me, bro. And if I
do get matches, they don't even respond.
typical lad. Typical.
Yeah, I've had chances in the past, JA.
I've had dates in the past, but I used
to screw up a lot of the chances that I
that I got.
But I learned from my mistakes, you
know. I learned from my mistakes. You
know, if I ever found anyone again by
miracle, some kind of miracle, it would
never happen again. Why do you think I
was I made sure no one on YouTube was
ever going to find Christian Izzy? Why
do you think I didn't say anything out
of pocket? Because, you know, bro, if
you if you ever ever do get given a
chance and you [ __ ] it up, bro, that's
not good. Could take you years again.
>> I remember I remember JNA. Yeah. The
first one night stand I had wasn't even
it wasn't even in London. I swear to
God, bro, I was trying for a whole year
in London approaching everything. Same
[ __ ] I was more confident back then
because I had more energy back then. I
was younger back then, bro. I used to
get like eight, nine numbers. Didn't get
a date sometimes. Didn't even get a
response. [ __ ] it went on for ages,
bro. cuz I used to I started in London
and then I went to Manchester and that's
when I had my first like one night stand
and then I came to London then came back
to London then then my first one night
stand down was with an American and then
it just went from there really then I
had some like good runs in April then it
went back to [ __ ] again and now it's
just like completely impossible but yeah
I think I went through like 8 months to
a year again nothing
and I approached I was bang on it bro
trust Trust me. So, I assure you, bro,
there's nothing in the slightest easy about dating.
I can't think of one thing easy about
any of it.
I come back for Manchester and Yeah, bro. Like,
and then the first one down was with an
American. Yeah. Which is [ __ ] weird. So, yeah.
What can you do, lad?
Well, I suppose I suppose in Canada it's
the same thing. If you approach
I have a boyfriend. No more India.
Yeah, pretty much.
And if you do really want sex, you'll
have to go to an escort to join the pool industry.
There you go, bro. That's it, is it? It
isn't worth it, bro. It really ain't
cuz you don't get anything for the for
the effort that you put in. JNA, you get
it? You don't get anything.
You don't get any anything for the
effort that you put in. You get me?
Whereas in life? Yeah. If you put effort
into stuff and you want to get stuff
out, otherwise you wouldn't do it, would
you? Think about it. Would you go to the
gym if it didn't help your mental
health? If it didn't give you if you
didn't get a good physique, no one would do it.
No one would do it.
Yeah. Well, I wouldn't I wouldn't get
sex. I would just get [ __ ] anyways.
I wouldn't have sex. I would just get [ __ ]
So, I don't have sex.
But yeah, so like, you know, if you put
effort into most things in life, bro,
you get stuff out. But with this, you
could get a haircut every day. You could
wash your ass 10 times a day. You could
be you could have money coming out your
ass and it still wouldn't make a
difference. You're just born in the
wrong era. It's as simple as that, bro.
Like that's it. Um
yeah, that's that's that's where you're
at basically, bro.
Even offering people body dump work,
I think I done Yeah, I did that before
many times. You can't do anything. It's
it's just impossible.
Like you got more chance of like pigs flying, bro.
Pigs flying over chimney. It ain't
happening. Greavves is going to Greavves
is going to understand how hard it is
when when he finally dates. I can't
wait. Bless him. Pucker.
He thinks it's a walk in the park.
Nothing easy about it, bro. Nothing easy
about it. Poor [ __ ]
Yeah, poor [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, if that if that Christian Izzy
thing worked, I would have just stayed
with him, bro. Like,
yeah, I didn't care about the sex or
anything, bro. I really didn't.
Yeah, good luck. You're going to need
it, lad. Good luck, mate. That's all I
can say. Hope you do better than me, bro. Yeah.
People on Reddit, JNA says you can get
sex whenever you want. Yeah, right, bro.
These people are not living in a real world.
[ __ ] hell, man.
Get the pain sorted. Oh,
to be fair, bro. I think it happens to a
lot of people, bro. Black or white. Some
people are racist towards black people,
bro. Some women are racist toward black people.
I think they're I just think they're just [ __ ]
I used to get some instant dates as
well, JNA. I used to get some instant dates. Um,
do you remember that guy I met on
YouTube called John? He used to go by
the name of John and and we went I went
approach him with him grievy. Me and him
went approaching together.
Do you remember that?
I never saw him again after years, bro.
I wonder what happened to that
[ __ ] Bro, I met him. The guy
actually met him on on YouTube. What I
would do, J. Yeah. Listen, bro. If I was
really going to date in the West again, bro,
the smart the smartest thing to do, I
think, is to go somewhere where there's less competition.
Long-term JNA. Like, you need to go
somewhere like where there's where
there's less people.
that way, bro. Like, if they're too poor
to get out of their area, they're not
going to have much. They're not going to
have many options.
That's I'm saying. Obviously, it might
not work, but I'm saying that is
probably the smartest route to go down,
bro, if you did want to date.
Um, because obviously,
you need to you need to be somewhere
where you sort of like, how do I explain
it? Like, [ __ ] stand out. See, the
thing is the the the the um people
misunderstand it, bro. Like people seem
to think JN or London, London, London,
London's easy because there's loads of
people, but it isn't cuz people are
stuck up in London because they've got
money and people have got options in
London. Yeah, that's the only bad thing, JNA. Yeah,
if I was if I was if I was going to go
to one of them states in America, bro,
it probably be like [ __ ] Georgia or somewhere.
build you a Florida somewhere you could stand out
and even then it'd be hard but you know
[ __ ] like you need to go somewhere
where like you kind of stand out in a
way I can't explain it but like yeah Right.
But what makes me laugh day and age is
how people think there's still hope.
When people are getting worse, things
are getting worse.
The only thing that will never ever
change your life is probably your dating
life, bro. Not I'm not talking about
you. I don't know you, bro. I don't know
you. I'm not trying to put [ __ ] into
your head, bro. what I'm saying for like
realistically that's probably the only
thing that probably will always stay the same
because of the day and age that we're living in
cuz how I use this analogy then is that
if it's been going on for years what
makes you think the next time you go out
it's it's going to change think about it
think about the odds right now yeah it's
not like you're getting dates you're
getting kisses anymore you're getting
replies then we can say okay we're
cooking on gas You understand what I'm
saying, bro? So, if you're like trying
Yeah. like if you're um it's just it's
just common sense.
It's common sense that it's very
unlikely, you know, like it's
people on Reddit seem to think that like Nah,
I don't know, bro. It's weird.
Nah, it's never going to happen again.
It's going to get worse. See, when I
used to go out JNA, I used to get
kisses, numbers, the occasional dates.
Um, things used to happen. It was still
[ __ ] hard as [ __ ] but it's still
[ __ ] used to happen. Now, nothing happens.
Nothing happens at all, bro.
Just nothing progresses. There's no progress.
You get me, lad? Yeah, right.
I don't think so, Dad.
Nah, bro. Like I said, I haven't had a
date since April.
If you can barely get a conversation out
someone, I very
much doubt that you're going to just meet someone.
Bro, listen. I saw you on L J saying
that I'm uh out of shape. I'm not
[ __ ] out of shape. I ain't even got a
[ __ ] beard belly, you cheeky [ __ ]
About I'm out of shape.
Yeah, but bro, there is no hope, lads.
There is no hope. [ __ ]
I'm out. I'm out of shape, bro. No, I'm [ __ ] not.
Not even anywhere near out of shape, lad.
Oh my god. This is disgusting, bro. One second.
I'm out of shape. Have you seen Have you
seen your boyfriend, Lord Jad?
wanted to talk about. You want to talk
about how to stay lad? Have you seen your boyfriend?
This is disgusting, bro.
Yeah. Fire stick. Sorry. Now, there is no hope.
The only people that can give you hope
is the women. And they don't. So yeah.
Oh, just this [ __ ] Dr. Echo
out of shape. Must be talking about himself, lad.
Must be self projected.
No, I'm just having a I was just having a [ __ ]
Yeah, I was just having a [ __ ] lad.
as as you do. Yeah.
Yeah. That Christian Izzy, bro. She made
me lose the last bit of hope, bro. [ __ ]
Yeah. I eat I eat I eat takeaways all
the time, bro. I got a false metabolism.
I actually leave the house unlike you
and Lord Jay.
Yeah, I actually leave the house unlike
you and Lord Jad.
It's called leaving the house, bro. And
actually, I didn't eat I didn't even eat
yesterday until 1:00 in the morning.
Yeah. Okay. I'm speculating, bro. Like I
said, when you can prove to me I'm
speculating, then tell me I'm
speculating. Well, well, let me put it
this way, mate. The fact the fact that
most of you people in LJ's don't come on
camera, it pretty much proves my point.
The fact that most of you don't even
come on the hangouts and talk and show
your face. I mean, it pretty much it
pretty much proves it's a fact at this
point. So, yeah,
you must be the only community where 95%
of the people don't show their faces. I
I wonder why that is.
I'll leave you to figure that one out, Fire Stick.
I will leave you with that one, Fire Stick.
I think that's a bit strange. Yeah.
Yeah. I'll put the link up, bro.
Just making a cup of cup now.
I'll be going over someone's face tomorrow. Grezy.
that I'll be going over someone's face tomorrow.
I might just get You know what I might
do? I might just get a hammer.
No, I might just use a hammer. Greasy.
No, I don't think I want to I don't I
don't even want to see another hammer
again in my life, you know, bro.
I don't think I want to see another
hammer again in my life, bro. [ __ ] that. Nah,
I don't think I don't I don't want to
see one ever again, bro. Nah.
No, I don't want to see I don't ever
want to see one ever again, bro.
I feel like when I go out there fire
stick, someone's just going to randomly
hit me over the head with a hammer. Scary, bro.
I feel like somebody's going to like hit
me over the head with a hammer, bro.
It's all that gir. It's all that G [ __ ]
isn't it? It's all that G [ __ ] isn't it, Greasy? Yeah,
it's all that G [ __ ] You didn't You
didn't even want to watch any of the
things, did it? I told you about
you didn't even want to watch any of
this [ __ ] How did I find out? Cuz
Antman told me.
He said, "Oh, I advise you don't watch
it." He said, "Oh, you should watch it.
You should watch it." I'm still He said,
"I've still got anxiety to stay because of it."
And I was like, "Oh, me being me. Let me
just watch it."
Yeah. I'm safely scared of hammers now. So yeah.
Yeah, bro. [ __ ] that.
No, I found it cuz of Antman. Antman
told me about it. I don't know how to
come up with conversation again.
I won't be backing out of no fighting
because Timmy's not going anywhere. No.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah, it doesn't matter if he's ordered
the tickets, lad. I've booked tickets to
places I've not been before.
>> Yeah, they're not going anywhere, bro.
If they know what's good for them, they
won't be going anywhere.
Doesn't matter if he's paid for the
ticket. I paid for a ticket to go to
America. I didn't go the first time.
What does that mean, bro? I paid for a
ticket to go to Nottingham. I didn't go.
What's a ticket mean, lad?
What does that mean, Joe?
Oh, you can also get refunds for tickets
as well, bro. Will I be going live
tomorrow? Of course I will.
Of course I will be, bro. Nothing's happening tomorrow.
Never mention Thailand.
Never mention Thailand, bro.
Listen, Fire Stick, like I said, lad,
I'll believe it when I see it.
Yeah, I'll believe it when I see it. I
think that's fair enough, isn't it, Grezy?
Yeah, I'll believe it when I see it.
You know what I mean?
But he's [ __ ] either way. Whatever he
does, cuz if he doesn't go, he's going
to get mocked. If he does, I'm going to
finish him. So, whatever happens, he's
going to lose.
Either way, so
he has to understand as well that like
he's actually come before with another
person and I met both of them. You
understand Fire Stick? I don't know how
long you've been on this community, bro,
but I was on this um thing three um he
went on the door, bro.
I've been to Amsterdam.
I've been to other countries, bro. What the [ __ ] Anyways, um
uh what was I saying? So, we come with
Tiger years ago and I still went in broad daylight.
It doesn't matter if he's booked the
train, bro. I can book a train right
now. Doesn't mean I'm going anywhere.
Like I said, I believe it when I see it,
bro. I believe it when someone's actually here.
That's it. That's fair enough, bro. Is it?
Yeah, he's showing the tickets. That's nice, bro.
I mean, okay. I'll see you tomorrow then. Simple. Yeah, man.
And that's that, bro.
So, um Yeah.
Yeah, he ain't coming anywhere, bro. Trust me.
He ain't coming anywhere, lad.
Trust me. This is what he does. This is
how this community goes round and round
in circles. Fire stick. That's why we
call it a disabled community. You see?
No, I'm not meeting him in no train station.
I'm not meeting anyone anywhere, lad.
Unless they come knocking on the door.
I'm not doing anything. I'm not meeting
him anywhere. I've already said this.
And you know what's going to happen
tomorrow as well?
Do you know exactly what's going to
happen tomorrow as well?
I'm not meeting anywhere. I'm not
meeting anywhere, bro.
Unless someone actually physically comes
knocking on the door, I'm not going
anywhere. I've said this.
Wasting my time, wasting my energy on
jealous ass people. But you know,
obviously if they come Yeah.
I don't want him to go anywhere. I agree
with you. I don't want him to go anywhere.
I don't want him to go anywhere. I'm
stating that if he comes on the door,
I'm finishing him. I don't want him to
go anywhere. I don't give a [ __ ] where he goes.
At the end, I don't care where he goes,
bro. He started it. So, all I'm saying
is where if he comes knocking on the
door, I'll finish him. Simple.
Yeah. Okay. You think I'll back out? Okay, whatever.
Basically. Yeah. Yeah. Basically, yeah.
Simple. Yeah. recently. Yeah.
Stop it, Indigo. Bro, it's boring now, lad.
Very, very boring, Indigo.
No, I didn't say that. No, I didn't say
Anyways, let's stop talking about
something that's never going to happen,
bro. It's a waste of time. Yeah.
It's just a waste of time, bro, with
these retards. I'll believe it when I see it. Yeah.
That's it. It's a waste of time, bro.
Until something actually happens. Uh
yeah, we'll believe it when I see it.
And if he doesn't go,
no, I'm not meeting him. I don't I don't
need to meet a [ __ ] I don't need to
waste my time meeting a a jealous [ __ ]
But obviously, if he comes on the door,
that's a different story. He started it,
so that's it. Yeah.
So, you didn't like the look of my new
mammas then, Greavesy? No.
I don't want him to come down. He
started it. I don't want the [ __ ] to
come down. Fire stick.
He's the one that started it. So I said,
"Yeah, okay. If you're going to come,
I'll finish you." He's just trying to
show off for YouTube. No one asked him
to come down. You know exactly how it
started. You know exactly how it started, bro.
You know exactly how it started.
So you know what I mean? Yeah.
I'm afraid to leave the house.
I'm afraid to leave the house. Really, bro?
Yeah. Okay, bro. I'm afraid to leave the
house. Okay, bro. Yeah, you're right,
bro. You got me, bro. Yeah.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
Fire stick. Fire stick. Fire stick. This
is how it happened. This is what this
little weasel does. It's the same thing
as what he done to Monty, man. He was
doing videos trying to wool me out,
mentioning my name, mentioning my name.
Mentioning my name. I said, "Okay, [ __ ]
it. You don't stop mentioning my name.
I'm going to message your family." Then
he was like, "Oh, I'm going to come
here. I'm going to come here. I'm going
to do this." I was like, "Okay, bro.
Yeah, I will I I'll pay for your taxi."
Yeah, I'm not afraid of anyone. Yeah,
I'm not afraid of anyone. And I I don't
need to prove myself to anyone on this community.
And I don't need to prove myself to any
jealous people in this community either.
So, yeah. I'm scared to leave my house,
bro. Yeah. Terrified.
No, it's not going to be back and forth.
It's not going to be back and forth.
None of it's going to be back and forth,
lad. Maybe without [ __ ] but I will
not be entertaining back and forth, lad.
Yeah, but no, Fire Stick, he started it,
bro. He started it. Just like a lot of
these jealous people in this community start it.
Yeah, I didn't leave the house, but I
was out all day yesterday and I was out today.
But I'm scared to leave the house.
Really, bro? You're funny, lad. You know.
Yeah. I lose brain cells on this
disabled community, bro. I really lose brain cells.
You've booked. You booked a cinema
screen and then nothing's going to happen.
Nothing's going to happen, bro. Nothing
is going to happen at all.
Nothing's going to happen at all.
Trust me, he's not brave enough to come
on someone's mother's door, bro. Trust
me, he's not that brave. He's not that big.
Yeah, bro. The neighbors know about me.
The neighbors know all about me, bro. So
that's not the neighbors will tell them
to [ __ ] off. Everybody knows me around
there, bro. So,
um, no, I will not be having a pipe with that [ __ ]
No, I will not be having a point with
that [ __ ] [ __ ]
So, yeah. And you know what's going to
happen now as well, Fire Stick?
You know exactly what's going to happen
now as well. This is how these people
draw you back in, bro. Do you get it?
No, I'm not I'm not wasting my time and
energy on on spasticated jealous people.
Nope. I don't need to. I don't waste my
time on jealous people. I got better
things to be doing with my time, bro.
Nope. Not at all.
I'm not wasting my time on jealous
people. Been there, done that, lad. Not doing it.
Yeah. Simp. We know what the rules are anyways.
You know what the rules are anyways, lad.
I've already told you, bro. And I don't
want to Let's stop talking about this,
bro. Until it actually happens. Can we
stop talking about it? It's boring. It's
[ __ ] boring, lad.
Lamp me hard, bro. He's not even going
to get a chance.
Yeah, I won't leave the house, bro. I'm
housebound. Yeah. Yeah, I know, bro.
Yeah. I wasn't out all day yesterday. I
wasn't out the other day.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Bro, you're
right, man. I'm just agrophobic in it.
I love it, bro.
That's [ __ ] funny. No, I'm I'm
wanting to get out of this jealous
community as soon as possible, bro. As
soon as this all [ __ ] this [ __ ] ends
tomorrow. We're We're out this
community, bro. We're out the jealous
weirdo old man community. Isn't that right, Greavvesy?
with these little self-reflecting little
weirdos. Isn't that right, Greavves?
Isn't that right, Greavves? We're
outside. We're out of this jealous ass
community. I know I am, bro. Do you know
what? I'm going to link you the channel
right now. Actually, are you on Instagram, bro?
You're going to laugh at You're going to
laugh at the name, bro.
Bro. Yeah. You know, in it, lad. No.
Hey, bro. Listen, I'll link it to you
now. Yeah. You're going to laugh at the name.
Do you want a channel, bro? I'll link it
to you on Instagram now. Yeah. All
right. One sec.
Yeah. I'm running away from Timmy. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, bro.
Right. I'm going to link you it. Yeah.
There you go. You got my new channel. Easy. Yep. Yeah. Okay. [ __ ] sake.
No, I'm talking to Greasy, lad. Yeah, bro.
Hope you love the name.
I'm not meeting that [ __ ] I've
already told you what's happening. I'm
not repeating myself again, bro. I'm not
repeating myself again.
It's cute though, isn't it, Grezy? It's cute.
It's cute though, is it, lad? They're
never going to find it though,
Greavvesy. They're never going to find it.
I'll link it to you as well, Stephen.
Uh, Steven Howard,
email me, bro. I'm going to send you
this new channel cuz we're off here on
Thursday. We need to stay here for
tomorrow. We'll be on here Thursday and
then we're bouncing, bro.
Yeah, we're bouncing. And same with you,
Fire Stick. You can email me, lad.
Oh, and out of this jealous ass community,
full of these weirdos.
Whoa. Bro, they're not going to find it, bro. Yep.
New subscriber Grezy. Yay.
Oh, is he coming with backup?
Yeah, it's not Christian, is he? Try
again, lad. You'll never find it. Yeah.
Get away from this toxic little sector.
Isn't that right, Fire Stick?
Nah, I'm not a copycat, Doc. I'm not a
copycat, Dr. Echo.
I'm not a little copycat.
I'm not a little copycat. She's hot.
She's hot. I'm not a copycat, lad.
I don't cop I don't follow crowds, lad.
I'm getting away from these people. You
got my email, ain't it, lad? So,
where's that Smokeoky be gone? I ain't
seen him for a while.
And the reason though, trust me, this is
the best thing to go on this channel,
this new channel. It's the best way,
lad. It's the best way. Trust me, it's
the best thing because we can say more
stuff without having to worry about
stalkers. We won't have, you know,
people create drama and then you argue
back with them and then LT gets involved
and the same [ __ ] happens. Like, trust
me, this is the best way, bro. And we're
not going to know nothing that happens.
Now, see, if people mention me, no one's
going to I'm not going to know. If
anyone mentions me, no, I'm not going to
know. You see?
Because when I say I'm done, I'm done,
bro. I'm not going to be lurking on no
channels watching. I don't care, bro. You know,
I'll do a video talking about these
people before I go as well,
like on Thursday and that. Yeah, trust
me. No, I'm not going to know if anyone
mentions my name. I won't know.
Yeah, maybe you shouldn't have said
that, Grezy. You [ __ ] idiot.
Now you're just kind of like, you just
gave them that idea. You [ __ ] idiot.
No, we're jumping on my new channel,
bro. I just gave it to Grievy. I'm going
to give it to Steven Howard. We're
jumping off this sector on Thursday,
lad. Still going to go live on that, but
just on a different sector
cuz this is beyond weird now. Is it,
bro? Come on.
Yeah, the jealousy and the weirdness
from these people is so so weird. It's
just too weird, Dusty, to to to put into words, lad.
Yeah, but you've just baited it out by
saying that, bro. They're probably not
going to find it, but still, you're an
idiot, bro. Yeah, you will see me
tomorrow. Yeah, you will see me tomorrow
cuz I'll be live tomorrow, lad. Yeah,
I'll be live tomorrow.
Yeah, I'll be live tomorrow. Waiting for
this [ __ ] So, yeah, you will see me
tomorrow. Yeah, you're right. You will
see me tomorrow.
Yeah, you will see me tomorrow, lad.
You will see me tomorrow. You're damn
right. You bet you will see me tomorrow, bro.
Yeah. Well, that's that in it, lad. You
can miss me all you want. I don't care.
Look at Jo. Tim just calls a scene on
the street. You won't get nicked at all,
but Elaine will want him out. Another
one that's obsessed just Joseph [ __ ]
That's another one we don't want on the
channel. Um, Grezy. So, make sure you
don't give him the channel, lad. I don't
want none of them lying mongs on my
channel. Do you get it?
Isn't this same Jo the same guy that's
supposed to be meeting London Taylor?
The little [ __ ]
Make sure you don't give that my
channel, mate. I don't want none of
these spastics on my new channel, bro.
We're making we're giving we're getting
we've made a new channel to get away
from these people.
You understand? We We've done it. The
whole purpose is to get away from these
people, get some of the good people on
here and leave the rest. That's the
whole point of it. Do you get it?
Do you get what I'm saying, Fire Stick?
It makes perfect sense.
And we can talk about some more stuff as well, lad.
And I talk about this community, how
weird this community is as well. all the
weird things they do on it, bro.
No, I don't, mate. I don't want any of
you. I'd rather be talking to myself.
You people are freaks on this community,
bro. You're freaks.
I I don't want anyone finding it. I'll
delete their channel again. If you find
it, I'll delete it. As simple as that.
If they find a channel, I'll delete it, lad.
I'll delete the channel. Simple.
And I'll start all over again. It's not
a problem, bro.
The [ __ ] you people do on it is so
weird. Like no fire stick. Yeah. You You
know, the more you think of it. Yeah.
The more weird it is.
They're so weird on here. You get me, lad?
You would have thought they would have got bored.
That is the main That's a good point.
You would have thought they would have
got bored, lad. Yeah.
No, he's never going to find it, bro.
And even if he did find it, I would make
a new channel.
Little gay boys.
They're weirdos, bro. You would have
thought they got bit. No, when I gave
this [ __ ] Grief in America fire stick, I
I I I gave up after a while, bro. And
this was someone I actually met and
[ __ ] Imagine that. Five stick. And
these people are casually doing it for
four or five years and they've never
even met you. Imagine that, bro. Like,
no. No, just think about it. Imagine that.
Like, imagine that. Think about it, bro.
Like, use that analogy, bro.
Or a fire stick. man. You just use that analogy
and see how weird it is. Then you then
you'll know how real weird it is. And
they can't say that it's things you've
said because think think about it. Fire
stick. Yeah. You don't understand. There
are actually sick people in the world.
Like I would go as far as saying, bro.
Yeah. That you saying mad stuff about
people and people's kids, bro. That that
isn't even on the top 10, bro.
There was there were some really sick
people out there, bro. Trust me. Trust
me. You don't want to see certain videos
and things, but bro, there were like
proper like sick people out there.
When I was scrolling up, yeah, I was
seeing some mad titles and oh, I didn't
even click on the videos and that, bro.
Like, bro, trust me. Trust me, there's
there's some sick people out there.
Yeah. Yeah. Isn't that the same thing as
what LT said? Someone's being a little copycat.
Yeah, that's another thing. Greasy. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] Yeah. I hope yours is turned off.
Why is yours turned off, Grezy?
Is yours turned off?
Let me see. Yours better be turned off.
You're just trying to bait the whole
thing out, bro. Greavves is just trying
to bait the whole thing.
Yeah, you you're just trying to bait up
the whole thing, bro. Really, if you
think about it, you're just trying to
make it obvious. Why are you telling
them like what what what is to do with
and stuff, bro?
You've actually just gave them ideas
even though they're still not going to
find it. But you've just you could have
p you could have private messaged me
that you absolute idiot. Yeah.
Yeah. But when you're pointing out
you're pointing it out publicly where
people are watching.
Yeah. But you're point Yeah. But you're
you're you're pointing it out publicly
where people are watching. you idiot.
But all the stalkers are watching.
You're so dumb. I swear down to you
could be so dumb sometimes, bro.
So anyways, Fire Stick, what do you
think of that um Christian Izzy situation?
Yeah, that's what I was thinking.
Do you want to come on talk on the on
the link fire stick? You want to have a chat, lad?
Hello, Captain [ __ ] Do you remember
that one? Creepsy. Hello, Captain [ __ ]
I do want to have a chat fire stick,
bro. I'm hung over as [ __ ] man.
Yeah. But yeah, these people stalk you
more than you would stalk a woman you
was obsessed with and you and you [ __ ]
And they still say they're not gay. Fire stick.
They still not They still say that
you're not gay, you know.
It's not going to happen, bro.
Stop repeating. It's not going to
happen. Let's cross that bridge when we
come to it. Yeah.
Yeah. We We'll cross that bridge when we
come to it, lad. Stop repeating.
Oh, we got the tickets. Oh, I just saw
that video, bro. He said, "We got the tickets."
Yeah, right, bro. Yeah, right. Bro, did
you hear him? He said, "We got the
tickets." Who's we? Who's we? You
[ __ ] [ __ ] Please do come tomorrow
anyways, bro. Please do come. I'm ready
for him, bro. I'm [ __ ] ready. Anyways,
an early night to go to [ __ ] London
from Birmingham. Anyone would think this
guy's going [ __ ] America or
Australia. He's going nowhere, mate.
He's going absolutely [ __ ] nowhere.
Trust me, mate. He ain't going nowhere.
The fat [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah. You can keep thinking that, bro.
You can keep thinking that.
Anyways, we'll see you tomorrow then, won't we?
We'll see tomorrow, won't we?
I'll be up live early tomorrow. Don't
you worry about that, bro. Don't you
worry about that.
And what am I going to do if he does
turn up? You're going to see what's
going to happen.
Stop asking the same questions over and
over and over again, bro. I'll be live
tomorrow anyways, early. So, yeah.
Yeah, I'm going to title this video is
I'm going to title the video Greavvesy.
This is what happens when you try to
show off for YouTube.
I'm going to like literally make a video
of it, bro.
Yeah, I'm going to I'm going to make a
whole video of it. This is what happens
when you try to show off over YouTube. Yeah.
Yeah. You will never ever ever find my
channel, you sad, gay little jealous bastard.
But yeah, bro. Yeah, I'll be up early
tomorrow as well and I'm going to show
you what happens when you try to act the
big man for YouTube trying to show off.
Bro, I'm going to seriously seriously
seriously hurt him, bro. Seriously, I'm
seriously going to hurt him, bro. Trust me.
Keep it clean. I'm not keeping it clean.
No, no, no, no, no. I'm not keeping it clean.
I'm not keeping it clean at all.
But I'm not keeping it clean. There's no
rules. You're You're coming to where I
live and and you're knocking on my door.
I'm not keeping it clean. I'm banging
his head in.
I'm banging a fat cunt's head in. Trust
me, mate. Trust me. I'm not I'm not I'm
not playing it fair. I'm going to show
this little [ __ ] You're not going to
keep showing off for YouTube. Don't
worry, bro. Don't worry.
Trust me, there's not going to be no.
You're getting You're getting it in your
head. Simple. Yeah.
Teach you to keep showing off for
YouTube, you [ __ ] fat, ugly [ __ ]
You're going to see, bro. I'll be up
early tomorrow. I'll be live. I'll be
live. I will be live. I'm going to give
him one bang in his head, bro. And he's
never going to forget it. I swear to God. Yeah.
Yeah. That's fine, bro. That's fine,
lad. Yeah, I'm doing it dirty. I'm doing
it proper proper dirty.
I'm doing it proper proper dirty.
Okay, put it this way, bro. I'm not
losing. Put it this way. Yeah, I'm not
losing no matter what it takes. You
understand me, Fire Stick? I'm not
losing. I am not losing no matter what
it takes. Put it that way, bro. Yeah.
and read into that what you will.
It doesn't matter if he comes up if he
if he comes with free man. It doesn't
matter, bro. It doesn't matter.
So, what is this [ __ ] coming for? Is he
coming with backup anyway? He's a little [ __ ]
Is this little fat [ __ ] coming with backup again?
Is Is that what Is he Is he coming with
backup again then? Yeah, the little [ __ ]
the little [ __ ] [ __ ] off. Is he
coming with backup? The fat [ __ ]
Is that Is that what he's saying? Yeah.
Yeah. He got me. He got a bet of me.
That's not what happened.
I'm going to do a video. I'm going to do
a video for Timmy, bro. I'm going to do
a video for Timmy.
Yeah. Stripping me naked, bro. That is
never going to happen. Trust me, that is
never going to happen. Trust me. They're
getting battered. Even if I used to even
if I need to use a weapon, bro, I'm
going out there with a weapon. Please do
come tomorrow. Please hurry up. Let me
bang you in your head one more time. You
didn't even beat me the last time. For
[ __ ] sake, bro. You didn't even beat
me the last time.
You didn't even beat me the last time.
You [ __ ] clown.
Yeah, it would have been a good
opportunity for you to meet London
Taylor as well. Like you arranged, but
you never. But you never.
Yeah, but you never. H Yeah, but you
Yeah, I'll be f. Don't worry, bro. It
doesn't matter how many of them there
is. I'll sort it out, bro. Don't you
worry. Don't you [ __ ] worry, bro.
I'll be live tomorrow anyways, bro. As
soon as I like time I wake up, I'll be
live, bro. Don't you worry about that.
Yeah. And he's going to be getting
himself seriously hurt. And he's going
to be getting himself seriously hurt.
Hey, Dusty. Listen, bro. The last time
he went on the door, did I not show up,
bro? At the old house. Back at the old
house three years ago.
I'm not bringing any trouble to anyone's
door. He's the one that wants to come.
He's the one saying he wants to come
because he's a jealous [ __ ] who's
jealous of me like a lot of you people. Yeah,
you. He's He's bringing trouble. He's
the one saying that he's coming on the
door. So, I will batter him. Don't try
to reverse the psychology, you
narcissist. You have bothered me like
you have bothered other people. Don't
try and say, "Oh, you're bringing
trouble to your mommy's door." Don't try
and reverse the psychology, you jealous
bastards. Yeah. No one's No one's No one
made you Yeah. No one made you do a
video and start mentioning people's
name. Yeah. You little narcissist. Come
with whoever you want, bro. Come with
whoever the [ __ ] you want, you little
narcissist. You people start with your
jealousy and then people react to you.
Yeah. People react to you and then you
tell people that they're bringing
trouble to their mom's door when you
started it with your fat, ugly,
self-projecting self. Am I lying? Am I
lying, bro? Am I lying? Who done a video
on who? Who done a video on who? Who
started mentioning whose name? Fatty Iva
Virgin Eldridge started mentioning my name. Yeah,
he started mentioning my name because
he's jealous and he's done his balls in.
Yeah. So, I reacted to him. Don't try to
reverse the psychology, you narcissist.
Don't you even dare try to reverse the psychology,
you [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
Every single fight that's happened with
Timmy, he has started it. Yeah. He has
started it. You understand, bro? He has
Yeah. He has started it. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying? He has started
it. I think with every every fight I
think he started every single one of them.
Yeah. Simple as that.
Simple as that. He started it. He
literally started it just like last
time. Am I lying? I don't know if he was
around that time. Fire stick. Yeah.
What have I said? What have I said, bro?
What have I said, bro? What have I said?
What have I said, bro? Tell No, I don't
know what I've said. What have I said? Yeah.
Yeah. I'll be calling it embarrassing in
the morning, mate, cuz I'll be up
waiting for you. And this is what I'm
saying to people after after Well, I'm
getting off Thursday, bro. Just leave
this community. This is what will happen
with these jealous people. They'll never
leave you alone. It's like what someone
said to me, Fire Stick. I should have
listened to it ages ago. You're better
looking than them. You got more money
than them. You should leave. They're
jealous. I should have listened, bro.
Years and years. I should have listened
to the to the guy, bro. Like, we're
talking two and a half years ago. He
said, "You're better looking than them.
You got more money than them." And it
kills them. And And I should have
listened to it, bro. I swear to God, I
should have listened to it.
You know what I'm saying, bro? You're
better looking than them. You got more
money than them. It's the truth, bro.
It's the truth. I swear to God, bro,
years later. Yeah. I swear down it is
the truth. With the amount, you've seen
it yourself. Fire stick. Yeah. The
amount of people Yeah. that have got
these channels that are dedicated to me.
It is jealousy. The fact that they tried
to deny it, bro, is mad. Yeah. This is
all jealousy. Why do you think you've
got all these middle-aged men obsessed
with you, bro? Why do you think you got
so many old men obsessed with you
though, bro, for 5 years when they
should be obsessed with the love of
their life? Think about it, bro. Think about it.
Yeah, think about it, bro.
He's going to bed in a minute. Anyone
would think this guy's going [ __ ]
Australia tomorrow, bro.
Bro, anyone would think this guy is
going to Australia tomorrow.
And this is what happens, bro. They they
start [ __ ] and then reverse the psychology.
Yeah. And then they reverse the
psychology. You understand? Trying to
say that you're bringing trouble. Who
started this fire stick? You saw the
video. I saw the video. Yeah.
But don't worry, lad. Don't worry.
You're going to get knocked the [ __ ] out
tomorrow. Don't you worry about that.
Yeah. You fat [ __ ] I'm going to knock
the rest of your [ __ ] teeth out as
well, you [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
Yeah, he started it and I'll finish it.
Yeah, simple as that.
Uh, he just randomly came to London, bro.
Yeah. Uh, he just randomly came to
London with Tiger starting [ __ ] It's
always been him. Even with Monty Man,
bro. Even when Monty man Yeah. went back
and forth, back and forth, back and
forth, back and forth. He done it the
same thing with Monty Man. He done the
same thing with Monty. It's always been
this little [ __ ] It's always been this
Trust me, bro. It's always been this little [ __ ]
Yeah. And that's it, bro. Yeah. It's
always been this little jealous [ __ ]
IBA virgin. It's always been him, bro.
With everyone. With everyone. It's
always been him, lad.
No, there's not, lad. No.
Yeah. Yeah, I will. Oh, don't you worry.
you [ __ ] little [ __ ] Yeah,
it's what happens, bro. Yeah.
And that's that, bro.
Yeah, he's been doing it for years, lad. Yeah.
I don't want him crying tomorrow anyways, bro.
Yeah. Joe, you can't even talk on a
panel, you [ __ ] little [ __ ] You
can't even talk on a panel, you [ __ ]
disabled [ __ ] poverty ridden mong.
Yeah, you can't even you can't even
[ __ ] talk on the panel, you [ __ ]
Yeah, you [ __ ] [ __ ] Jealous [ __ ]
little nons lover.
Yeah, and it's going to show something
as well. It's going to show something as
well. Timmy's got more balls than you. Is it?
Bigger than you, mate. Yeah, bigger than
you, you [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah, I'm
bigger than you will ever be.
You're scared little [ __ ] Jealous
little [ __ ] Just like the rest of them.
Just don't make excuses tomorrow
anyways. Yeah. I don't want to hear no excuses.
You [ __ ] fat ugly virgin. Yeah. 100% bro.
No, they're not helping no one, bro. Cuz
they were just I'm not even going to
tell you what's going to happen, bro.
Yeah, but that's it. But I'll advise
anyone Yeah. after this, don't join this
community. Anyone that's younger and
better looking than these people, they
will they will start on you. They won't
leave you alone. I'm going to say that
as well. I'm going to say like when I
leave on Thursday after I deal with
this, I'm going to be like, "Anyone stay
away from this jealous ass gay
community." Yeah. I'm going to talk
about all the [ __ ] they do, everything
that they do on Thursday, bro.
They're jealous of anyone better looking
than them. I will say it how it is. I'll
talk I'll talk I'll talk the most, bro.
Trust me. Yeah.
Yeah. And that's it, bro.
That's it. They're jealous. Anyone just
leave this jealous ass community? And
I'll say like, listen, bro, these people
don't even leave their house. They're
sat on there 24/7, 24 hours a day. They
will not come on camera when they're
asked to come on camera. Trust me. I'll
put I will do all of it, bro. The video
on Thursday, I will do all of it before
[ __ ] off. Trust me, bro. Just so
everyone knows. And if anyone ever comes
across this channel, they they they will
know what I tell them, bro. You know
what I'm saying? Yeah.
They will know what I tell them. Yeah.
They will know what I tell him, lad. Yeah.
No, I haven't called everyone out. Timmy
started on me. Yeah, we have all seen
Timmy started on me cuz he's a jealous
little virgin, right?
Do you understand? Simple.
Yeah, it's as simple as that, bro.
he's a jealous little [ __ ] I'm going
to do a little video. I'm going to do a
little video, bro. Don't you worry about that. Yeah,
cuz I don't want this [ __ ] coming out
with [ __ ] excuses. Yeah.
Yeah, Dr. Echo, no one cares about that,
lad. That's repeating.
That's repeating, lad. Go away, you
jealous bastard. Go back to L Go back to LJ's channel.
Yeah, go back to LJ's channel.
We've also seen you afraid to come on
camera and show yourself, but Yeah.
What the [ __ ] No one's encouraged it.
I've already explained it to you,
[ __ ] boy. All right, Joe. I've
already explained it to you, [ __ ]
Yeah, and you have started it on me. You
have started with me again. Stop trying
to reverse the psychology.
You've you've don't stop trying to
reverse the psychology. You jealous
people go for people like you. You
jealous ugly [ __ ] Like your boyfriend
nonslegs, right? You start on people due
to your jealousy and then people respond
back and then you try to play the
victim. Isn't that exactly what happens?
Joseph [ __ ] Virgin Boy, Nod Legs,
Timmy, they all start on people that are
better looking than them cuz they're
jealous. deep down they're jealous and
then they try to play the mole high
ground. It's exactly what a narcissist
do. You go for me cuz you're jealous
every day. Whether someone's on it,
whether they're not on it, you're
jealousy every day. So don't worry. He
said he's going to come. So see what
happens tomorrow. It's as simple as that.
We will see what happens tomorrow.
Simple as that then. Yeah.
Should have mentioned my name, [ __ ]
Shouldn't have mentioned my name. That's it.
Don't [ __ ] self-reflect your [ __ ]
[ __ ] onto me.
You get me, lad
Shepherd. I don't give a [ __ ] I'm not
answering stupid questions. Yeah, we
will see. Are you going to meet LT and
lead like you said you was going to? You
little [ __ ] house. Are you going to Are
you going to meet LT and lead like you
said, you little [ __ ] house? H
Yeah, we will see. [ __ ] jealous
little [ __ ] See what happens to him
tomorrow. know the IBA wrong. We booked
the tickets. Come tomorrow and stop
talking. Stop. Come tomorrow and stop talking. Yeah.
No one's calling him out again. You
started on me.
You started on me. Yeah. Again, jealous
people. Jealous jealous ass people in
this community. Yeah.
Oh. Oh. So it wasn't an L then. Make up
your mind, mate. You can't you can't
play two sides of a coin. Yeah.
Yeah. [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] You make your
little gay videos. You make your little
gay. And bro, if you bring up if you
bring who you want, don't cry when
people use weapons.
Don't cry when people use weapons. I
will use any weapon I want. Simple as
that, bro. Yeah. It's as simple as that. Simple.
I'm going to [ __ ] bang the [ __ ] out
of that fat IBA [ __ ] nons legs loving
[ __ ] Watch, bro. Yeah. Watch. Watch.
You [ __ ] dirty little nons legs
lover. I'm going to give him a bang for
that as well. I'm going to give him one
bang for defending these boyfriend non
legs. Another bang for [ __ ]
mentioning my [ __ ] name. I'm going to
bruise his whole face up, bro. Trust me.
I'm going to bruise his whole [ __ ]
face up. Trust me, I'm a big bastard,
bro. This ain't This ain't 3 years ago.
This ain't 3 years ago, bro.
This ain't 3 years ago, bro. And you
still lost. You still lost 3 years ago.
You still lost 3 years ago, lad.
You still lost 3 years ago.
Oh, shut up, Joe. You little [ __ ] You
can't even meet LT, you little gay boy.
[ __ ] off, you little [ __ ] You [ __ ]
northern [ __ ] povertyridden [ __ ]
with a 300 pound phone. I'm so tempted
to get the money out again and [ __ ]
show you that I got more money than you.
Embarrass you again, bro. I'm so
tempted. You know that, bro. But you
know what? There's no point with you
biased people. I want to show you I got
more money than you. I want to do it,
bro. Again, 100%, lad. Yeah,
bro. You said you was going to meet LT.
Yeah. You said you was going to meet out.
You said you was going to [ __ ] meet Ali. Yeah.
No, there's not this again. Oh, look.
LT's watching again. I thought he left,
but he's on he's on here straight away.
Welcome back, bro. Welcome back.
Welcome back. And this is the same
pattern that keeps happening over and
over and over and over and over and over
again. I'm so bored of you people now.
I'm so bored of you people now. Like
seriously, I'm so bored of you people.
I'm so bored of you jealous people now.
Like it's so awfully boring. You jealous
people are very boring now.
Yeah, bro. You're always on here. You're
always on here. You're always on here,
bro. You know everything that goes on.
Let me ask you this question. How did
you know about that Rick's thing,
bro? Wait, hold on. Hold on. How did you
know about that Rick's thing? That is
That is mad, bro. Cuz this guy was
talking to you for about 20 seconds. How
did you know anything when it happened
in 20 Bro, come on. You sit and you
watch YouTube all day, bro. Come on.
Come on. It's so obvious. It's so
obvious. Come on, bro. He was speaking
to you about you for like 20 seconds and
somehow you know straight away.
It's so obvious, bro. It's so so so
obvious because guess what, bro? Yeah.
When when everyone goes to my channel,
well, listen listen. When everyone goes
on my channel Yeah. I'm not going to
know anything that said. How about that?
Listen listen. You know my new channel
that I've gave Greaves and I'm going to
give more people. I'm not going to know
what anyone has said. How about that?
I'm not going to know anything that anyone said.
How about that, bro? No, I'm not going
to know anything that anyone said. You
get me, bro? I'm not going to know
anything that anyone said. You see the
difference? Do you see the difference?
And no one's going to find my channel.
Do you see what I'm saying?
Do you see what I'm saying, though? You
see the difference? No one's going to
find it. And no one's I'm not going to
know if anyone talks about me. Yeah.
Trust me. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Whatever. Yeah. Yeah.
All I know is when I'm on my new channel. Yeah.
Yeah. All I know is All I know is no
one's going to find my new channel, bro.
And I'm not going to know anyone talking
about me. That's all I know. That's all
I know, bro. That's exactly who who I know.
I'm not meeting Timmy.
I'm not meeting Timmy at all.
And exactly. I predicted it. Hey, bro. I
I agree with you. Didn't I just predict
this? Yeah. Didn't I just predict this?
Didn't I not just predict exactly what
was going to happen? Bro, I know
everything. This community is too
obvious. It's the same thing every time,
bro. It's the same thing. I'm not
meeting that [ __ ]
You You left a comment. I didn't see it.
Bro, I deleted all my live streams.
I agree with you. I told you it's the
same thing every time, bro. This is why
I'm trying to get away from these
people, bro. Do you not understand? This
is why I'm trying to get away from these people, lad. Yeah.
try. This is why I'm trying to get away
from these people. But it's always this
fat [ __ ] that that drags people in
time and time again. Time and time and
time again. Do you see what I'm saying?
You see what I'm saying? Why do you
think I made a new channel, bro?
You got No, no, no, no, no. It's not a
madness with PJ. It's a madness with you
people. It's a madness with you people.
And you know what? It's always going to
start with this [ __ ] Timmy. He's done
it to me multiple times. He's done it to
Monty. It's always going to start with this [ __ ]
That's always how it's going to start
with these spastics.
Yeah. You You know what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah. It's That's how it's always going
to start with these little weirdos on
this community. These little weirdos.
And you know, the only reason I'm not
off here right now, bro, is because
Yeah. We're not letting this guy laugh
at us tomorrow. Simple as that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
True say, lad. True say, bro. Yeah, actually.
So, yeah, like I said, Grezy, we'll
cross that bridge when it comes to it, lad.
We'll cross that bridge when it when we
when it comes to it.
Do you not understand, Fire Stick, what
this Timmy does? Do you not understand
what this [ __ ] does?
Do you not understand what this little
[ __ ] does? It's so obvious what he does, bro. You know,
listen, listen, Joe, you're not meeting
LT, but you're supposed to meet LT. Stop
trying to [ __ ] you little wanker.
You little wanker. Oh, and did you see
my reply to your comment as well?
You didn't reply to the com. You didn't
reply to my comment as well, did you?
You didn't reply to my comment, did you?
Why is that? Cuz you know I'm right, is
it? Cuz you know I'm right.
>> Right, mate. You're [ __ ]
>> Listen, mate. Shut up and get to bed.
>> Shut up and get to bed like you said
you're going to do. Stop having anxiety
now. You're the one who's [ __ ]
rattling my name out your face and I'm chilled.
>> You know what I mean? Okay, mate. It's
going to happen, right? I'm not shaking
hand this time. None of this. Yeah,
you'll be like, "Oh, this [ __ ]
community and you'll be like crying in
front of the police." I can imagine what
tomorrow's going to be. You are beyond
pathetic. [ __ ] your little Discord. [ __ ]
your little [ __ ] wedding and all
that, mate. This is on. Good night.
>> [ __ ] off, bro. You're not going to do
anything. Shut up. You're not going to
do [ __ ] nothing. Shut up, you [ __ ]
little [ __ ] Yeah. [ __ ] Iva little
[ __ ] fat virgin.
Yeah, there is no meet up. I'm not meeting anyone,
you know. Yeah, he's owning. Anyways,
like I said, if he Yeah. Yeah. Whatever, bro. Yeah.
This is what I mean with you little
weirdos. You see you little weasels.
Jealousy is a horrible drug, bro.
Jealousy is a horrible drug.
It's got to be worse than crack. It's
got to be worse than crack. It's got to
be worse than than heroin, bro. It's got
to be. It's got to be a proper proper
drug in it with you people in it. Yeah.
It's got to be, bro. Yeah.
It's got to be heroin, bro. It's got to
be more addicting than heroin.
Yeah. No, serious serious serious serious, bro.
Yeah, that's good for him, bro. That's
good. If he wants to see me, I don't
want to see him and I don't want to see
you either. Yeah. How about that one? I
don't want to see you and I don't want
to see him. How about that one?
I don't want to see any of you people in
this community. Really?
Which is why we're getting away from you.
Yeah. Which is why we're getting away
from you. Yeah. Literally.
Yeah. Yeah. Back in Iden. Like I said,
Joe, you can't even talk on a panel. You
little [ __ ] stirer. You can't even meet
someone in Nottingham. You little [ __ ]
stirer. [ __ ] off, you little lathery mong.
[ __ ] off, you little [ __ ] off, you
little lavry Mong. You little L [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. See, look. You're always
you're always on it, LT. Why do you
pretend that you've left? You You
haven't left anywhere.
You haven't left anywhere. You You
always You're always on. I've never
known someone to leave YouTube to be so
on YouTube the way you are. You You're
not off YouTube, bro. You might as well
just change your name back to London
Taylor. Bro, you're back on here. You're
obviously always watching. And I know
you're always watching as well, bro.
Every time I'm talking, every time I'm
talking, I can I I just have this vibe
that you're watching. I know it as well.
I know that as a I know that a fact.
You're always watching. You're always
watching. You know, you complain about
this sector. Yeah. You complain about
this toxic sector, but you're the one on
it. You're the one watching it. You
know, I'm a lion. You're the one on it.
You're the one watching it. You're the
one that seems to know everything. Like,
who the [ __ ] do you know that's watching
Rick Space's channel?
Come on, bro. Make it make sense. You
said that you made a channel. Yeah. You
said that you made a channel. I've got
no life. Okay, bro. Yeah. Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait. I've got no life.
Okay, bro. Come on, bro. Yeah. I've got
no life. I was out all day yesterday. I
was out today, but I've got no life.
Okay, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I've got no life. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro.
But who the [ __ ] are you? Who the [ __ ]
do you know that's watching Rick Mace?
See me when I'm on when we're all on
this new channel, I don't want anyone
telling me anything anyone said about me
because you know if they do, they're not
going to get a response.
If they do, I'm not going to I'm not
going to I'm not going to have a I'm not
going to I'm not going to give them a response.
So, you're doing the opposite. So,
you're kind of just contradicting
yourself. But, okay.
But yeah, you're just contradicting yourself.
Bro, I went on Rick's channel the other
day the first time in years. I ain't
watched that dude in years.
Yeah, I ain't watched that I ain't
Yeah, man. Until the other day, bro. I can't lie. Yep. Yeah, bro.
Nope. Wasn't running my mouth about you
at all. I just told I just told him that
I had beef with you in the past and I
said, "Does he still talk to you?" So,
no. No one was running their mouth.
If anyone told me that [ __ ] bro, I'd be
going mad. I'd be like, "Why are you
telling me?" There's the next person
that tells me when I'm off here about
something that someone said, I'm going
to block them. For example, Nonlegs has
said this for for example Red Star has
said this. I'll block him, bro. Anyone
that tells me about any of these people,
they'd get blocked. Simple as that.
And I have blocked people because of it.
You know what I'm saying? I have blocked
people. So, what you're saying doesn't
really make any sense at all. But each
to their own, whatever. Don't care. Yeah.
Yeah, it's the truth.
It is the absolute truth.
It is the truth, bro. Yeah.
Let me see how many subscribers. Still
got two subscribers, so they still ain't found it. Yeah.
You people need to get a hobbies or
something. Seriously, bro. You seriously
seriously do need to get a hobby now.
It's that bad. Now I've unsubed from
Timmy. That's how bad it is. Cuz I know
what this little fat little virgin
I know what this fat virgin is going to
do when he's done his balls in again. I
know exactly what he's going to do. And
he always does it. He always does it.
Tries to put me in a bad mood. Yeah.
When he's lost all his [ __ ] money. It
happens all the time. Yeah.
Uh because we're having the good people
from this community go on that channel.
So we will just carry on as normal, but
the toxic people can't find us.
Yeah. Simple as that. Yeah. [ __ ] man.
Yeah. So, we'll get the good people from
here that won't dox the channel. We'll
just carry on as normal
and then more people will join. We won't
have people stalking. We won't go on any
people that are trying to [ __ ] stir like
Timmy. And then we'll just carry on as normal.
It makes perfect sense. It makes perfect
So, we're just we're just carrying on as normal. Yeah.
Yeah. That's fine. That's fine. Yeah,
that's fine, man. I'm not asked. I'm not
And I'm going to give anyone advice to
people like that ever come across this community.
I'm going to tell anyone as well like
about this community as well. Anyone
that comes across it
so they don't [ __ ] You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to give them some
advice as well, bro.
Yeah. Anyone that's younger and better
looking than these people, stay away
because you're going to have the
problems that I've had.
People get jealous. People start [ __ ]
They do jealous [ __ ] They try to draw
you out. And that I'm This is another
thing I'm going to be mentioning as well
cuz it's important. You know, if anyone
comes on this community, they any anyone
that's like or even someone that's
simply got a life, someone that's got
more of a life than these people.
They're not fat and ugly like these people.
There's so many different things, bro.
Like, it's so many different things
cuz these people on here, they're
they're [ __ ] society's rejects.
Got nothing going for themselves. They
don't even have a life, bro. A life.
Imagine that. Not even a life on here. Yeah.
And that's it, bro. That's that, lad. Yeah.
Yeah. You booked a cinema room waiting
for the upload, but the upload might
never you might never get the upload. Greavesy. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. You'll be you'll be waiting
and there'll be no video posted.
So, you'll wait, but it ain't Yeah. Oh, man.
It's [ __ ] hilarious, bro. It really Yeah,
you know. So that's it.
Yeah, it is jealousy. That's what it is
with this community. It comes down to
jealousy with these people. Jealousy, gayness.
Um, already explain already explained
all the reasons why as well, bro. Like,
I don't even need to repeat myself
again. It's just facts. Utter facts.
It's just it's just obvious now, bro. At
this stage, it is obvious now.
You are. Most of you are jealous. Yeah,
not everyone on this community, but mo a
lot of you are. Yeah, a lot of you are
jealous. You a lot of you 100% are.
That's the only thing that could justify
why you do what you do. No, no, no, no.
A lot of you definitely are. A lot of
you definitely definitely definitely
are. 100% you are. 100%. And I've I've
already used the analogy as well. I've
used I've already explained it multiple
times. No, you definitely a lot of you
definitely definitely are. You
definitely definitely definitely are.
And I stand by that as well. Yeah. Yeah. 100%.
Yeah. It's as simple as that. Yeah.
You definitely definitely definitely
are. Joe, look at yourself. You go on
Law J's and you write 30 comments in a
row about me. A man that you don't even
know. Bro, make it make sense, bro.
Make it make sense.
Make it make sense. So what you're
saying is there's going to be like a
five on one.
So what is it going to be like a five on one?
So hold on a minute. So now it's So now
it's going to be a five on one.
No, no, no, no, no. You're you're a gay
bastard. You shouldn't even be thinking
about me. You're a gay bastard. So, what
you're saying now is it's going to be a
five on one. Yeah.
So, it's going to be a five on one now. Yeah. Huh? Retards.
Absolute little retards.
Yeah. So, it's going to be a five on one
now. Yeah. [ __ ] retards, man. Yeah.
Yeah. F. This is mad. You got Tibby.
Tibby can't fight Tibby can't fight his own battles.
This is all jealousy as well. This is
the madest thing about it, bro. I can't
wait yet until this is all over. And I
want to talk about the jealousy and
everything. It is jealousy. It is. And
you know it is as well. All of this is
jealousy. That's the weirdest thing
about it. You're better looking than
them. You got more money than them. It
is. It is. It 100% is, bro. I can't wait
for tomorrow to end and tell people the
jealousy. I've never known such jealousy
in my life, bro. In 28 years of my life,
I've never known so many closeted
homosexuals. I've never known so many
jealousy. Yeah, 100%. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Anyways, I'm banning you
now. Anyway, see you later, bro. You're
boring. Yeah, you're boring. And this is
exactly what I mean, Grezy. Do you
understand? This is exactly what I mean.
It will never end with these jealous
people. Do you understand, bro? You're
banned now. See you later.
Yeah, bro. Okay. Like I said, okay.
Okay. Like I said, people, you want to
live, pimp, bro. Bruh bruh bro, listen.
Listen to me. Yeah. You people are
[ __ ] fat and ugly on benefits. Yeah.
You are jealous. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Bro, bro, look. Look at you people.
Okay, let's talk about you people sat on
there 24/7, old men, no life. Yeah. You
are jealous of someone younger, better
looking than you live with their mom.
Yeah. Yeah. Like I said to you multiple
times, there's a reason why you don't
come on camera. Cuz you're ugly as [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying, bro? We go all
day. We'll do it all day, bro. But you
can just wait for You can just wait for
the video Thursday if you want.
You can just wait for the video Thursday
if you want.
You understand? Oven, did you email me,
lad? I can't even get a date. Like I
said, bro, come on camera and show us
what you look like. Show us your misses.
You're probably a [ __ ] virgin in your
40s, bro. Stop self projecting. And that
just goes to show if I'm 28 and I can't
get a date, then bro, you're definitely
a virgin, which is even crazier. If
someone younger than you and better
looking than you can't even get a date,
then bro, we know you're a virgin. And
that's even crazier then, isn't it? You
fat ugly bastard.
You fat ugly bastard. Yeah.
[ __ ] I'm younger than you. I'm better
looking than you. I've got more of a
[ __ ] life than you. You don't see me
sat there every day talking about people
like you people do. You can't come on
camera. Why can't you come on camera? Huh?
Yeah. You laugh, but bro, like I said,
you people's lives are worse. But you
people lives are worse
because you are fat, ugly people in no
life. So your lives are worse. So, but
if you like but end of the day, bro,
like listen listen to what I said to
you. Yeah. If your if you if your fake
laughing if your fake laughing makes you
feel better about if you leave any
everyone else alone, keep doing it, bro.
Keep false laughing at my life and
whatever. Like you people aren't the
fat, ugly old washed up men with
nothing. Then keep doing it, bro. Like,
you're leaving you're leaving someone
else alone. Like I said, if it's
speculation, prove me wrong. You can't
do it. If it's speculation,
if it's speculation, you'll prove me
wrong. One thing you can't do. It is not
speculating when you can't prove me
wrong. Okay, listen. Listen. I'm telling
you right now, most of you people are
middle-aged, fat, and ugly.
Is Is that Is that accurate or is it not? Huh?
Is that Is that accurate? And if it's
not accurate, prove it's not. Simple.
Prove it's not.
Anyways, bro, you're going to message me
so I can give you this channel, lad?
Speculating, but you can't prove otherwise.
otherwise. Come on now, bro. It's embarrassing.
Keep false laughing at my life, bro. If
it means you leaving someone else alone,
keep false laughing. That's good then
cuz then you won't bother no one else.
But we know that you people are [ __ ]
fat and ugly as [ __ ] and got no life sat
on YouTube all the [ __ ] day, bro.
Yeah. Is it Is it like you What am I
lying though? Am I lying? Tell me I'm
lying. Fire stick. Tell me I'm lying
about these people.
Tell them tell me I'm lying and prove
it. Prove me wrong. You can't do it.
Can I ask you then? Can I ask you why
you're sat on YouTube every day talking
about men? Talking about men that you don't know.
That's another weird thing you do.
Can I ask you if your lives are so
great? Go and live it, bro. All this
money, all this, but you can't, you
know, I'm right, bro. You can't even say
anything cuz you know I'm right, bro.
Yeah, I'm right about everything with
this community. I can tell you what's
happening, when it's happening.
Yeah. And that's it, lad.
Just jealous ass bastards. That's what
you are in this community. You sit there
and talk all day, every day about people
that you don't even know.
Yeah. It's the truth. It is the truth, bro.
Facts. You know I'm right as well, bro.
You know I'm right. Yeah.
Yeah. You do know me though. But you
don't know me though. Have you ever met
me? Have you ever met me? No, you
haven't. Have you ever met me? What
color boxer shorts am I wearing? How
much money do I have? How much money do
I get? What did I do today? What am I
doing tomorrow? You don't know me, bro.
You literally don't. You've never met me.
You've never met me, bro. You've never
ever met me. You sit online, old ass
[ __ ] wrinkly men talking about people
that you don't know.
Yeah. And that's what you do, bro.
talking about people that you don't know.
>> Yeah. What is it?
>> Unblock me, man. Why you Why you being like that?
>> I'm not unblocking you because you're
just trying to [ __ ] on my channel and
I'm not interested, bro.
>> I said a legitimate statement.
>> No, you didn't.
>> Yeah, I did.
>> What did I say?
>> You're talking [ __ ] bro. You're talking absolute [ __ ]
>> I never said nothing crazy.
>> I'm not, bro. I'm not interested. I'm
seriously not interested, lad.
>> Well, unblock me so you know when I'm
talking. Cuz what's going to happen is
someone's going to make a fake account
and they're going to pretend to be me.
So go on. >> Huh?
>> I'm saying you might as well just
unblock me so you know it's me when I'm talking.
>> No, but you just talk [ __ ] Why do I
want you on?
>> It's not because of that. Because you
ain't blocked nobody else. You're just
blocking me on purpose.
>> No, I blocked Timmy.
>> Oh, you blocked Timmy cuz you know he's coming tomorrow.
>> No, he ain't going anywhere, bro.
Anyways, see you later anyways. I see
what you're trying to do and it's not
going to work. So get kicked.
>> So obvious, bro. So so so obvious with
these people. You can predict it. I
swear to God, you can predict it, lad.
Yeah, you can predict everything that
these people do. Everything that these
people do, it's so predictable. See you
later, lad. Anyways,
and this is what I'm saying, bro. This
is this is this is a pattern with these
people. Do you understand? This is the
same thing I'm talking about, bro. It's
a pattern with these people. It's a
pattern, bro. Yeah. Do you remember I
told you about patterns repeating itself, lad?
Yeah, that's it, bro. Simple. They do
repeat themselves, bro.
Anyways, did you message me on email?
Did you message me on email?
I want to give you this channel, lad. Yep.
It's the same [ __ ] I told you exactly
what was going to happen, Fire Stick. I
told you exactly what's going to happen
and and it always happens, bro. The same
thing always happens with these people.
This is why I'm trying to get away from
him, bro. Not watching in the
background. None of that [ __ ] Away
from him, lad. Away. Way away from these people.
Believe it, bro. Believe it. Did you
send me it? Yeah.
You get me, lad. Yeah.
What was I right about? What do you
agree with, Fire Stick?
What do you agree with that these people
can't show their faces? It's the truth, isn't it?
Yeah, it's the truth, isn't it, lad?
Yeah, it is the truth, bro. They big
themselves up, but ain't no one on there
showing their faces, bro. Best believe
that. Best believe that, bro.
Yeah, it's the truth though, Dr. Eko.
It's the truth of you people. It is the truth.
It is the truth though. It's the truth.
You might not like hearing it, lad, but
it is the truth.
Definitely is the truth.
So weird what you people do on here,
man. So weird.
the truth, isn't it?
>> It's properly the truth, lad.
Yeah, it is.
Yeah. Yeah. Like [ __ ] bro. Yeah. Like
Oh, you definitely definitely are. No,
no, no. A lot of you people definitely
definitely are. For people to sit on
YouTube for four or five years having a
channel stalking a man you don't know
who you've never met for 5 years.
Absolutely. You are jealous of
something. Anyone that does that
absolutely 100% is jealous of something.
Oh, 100%. You could give me a million
pounds right now. I'm not jumping on on
on a site for four years stalking a man
that I don't love every day. You best
believe that ain't happening, bro. Best
believe that ain't happening. Send1
million pound to my account right now.
Just give me a million pounds and I'm
not doing it. So what's your what's
what's your excuse for them doing it
then? I wouldn't do it to a woman even
if I was obsessed in love. [ __ ] her. I
ain't doing that for years. Ain't
stalking someone every day for years. I
ain't doing it, lad. Yeah. I'm
definitely definitely not stalking a man
every single day.
Bro, there's not even any excuse for it,
lad. You give me1 million pounds right
now and I'm not doing it even for 3
years. Does that not tell you something,
bro? Does that really not tell you something?
You sit online recording men every day
and you don't think there's a problem with that? Okay, bro.
Yeah. You don't think there's a problem with that?
You definitely definitely are jealous. I
mean, okay, look, look at this, Dr. Eko.
Okay, since you say that I'm
speculating, right? You say that I'm
speculating. Okay, bro. Yeah.
[ __ ] Timmy, ugly as [ __ ] You'd kill
yourself if you look like him. Your
boyfriend, Lord J, ugly as [ __ ] You'd
kill yourself if you look like him.
Money Mike, ugly as [ __ ] You'd kill
yourself if you look like him. Do you
not see the pattern with these people?
Jamie Thompson. Oh, you definitely kill
yourself if you look like him. Do you understand?
I don't even know who the [ __ ] that is.
But do do you not see the pattern? Yeah.
Do you not see a pattern? Do you not see
the chains connecting here, lad? Huh? Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Whatever, bro.
I'm not talking about this anymore. Anyways,
okay. Greasy. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. But how
much time does that take?
Okay. Okay. Greasy. But how much time
does that take? I don't get it. No. It's
weird. I don't understand how a man can
sit on YouTube for four years stalking
someone they don't know. I don't get it.
I don't always think I'm right, bro. I
don't get it. No. No. No. No. No. I
don't understand it. You're right. I
don't get it. I don't get it. I'm not
going to pretend I do. To me, that's
very gay. To me, that's very weird.
No. I don't get it. I simply do not get
it. No, it's weird to me. It's gay to
It's weird to me. It's gay to me. And it
suggests that the people that are doing
it ain't got a life. So, it's as simple as that. So, yeah.
One second, bro. M mia.