Yeah. You know what I'm saying, bro?
Listen. Yeah. I went out drunk to try to
diffuse the situation. I thought, "Fuck
it." In it. Soon as he saw I saw him on
the door, bro. I went on that cab. I
went straight into that cab. £20 it cost
me that cab. Am I lying? Am I [ __ ]
lying, bro? Am I lying? No. No. He
started it, Mom. He He Okay, cool. Fine.
I'll meet him away from the house. I'll
meet him away from the house. Simple.
I'll meet him away from the house then.
Simple, bro. [ __ ] that. He ain't going
to burn him. [ __ ] that, bro. I need If I
need to go back to gone through said I
I'll do it. Yeah. I refused it by
leaving. Do you understand? By leaving
and not going on YouTube. Did I not
diffuse it? Did I not You didn't invite
him here. No, I did not invite him here, man.
Yeah. It doesn't matter. Come back now.
I'm here. Look. Simple. You got to say something.
You get me? I can't
understand. Anyways, it doesn't matter.
Defend him to show me where he is. Tell
him to show me where he is, bro. Yeah.
Defend him to show me where he is. He's
not going to be back in Birmingham, is he?
I was in a cab. I was in the house.
>> I was I was Is that where he live? Yeah.
I was in a cab. I was in a cab. Yeah. I
was in the back and I saw a black
outside. I open the door, bro. See
what's in there. You know what I'm saying?
I thought, "Oh, you got black cab. I got
black." No one was in the cab row.
>> He's a [ __ ] Yeah, but that's what I'm
saying. There was one cab up the road. Yeah.
Simple, bro. Give me a little bit. I'm
going to charge my phone a we bit.
Anyways, yeah. Just tell him to stay in
Romford, bro. Tell him to stay in
Romford. Did he Did he also mention that
he's making videos mentioning my name?
Mentioning my name? My name?
>> Yeah. Do you understand? Yeah.
Yeah. It doesn't matter. He'd be showing
me last. How long was he here for? A
minute. 2 minutes.
I was in that cab, bro. I was in that
three or four minutes, bro. I was in
that cab. I told you tell him I'm
coming. Wait. Did I not tell that? Did I
not say that to you?
Bro, you should have called the police.
I was coming. I was on my way. You
understand? I was on my [ __ ] way, bro.
>> Yeah. Tell him, bro. Just tell him to
walk up the road away from the house.
Just tell him to walk out the road away
from the house. Yeah. Yeah. He is a
[ __ ] stupid little n mate. He is a
little n. Yeah. This is what I'm saying
with the jealous people in this
community. Do you understand it now? Do
you Yeah. Okay. It doesn't matter.
Anyways, just just let me know where you
are. Just let me put the link up. Let me
know where you are, bro. Anyways, this
is an example, bro. Yeah.
Nerves as well. Nerves, bro. [ __ ]
nerves as [ __ ] bro.
Yeah. And this is what I mean with these
jealous people. They don't stop. Do you
get it? Do you understand what I'm
saying? One second. Let toss my little
phone up a little bit. to us.
Did he also tell you that he keeps
putting my name up? I'm defensing a
nons. Defending a nons. I would have
said that to him, bro. [ __ ] hide
behind that back door, bro. Yeah.
>> I don't need it. He's starting. He's He
is starting. He's starting. He's the one
starting. He is.
>> I know. And this Dennis [ __ ] won't stop
keeping my name out of his mouth. I've
just told him. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Whatever. Listen. So, it's all me then.
It's all me then. It's not jealous
London Taylor. Jealous London Taylor.
Jealous Kimmy. It's not them then. No,
it's not these jelly f jealous fools
that always watch me. No,
>> I don't.
>> I don't go to their houses. No, I don't
go to their houses anyways. [ __ ] all
that [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
Where is he anyways, bro? Where is he?
Where is he? In the moon and stars. Is
he really, bro? Yeah.
This London Taylor is going to get
involved. They don't stop these jealous
people, bro. I'm telling you, I will go
to Runford. I will keep it away from the
house. I don't give a [ __ ] But I'm
telling you, you can't win. You will
never stop with these jealous people.
They're so jealous. It's unbelievable,
bro. Yeah. Simple. Why was you here for
4 minutes? I wasn't even in the house.
I wasn't even in the house, bro.
Yeah. All he does is repeat himself. All
he does is repeat himself. That's all he
does. One second. My phone's on 28% and
I'm charging it up, bro. You know what
I'm saying, lad? Yeah. You should you
shouldn't even open the door anyway. As
I told you, don't even open [ __ ] him.
Cuz you want if he wants to embarrass
himself outside the house that I'm not
in, let him embarrass himself. Let him
embarrass himself. You've already got
the neighbor trying to [ __ ] do it,
man. You get me, bro.
Yeah. One second. Just let him stay
there, bro. My phone's on 28%. I'm
going, bro. [ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that
[ __ ] No, no, no, no. [ __ ] that, bro. As
soon as I saw you on the door, I I was
straight in that taxi. I swear to God, I
was straight in that taxi straight away.
I I was going to, bro. I I went up the
road. I opened the taxi door. I [ __ ]
did. This is what I mean with these
jealous people. This is why How many
times have I tried to get away from
them, though? How many times have I
tried to get away from these jealous ass
people? I Bro, I opened the cab door,
bro. No one was in there with a black
cab. Black and yellow. Yes, I [ __ ]
did. Yeah. Yeah. I didn't come outside
cuz I wasn't outside, you little [ __ ]
Cuz I wasn't in the house. Was I in the
house for the millionth time? Was I in the house?
>> Was I in the house?
>> You know what I'm trying to say, bro? Yeah.
One second, brother. Yeah. One sec.
Let me charge my phone up a wee bit. Let
me charge my phone up. Yeah. For like 20
minutes, bro. Yeah. One second. I'm
going to come back. Don't leave. Do not
leave cuz it's raining my [ __ ]
battery with me. Two seconds, bro. Don't
leave, bro. Do not leave, bro. I'm
coming back, bro.