Yeah. What is it now?
Yeah. Come on. Hurry up, man. I [ __ ]
finished the off, bro. Stop adding on
bloody time. They ain't scoring for
toffee, mate. Just hurry up and [ __ ]
end the match cuz they ain't scoring.
It's as simple as that. They're not
scoring, bro. So, just end the game, man. Nope.
Bro, you could you could add on another
you can add on another half an hour,
mate. They're not scoring, mate. You're
wasting your time, bro. Stop adding up
stop adding minutes on. If you if it's
not going to score, bro, it's pointless.
Let me see.
They had so much time, but they're not scoring.
I knew it, bro. It's Hey, bro. It's so
funny, bro. It's actually so funny, bro.
Like, you know, if you're waiting for
one more goal, they're never going to
score. They could have a million
minutes. You just know that they're
never ever ever ever going to score, bro.
You know, you know, if you're waiting on
one team to score, you just know they
ain't scoring. And even if they get
penalties, they're going to miss
penalties as well. What is even the
[ __ ] point of accepting bets, bro, if
you're just going to make the other team
not [ __ ] score? What the [ __ ] bro?
Didn't that team beat someone [ __ ]
last week 7? Yeah.
Yeah. It's [ __ ] pointless, bro. It's
absolutely [ __ ] pointless. Absolutely
Well, it was 20 pound, but I got a free
bet today cuz I won on the FB Ty. So, I
was playing a bit of pool. See, and
that's not even 20 pound of my own
money. That was money that I won. See,
that's what I'm saying, bro.
There's no way Enfield didn't score,
bro. No way. I don't I don't afford I
done a farfold both teams to score. All
I needed was Enfield to score. [ __ ] off,
bro. They saw a white man coming. Get
out of here, bro. There's no way they
didn't score a [ __ ] pissing [ __ ]
goal, bro. They beat someone [ __ ] 7-0
last week or the week before that. Yeah,
stop having a wank, mate. They they beat
someone eight Was it 7 or 8? Was it the
week before? The week before that? I
know they trashed some team because I
saw it when I was betting and now what?
They can't even They can't even score a
[ __ ] goal. [ __ ] off. Go and have a
wank, you silly [ __ ] And that was And
that was free money as well, by the way.
That was a free 20 pound bet. So, I
mean, if that doesn't if that doesn't
show you that there's no such thing as
gambling responsibly, then I don't know
what possibly will. Simple as that.
Nothing. No. No. I don't even know what
what was the point of them of them
playing. Seriously, don't know what was
the point. If they were going to make
the other team not score on purpose, I
wouldn't I wouldn't have done it cuz
there's no way they didn't score a goal.
No, there's no way they didn't score a
goal cuz they beat someone 78 nil the
last week. Yeah. So, there's no way they
did not score a [ __ ] goal.
But they didn't score one goal and they
had enough time to score a goal.
You know what I'm saying? There's no way
they did not score a [ __ ] goal, man. You know,
now I feel like strangling someone, like
actually just throttling someone out.
You don't You don't know my moods, bro.
Seriously, you don't know my moods. I
feel like getting someone and throttling
them, bro. You know how Homer what Homer
does to Bart Simpson. Just throttling
someone until they I swear to God I do.
It's [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
Yeah. It's [ __ ] And that was a free
And that was a free 20 pound as well as you know.
>> Yeah, it does. Cuz it's cuz there's no
reason why they because if you don't bet
on them, they score like a they score
like a madman. They score like a mad
[ __ ] They score and score and score,
mate. You can look up the scores. But as
soon as you as soon as the white man
puts the bet down, they lose. As soon as
the white man does it, they lose. It
happens every time, bro.
You know what I'm saying? It happens every time. £1,20.
Yeah, there you go, bro. Simple.
It's [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. There's no
There's no way they did not score one
goal. There's not one There's not a way
they did not score one goal, bro.
There's literally no way, bro. There's
actually like no way they didn't score
one goal, bro. There's no way. I had a
four-fold both teams to score. There's
no way, bro.
There is really literally quite
literally no way they did not score a
goal. But I wasn't excited anyways cuz I
knew it was going to happen. I knew this
was going to happen. Uh even though it
was 60th minute, you just know if you're
waiting if you're waiting for one goal,
you're not going to get it. If it's one
goal, you just know you're not going to
get it, bro. It's not happening. It
don't even excite me.
hot pumping. It doesn't work, bro.
Bro, I won I won I won30 today on the
property, so I done 20 worth of bets.
I mean, I didn't spend any of my own
money. Does that make more? Does that
make a difference? No.
Spend my money, bro. It was £20 that I won
earlier just so I could do these bets.
So, I mean I mean that tells you there's
no gambling responsibility, bro. That
tells you that there's no gambling
responsibly, bro. That even That tells
you even more, bro.
That tells you even more.
Oh, only £147, but it doesn't matter.
£147. £147 from 20. See, the returns are
even [ __ ] as well.
Always one team. It's always one team. Always.
And no, I won't be sending it tonight
because as I've stated multiple times, I
don't know if you people have a brain or
not in this community, lad. Um, if you
people have a brain on this community,
but I literally told you I gave up. I
don't know how many times I told you I
gave up with this [ __ ] So, I don't
know why you're asking me questions that
you already know the answers to. And
I've got a reason why. And there's an
excuse why I gamble today as well. If
you want to know, because in case you
want to say, "Oh, you said that you gave
up gambling." I can tell you the story
with that if you want. So yeah,
there was an actual like reason for that
as well. So yeah, I mean, so there's no
point asking me the same the same questions, bro.
That's put me off my food and
everything, bro. And that weren't even
20 of my own money. [ __ ] hell. See,
it doesn't matter the amount of money.
It just goes to show, bro. You know,
whenever I act like this, yeah, people
need to record this. They need to record
this and send this to secular slots or
send it to like the gambling commission
and all of that like to say like there's
no gambling response to me. People need
to record this [ __ ] bro, and start
sending it, you know, because it's the
truth, lad. It's [ __ ] There's no
way they didn't score. There's no way
Enfield didn't score, bro. There's no
way they didn't score. These [ __ ]
beat someone 7 the other day. [ __ ]
stupid little wankers. That's what they
are, bro. Stupid little [ __ ] wankers.
What happened was there was no change
for the pool table. So, uh, well, no,
sorry, the card machine weren't working.
So, I withdrew 10 pound, put the £5 on
roulette, got it to 32, done 20 worth of bets.
That's the story basically. So, cuz I
was only doing a couple of games of 1 pound50 each.
So, yeah, that's the story of the g
that's the gambling story really. So yeah,
but I wasn't excited anyways cuz I knew
they weren't going to score. It's always
the same old. I knew they weren't going to score
pretty much. Yeah. Well, I done the bet
earlier, but then I I played in roulette
with£5 because I was going to play with5
and change the £5 into coins because
it's annoying. Because losing's annoying
because losing's annoying. It It's as
simple as that. I weren't even going to
come on YouTube today, lad. Yeah, you
are the mon. See you later, lad.
You can have a timeout if that's the
real you. So, yeah, I weren't even going
to come on YouTube today.
Yeah, I weren't even going to come on
YouTube today. But yeah, that's [ __ ] it.
Yeah. All negative, is it? Doesn't
matter how much the money is. Doesn't
matter how much money you got as well.
It's bad, is it, bro? It's really,
really bad, isn't it?
Really bad, bro.
It's really bad, isn't it?
I don't think it's a bit of fun. I don't
think it's a bit of fun at all.
I don't find any of it fun. And I don't
find any of it funny either.
I don't need £140. I've got money. It's
not the point. It's not the point at all.
Already explained it, lad. I'm not
explaining it again. I'm not explaining
this. So, I'm not going over all of this
again, bro. So, if you didn't listen the
first time, that's your that's on you,
lad. When I say things now. Yeah. And
And you don't listen the first time.
That's just your problem.
No, I don't want to see I don't want to
go on your channel, lad.
You're another obsessed nonslegs. You're
another red star. Why do I want to go on your channel?
Why am I going to go on your channel?
[ __ ] off, man. I'm not even subscribed
to Timmy anymore.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro. But like I
said, I've already I've already
explained this, so I'm not explaining it
again. If you was too ignorant to listen
the first time, that's your problem.
Simple as that. Yeah.
Cuz I don't want to go on your channel,
lad. I don't want to. Cuz I simply just
don't want to go on your channel.
I actually done three bets today.
I done two to end nil nil. That got
[ __ ] which was going to happen.
They're on a free both teams to score
teams to win. Then I done
Oh, well I actually spent um
£24 on bets cuz I had some more change
from the Fiverr
cuz I decided to not play any more games
of Paul. So yeah, [ __ ] basically. Absolutely [ __ ]
And it doesn't matter if you don't need
if you don't need £140. I don't need
£140 but £140 £140 isn't it to anyone
I was happy today just winning 20
I know I noticed this as well you know
yeah you could have loads and loads and
loads of money right this is what's so
weird about this [ __ ] you could have
loads and loads of money right and you
wouldn't care you wouldn't feel happy no
but you could win 20% of that money and
you'd be on a high it's mad I I know. I
know it's [ __ ] up. I was actually
thinking about this earlier. You know, I
was actually thinking about this. You
could have money like coming in, you
could still be depressed. You could have
loads of money. You'd still be
depressed. But, however, if you win the
money, it could even be two 300 pound.
It doesn't even need to be any amount of
money. You get this dopamine high, bro.
And if you lose, then you get the dopamine low.
So, yeah, that's that. I noticed that,
you know. I know. I did notice that. I Yeah.
I don't know what what it is, but yeah.
And obviously I lost this bet. So yeah,
don't know why the [ __ ] didn't score. Yeah.
I don't know why but they never
just another slap in the face
as a lot of things in these country a
lot of things in this country it's just
a slap on the face slap in the face
and the reason I'm not going out
drinking is not even just because the
women because of the whole like vibe in
this country I don't like it which is
why I'm leaving so
yeah it's just I just don't like the
country. It's as simp as as simple as
that. The people in it, the management,
the pools that don't make no sense. Like
I' I I'd rather save myself the toxicity.
I'd rather save myself from the negativity,
if that makes sense.
Yeah. I'd rather save myself from all of that.
And just have a bit of peace. Simple as that. Yeah.
[ __ ] getting banned from a premises
for [ __ ] for [ __ ] talking to
people. What the [ __ ] is this, bro? Like
Yeah, [ __ ] all that, bro. I'd rather
save myself this piece. I don't want to
get any more annoyed. Yeah,
the truth of that.
>> Yeah, bro. So, that's that is in it. I
already drunk twice last week as well.
Yeah, I drunk last I drunk last week
twice last week.
No, it was only 20 pound that I won. Yeah,
All a fy basically. Yeah.
Yeah. Everything is just like a slap in
the face in this country, bro. It's just
all negative gambling, women, uh, stupid
rules they make up cuz they got their
own agenda. It's just such a big fat
dirty negative in this country. I don't
know if I'm the only one that that um
that has realized this
or like being led on and just stupid
people and weather and stuff.
Everything's just a negative in this
country unlike other countries. You know
what I mean? Yeah,
but I knew they weren't going to score
anyway, so I weren't even excited. It's
obvious. It happens all the time when
one team let you down all the time, lad.
It is bad
being banned from somewhere cuz you
approach when it's a free country, the
country you was born in, being led on
the weather. Um,
just all sorts of stupid stuff that
makes no sense in this country. It's
just stupidness. That's why I don't
bother going drinking in it.
That's why I don't bother going drinking
in the [ __ ]
There was a reason last time. It's so stupid.
You got a [ __ ]
You got some puff. Imagine that. Imagine
that. Yeah. It's actually quite
embarrassing as well. Um Cory, now I'm
talking to this black dude. Yeah. Who
who I noticed from before. So you're
talking to this black bartender, bro.
Yeah. And then you got some [ __ ]
[ __ ] cuz that's what he was. He was a
[ __ ] He's gay. Trying to trying to
tell me who who I can and can't talk to.
and then and tries to b Oh, [ __ ] off you
gay [ __ ] Go suck some dick, bro.
You're a puss. [ __ ] off. You're gay.
You're homo. You get bullied for being
gay. Like a a a gay person, a a [ __ ]
gay person is is trying to tell me where
I can and can't be. Oh, [ __ ] that, bro.
It's a piss, is it?
Bro, listen, Joe. Listen. Same as what
you've done. You have never done nothing
to anybody and you can't even talk on a
panel. Same thing as you. Same thing as
Timmy. Nothing. Because you will never
do anything. I done more to him than
you've done to me.
Joe, listen. Listen, listen, listen.
You're scared of talking on a panel.
Stop acting a bad man. It don't suit
you. Yeah. You have never done anything
to anybody. Never done nothing to me
when I've been up north multiple times.
You've never done nothing. You've never
tried meeting me. same as you. Nothing,
which is your favorite word. You've let
me come up north multiple times and
you've done nothing. Which is probably
why you use the word nothing so many
times cuz it's your middle name. Joseph
nothing. [ __ ] Ferrar. Because you have
never done nothing to me and you never
will. No matter how many times I've left
London. So that's that, bro. Yeah. What
have I told him? I told him that. Well,
I told him Well, I told him that it
doesn't make any sense and I don't
understand it. It's a stupid rule.
something that you can't do because you
can't I've already gone over the Timmy
thing. Listen, lad. If you keep bringing
it up, that's on you.
If you keep bringing it up, that's on
you. I've explained it again and again.
If your brain don't work properly, then
that's on that's not on me, bro. That's
on you, is it?
You know, that's I'm not going to
explain the same thing over and over
again. So, you can keep bringing it up
and up and up and up and up and up, but
I'm not going to keep explaining it
again. It's as simple as that.
You know, bro, listen and you can't even
talk on a panel, you coward. You didn't
even sort me out, Giza, when I went up
north multiple times. Simple as that,
lad. You know what I mean? Like, that's
it, bro. Yeah, he stayed outside for 30
seconds. He got bullied by the neighbor
and ran into a field. Congratulations,
bro. And I weren't even at home as well.
Yeah, that's the funny thing. Remember,
Cory, I wasn't even at home. Yeah, I'd
already proved that. So, yeah. But
anyways, we're not going over that
anymore. Anyways, bro, cuz this is what
happens on this community. People like
to um like to bring up the same stuff
over and over and over and over again.
So, we're not going to fall into these
people's trap. So, that's that, lad.
But yeah, as as I was saying, Cory, it's
quite embarrassing. Um, as as I was on
my to my original story, bro. So, you're
talking to a bartender, the guy's
talking to you who you known before, and
then you got some [ __ ] gay guy trying
to tell you you're [ __ ] banned.
That's embarrassing, bro. I swear to
God, bro. I got I got put off drinking,
bro. I swear to God.
Yeah, of course, bro. But like, that's
what I'm saying, bro. Like, it's not
even a joke, bro. Like, it's literally
not even a joke. Like, it's not one
thing. It's multiple things in this
country. The vibe's dead, bro. Like, if
I was in another country, maybe I'd go
out drinking every week, mate. Probably,
bro. But yeah, it's just dead. So, yeah.
And I just don't need that negativity
and toxicity, bro. I mean, it's it's as
simple as that.
Anyways, moving on. Joseph [ __ ] for
all. We're moving on now. This Joe just
wants attention, so we just ignore him,
bro. But yeah, uh anyways, Cory, that's
why I don't like um really bother anymore, bro.
I'd rather just like have the peace, you
know what I mean? Um yeah,
it's [ __ ] though, is it Cory? uh Cory
lad cuz it's like they they try to do
all of this do all of that all of this
extra [ __ ] Okay, whatever. So you get
you get through all of that and then if
it's not that that [ __ ] you over, it's
the women that [ __ ] you over and if it's
if it if it if it isn't the women that
[ __ ] you over, it's the weather that
[ __ ] you over. It's always something
going to [ __ ] you over in this country.
You get me, lad?
So yeah, and that's that, bro. You know,
you you're always going to get [ __ ]
over, bro. and and made her feel like
[ __ ] which is why people just leave.
This is why people just leave, bro. So
that's that, bro. So yeah.
So I mean, you can go to pubs and stuff, but yeah,
you can go to pubs and whatever, but yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ] Oy, didn't you watch L's yesterday, bro? All right.
Um, oh, [ __ ] [ __ ] Did you see J? I was
watching his stream yesterday. Bro, this
guy is so anxious. I've never seen
someone so nervous in my life, bro. He
kept like looking around, bro. That
guy's got mad anxiety, bro. It's not
even a joke. He was looking up, down,
left, right. Bro, the guy is scared,
bro. Like, he tries to be like me going
out drinking, but he can never be like
me, bro. The guy goes out on these ones
and comes home at like 6:00 in the
[ __ ] 6:00 p.m. Bro, the guy will
never be like me, bro.
Yeah, he can slack me off all he wants,
bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm a I'm a ass, lad. He's proper nervous, bro.
Proper proper anxiety, bro. Like looking
up, down, left, bro. He's proper
nervous, bro. And here's the thing.
Yeah. He talks about people not having
friends. One second, Cory. Yeah. One
second, bro. Yeah. He said that. He He
said he talks about people that have
been friends. Where was his friend yesterday?
Where was his friend yesterday, lad?
Yeah. I don't care, Harry. I don't care, bro.
Yeah. See you later, lad. You get
kicked. Yeah, Harry. I don't care, lad.
I don't know where he is, bro.
I got Oh, uh, one team let me down for
fourfold. Steven Howard.
Yeah. See you later, lad.
You get kicked.
And you get kicked as well.
There's no point going over the same
stuff with these people because once you
explain it, they ask you to explain it
again cuz their brain don't work
properly. So, I'm not trying to get
brain damage today, bro.
I'm not explaining it again and again
and again. If you was um if you didn't
listen the first time, that's your
problem, bro. Enfield. It was Enfield.
And why was I banned? What? Cuz I'm not
going to let someone put their [ __ ]
hand on me and I stood up for myself. Or
was it that reason then as well? Cuz
that's all that happened. So yeah, it's
just negative, bro. It's just it's just
all negative, bro. In this country, and
it we're just going to leave it at that,
bro. Yeah, that's the end.
So yeah, we'll just just leave it like
that, bro. And I'm still pissed off what
happened the other day as well, bro. Cuz
that's a piss take, bro. That is, you
know, that is a [ __ ] that is a
liability, bro. It really really is.
That is a liability.
Yeah, it was Enfield, bro. I had a four
fold and all I need was them to score.
It was a free bet from 20.
That's always a free bet. I won 120
pound in the FBI.
So when it was out earlier and stuff. Yeah.
So and and no one deserves it, you know.
No one deserves it in this country, bro.
So you need to think about long term what's best.
You know, at the end of the day, I could
go out drinking today. I could have a
good oldfashioned piss up, bro. But the
thing is, it's like I'd rather not, bro.
I'd rather I'd rather not.
It's not good, bro. Seriously, you need
to think long term. That's what a lot of
people don't do. They they they live in
the moment. They live they you know, you
know what I'm saying, bro? Um but they
you need to think long term, bro. That's it.
like when it comes to drinking and stuff
and like dating and stuff, you need to
think long term. So yeah,
it was raining yesterday, wasn't it?
Yeah, I saw a law went out and then come
back at 6 p.m. What was the [ __ ]
point of that? See, this is what I mean,
bro. Like, you you can do what you want.
Yeah, but it's when you start trying to
talk about other people. This is what
makes me laugh about the people on this
community. You can do what you want.
Drink your 99p cans of beers. Go out by
yourself. Do this. Do all of that, bro.
Do what you want. But then don't start
talking about other people when every
time you put up content is clear as day.
It's self-p projection.
This guy is so nervous, bro. I've never
seen someone so nervous in my life.
I swear to God. I've never seen someone
so anxious in my life for someone to
talk about anxiety. Bro, you're the
biggest sufferer of it. You must be the
biggest sufferer of anxiety.
Madness, bro. Matt is that is mad, bro.
But then he talks about other people not having friends.
L in the Weather Spoons yesterday. He's
a nervous. He's a He's nervous, bro. Proper nervous.
See you later, lad. You get kicked.
See you later.
This is how you avoid going around in
circles with these people. Um, car lad.
Yeah, cook it. I'm not even hungry. I've
been put off my food cuz that football bet.
Yeah, I was going to have steak for tea today, but
uh yes, he is nervous, mate. I was
watching him yesterday in the Weather
Spoons. Yes, he is. Uh yes, he is.
Yes, he is, mate. I was watching him in
the Weather Spoons yesterday and he was
[ __ ] nervous as [ __ ]
No, he was nervous as [ __ ] bro. You can
be nervous and still leave your house.
What are you talking about, you [ __ ]
You do realize that more than half the
population suffers with anxiety or has
done or or traits of it and they leave
the house. Are you a [ __ ] or
something? Just because you can leave
just cuz you leave the house doesn't
mean you're not nervous. Um,
bro, the guy is a is a [ __ ] house. And
the fact that he doesn't approach anyone
when he's out and stuff, he's a he's a
he's an outcast, bro. He's an outcast.
Yeah, that's what I was supposed to have
today. So loin, but I can't eat, bro.
I've lost my appetite.
Yeah, I'm good, bro. The kind that kind
of [ __ ] makes you just lose your appetite.
No, go and eat.
You might as well eat.
I'm not eating because I don't want to
eat. Me and my mom was going to have a
steak together, but I can't eat, bro. I
don't have the appetite.
Yeah, but LJ was literally nervous in
that Weather Spoons, mate. And the fact
that he doesn't approach anyone when
he's out and then results to sing again
online, it shows the guy's got anxiety, bro.
It shows he's got anxiety.
It shows he's got anxiety, bro.
Anyways, I don't really give a [ __ ]
anyways. I'm just saying what I saw. I
don't really care. I don't need to. I'm
not obsessed other people's lives, lad. You know.
Yeah. You're talking about yourself and
you call people m lad. You're just self
projecting. See you later. Yeah.
Why do people need to approach anytime
they're out? Um, maybe because the guy
was out drinking and
I mean, if you're out drinking, why not?
Cuz you're out drinking. You simp over
women on the internet. So, why not just
approach someone and not have to simp on
the internet? I mean, if you're out
drinking, most people do it.
I wouldn't go out drinking if I wasn't
going to do it.
But I don't really like drinking in this
country. So I mean, yeah, he's single.
He was out. Why not? Because he's got
anxiety. Because he doesn't have the
balls to do it. Do you not understand?
But then he'll come back on this
community and then start sing over these
ugly ass women. Does that make sense to you?
It'll be different if he was as if he
was like, well, not okay, let's just say
not asexual, but like not looking right.
But he begs women on on YouTube.
So, if you're begging women on YouTube,
and trust me, he does, and he's done it
to that Sarah as well, who I used to
talk to, to how hard can it be? Then, if
you're out drinking, would you just talk
to someone, you know? Um,
why wouldn't you someone in your actual
country? Cuz he's got anxiety. The guy's
a nervous wreck. So yeah,
you'll never be like me, lad. You'll
never be like me.
That's why we call this the copycat
community. You see, you'll never be like
me, mate. You virgin boy. You never be
like me, lad.
I ain't got I ain't got a clue. Yeah,
bro. Yeah, bro. I haven't got a clue.
No, no, no. I don't No, no, no, no. I
don't have a clue about anything, do I?
No. No. No. No one has a clue, do they?
But you people that have no life. You
You're very clued up. Pluto the dog,
aren't you? You know everything, don't
you? You people in this community. Yeah.
Know everything. No [ __ ] all. Probably.
Yeah. Don't have a clue. I heard that.
I've heard that been said about for
seven years now on this community.
Another repeating line by alcoholic
people telling other people they ain't
got a clue. Yeah. But Yeah. They ain't
Yeah. You haven't got a clue. Clearly,
Joe, you clearly don't have a clue, do
you? trying to say that you need to
speak to people for longer and that's
going to that's going to give people um
No, the steak's in the fridge. I don't
need to get the steak. The steak's
already in the fridge. It's already been
bought. I've just lost my appetite. Anyways,
um when you were trying to say, "Oh, you
need to speak to people for longer in in
um in in hopes that they'll meet you."
Huh? And look what happened the other
day. And look what's happened in the
past. [ __ ] off. Do one, mate. You're
trying to tell people they don't have a
[ __ ] clue about stuff. Well, you was
clearly wrong on that one, wasn't you?
You was clearly wrong on that one. So,
you clearly don't have a clue about a
lot of things. And that's already been proven.
No, I won't eat later, bro. I won't eat
later. I've been put off my food.
No, I won't eat later, bro.
I'm good, bro. I'm all right. Who's this?
Don't know the [ __ ] that is.
Oh, I do actually know. Yeah. Yeah.
Basically, that's that's that.
Nah, bro. I won't eat.
No, I'm not eating, man. I'm good, man.
Got some money on the side as well, but
nah, I'm not eating, lad.
See, it kills the whole vibe.
Below average looking, brother, you
people are not going to make me feel
like you, lad. You're wasting your time.
We went over this yesterday when I put
the link up and none of you people could
join the none of you people could join
the live stream. Like, bro, save yourself
your years of time. You're not going to
make me feel like you ugly, fat. It's
not going to work, bro. Like, you can
try and try and try and try again. But,
like I said, I stuck the link up
yesterday for people to join. They would
not join and show their faces. It's
projection. Very, very boring. And if it
wasn't for this football thing today, I
weren't even going to come on YouTube
because at the end of the day, bro, like you're
you're just self-reflecting your looks
onto other people just like you
self-reflect your weight onto other
people just like you self-reflect your
skinnness onto other people.
You just self-reflect.
It has no effect on me. I don't know
about anyone else, but maybe they're
affected by you, but I've seen what a
lot of you people on here look like.
So you're not going to make you're not
going to drag me down to your level.
Do you understand? So you're just
wasting your time.
So yeah, man. You people are well below
average looking. You're well overweight.
You're well spastics.
And then you're trying to talk about
people that are better looking than you.
It's ridiculous, bro.
I've gone here cuz Elena's gone to my sisters. Mom.
Oh, proves you're full of [ __ ] Are you
having your steak? Yeah. Okay.
No, I'm not hungry.
When I lose my appetite, I lose my
appetite. You understand? Like, it goes, bro.
Yeah. That's funny. At my sisters and
we're we're the people that don't have a
clue about things. Okay, bro.
You can't even Okay, bro. Yeah. Okay.
Um, medium. Well done.
Yeah. Well, I didn't hide from Timmy, so
I would never know, lad. I would never
ever know cuz no one hid from that
[ __ ] So yeah,
we're not going over this anyways. This
is how you this is how you lose brain cells.
Can you make me a tea, please? Yeah.
Self so much self-reflecting on this
community. It's unbelievable, bro. What
happened to people [ __ ] just putting
up content? You know what I mean?
So yeah, she didn't get abused by Timmy
at all. She stood her ground. He got
bullied by the neighbor. You [ __ ]
[ __ ] My mom didn't get abused. She
stood there and done. She stood there
and she wasn't intimidated at all and he
got bullied by the neighbor. The
neighbor called him a [ __ ] nons and
he got told to [ __ ] off, which he's
trying to deny, which was on live stream
and everyone heard it, but he's trying
to deny it. So that's funny, bro. But
the guy got bullied by the [ __ ]
neighbor and he's trying to say that he
didn't when everyone heard it. [ __ ] off,
bro. [ __ ] man.
Yeah, I did watch the video. Yeah. Yeah,
I did watch the video back. Yeah. And
she was stood there. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. She didn't close the door.
She stood there.
Anyways, we're not getting into this
again, bro. This is self projecting.
This is repeating. Anyways, Steven
Howard, did you do a football bet today?
It's pointless getting into it with
these people. Stephen Howard, you're
never ever going to win, lad. When you
realize you're never ever going to win,
whether you win, whether you lose,
they're just waste of space. Jealous ass
people. There's it's not there's no
point trying to get into it.
You know, if you read uh the comments
from LJ's the other days, you would have
known they already had their own little excuses.
They already had their own little
excuses. Steven Howard, they were trying
to say um they were trying to say how oh
um I went um I I went for Timmy but not
LT. See, they've got loads of excuses.
They're not even worth the brain power, lad.
They're not even um they're not even
worth the brain power, bro.
They're not worth like even getting into
into with them, bro. You know,
cuz it's jealousy deep down. And that's
what it is with these people. So, the
more you get into it with these people,
the more stupid you are really, isn't it? >> Yeah.
20 to win. Whereas, it's £147 I was
going to win. Yeah.
Yeah. I can't drink today. I drunk
[ __ ] Monday. I drunk Wednesday.
Yeah. I drunk Mon Monday and I drunk Wednesday.
Yeah. And that's exactly and and and you
would do and you would have said exactly
the same thing if I beat Timmy. If I
beat Timmy or I caught up with Timmy,
you would have said the same thing about
London Taylor. That's what I'm saying.
There's no point with you people. That's
exa that's the point I'm trying to make. That is
that's exactly what I'm trying to say.
You're always going to come out with excuses.
And do you know what made me laugh right
Steven about all of this is nonslegs was
was trying to call me a coward. I was I
I was saying this to my mom yesterday. I
was like what the [ __ ] bro? Like people,
there's one thing L J um LT and all of
these other people trying to say, "Oh,
you're this, you're that." And then they
have their opinion. But but someone like
him who ran away from me three times,
who let me put posters up about him all
over his area, had him stop leaving his
house for two weeks, had him stop coming
on YouTube for two weeks. But people
forget that cuz they got selective
memory and say that they owned you. But
you're you're calling me a coward or
bro, you know, Timmy, right? What Timmy
done is not even 1% as bad as someone
plastering up posters all over you about
you in your area, bro. Like, it it
really just isn't. It really just isn't, lad.
That That is the biggest coward ever. I
I don't know how someone like that can
ever have an opinion, but
they they write stuff. So, I mean, it's
the internet in it, bro. What can you
It's the internet.
Um, but that is that is mad how someone
like that can call you a coward.
That is he's the biggest coward ever.
That's the thing, bro. Like, I can't
think of a worse coward, bro. I
seriously seriously can't. You know,
don't forget I've met people. Don't
forget I've met Timmy. Don't forget I
went back for Timmy.
Him. He will make sure that he'll never
meet you and never has to face you.
Somebody could be beaten, right?
Somebody could be beating his dad to
death and he still wouldn't do anything.
Do you understand what I'm saying, bro?
Somebody could actually be beating his
dying dad to death and he still wouldn't
do anything. That's That's bad, bro.
That's really bad.
He is. I'm I'm telling you, bro.
Why do you think I went Why do you think
I went back? Why do you think I went
back for Timmy, bro? Because he [ __ ]
tried like [ __ ] um scare my mom. I
was like, "Oh, no. [ __ ] that." Why do
you think I went straight back, lad?
Why do you think I went straight back?
[ __ ] that, bro. Absolutely [ __ ] that,
bro. [ __ ] that completely, bro.
And I was going to start swinging as
well, but yeah. And then people told me
to go to the pub and then he wasn't at
the pub. So yeah, whatever, bro.
No, I shouldn't have been in. I will go
out whenever I want. I will go out
whenever I want. Simple as that. There
was no guarantee he was even going to
come on the door. Anyways, I'm losing
brain cells going over this again, bro.
We're moving on because we're just we're
just going around in circles.
Yeah, we absolutely just completely go
around in circles. So,
so we just go round and round in circles, bro.
And there's never going to be no end
until you terminate the conversation.
It's as simple as that. So, yeah.
And it's as simple as that.
How can you go out? Anyways, I've
already explained this, bro. You're
asking the same questions I've already explained. So,
yeah, we're we're having this you're
asking the same stuff, bro.
You're asking exactly the same question.
That's all you been asking, bro. So, yeah.
No, I can't understand that. No.
Anyways, I'm not talking about this
anymore, lad, cuz you clearly can't
comprehend things in your brain. So,
yeah, we're going over the same thing
again, bro. Yeah.
See, I could go. The thing the reason,
bro, the thing is, Greasy, I would have
went to I would have went to Birmingham
today. But do you know what's exactly
what's going to happen? I'm going to
waste time again. I'm going to waste
money again. It's going to go around in
circles again. And that's all that's
going to happen. That is literally all
that's going to happen. Nothing else is
You know, it will never ever it will
never ever stop. See, if if it's
stopped, bro, then I could understand. Yeah,
they will literally say, "Oh, well, why
do you meet Timmy and not London Taylor?
Then London Taylor will get involved."
Then then it just goes round and round
in circles. It just goes round and round
in circles. They told me to go to a pub.
I went to the pub. I stayed live when
Timmy was still in the area.
He was still around that area by the
time I was in the pub,
but I never heard from him. So
yeah. No, no, no, no. That would have
not ended the cycle. No, no, no, no.
That would have not ended the cycle.
Even if I was in and I beat him or or
whatever, that would not have ended the
cycle because then London Taylor would
have got involved and then eventually
Timmy would have started again. So no,
it wouldn't that would have not stopped
the cycle. It would never that wouldn't
have stopped the cycle at all. Think of
it. How many times has Timmy and Monty
met? They still had the same argument.
No way would have it stopped there, bro.
No, it wouldn't have stopped there. No
way would have it stopped there, bro.
No way would have it stopped there.
It wouldn't have stopped. It wouldn't
So, it wouldn't it would not have stopped.
It would not have stopped. He wasn't in
Molly. Yeah, but when I was live and I
was in the pub, he wasn't in Marley
Bone. But Yeah. Yeah. But when when I
was in the pub and when I was live, he
wasn't in Marley Bone. He was still
around the area because it takes over an
hour to get to Marley Bone from where I am.
So, he wasn't in Marley Bone and he
wasn't in Paddington. I don't know where
he was, but he wasn't there and he
wasn't on a train either. So, where was
he? Anyways, we're just having the same
argument. Hey, he's moving on now.
It's the same argument.
He wasn't He wasn't nowhere near any of them places.
So yeah, that's that, bro.
if you want to think I was in, think I
was in, bro. If you want to think I ran
away, okay, think I ran away, bro.
Whatever. It's up to you.
You You You want to think that, bro?
That's on you, lad.
You want to think that, lad? You think that?
It's as simple as that.
Yeah, just let people think what they
want, bro. I don't really care.
I don't really care. We're having the
same argument over and over again, bro.
It's very um boring. Um, yeah.
Oh, Joe, you're boring, lad. You're
boring. You're very, very, very, very boring, lad.
Very, very boring.
And Monty was no better either, to be
honest. Hey, listen. Monty can't even
talk about me, bro, because Monty, if
you actually watch that video properly,
Monty backed down. I didn't back down
when I if I saw him, bro, at the door, I
would have went swinging, bro. Trust me,
I would have went swinging. Trust me.
But he had gone.
Nah, it's just it's just boring trying
to argue with biased people. It's
boring. It's the same conversation with
biased people. It's the same thing when
I call when I call nonlegs a virgin. Oh,
don't say that. He's got a girlfriend.
But then when he calls me it, nothing
nothing gets said. It's boring. Arguing
with biased people is very boring.
Biased people is very boring. It's a bit
boring, isn't it, Steven Howard?
Oh, don't say that about him. He's got a
girlfriend. But then when someone
showing you them getting their dick
sucked on camera, you got no opinion on
that, bro. You're biased, which is why
people don't waste their time on you. Simple.
[ __ ] shut up. You're boring. Simple.
You know what I mean, bro?
So, but yeah, Monty actually did back
down. I actually watched that video
properly. He kind of actually did back
down. I mean, he showed up. No, fair
play. He did show up, but no, he kind of
did back down.
Um, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. There's
a big difference. And I'm not explaining
it again. I've already explained the
white knight thing again. I've already
explained that multiple times. cuz I'm
not explaining it again. Like I said,
bro, if you didn't listen the first
time, then um I mean that's that's
your problem. I'm not explaining the
same thing to disabled biased people. If
you don't understand it, bro, then you
don't understand it. Simple.
So, bro, like I've already explained
this before about white knights and
stuff. So, if you missed it the first
time, I'm not explaining it again. Simple.
Brother, I'm not explaining it again.
So, stop asking me questions. I've
already explained this multiple multiple times. Simple.
You're taking it out of context. I've
already explained the context. I've
already explained everything. And that's
it. I'm not explaining it again.
I've already explained the why not and
stuff multiple times. So, that's on you,
lad. I'm not explaining it again.
So, what makes me laugh, Stephen Howard,
is they're asking you to explain the
same thing over and over again, which
you've already explained.
I've explained the same thing literally
over and over and over again, and
they're asking you to explain it again.
They're just retards, bro.
So, if they didn't listen the first
time, that's their problem, you know? Right.
It is boring. Bro, I'm not going to come
on here today. It's just that football
bet thing pissed me off. So, I can live
without YouTube. I can come off YouTube.
These people can't. That's the big difference, bro.
That's the That's the big difference, you know? Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, bro. I couldn't imagine,
you know, I couldn't even imagine going
out drinking today. I think I've
actually been put off again, bro. I
actually feel like I'm allergic to it,
bro. I swear to God. Bro, I think I've
been put off again.
I've actually been put off, bro. I'm not
I'm not going to lie, lad.
I've already explained it.
Uh I've already explained it, lad. I
explained it the other day.
Yeah, Monty actually did kind of back
down to be fair.
If you watch properly, he kind of did.
He kind of did back down.
I'm not saying to Monty like fight
Timmy. I don't obviously don't. I'm not
I'm not I'm not [ __ ] sto nothing. But he
kind of actually did to be fair,
bro. Think what you want. I don't care.
Simple. I really don't care. You can
have your own opinion, bro.
You can speculate to accumulate. That's it. Yeah.
So that's it, bro. Yeah.
I really don't care, bro. To be honest
with you, I don't even know why I still
talking about this.
It's like, you know, when I first went live,
this account was like, "Oh, you going
out sending it today?" Well, no.
I only went out Monday, bro, cuz I
couldn't bear [ __ ]
I couldn't bear being sober, so I just
got drunk. And then I got drunk again
Wednesday. And then yeah,
I had to deal with a lot of stress, you
know, from [ __ ] and that. So,
but I'm a bit better now. I'm sleeping
better now as well. Kind of. I'm sure 100%.
Never sim to my life, lad. Henry. Never
s to my life. Never have, never will, man. Yeah,
but the point I'm trying to make is
Gregy that even if I went to Birmingham
today or I go to Birmingham tomorrow,
it's just going to go around in circles.
That's what I'm trying to say to you.
It It will go around in circles. It will
100% go around in circles.
And that's not even an excuse, bro.
That's not even a joke. It will go
around in circles. It will 100% will go
It will 100% go around in circles, bro.
Trust me, bro. I'm not even on bail. And
it's not even anything to do with that.
And I'm not even on bail.
The thing's probably dropped already,
but it's nothing to do with that. It's
And it's got no And they've got nothing
to do with each other either. It's not
even it's not even just that. It's
you're going to waste money and waste
time on people and it's just going to go
around in circles again.
Yeah. Just like you've done suddle when
I've been to Leeds and Sheffield. Isn't
it Joe? Just like when I've been to
Yorkshire and you've done subtle and
you've kept quiet like a good little
boy. Yeah. Just like you've kept quiet
isn't it multiple multiple times like
when I was live in Newcastle as well.
Just like you've been quiet.
Yeah. Yeah. A bit like you then, is it?
Bit like you.
Yeah. You know, to you knew to not have
issues with me. Of course, there was no
issues. You start your [ __ ] when people
are back in London. That's what you
people do. So yeah, there was no issues
when I was there because you make sure
you make sure you should you make sure
um that you have problems with people
when they're back in London. It's the
same as what people in Liverpool done.
No, I'm not interested, bro. I'm not
interested. Dr. Echo, not interested, lad. Yeah. You know.
Yeah. It will just It will always go
around in circles. It will always go
Yeah. Okay. Whatever. But I didn't show.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Whatever.
Yeah. Whatever. No one cares.
Nobody cares, lad. I've already
explained this multiple times.
I haven't uploaded anything on it to be
fair. Any what? Anything new? I haven't
uploaded anything new to be honest, lad. Oh,
headaches, bro. Headaches. I I suffer
from massive self-esteem issues. No,
that's you people. No, no, no, no, no.
Joseph, that's projecting now. Come on.
That's projecting. Most of you people on
here talk about people's looks, but you
won't show your faces. No. That's That's
self projection, Joe. You can't even
talk on a panel.
No, no, no, no. Joe, Joe, that's a lot
of you people on here now. Come on. That is self-projecting.
You people don't. A lot of you don't
even talk on the panel. For [ __ ] sake,
you won't show your faces. No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no. That's you, Joseph.
That's you and a lot of other people
now. You are self projecting now, lad.
You are actually self projecting, lad.
I just need to upload some new things to
it, Stephen. How would you be fair, bro?
Yeah. Yeah. Whatever, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Whatever, bro.
Yeah. It is always someone else's fault.
Yeah, it is. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It is
always somebody else's fault. I do think
that. Yeah. And what are you going to do
about it? Nothing.
Yeah. It's always someone else's fault.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It is. Yeah. I do
think that. What are you going to do
about it? Nothing. So, yeah. Yeah. It is
always someone else's fault. Yep. Yep.
Yep. And you're going to do nothing
about me thinking that. It's as simple
as that. Yeah. And that's that. Ain't it?
We're not getting into these pointless
debates. We're not getting into these
pointless arguments, bro. They go nowhere.
Yeah. They literally go nowhere.
Yeah, that's nice, bro. No one cares.
See you later, lad.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You can say whatever
you want, Joe, but you'll never say
anything to anyone's face. So, yeah, you
can say whatever you want on a keyboard.
A 10-year-old, it's like what LT said in
his video. Literally, a 10-year-old kid
could come on here and write the most
mad stuff and say the most madest stuff,
but I mean, at the end of the day,
they're still a 10-year-old kid. So, um, yeah.
You're just a keyboard warrior, lad.
That's all you are. You're just a sad keyboard warrior.
A sad sad sad sad sad sad sad little cable lawyer. Yeah,
bro. I don't know why you're still
talking about Timmy. We're not We've
moved on. You are the ones that keep
bringing it up. I've We've moved on from
this. I've already explained the story.
I've done what I had to do. I went where
I was told to go. You keep talking about
it, bro. You are the ones keep bringing
it up. Not me.
You must be obsessed.
You are the ones that You are the ones
that are [ __ ] obsessed, bro.
You the ones keep bringing it up, you know. One second.
Happened again today, Dusty. Happened again today. down £70.
Yeah, I done £23 on a football bet on
football bets today, bro.
But it was money that I won.
Yeah, I done a farfold both teams score.
All I needed was Enfield to score and
they [ __ ] me. Yeah.
No more drinking for me, lad.
You get banned for banned for approaching.
Jesus Christ, lad.
Everything's a slap in the face in this country, bro.
Everything's just a slap in the face in
this country, bro.
No, they didn't complain. I've already
explained the story anyways, lad. I'm
not explaining it again.
I've already explained it. I mean, I've
I got banned from somewhere calling a
calling a bartender. I said to I said
that the b in one place I said the
bartender is acting like a bit of a [ __ ]
Got banned for life.
So, I mean, yeah. No, they definitely
definitely do. It's a particular bar.
It's a particular brand of bar. Um,
it's a it's a brand. It's the same
brand. They're just multiple ones. And
they will literally ban you for
anything. If you go on the reviews
thinking, "Bro, it's a free [ __ ]
country, bro. What the fuck?" So, yeah.
So, no, they didn't. They definitely
definitely definitely didn't.
It's just a negative anyways, bro. That
people's attitude like [ __ ] all that,
bro. I'd rather just stay here, bro.
[ __ ] all that.
It's depressing, bro.
Don't know, bro. Not many.
Not many at all.
And no one complained as well because I
saw where everyone was cuz where I was
sat. And at the end of the day, if that
was the case, all they had to say was,
"Oh, can you just not do it anymore?"
Whatever. So, no. And then the bouncer
tried thinking he could put his hands on
me when he couldn't. And he knew that as
well. Tried snatching the drink out my
hand. I said, "I'll finish it when I'm
ready about you're going to snatch a
drink out of my hand. Are you mad?"
Uh, so just all negative, bro. It's not
good. It's not good stuff to talk about,
bro. You know what I mean?
And then the women will [ __ ] you over.
And if it's not the women that will [ __ ]
you over, it's the women that will [ __ ]
you over. So you all always going to get
[ __ ] He said he said, "Oh, like don't
don't give me He was like, "Oh, don't
give me attitude. I'm going to snatch a
drink out of your hand." I said, "You're
not going to be snatching no drink out
my drink out of my hand."
You don't know who you think you're
talking to, mate. Right. You're not the
[ __ ] government. And yeah, he tried
snatching the drink out of my [ __ ]
hand. I pulled it back and there was
like a little bit left of it and it went everywhere, bro.
And then I and then I just started like
slabbering slabbering about him being
racist and everything. It wasn't a black
guy. It was it was some Polish guy. So
yeah, that's just it's all negative,
bro. Like it's that's why I don't like
that's why I don't um really like like
going out and drinking and stuff, bro.
You know when you go if you see these
like Scandinavian countries. Yeah.
The Scandinavian countries, you don't
you don't see any stuff like that.
Like Finland and Sweden. You don't see
any of stuff like that, bro. You don't
see any stuff like that.
You don't see none of stuff like that,
bro. From what I've seen, you don't see
any of it. Um, but yeah,
you're allowed to talk to who you want.
It's a free country. You're serving
drink. You're making people pay your prices.
I mean, [ __ ] hell, bro. What a what
better place to do it, you know?
Yeah. He thought he could try to like
talk. I was like, "No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. You're not you're
not you're not snatching no drink out of
no one's eye, bro. So yeah,
and if people complain about you, you
don't just get kicked out. The bouncer
basically just says, "Oh, like can you
just They normally try to calm
situations unless there's like a big
fight." You get me?
That's what usually happens? Yeah.
Oh, you get banned like for a couple
months or something maybe. Depends what
it is. You know,
my friend got banned from the O'Neals
for 3 months. I got banned for 3 months.
But they literally banned me. All the
reason they banned me for 3 months,
Dusty. There was no reason, bro. You
know what happened is because Yeah. When
I went in with one guy, they were like
trying to drag him out. This is what I
mean. How they've got a vendetta. They
were trying to like drag him out and I
wasn't helping them
and then that's why they banned me for
three months. Well, they banned me.
Yeah, they basically banned me for 3
months because basically I didn't help
them even though I didn't even do
anything. Do you understand? Like
they've got their own little vendettas,
bro. Trust me. It's a it's a country
designed to [ __ ] you over, bro. And I'm
not even just saying that, bro. I swear
to God, bro. Like I know it might seem
like oh like it's it's a victim
mentality and whatever. I'm being ser
I'm being deadly serious but it is a
country designed to [ __ ] with you bro.
I'm telling you it is.
Trust me. I'm not even just I'm not even
like bro that's what I mean.
You know I swear down bro. Like they Yeah.
So I just don't really bother with it
anymore bro. Like um yeah,
then you meet someone, you get led the
[ __ ] on, you get made to feel like [ __ ]
It's not really a life, is it, bro? Is
it? It's not really a life, is it,
Griezy? Come on now, bro.
Or Dusty, sorry. I mean, it's not really
a life, is it, lad?
It's quite depressing to be honest. So yeah,
cuz he's an horrible old [ __ ] bro.
Surprised Waxies ain't banned me yet.
I know you like the drinking and stuff,
Stephen Howard, bro, but I can't be
dealing with it, bro. I ain't got the
stomach for it anymore, man.
I know you love the drinking and
whatever, bro. But I just ain't got the
stomach for it. Like, to be honest with you,
that Christian easy thing put me off as
well, bro. I'm not going to lie.
It actually put me off, bro. I'm not I'm
not even joking.
I know you like to see madnesses and
stuff, bro, but I'm sorry, bro. I just
can't be doing that
anymore, bro. Like,
yeah, I'm not going to lie. It put me off, bro.
All right. Do you remember what they
were saying about the high school
massacre? Um, Grezy,
it created a bunch of copycats.
That was class, isn't it, bro?
They created a bunch of copycats. Greasy.
Yeah, that put me off, bro. I'm not
going to lie. Yeah, I'm not going to lie
to you, bro. That actually proper put me
off. But Greavvesy is so like insensitive.
He doesn't care.
Rey doesn't care. He's got no like
feelings or anything, bro.
Seriously, he doesn't care.
He doesn't care when Peter Benny gets
hurt or anything. He just laughs. He's
so He's a narcissist, bro. He just
grieves. He is.
That's what he is, lad.
No, I ain't going anywhere, mate.
I'm not going anywhere. So, yeah,
cuz I don't want to, bro.
I just don't want to.
Oh, Dy, that's nice. I'm not interested.
That's nice, lad. He makes posts of me
all the time. No one's interested. He's
just an obsessed loser. No one cares. So, yeah.
Yeah. So, yeah, I got put off anyway,
Stephen Howard. It put me off, lad. Yeah.
[ __ ] these westernized [ __ ] bro. Leave
them where they are.
Just leave them where they are.
People are so lethal nowadays, bro.
They're so lethal. Yeah. See you. Don't know.
Probably get a camper van and go
drive all around Europe. Probably. Yeah.
Maybe try to start my own business. I'm
not sure if I could with 15 grand, but let's see.
of course I can drive.
Of course I can drive, lad.
I can drive, man. Of course I can. How
do you know? You don't know me.
I don't even like speaking to people
nowadays. Stephen Howard, bro.
Don't need a license to drive to to know
how to drive.
Don't need a license to know how to drive, lad.
Boogie boogie boogie.
Yeah, but I don't have a license, but I can drive. M
that football bet completely ruined the day.
Completely ruined the vibe.
What a buzzkill.
What a boring buzzkill.
Pretty much. Yeah,
that's what I would do. Yeah,
I know how to drive, lad. Yeah,
trust me. I know how to drive, lad.
Stop asking questions.
I can't get any takeaways either because
I need to be careful with my stomach.
Nope. Indigo. Nope. Nope. Nope. No, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
Bro, do you know what I ate yesterday?
I had a [ __ ] Savoy, battered sausage,
chips, and a real I don't know how I ate
it all, bro.
How I ate all I don't know.
I'm good, bro.
No indigo. No. Right.
No, I'm not hungry. Um here. Yeah.
It's just sad that we was born in this um
day and age, isn't it?
Sad, isn't it? It's just so sad to be
born in this era.
It's so mad. Like, we actually live just to die.
We live, we get bad experiences, then we
die. It's mad, isn't it? When you think
about life is it? Yeah. We live, we get
bad experiences and we die.
It makes you actually think what is
actually the point
to die basically. up.
Swear it up. Yeah.
You live, you get bad experiences and
then you die.
Everyone laughs at that. Everyone laughs
at that [ __ ] lad.
Really greasy. Do you think that?
pretty much cuz there's not there's no
excite there's no excitement to do
anything is there.
Can't be asked, lad. Can't be asked.
Yeah. 80s old lad.
And women are [ __ ] as well. Greasy.
They're [ __ ] as well. They're all the same.
So many different things as well. And it
all so many different things.
It's bad, bro.
Well, you're going to put your treadmill in CX.
You funny bastard.
Did you eat your steak? Yeah.
Oh yeah, bro.
It ruins the whole vibe this these
football bets and stuff in it.
I'm just the whole vibe.
Whole vibe you got going on.
I've been put off my appetite for like a
week, bro. But I kind of still wait to
be fair. I ate yesterday. But
you don't need to know that, bro. You
don't need to know that.
Doesn't matter how many jobs I've had.
Just a far forward. Both teams to score.
Never had delivery in my life.
Wrong one, lad. Wrong one.
Nope. I got let down by one team. One
team had to score and they never and it
was and it was Enfield.
Just another slap in the face, isn't it?
Just another slap in the face in this country, bro.
Just another slap in the face. Yep. Enfield.
It was a free bet as well. I won 20
earlier, so I just put on the bet. Another loss,
bro. I won the 20. It was a free bet,
bro. It was a free bet, bro. Um,
bro, it was a free bet, so you might
want to you might want to calm down.
It was a It was a free It was a free bet, bro.
one on the FBI.
Um, yeah, bro.
One error to be alive, bro. What a what
a what a day to what a society to be
alive in, bro.
It sucks, isn't it, Stephen Howard, bro?
It sucks, man.
It sucks, is it, bro? Yep. Obviously,
can anyone think of a worse thing than
to be led on?
I can't think of anything worse than
being led on. I think I'd rather get stabbed.
I'm not even joking, but I think I'd
rather get shot, you know?
Like, as long as it's not like directly
in my [ __ ] head on my face. I feel
like I'd actually rather get [ __ ] stabbed, bro.
No, I think I'd rather have cancer, bro,
because I might beat it. Who knows? I
might beat cancer, bro. If I got cancer,
I might beat it.
Cancer, you could beat, you know,
I can't think of a worse thing.
I can't think of a worse thing, bro.
It's pretty bad to be fair.
It's I don't know, Grezy. is pretty bad
to be fair. Being led on is pretty bad, bro.
It's got to be one of the It's got to be
up there with one of the worst things.
It's pretty bad, lad. or being Yeah, but nah, bro. No,
being led on is really bad, bro.
It's actually it's actually so under so um
like how do I say like people don't
actually understand how bad it actually is.
It's really bad, bro. Trust me, it's you know.
Yeah, I know. I know. I know. I read I know, lad.
I don't really give a [ __ ] bro, if I
got if I got cancelled and died, bro. No
regrets to be honest with you, bro.
I really wouldn't care to be honest with you, bro.
I wouldn't care if I got cancer and died.
happen. It happens to a lo It happens to
loads of people, bro.
I've already done so much stuff in my
life anyways, bro. I've had some cool
times, Grievy. So, I'd have like no
regrets, bro. I'm not even joking.
Yeah, no joke, lad. [ __ ] bollocks.
Absolute bollocks, bro.
Maybe if I was in a different country,
I'd feel better, bro. [ __ ] hell. Maybe.
I can't believe how much life I wasted,
bro. Like going out drinking and
approaching and stuff. I can't believe
like how much time I've wasted. Like not
even on here, bro. Cuz I was living my
life whilst being on here. But I just
can't believe how much time I've
actually wasted, bro. It's mad. Jeez.
It's quite sad really, bro. Think about it.
All right, there was a video earlier
that come up on YouTube, Greavvesy, and
it was like Elmo visits the farm. I was
dead. And it was like Elmo on like a
horse. Oh my god.
I'm not scared of flying, lad. I don't
need to try to get over any fear cuz I'm
I ain't got a fear of flying
and I don't really care about flying
either. So, and I'm not scared of
flying. But yeah, I was kind of tempted
to go to Birmingham when I saw that Greezy.
I was tempted to just buy a new phone
cuz I'm going to have to buy a phone and
go live there in it.
Yes, it was called Elmo Visits the Farm.
Elmo visits the farm, lad.
Oh, that's some funny [ __ ] bro.
You don't need to know that, lad.
That's just self-reflecting. You can
definitely tell that you come from L J's
channel, bro, when you're talking about flying.
I mean, bro, your your mate Lord Jay
can't even sit still in a [ __ ] Weather Spoons
without [ __ ] going left, right, left,
right, up, down [ __ ] because of anxiety. Lad,
your your your friend LJ that you
watching can't even can't even sit still
in a pub for [ __ ] sake.
in an actual pub on the ground. So, you
need to worry about him, bro, before
worrying about me.
How about that one?
[ __ ] anxious as [ __ ] bro. I've never
known someone so [ __ ] nervous in my life.
He flew to Vegas. Uh, good for him, bro.
Do do you want to medal?
Do do you want to medal, lad?
And guess what? I can be in a pub
without being anxious,
unlike him. That's embarrassing, bro.
That is really embarrassing.
Maybel stock come for eating greasy. Nah. Nah, bro.
I would never do that, matey. Please do.
I will knock him out. Do you remember that, Greavvesy?
Yeah. I reckon if Mike weren't there, I
think Monty would have got knocked out.
What do you think, Greavvesy?
Yeah, Monty did kind of back down to be fair, bro.
Actually, looking back on it, he kind of
did. I weren't going to back down. If he
was still if he was still outside that
door or even still, I would have just
went whacking, bro. I would have just
went flying punches. Trust me.
And he he would he would have went down.
Is that what you would have liked to
see, Greavvesy? Is that what what you
would have liked to see? But I don't
understand the point of all of this. I
mean, why can't we all just play nice?
Why can't everyone just play nice?
Why can't you all just play noise with it?
I will knock him out. Oh, you heard it
though, didn't it, Grezy? That's what he
was saying about Monty. Come here, lad.
I think Monty punched him or something, could it?
I will knock him out.
Why did you like that greasy with the
Discord thing? All of a sudden they were
all there. Was it? They kept off YouTube
and then all of a sudden they were all there. Grezy,
weren't they greasy? They were all
there, weren't they? I've got We're all
going to get nicked, bro. That's what he
said, is it, Mike? We're all going to get nicked.
Yeah, they would have, bro. Yeah, 100%.
And what's the fight over, Grezy? What?
What? So, if the police ask what's the
fight over, what's it all over, Grezy?
That's crazy. That's so embarrassing, isn't it?
That's so embarrassing though, isn't it?
That is embarrassing, bro.
You have to admit. Yeah.
Yeah. It's mad, isn't it, Indigo?
Yep. Mad, isn't it?
Maybe I'll get a curry. I don't know.
I had a take away yesterday.
Nah, bro. I'm not going to eat.
I'm not going to eat, bro. No.
No, I won't eat, bro. Well, at least I
can sleep now. Bit better. Like I was
saying earlier, at least I can sleep a bit better.
Nah, I don't don't need to, bro.
I have no I have nothing left to say on the matter.
Nons legs found the trend and he didn't
want to feel left out so he copied. So
you that's that's that's it is it. It's
a trend that created a bunch of copycats.
Is that right?
So that's all you need to Yeah. Nope.
Sounds about right, lad.
Nah, don't want to eat today, bro. I
don't want to eat at all.
Don't want to eat. Don't want to eat. No,
they put you off, bro.
It puts you off. like football bets and
stuff puts me off eating and [ __ ] bro.
It's depressing as [ __ ] Don't know
about anyone else.
I'm really bad with it me, bro. Trust
me. Really bad with it me.
Joe was like, "Oh, I put something on my
channel similar to yours. Do you want to
see it?" I said, "I don't want to go on
your gay channel, Joe. You're another
nonslegs. You're another red star. I
don't want to go in your [ __ ] gay channel.
You get me, lad. Yeah,
you couldn't win that football bet
today, could you?
Nah, be too easy, Grezy. Be too easy.
Don't know why people on here are so
ashamed to admit the fact that they've got uh
they've got anxiety, bro.
on this community.
Nothing to be ashamed of having anxiety.
People are so defensive about it, you know,
admit that they've got these things. You
know, you've you you admit your little
conditions, don't you, Greasy?
You admit your little conditions.
Bless you. You need to find a job that
will accept you, Grezy, with with your little conditions. Oh, bless.
That's really cute, actually. greasy.
We got someone that says they don't have
anxiety, but then they're [ __ ]
themselves in a pub. So, I mean, [ __ ]
make it make sense, man. You know, anxiety Yeah,
Timmy's got anxiety in it, Grezy.
He couldn't wait to get out of London,
bro. Look at He couldn't wait to get out
of London, bro.
He couldn't wait to get out of London. Nah.
does. Yeah. Doesn't mean he hasn't got anxiety, lad.
It doesn't mean anything, bro.
I remember when I done that with bomb.
You see back before I knew this [ __ ]
would go around in circles. I used to do
that with bomb and [ __ ] Yeah,
I just got this thing still thinking about ordering.
He was He was beyond drunk.
He was beyond drunk, bro. Like [ __ ] mad.
Beyond drunk. Like mad. Like, do you
remember Hey, do you remember Stephen?
The first time I met Timmy. Yeah. I
called Timmy out. I went all the way to
Birmingham. I called Timmy out.
See, I used to be a mad [ __ ] But then
when you realize with these people,
Yeah. it just goes around in circles.
Yeah. This is the smart thing. Do you
understand? This is the smart thing.
What I do is the smart thing. Steven Howard.
It's the smart thing.
Look, I've got I've I I got friends that
live in Birmingham, bro, who I could
stay with, you know, for a couple of
days. I've got friends that live in
Birmingham, bro. I know a couple of
people that move there. Do you know what
I'm saying, bro? I actually do, you
know. But the thing is, bro, like, it
just goes round and round in circles.
Trust me, it does, lad. Trust me, it does.
No matter what you do,
if there was someone that generally
wanted to meet me, bro, up there. Yeah.
And like I knew I was going to get
something or I was going to get paid for
doing it, then then I would do it, bro. Obviously, 100%.
Well, if there was like a woman up there
and that that was different and stuff, I
could stay there. I would maybe go up there, bro.
Yeah. I'm not doing that. [ __ ] that.
That's long, bro.
Not as long.
Does anyone have Timmy's address though?
Does anyone have his address?
I used to have his old address, but I
think he moved.
That's B on a woman's account, bro. Yeah.
I don't actually know where this guy
lives. Like the address.
Would you like to see me go on the door
with a Spider-Man t-shirt? We
want to see me go on the door in a Spider-Man t-shirt. Bless you.
Nothing wrong with having anxiety, Dr.
Echo. There's nothing wrong with having anxiety.
Don't know why LJ just don't admit he has it.
Like some other people that used to come
on here, they said, "Oh, they don't have it.
I did the other day. Yeah. For the past
5 days. Yeah. Nothing nothing wrong with admitting it.
Yeah. There's mad stuff that can trigger me. Yeah.
So there's nothing wrong with that, bro.
But generally, no.
Yeah, there's nothing wrong with that,
bro. It's Yeah, I had problems sleeping
and stuff. Not now. Well, still a little
bit now, but it's not 100%. But yeah,
what's wrong with that? but yeah,
not usually. Uh
I think anything can trigger anxiety in people.
Yeah, I've got anger issues. Sorry, I
was typing to someone.
I think being led on gives me anxiety issues.
The dating game gives me anxiety issues.
The dating game, that's what gives me anxiety.
Don't know about anyone else.
Yeah, that's what gives me anxiety.
It's so um underrated, you know. See that?
give what up the dating thing. Oh yeah,
of course, bro.
No, I'm not eating, man. I'm not eating, bro.
Don't be serious. I'm not eating, brother.
[ __ ] that, bro. Sorry, bro. Lady
Lady wasn't shook in the first place, lad.
One second, bro. Sorry, bro. Sorry ma'am.
So I was typing something.
What do you think of that? Um Grezy
like going to another country to go on
someone's door over YouTube.
Is that something you like seeing? What'
you say? Greasy.
Is that something that you like seeing?
It's pretty funny though. Is it? Yeah.
I like it. I like the part where the
neighbors get involved and the neighbors watch.
That's what I like.
Yeah, the neighbor said to me, "Fuck
off, you nons." And he went running, bro.
[ __ ] off you nons.
That was jokes, bro. That was [ __ ]
That was jokes.
Oh, bro. That's funny, isn't it? So,
what would happen if you got beat up by
the neighbor then, Grezy?
Then he would have lost you.
I greasy. Was that the same website you
could watch Elmo on or was it a different one? Was it?
Oh, [ __ ] funny, bro. That's funny as
[ __ ] is it? I might have to get a Valoo
for that, lads. Yeah.
That's funny. That is funny, bro. Yeah.
Cuz the thing is they can say what they
want about me, greasy, but people know
me. People know what I'm like. People
know what I'm about. Is it? [ __ ] off you not. You see?
Are you actually having a kebab or you
just taking a piss?
He doesn't need me to go. He doesn't
need to give me push. I'll go live
whenever I want.
I'll go live whenever I want, lad.
As long as that's okay with Grezy, [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm just going to get Okay, I'm
going to get a bindaloo. Yeah,
right. Okay, I've ordered it.
See you later, lad. You get kicked for that, lad. Yep.
I can't have the chicken tick or
anything like that, bro. I can't eat
Trust me. I'm just going to try to get
this down me, you know.
[ __ ] off you nons. Ah, bro. Imagine that.
But what I'm saying, Greavves, is you
know when uh did you see when Timmy was
making videos to Monty yesterday?
Do you remember that was because Tim
Monty was sticking up for me? You see,
I'm the Roos. He said, "All right." He
said, "Timmy, you're the nons
not PJ." You see what I mean?
See what I mean? It backfires. It's like
that thing with the labor when the labor
ended up getting nicked as well.
Do you remember scene? Yeah.
On the on the um nonstings.
But yeah, no, but seriously, bro. Um,
yeah, the dating thing is is is shitty, bro.
Proper proper shitty, lad. Proper proper shitty.
So, there's not going to be no drinking content anymore.
What do you think about that? Um, Steven Howard
No, lady's already had a steak.
Bless you, Gregy, if you got paid your
little benefits. Oh, bless you.
Bless you in life.
And you, you fly master [ __ ]
I want to be glowing this year. Grievy.
I want to be [ __ ] glowing, lad. Really?
It feels good winning any kind of money,
Dusty. It could be £100,£150,
but losing any money feels like [ __ ]
Working for any amount of money makes
you feel like [ __ ] Mad how it works, eh?
Yeah. I just got myself a vinderoo. Yeah, man.
No, I didn't get any ticker. Mommy,
no tickle, lad. No ticker.
You [ __ ] virgin [ __ ]
You You [ __ ] virgin, can't you?
Nah, no chicken, bro.
I'm still building my appetite back up, bro.
I was having some mad problems sleeping, bro.
Not anymore, though. It's good.
Yeah, I was having some mad problems, bro.
No, just multiple things, bro. Multiple
things to be fair.
That's part of it. But yeah, and it
wasn't even a loss either. I won the 20 pound.
Uh, okay. So,
I'll just sit there with my little curry greasy. Yep.
My order is on its way already. [ __ ] hell.
That was quick, bro.
It's quite an easy thing though, isn't it?
You go on go on Instagram.
Yeah. Well, once one team let me down.
Yeah. One let me down.
I'm not drinking today. Sun-kissed. I'm
doing nothing, bro. Just ordering myself
a curry, just chilling. I was out
earlier playing pool. I did go out
earlier on the bets and stuff, but yeah, obviously. Yep.
Just fed up. tongue-issed. I see you
write some comments about me, bro.
Just fed up, lad. To be honest. 99 burger.
That's funny, bro.
Yeah, I saw that video to be fair.
Why is this guy eating 99 IP burgers and
he wants to call other people skint?
Anyone score other people's skin, lad?
That's funny, bro.
People like you shouldn't gamble. Do you
remember that, Grezy? People People like
you shouldn't gamble.
Oh, [ __ ] man.
That's what people say, bro.
>> Yeah, that's funny, bro. Crazy
Instagram, Instagram, Instagram.
I don't I go to the bookies.
That's not a good question that you're
asking me, lad.
That seems a bit sus that you're asking
me uh that question. To be fair,
it's a bit suspect. I can't lie. Ooh,
You'll never regret cashing out, bro. I
would never regret cashing out. If if
you got a good offer, cashing out, then [ __ ]
Yeah, you're giving bomb vibes. I can't
lie, bro. Ask me what site I do my
football betting lawn. That's a bit suspect.
I can't lie. That is a bit weird,
isn't it, Stephen Howard? Cuz
there's only one reason why they'd be
asking you that, lad. You know what I mean? All
right, Indigo. How comes you can watch
Elmo on the same website you can meet
Timmy Eldridge on?
That's a bit weird, isn't it?
That's a bit weird, lad.
It seems so stupid, isn't it? Fighting
over YouTube, is it?
It's quite pathetic, actually, isn't it?
Well, I'm not getting ticker, but yeah.
Yeah, it's weird, isn't it? Yeah, it's weird, lad.
Um, what tips can I give? Um, go to Thailand.
Yeah, that's the tips I can give. Go to Thailand
and save yourself the dignity and selfrespect.
That's what I'd say.
Cuz these [ __ ] bro, they're [ __ ] heartless.
Heartless. Evil. [ __ ] inconsiderate
and that's that. And I got many
experiences to back it up as well. Is
that right, Grezy?
I'd say go gym, save your money and get
out of here. That's what I'd say.
That is literally what I would say. Literally.
But I'm thinking of starting new hobbies
now. Like I'm I said to Gre I'm going to
go back to the gym and stuff and there's
other things. I can't all put it on
here, lad. I can't I can't put
everything on out here. But like yeah,
I'm even done with it. I'm done with the
[ __ ] So, you know,
but it's not though, is it? Because
Thailand works perfect.
Thailand works perfect and it will work
for anyone that goes there. Anyone that
goes to Thailand, it will work for them.
It will work for every everyone that
goes there. It will work for them within
within an hour. So,
Thailand works perfect. Cambodia works
How do I know? Cuz I know, bro. Simple
as that. I know these things.
[ __ ] quite disgusting what these people do. You know,
stop asking stupid questions, bro. Stop
asking sick questions.
Asking sick questions, bro.
Don't know everything.
I don't know everything.
I wish I did. I don't know everything. I
know some things. Yeah.
And yeah, like I said, I can't even I
don't even want to spend my money in
these places anymore like drinking and
that cuz of the way it is. So like
that's why I don't really like Yeah. You get me?
Yeah, man. So,
you're best off just doing other things, I reckon.
That's at least what I'm doing anyways.
Sunday tomorrow. Wow, I got so fast.
[ __ ] hell, man.
Ricky Millington can be a white knight
all his life.
Twice with no passport.
It's funny cuz I got a passport right here.
No passport. Even though I got a
passport right here. Interesting. See,
obviously I got rice. Bro, you can't
have a curry without rice. You silly goose.
It only come recently. I've had this
passport for about a year, lad.
When I had to re I had to renew my
passport. I renewed my passport in
February. February. Yeah. Oh, it was
February. I remember exactly when it
was. Yeah. It's been over a year, lad. So
yeah, this is why you shouldn't talk
about people that you don't know, lad.
Yeah. Why don't you people show me what
you look like to shut me up? You show me
your faces and I'll show you the I'll
show you the passport stamps. Is that a
deal? Last month, last year, you
[ __ ] I got the passport last year.
February. Last February. When I was at
the old house, I renewed it straight away.
Bro, I've always had a passport.
Since I was 17,
like I said, when you come here and show
me your face, I'll show you the passport
stamps. That's good, isn't it, Steven
Howard? These people come on here, show
me what they look like, and I'll show
them the passport stamps. Simple.
You like to call people a m and stuff.
That's cute. That's nice. Everyone's
allowed their opinion. But at least show
what you people look like. And unless
you show what you look like, I'm not
showing you nothing. I've actually got
some money on the side there. Actually,
not showing you it. Simple.
Until you start showing your faces.
Um I'm not I'm not showing you nothing.
That's what the rules are. Well, you
people seem to keep judging men's looks
every day, lads. So you people you
people like judging people's looks every day.
You think it's bad the west? Do you know
the thing is dusty? It's not even that
bad, you know,
talking and hear and I've got a
boyfriend and that. Do you know that's
not even that bad, you know, bro? Even
when people walk away, why isn't it bad,
Dusty? Cuz you don't know these people.
You don't really know anything about these people.
But the leading on, however, that's a
completely different thing.
That's a complete completely different thing, lad.
You see, that's a complete different thing.
That's like a whole another chapter. Do you understand? So,
I'd avoid that, bro, if I was you.
No, no, no. But as I was saying, uh,
what was I bringing up before? Yeah, let
let Ricky Millington be a simp all his
life. Let him be a white knight all his
life and see where that gets him.
See where that gets the [ __ ]
See where that gets the [ __ ] in it, Grezy.
Let them let them do them do them things, bro.
You're never going to change simps,
Dusty. You're never going to change
white knights, lad.
That's just the way it is, bro.
It's not that expensive, but it's
getting more expensive.
I couldn't try day again, bro. The
thought of it makes me feel sick.
Actually makes me feel physically sick, bro.
I'm not even joking, bro. It is. So,
who the [ __ ] is that, bro?
No, just nothing, bro. Just not drinking
again. Bob Bills, I'm not going out
approaching or anything like that again, bro.
No, just like the leading on and [ __ ]
bro. The games and that.
Just just the leading on and false hope,
bro. I can't deal with it. I'd rather
get stabbed. I'm not even joking, bro.
I'd rather get stabbed.
Yeah. I just can't be dealing with it.
And just the way the the country is and
stuff like with the bars and the clubs
and them having their own agenda and
it's just the negatives outweigh the positives.
It's just it's a waste of everyone's
time, lad. So
I actually think, bro, about two years
ago there was hope. I actually think
there was hope two years ago, bro. I
actually think there was, bro. But now
there's completely there's completely none, lad.
Well, I know it ain't good, bro, but at
least it doesn't linger.
Do you understand? At least it don't
linger. Come on now, bro.
Where's his [ __ ] food?
Yeah, I reckon two years ago there was
there was actually hope, bro. There was
actually like, yeah, okay, cool. But now
I think it's just completely over, bro.
It's completely completely [ __ ]
Yeah, I don't know what's changed in 2
years, but something has. So yeah,
and then you can get battened for
[ __ ] cold approaching. Like what the [ __ ] bro?
Nah, I'm all right, bro. I'm all right with that.
I don't I don't I don't care for football, bro.
And Bob, the more you go out and the
more you try, the more you're going to
be made to feel like [ __ ]
So like, and that ain't even a joke,
bro. That's not even an excuse. That's
not even a joke, bro. Seriously,
a woman's wild family financially.
>> Yeah, exactly, Dusty. That's what I'm
saying. It's just a country designed to
annoy you. But I don't know if you've
ever been to the sub I don't know if
you've ever been to the Simmons Dusty,
but they're so like stuck up. They're so
like if you go out outside,
there's another club. I'm not going to
tell you the exact one. They're all
right. Like you don't have these
problems, but you know, you go Central,
bro, like you go to this Simmons,
they're just stuck up to [ __ ] I can't
even I can't even bloody um tell you,
bro, like how bad it is. Like they the
the the staff have got attitude. You can
see it from their face. Um obviously the odd one
like that black guy talking to this
black guy who who who I spoke to before.
Oh, was like got a good memory. Yeah,
we're talking and then some and imagine some [ __ ]
some [ __ ] coming up to you telling you
that like you you're barred for
approaching. Bro, that's embarrassing,
bro. That's actually embarrassing, bro.
Like, I don't actually understand,
Dusty, who these people actually think
they are, lad.
You know the Simmons bar, Dusty, in in
in in central London.
They are so so so stuck up.
It's just Oh, bro. I can't think of a a worse place.
Them places there, lad. now.
>> Yeah, you got no chance, lad. You can be
good-looking, bro. Whatever. But you
still have no chance, man.
>> I remember them paying super.
>> And then they don't And then Yeah. They
want you paying They They want you
paying their prices, but they don't want
you They don't want you making new
friends. They want you pay They want you
paying their prices.
It's just a [ __ ] country, bro. It that's it. Sorry.
But yeah, that Simmons is very stuck up.
Very, very westernized. Dusty, very very
London is very westernized, lad.
Yeah, I should do that. Bro, there's a
place in in called Simmons in Leicester
Square, Dusty, and never had a date
there. Never had a date there.
I have in the other one, but not that
bro. You them places are just impossible.
Impossible, bro. Them places there right there, bro.
They're called Sibons. It bro, you just
you get banned for anything. I said to
the I said to a member of staff, stop
acting like a [ __ ] Got banned for life. Dumb.
So it's like they
Yeah, they Yeah.
You got Weather spoons, bro. Fill your
boots. Any of these pubs, you can do
what you want. They don't care.
How dare you? How dare you come into our
premises, buy our overpriced drinks, and
try to speak to women. Oh, do you know
what I'm saying, bro?
Imagine that, Grevy. How dare you? That,
mate. You get locked up for [ __ ]
life. [ __ ] retards, bro. Yeah. Mad
lost. And what? Dusty ring here.
You want me to You want me to expose
stuck up London?
Yeah, that Simmons is the worst place, bro.
Full of stuck up people.
Full of stuck up people, lad.
I don't know how I was able to go there
last month without them noticing me. Dusty,
I'm not sure how, bro. But yeah,
like I said, lad.
Nope. Didn't know that.
Yeah. Like I went in last month when I
met that Christian Izzy, bro. I swear to
God, I went to the same one. Yeah. Oh,
well, you can't wear Truxy Buttons.
I said, "Okay, well, I can change." And
he was like proper a [ __ ] about it. Made
me change. I said, "Okay." Went back to
the bar. [ __ ] comes over again. Oh.
Uh, you're back. I was like, "Oh,
really? Forever?" He said, "Yeah."
[ __ ] [ __ ] How embarrassing is
that, bro? When you're trying to speak
to people, they probably think you're
some [ __ ] sex offender or some [ __ ]
lad. Probably thinks you're some [ __ ] pedophile.
Utter embarrassing, bro. I got put off
after that, bro. I'm not going to lie.
Then the bad and then the lead being led
on and [ __ ] Oh, [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] all that.
Yeah, it's bad enough, Grezy and Dusty,
the way that women already are. And then
you've got that extra [ __ ] that
comes with it.
Like you got that extra [ __ ] that
doesn't need to come with it that comes
with it. Do you get me, lad?
You got gay people trying to embarrass
you like, you know what I mean? in like
a roundabout way. And and I I will say
it, bro. It's worse when a gay person's doing it.
It really, really is. It really is. That
that to me just seemed like more of a
slap in the face. Even though I don't
have a problem with gay people, it just
did. Sorry, bro. But it just did, you know.
And you could tell it was gay by the way
he sounded. It's obvious, isn't it?
So, it's okay for you to go and grind up
and and and start sucking up people's
dick every day, but we can't we can't
speak to people in in a in in an
environment where you're supposed to be
talking to people.
Can you can you explain it?
And he says, "Oh, thanks for
understanding." I said, "Well, I don't
understand. Can you explain it?" I said,
"Well, I don't understand."
That's the thing. Like I actually I
literally do not understand.
So you're being stuck up for the sake of it
because you can't explain it. They can't
like you ask them, they won't explain
it. Grievous. They literally will do
anything but explain it because they can't.
You know, that's it. It's like they have
places where they where they where
they're conning people with the drinks,
but then they're trying to tell you what
you can and can't do.
Like you give our city a bad name.
People like you give our city a bad name.
You you you give where we come from a bad name.
Know what I mean, bro?
I wonder what they would do if you
didn't leave. They call the police. I
think they would call the police, but yeah,
I don't know what would happen. They
would probably call the police in it, I guess.
But like I said, uh, Dusty, just a
country designed to annoy you.
Simple as that, bro.
That's that is it.
I hate this country, bro.
That's my com coming.
Come on. Come here.
But yeah, but like
not [ __ ] gay people trying to tell
you what you can and can't do.
You know what I should have said?
Oh [ __ ] You know what I should have
said, bro? I should have said, "You
don't see me [ __ ] moaning and you've
stopped me making money that day cuz of
your [ __ ] pride."
That's what I should have said. Why did
I think of that, bro? Bro, I swear now,
bro. There was about two Saturdays, bro.
I tried to make money.
Place got closed. Whole of these roads
got closed down because of this gay pride.
I [ __ ] lost out [ __ ] money.
I lost out [ __ ] money, bro, on that
Saturday. But then you're trying to tell
me who I can and can't talk to, bro. [ __ ] off.
I'm saying, bro, they stop me making
[ __ ] money that day, bro. Remember
see it. Yeah, it's not watery. It's
actually nice to be fair. Not it's not
watery or nothing.
Not like the ones [ __ ] Virgin boy
um goes to them shitty ones. Them sticky
virgin ones. You like proper ones, bro.
Never been to Never been to Peter Express.
Yeah, but you get me like,
you know what I mean? No, [ __ ]
okay for them to do a little gay pride
thing and stop people making money.
People couldn't work that day to do that
thing. But then you're trying to tell me
I can't speak to people.
in in my own country where where you're
over you're ripping people off with
drink prices, bro. Come on. Make it make sense.
You don't see me trying to [ __ ] you
don't see me trying to stop gay pride.
You're not You're not trying to see me
stop your vibe, lad. So why are you
trying to stop v you [ __ ] puss?
I didn't think about the bike thing when
I was working. You don't get to think of
things like that. You know what I mean? Yeah,
mate. Two Saturdays I tried working. It
happened. No one cares about your gay
pride. [ __ ] off. You're gay. No one
cares. [ __ ] off.
You know what I mean? You're gay.
Really, that doesn't mean anything.
You're gay, bro. No one cares.
You know what I mean, bro? It's not even
a thing now, Greg. People just come out.
It's not like it was, you know, years
ago, bro. people loads of people come out.
You know what I mean, bro? It's just
Yeah, it's just [ __ ] This country is
just [ __ ] bro.
No one cares. Gay pride. [ __ ] gay
pride. [ __ ] off.
People use it to get attention as well. Green.
They use it to get attention.
They actually use it to get attention.
You get me?
Yeah. You don't see me stopping gay
fries. So why you stopping my van, lad?
Why are you trying to stop my van?
[ __ ] [ __ ] Just a country designed
to annoy you, lad. Say it multiple times
day till the day I'm to the day I'm blue
in the face, bro.
It is a country designed to annoy you.
They should give us a break.
They should give us a break now. You
know what I mean? They should give us a
[ __ ] break. We already have a hard
time getting [ __ ] led on. You know
what I mean? It matter.
You know why it's not too hot for me, Grezy?
Cuz I'm not a [ __ ] virgin [ __ ] That's why
I'm not no [ __ ] virgin [ __ ]
That back down for my [ __ ] [ __ ] video. M
I'm a big strong Turkish man.
So, it's not only the women that's
keeping you single, Bob. It's the
[ __ ] You got [ __ ] managers.
You got [ __ ] gay managers trying to
tell you what you can and you can't
[ __ ] do. Even though their pride
stopped a lot of [ __ ] making money,
[ __ ] little [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] lad.
[ __ ] gay [ __ ] bro. Yeah,
it's all right for them to have a pride
to stop people making money.
A lot of people probably didn't go to
work that day, lad. [ __ ] [ __ ]
I've complained about people that
first sip of Coke.
Now, if this was the virgin,
two cans of coke would have already been drunk.
Is that right? Um,
that was the virgin. Virgin boy
doing the [ __ ] D.
That Echo is a sick bastard. You know
that Echo is a sick bastard, man.
You watch that two guys, one hammer.
He's a sick bastard.
Yeah, he's a proper sick come ears, dad.
No, he's sick. I've been trying to get
Gi to watch it, but he won't watch it.
That is, mate.
Yeah, he's a sick [ __ ] mate.
They all s
what I'm saying. They can say what they
want, but they can try and say what they
want about me. Say that I'm a I'm a one.
I'm this, that, and the other. That's
fine, bro. But, you know, at least if
you're going to say this stuff, just
show us what you look like. They can't do it.
That's fine, bro. I'm this that. That's
nice, bro. Let's see what you look like.
They can never do it.
They can never do it, Stephen. Because
deep down, these people are ugly as [ __ ] lad.
These people are ugly as [ __ ]
That's part of the reason why they go
for people every day, lads, cuz they
know that they're [ __ ] just ugly people, bro.
Yeah, he is, bro.
But Steven, but at least with Lord J,
right? Listen, bro. As much as they have [ __ ] here,
at least when they're talking about
Timmy, Timmy's done this, you don't do
this. But at least these people have
have actually like put themselves out
there trying to meet me, bro. Unlike the
[ __ ] skinned virgin in Orington.
Unlike that virgin these people about to
like put themselves out there. You know
what I mean?
To be fair, bro. Like in all honesty,
people can have their opinion. I don't
mind anyone having their opinions, but
it's when [ __ ] nonsense thinks he can
have an opinion. But he's the biggest
coward out there.
That bird. What am I celebrating?
[ __ ] off you lunch.
I'm Coming to Birmingham soon, Jimmy.
I'm coming to Birmingham soon, Jimmy.
You better [ __ ] run, lad.
I'm [ __ ] coming.
I'm going to knock you out. Yeah.
there. [ __ ] off your nons.
Oh, Timmy, [ __ ] off your nons.
Timmy, what's your address?
And I'll come on the door.
Is that something you Is that something
you'd be interested in seeing? Grimsy me
going on the door.
Hey, Jimmy. What's your address?
I'll come in your door if you want.
I'm going to knock him out. Yeah,
I'm going to knock him out. I swear to
God. I swear to God.
Come here, lad.
Crazy. Come here, lad. Remember,
I will knock him out.
Oh, really? Yeah. No, Timmy. Seriously.
Give me your address.
Give me your address to me. Yeah.
Will it be the same website for watching?
mate. Vicky, you hide behind a fake account, lad.
Apply that to yourself, buddy. You You
You won't even come on the panel and talk, lad.
No one hid from Timmy. No one ran from
to me, lad. Everyone saw it.
Sorry. Must be yourself there, lad.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. That was nice. Oh. Oh, Jesus.
But yeah, um
Jimmy, I'll put the link out. Timmy,
we need a shot. We do.
Ricky, you're you're white like that.
>> No, you can't accept your defeat to be a
[ __ ] Yes. Anyway, anyway, Mong, I've
given you my address. 96 Albert Square,
Birmingham. The neighbor bullied you.
Hurry up, PJ. The neighbor bullied you.
>> The neighbor bullied you. PJ, be man.
>> The neighbor called you a n, Timmy. Stop
it now. The neighbor called you a na.
Stop it now. Sh. Stop shouting. Yeah. Hey,
that's funny, bro. That was funny. All right.
Oh, Timmy, Jimmy, Jimmy.
Why can't this guy give me his address, bro?
I've got some questions to ask Timmy.
Right. I don't want I don't want him
talking over me. I just want to answer some questions. Come on. you know.
No, I'm going to knock him out. I swear
to God. I've already I told Gregy this
as well. I'm going to knock him out. Yeah, Seriously. Seriously, lad.
Yeah, I see that gym skin around Dusty on Instagram.
He looks a [ __ ] though,
Dusty. He looks all right, [ __ ]
I'm going to knock him out. Yeah.
Yeah, I see that gym skin, bro.
Yeah, I see I see that guy, bro. He just
looks like a [ __ ]
though. Dusty, he looks all right, [ __ ] Mama.
Mama with a H in the end.
H at the end.
It's funny, bro.
So yeah, that's the um that's where
we're at, bro.
That's where we're at, bro. I don't know
what to say.
What a country to live in though in it.
Dusty being told what you can and can't
do. Can't win money. Be [ __ ] around
with by women. England is just a great
place. I can't think of a better a
better place to be than England.
I can't think of a better place.
I really can't, bro.
I like this game. Do you remember that
Greasy when Seaside Malt was playing
roulette? I like this game. This game's fun.
I like this game. That was one of That
was a banger, bro. I remember that.
Yeah. I like this game. And he kept
going. He kept going next door.
>> Oh, that was funny, bro. Oh, bless.
Oh, bless. That was funny, bro.
Sounds a [ __ ]
Sounds like a cult. Oh no,
I need to have a shower in a minute.
Let that curry go down and it's shower time, [ __ ]
It's shower time, [ __ ]
Okay with you, boss. Nah,
sick of the dating game here though,
Gary Glitter. I hate England, bro.
Where do I begin? If someone said to me,
"What do you hate about England?" Um,
I'd be like,
"Where do I begin, bro? Where do you actually begin?" Seriously,
the women, the people, the weather.
Everything just sucks about England, bro.
You have a gay pe You have a gay person
telling you you can't be somewhere. You
Oh my god, bro. It's mad.
It's bad, bro. What can you do?
Yeah. So, do I make a fair point,
Grievy, about the pride?
We never tried to stop your pride when
you were stopping me making money. So
why why why are you trying to stop my my
my momentum? Why are you trying to stop
my vibe? You get it? I think that's a
pretty valid point to be fair.
So what if you're gay, bro? You like
men, bro. But like bisexual people, you
know what I mean? I could have made
about £120 that day, you know?
I could have made £120 that day. probably. Yeah, probably. Yeah. So, yeah.
I want your opinion on it all. Griezy,
do you want my opinion? Yes, I do want
your opinion, Grezy, I do want your opinion. Yes.
I want your opinion, Greasy.
I But dusty people on Reddit say dating is easy.
They say it's easy. in uh
I need to catch up with another Billy Moore video.
You know who Billy Mo is, don't you, Dusty?
He's a lovely fellow.
Yeah, Billy Mo is a lovely fellow.
I see was in South End.
I watched that South End video, bro. I
used to go south end a lot when I was a
kid. I know all about South End, bro.
It's our nearest seaside.
Yeah, I watch some of his videos when
he's down south. I watch some of his
videos. I'm subscribed to him,
bro. It's not [ __ ] easy here, Gary.
Women are horrible here, bro. [ __ ]
horrible people, bro. Horrible. Horrible people.
Trust me, lad.
I ain't been self in years, but I've
been many times. Groven by the side of
the pier. I know all about self, bro.
That's where seven neighbors lives.
Probably have more chance pulling there
though than you do London.
But saying that, that's probably
everywhere's probably the same now.
I think everywhere's probably the same.
Yeah, that Billy Mo, bro. He would be
quite hard to beat in a fight in it, bro.
I don't think many people could beat him
like your average Joe in it, Dusty. Nah, bro. No thanks.
Yeah, he looks quite strong, that guy,
bro. Yeah, I know all about him, bro. I
know all about him.
So maybe he could beat LT then. Is it
Dusty? Maybe he Maybe he could beat him in it. Maybe, bro.
Maybe. Yeah, I know all about that.
That, bro. I watched it. Yeah, I know. I
saw it all, bro. I see it where he
slammed this guy in Manchester.
Did you see that, bro? When he slammed him,
he just like he just slammed him, bro.
Cuz he kept like following him or
something. Did you see it?
Yeah, I saw that, bro.
Yeah, that guy would be hard to beat,
bro. He looks quite strong, bro. I'm not
going to lie. There's a boxer in it. Yeah,
he's a boxer is he or he was a boxer.
[ __ ] that, bro.
Why does this nonslegs keep making posts
about me being a [ __ ] house? I think
this guy's got like like brain damage or
something. Does you not remember the
time that I had him stop going on
YouTube for two weeks? Severe brain
damage, bro. Severe severe brain damage.
guys actually got brain damage, lad.
No, but if you don't leave, they they'll
just call the police and that is it. So,
it's just all negative, lad.
It's just all a negative here. Um
maybe I'll do a video one one day about
it or whatever. Yeah.
Then you got to put up with the women as well.
They're leading on the [ __ ]
And then you got gay people telling you
where you where you can and can't go.
What a life, lad.
Cheeky cheeky bastards.
That is cheeky, bro.
Cheeky. I've even had a I've even had a
bouncer try to cop block me before.
I've actually had a bouncer try cop
blocking me with this American. She's
like, "Oh, do you know this man?" And
she's like, "Yeah." He's like, "Okay."
I've actually had a bouncer try cop
blocking me, bro.
It's the time I got that [ __ ] in the
alleyway. Yeah, he was trying to cop.
Bro, I've got so many stories, bro.
Some of it is cheeky. Some of it is cheeky, lad.
Yeah. Really? Yeah.
Yeah. I've had an American bouncer try
telling me what I can wear. He said,
"You just got to go Prair, man." I was
like, "No, you don't tell me what I can
and can't wear. I'm not changing for
you, bro. If you're not going to let me
in, you're not going to let me in. I'm
not changing. You You don't come to my
country and tell me what I can and can't wear, bro.
So, I we'll just leave it." It's cheeky,
bro. I don't know. It's cheeky, bro. I
find stuff like that cheeky. So
it kind of Yeah, it's just it's just
it's just all negative, isn't it?
What else is there to say, lad?
That gay one was the worst, though. That
was That was the worst, bro.
That one was the worst, lad.
That one was the ultimate worst.
Considering I had dealt with so much
[ __ ] the week before, bro, with one of
these people that I met. Um,
you know what I mean? Yeah.
See, Indigo, I can take anything, lad. I
can take anything.
Like anything. Just Just not the leading on, bro.
I can take the boyfriend [ __ ] I can
take the walking away. I can take the
replying once and then not replying
again or the not replying. I got three
numbers. None of them replied. Didn't
really care. You get me, lad?
That's the worst thing, bro. That's the worst thing.
What do you reckon would have happened
today, Indie guy? If I went out approaching,
what do you think would have happened?
Yeah, but like that wouldn't be the only
thing though, would it?
No, that Christian Izzy is a [ __ ] bro. Proper [ __ ]
I just expected them to be different,
bro. Like I The thing is, bro, I I I
give people I try to give people the
benefit of the doubt, you see.
So, I just expected they were going to
be different. You know what I mean? But nah,
I can safely say, bro, all women are
exactly the same. I can actually say
that now, bro.
In 2026, I can safely say that, bro.
I can actually say that without hesitation.
Yep. Gay managers trying to cop block you.
Gay a gay manager trying to cop block
you. What could be more annoying than that, bro? Yeah.
Yeah. I can actually say Dustin without
hesitation that all women are actually
the same, bro. Before
I could have said like, "Oh, I don't
really I was hesitant about it." But now
I'm I'm sure they are, bro. Christian,
Muslim, Catholic, atheist, black, white,
Indian, Pakistan, Chinese, Arab,
Swiss, German, wherever the [ __ ] they
come from, bro, they are all the same,
bro. And you know when you when you
realize this, yeah, your life gets easier. dusty.
When you realize these things, it gets
easy. You see,
and you realize they are
the amount of times I've been done over
in my life, bro. I'm surprised I ain't
had a mental breakdown.
I'm surprised I ain't had a mental
breakdown, Dust. Uh dusty bro.
Yeah. Well, it's well it's actually
worse, lad. In 2026, it's actually
[ __ ] triggers your anxiety and
everything, bro. It's bad.
But people on Reddit say it's easy, Indigo.
People on Reddit say, "Oh, it's it's easy, lad. Yeah.
I remember I got 10 numbers before and
not one replied.
I've had three numbers. They've all replied.
Going out just makes you feel like [ __ ] lad.
It just makes you feel like [ __ ]
I was very tempted to buy that Lego from
HMV Grezy, but I didn't bother, lad.
I should have though.
I know if I drunk today, lad,
I would have ended up [ __ ]
messaging people. I know what I'm like,
lad. Is it Oh,
good luck though, lad. Good luck.
It's all I can say to you.
>> You right, Jimmy. >> Virgin
for life. The only virgin for life. You
got numbers in the virgin.
Can we have a normal chat? Can we have a
>> No, virgin.
>> Let's have a normal chat. Let's talk
about how you ran away from the
neighbor. I don't know what your name
when he ran in the house and I couldn't
run around. You are constantly full of shi
cuz you were afraid you're going to get
a sky pork in the face and the house
coming down. You put the video back. You
are a [ __ ]
Put the video back.
Give me Give me your address. I'll come
your daughter and I'll come your daughter.
>> No, I'm really going to give you my
address on YouTube. You clown.
>> Give me email address. Email me your
>> Okay, I will email you my addressimmy.
Timmy Timmy, the neighbor told you to [ __ ] off
and the neighbor [ __ ] I called him
around the corner. He did nothing.
>> Timmy Timmy.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Anyway, Steven. Yeah, lad. Um
because what I'm trying to say, Grezy.
Yeah. Is like if I knew someone's address Yeah.
like a woman's address who [ __ ] me
over, whatever. I'd be drinking in it,
Grezy. So, I'd just be drinking normally
and I'd be like, "Them [ __ ] were
laughing at you. Mocking you." Nah, bro.
[ __ ] that. Ain't it mocking you? That's
the only That's the only thing that
would just keep playing in my head, bro.
You know what I mean? No. [ __ ] that,
bro. No. No. No. [ __ ] that, bro. Oh, do
you remember do you remember when I went
on Isabelle's dogy? >> Yeah.
>> Just to let you know, I am coming back.
I am coming back virgin. And next time
you won't run away the last time.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Next time. See you
later, Virgin. I will your wife. I'll be
shouting good afternoon through the You
are the virgin.
>> You ran away. You want to play the money game.
>> You were scared to get
>> Why do you want to play the money game?
>> What money game? You haven't got any?
>> Have Have you got Have you got money on
you right now?
>> I've got about £325
in cash on me right now, PJ. Yes.
>> Can we see it?
>> Can we see you your Can we see your
lousy 20 quid you got to your name?
>> Yeah. So, if if I show you 20 pound if I
show you 20 pound, you'll show me 300.
>> Maybe I will. Maybe I won't.
>> Okay. I've actually got some money on
the side. I'll show you 20.
>> You want
the only 20 he's got in the world. There
you go. Let's see your money.
>> Double it to 40. Peter,
>> no. There you go. 20,
Peter. Mommy's Uber account.
>> Do you really want my Peter?
>> Yeah. Come on. You know what, Peter?
I've just got out the shower. You can
see my cash after the commercial break.
>> You ain't even got 40 quid.
>> Yeah, I have like I have some money on
the side, bro, from um
>> what done earlier. So, yeah. Come on.
Come on, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Steven Howard, that she's a she's
a [ __ ] bro. Christian is he's a [ __ ] in
it, Steven Howard.
But yeah, I need to I need to come off
this [ __ ] anyways. I wouldn't come on
here today if it weren't for the
football, bro. I'm I'm a man on a
mission, Grezy. Do you understand?
I'm a man on a mission, lad.
Do you get me? I need to go gym, bro. I
need to I need to do stuff. I need to
get out of there, bro. I'm a man on a
mission. And that's what a lot of the
people in this community need to be. Like,
that's what I'm doing, lad.
Laughing at you. [ __ ] you, Steven Howard. Mocking you.
Is that right, Grey? [ __ ] you. Yeah,
it's madness, bro. Stay away from the
dating game, Dusty. It makes you feel like [ __ ] Yeah,
them army [ __ ] were laughing at you,
mocking you. Dusty,
>> I'm going to come back and humiliate you
when you can't hide behind.
>> Don't run away next time. Don't run away.
>> You're the one who ran away, Fed.
>> Okay. Okay. Where was you when I was
like, okay, listen. Where was you when I
was See, he can't let He won't let me talk, lad.
>> He won't let me talk. See, this is what
I'm saying. He won't let me talk.
See, cuz he knows Cuz he knows, bro. Why
is he not letting anyone talk? Cuz he
knew he was storming the area and he ran
into a field.
Why did I take Cuz it just paid for the
football bets, isn't it? Why did you
watch two two men one hammer?
Dr. Echo, you sick bastard.
Why did you watch that? You sick [ __ ]
You're sick in the head. You are.
You're sick. You watching that, lad.
Yeah, this Dr. Echo is quite sick
watching stuff like that.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
What was that all about? Yeah, this Dr.
Echo guy is a sicko.
Yeah, but you liked it, Dr. Eko. You liked it.
Yeah, but you liked it.
You're sick cuz you liked it in it.
You liked it in there. Yeah,
mate. If Timmy was there, he would have
got a [ __ ] bang in his head, bro. I
would have knocked him out, I reckon.
What do you think, Steven Howard? I
think I would have knocked him out.
Yeah, I reckon so, bro.
There weren't even going to be no talking, bro.
Nah, I only watched what I only watched
one video and that was it.
No, I only watched one video.
I only watched the hammer one.
There was other ones I didn't watch it.
I've never watched anything else, but uh yeah.
No, I haven't. There was one where it
says pregnant woman stabs baby
in the stomach and that. I didn't watch
it though, bro.
I don't think it was that video that
actually [ __ ] me up, bro. It was
actually the dating thing. It's actually
go what's going on recently with the dating.
It weren't even that video to I thought
it was that video, bro. That was But it
was actually the dating.
It was the dating thing and being led
on. I think that was that was a word. I
I thought I just contributed it to all
to that video
that it was actually the dating thing.
I don't want to attack people with a
hammer. That's gross. That's vile.
Makes me jump.
That makes me jump. That does, lad.
No, that makes me jump. Yeah,
cuz when I was live, when I just come
back, I was live. Where was Timmy? His
phone didn't die. He wasn't back thingy.
So, where was Timmy?
Where had Timmy gone?
Where did he go?
Where was Timmy?
He He ran to the bus. My mom said he ran
to the bus. So if he was on the bus,
then he was still around the area.
Yeah, he was still around the area, lad.
But I don't even know what that video is, lad.
Yeah. So if he was on the bus then.
So he This is what I was trying to say.
But do I don't know what that is, lad. So yeah, no.
Bro, I reckon if I hit Timmy once, I'd
knock him out. I'm not even joking, bro.
I was going to knock him out, bro. I was
expecting to see someone outside the
door. I was running. I would just run
for the [ __ ] bro.
I'm not even joking. Yeah,
you never know. Maybe Timmy could beat
me. You don't know.
Nobody ran out the house from anywhere, lad.
No one ran out the house from anyone, matey. Mia.
No, no, no.
What a life.
What a life in this country. Hey, Stephen.
What a [ __ ] life in this country, mate.
Where are you even supposed to meet
people nowadays if the dating apps don't
work? [ __ ] bars and clubs have got a
[ __ ] agenda. People don't like People
don't like being spoken to on the
[ __ ] street. That got worse as well.
I noticed that got worse, too.
I don't blame myself for not giving up a
years ago cuz it wasn't like this years ago.
It wasn't like this a couple of years ago. So,
it's only started being like this now
for the past maybe 18 months.
The past 18 months
to be fair.
It was never like this. So, I just
didn't think anything of it in it.
But now it is definitely is definitely
impossible now, bro.
What content would you like to see? Bro,
I'm not going out drinking, bro. For the
reasons I've already explained.
You can't even
drink somewhere properly
because you know what these people are like.
So, and then obviously they're leading
on and [ __ ] bro. It's serious. It's a serious thing.
I don't know who USA KD is, but yeah.
But it's a serious thing, bro. So,
I don't know what content you like to see, lad.
Oh, the one on the approaching video.
Yeah, she's a [ __ ] though. Pretending
she had a boyfriend when she don't.
Yeah, but just another liar. Well, say
liar in it.
It's the It's the leading on Bob bills,
bro. The way these like managers try to
ban you for anything and then even if
you meet someone, you get led on. I'm
too old to be dealing with this [ __ ]
now, but bro, it's it's boring, bro.
It's depressing, man.
I had anxiety the past week, lad. It's
only just gone now.
I drunk [ __ ] I drunk [ __ ] twice
last week, bro.
Because of this [ __ ] I had problems
sleeping as well. It's only just kind of got better. So,
it's not good, lad.
Yeah, I got three numbers. None of them replied.
Nah, she's just a liar. Stephen Albert,
we're just like all of these women are liars. Bullshitters.
After that Christian Izzy thing, yeah, I
can safely say now all women are the
same, bro. After that Christian Izzy
thing, I can safely say, bro, that they
will [ __ ] you over. No problem. Doesn't
matter how long they speak to you for.
Doesn't matter how genuine they might
try to appear. They are all the same.
believe that, bro.
They are generally all the same and all
they do is try to make people feel like [ __ ]
And that's not that's not a joke, bro.
That's the truth.
Sounds sad, but it is the way, bro.
Christian Izzy was all right. Yeah, bro.
She seemed nice, bro. That's the only
the reason I was like, "Okay, we'll roll
with it in it. She's not ugly and that."
So, but then she turned into a [ __ ] when
I sp when the exams finished, I was
like, "Oh, let's let's meet up next
week." And then she started coming up
with these excuses.
That's when it all started, bro. That's
when all of it started.
Just like that. Yeah.
So yeah, you can't trust any of them,
bro. None of them are good. None of them
If a Christian person can do it, there's
Muslims that done it in the past. Just
you can't trust any of them, bro.
None of them. None of them are
different, lad. Believe that, bro. Believe that.
So yeah, I still can't believe I've
spoke to someone for a month for no reason.
I can't I can't get over that, bro.
I spoke to somebody for a month for
absolutely no [ __ ] reason, bro.
Imagine the scenes on that, you know,
and all they do is talk about their exes
and rare and [ __ ] they probably gone
back to their [ __ ] ex now.
Uh, shag them quicker, huh? Good one,
Bob. Try getting a conversation out of
one of them first lad. try and get a
date out of one of them first lads and
maybe the shag might lead then might
maybe the shag might lead the way after
that. We know we need to try getting a
conversation out of the [ __ ] first lad.
Yeah, bro. I spoke to someone for a
month for no reason. So yeah,
that is [ __ ] isn't it? If you think
about it, Dusty,
when someone's sending you voice notes
all day and someone's messaging you you
all day, bro, you just believe it when
they say stuff to you. Do you get me?
You just believe it. But no,
that's why you don't speak to people for
long before trying to meet them.
There was an issue with that though,
wasn't there? So yeah.
Yeah, it sucks, bro. It sucks.
Really does suck, lad.
Makes you feel like [ __ ] as well. You
can look it up. It will tell you. It does. So yeah,
probably the best just to give up, bro. Serious.
Speaking to someone for a month, they
don't even meet you. What the [ __ ]
This world is so [ __ ] up, bro. It's so [ __ ] up.
I said, "Oh, let's meet now." I was
drinking. I said, "Oh, let's meet up
now." Sent me loads of messages,
deleted the messages, then blocked me.
Huh? Trying to reverse the psychology
cuz I'm right, lad.
You know I'm right, bro.
Yeah, it's true. Is it though? Yeah.
Bad, bad, bad.
These women are [ __ ] Dusty.
These women are [ __ ] lad. Antman
done the right thing in it. Dusty
leaving and never coming back. Yeah.
Oh, it's hot, bro. Jeez.
Probably have a shower tomorrow to be fair.
>> Yeah, probably tomorrow, bro.
Yeah, bro. I got like a bit of anxiety
from the um abandoned issues, Dusty.
Cuz you know, like it's the whole this
whole USA easy thing. You you feel like
you've actually been abandoned.
That's not even a joke, bro. Like, I
know we joke about like um yeah, taking
a baby away from its mama, but they are
it's actually a real thing, bro. It's
like abandoned issues.
If you don't know anything about the
person and they dip after a day or two,
then it's fine. You don't know them. You
don't know back. You don't know the
backlog of this person. But the more you
get to know people,
the more you become invested, the worse it is. Doesn't matter.
That's the worst thing, lad. That's the
worst. It doesn't matter if they don't
owe you anything or not. I don't know
anything any Does that mean I can go
around being a [ __ ] and leading people on, Dusty?
Does that mean So, does that mean I can
go around and be be a [ __ ] to people and
say, "Oh, I don't owe you anything." Can
I can I do that then? Will will I get a free pass?
You know, if you don't know someone or
you speak to someone for a day, two, you
don't that doesn't matter. You don't
know you you don't know them anyways.
But how do I explain this, bro? You're
not invested. The more you get invested,
right, the more you get to know these
people and the worse it will be when
they [ __ ] you over. This is what I'm
trying to say.
They're evil people, bro. They really
are evil, evil people. And I'm I swear
to God, bro. I swear. I'm not just saying this.
They are truly evil people, lad. And I
believe what I'm saying, bro. You know,
you know, I've just been gullible in the past
um to give people the benefit of the
doubt and stuff. You know what I mean?
Like, bro, when I had gone out, for
whatever reason, I went out.
You get me, bro?
You think that's okay? What doing stuff
like that? Because people don't owe you anything.
Is that is that how long is that's going
to be how long is that going to be used
to defend people's shitty behavior?
That's bad, bro. You don't you don't
you can't try and excuse stuff saying that, bro.
But yeah, man.
Obviously, you don't know, but you get
what I'm saying, bro.
Same thing with USA. They feel no way.
This how you know these people are
generally evil, bro. Is that they they
will ghost people and they wouldn't they
wouldn't think twice about it. They
ghost people that [ __ ] off and they
wouldn't give a [ __ ] They don't care.
Yeah. Even when I've ditched people in
the past, I've went to the toilets and
[ __ ] never come back. I never ghosted.
I just could never ghost. I said I told
them why I done it. I done this because
of that. I've done that because of this.
done that because of this. I've never
done that, bro.
I could never do it, bro.
And that's how you know they're [ __ ]
in their head. They are actual evil,
bro. They are actually evil people, bro.
I'm not even joking. They actually are evil [ __ ]
You know what I mean, bro?
I'm certain now, bro. I'm definitely
sure about it now.
In the past, I wasn't dusty, but now I'm
actually sure they really are
not good people,
you know? like they aren't
and you know the worst thing as well Bob
is when they're telling you about their um
telling you stuff you know bro like exes
and stuff and how their exes are always
bad people funny enough their exes are
always cheaters. They're always horrible
people. They're never people that they
just broke up with because it weren't
working. They're always bad people, Bob.
And that's the most annoying thing about
it is they're always bad people that
look similar to you.
That's the thing that [ __ ] with my
head, bro, is that they're similar
looking to you, but they're just not
nice people, but you are. But yet,
you're the one that gets treated this
way. Do you understand, bro? This is
what I'm trying to say. The more you
speak, the more you know backlogs about
people, the more you know the kind of
people that they've been with. That's
the worst thing, bro. That is the
ultimate worst thing. You know,
cuz you get to know a bit about people,
you know, they told you and stuff.
You know what I'm saying, Bob?
Nothing wrong with the way that you look.
You understand, bro? Like
this is so [ __ ] up in so many ways,
bro. I wouldn't even be able to explain
it. Like it's like
they're saying about like
exes and stuff being Albanian. Then they
asked me if I was Albanian cuz some
people think that I'm Albanian. I look
Albanian. So they're these people are
similar to you that they've been with,
right? But they're horrible people. But
then they're treating you the same way
that they've treated them. Does that
make sense? It's so [ __ ] up, bro.
Like, so I mean,
you're telling me mad stories, bro.
Where do you even find these
[ __ ] bro? You think yourself,
where do you even find these people,
lads? No, I have, bro. Like, no. No. Do
you know what it is, Bob? I generally
have, bro, because the only thing is,
yeah, cuz you realize, bro, yeah, once
once you get once you get to a certain
age, bro. Yeah. You realize that these
people are just they're just all the
same, lad. Like you you actually do, bro.
You actually you actually do, bro. Like,
why do you think I don't go out anymore?
Very rarely I go out now, bro. Why Why
do you think? Cuz I know the truth, bro.
I know what they're like. I know what they're about.
And it just pisses me off. Absolutely
pisses me off, lad.
You know? It absolutely pisses me off.
more than you could you can imagine. Trust me.
This person Bob was supposed to meet me. What happened?
H what what what happened all of a
sudden? You get me?
This person was supposed to [ __ ]
know what I mean? What the [ __ ] lad?
You know what I mean?
[ __ ] have an ex that cheated on you
and had a kid with someone else. Where
are you finding these people, bro?
There's no way you're telling me you do
not know what these people are like
before getting with them.
There's no way you are
you are finding these people and you
don't know what they're about, bro. They
got to be some drug dealer. They've got
they've got to be known for these kind
of things before getting with them, bro.
You get what I'm saying?
Mad, bro. It's just mad annoying as
well, bro. It's just mad annoying, man.
So, yeah, Bob,
that's it, man.
I don't worry about it. I don't even
have a sex drive anymore, to be fair.
The only reason I thought they were
going to meet Bob is because they were
speaking every day for a month. So I
just assumed, you know, someone's
talking every day for a month, then
somehow they still seem to try to re
they still somehow are able to reel you in.
You know what I'm trying to say? Somehow
they they they still seem to be able to do it.
and how they think like even people that
you've slept with how they think that
they can ghost you is mad. Like you
don't want to speak to someone. Give
someone an explanation. Then you've gave
an explanation. Leave. Bye. You know
what I'm saying, bro? Like it's it's
it's as simple as that.
These people they're they're not good
people. Like trust me, they're not good
people. Trust me, them days are gone, bro. Trust
You know what I mean?
Yeah. I don't even have a sex drive much
anymore, Bob. To be fair, lad. I don't
really care about it.
I think that's the only reason you cared
about it when you was younger. When I
was younger, that's like when I was 23, 24.
That's the reason I put up with it, bro,
for so many years. You know what I mean?
But yeah, [ __ ] that. Will I be doing
that again? You get [ __ ] man.
Make money, leave, lad. Go gym. Make
money. Get out of here. It's all you got to do.
[ __ ] [ __ ] start stops crying on a
voice note. Bob Bills like [ __ ] [ __ ]
was crying on a voice note. I'm thinking
what the [ __ ] And you know what? She
was crying over Bob all cuz I said yeah.
Oh, you're not going to find anyone like
as good as me. Like that's and I won't
even I wasn't even trying to be a
narcissist when I was saying that, bro.
And she I meant like as in somebody that
wouldn't do this and all of these things
that the people that you've been with.
Um that's what I meant. Not like
handsome and that. I didn't mean like
that. I meant like as in like someone
that would [ __ ] you over. And that was
the truth, bro. That was even me being a
narcissist. That was the truth, bro.
Yeah. You can't anymore. That's what I'm
saying, Bob. You can't. Years ago, you
could. Couple of years ago, you get
snogs, dates. You could get stuff now.
You can't get nothing.
I know you're taking a piss out of me. I
know you're taking a piss. But it's
true. It is the truth. It generally is.
It is generally the truth.
You notice it has gotten worse. It has
definitely gotten worse, bro.
But like I said, bro, if I went out and
I got a couple of numbers, I didn't
reply, I'd be like, "Okay, whatever."
It's the leading on, bro, that makes you
feel like [ __ ]
Cuz if people if people are lead like
the thing is yeah if people leading you
on you're starting to think oh this oh
that oh this oh that you understand
you're starting to like they're trying
to build hope they're trying to build
stairways up to heaven bro and then you
just get kic kick the [ __ ] down again
that's the worst thing bro like if
someone walks away they walk away or if
it doesn't go along that's what I'm
trying to like you will never really
understand it unless
um unless it happens basically.
So, oh, got a thing here.
And then what happens, Bob, is then you
start questioning yourself.
I don't know about you, but
I mean, I start questioning myself. Oh,
is it this? Oh, is it that?
Oh, what if I look better? Oh, what if I
look that? because they're saying that
because she was basically saying to me,
"Oh, yeah, you're you're good-looking
and stuff. There's nothing wrong with
the way that you look." So, you're
thinking, "Bro, if you're all these
things and I'm pretty much the same
heritage as these people that you've
been with in the past, what's the
problem then? What's what's the problem?"
You know, what what's the what's the business?
if they said, "Oh, I I like black
people." Okay, fair enough. You like
black people. Oh, I like I like white
people with blue eyes. Oh, okay. You
like white people with blue eyes. So,
this is what I'm trying to say. This is
all like game playing to make you feel
like [ __ ] Do you get what I'm saying?
They're just trying to make you feel
like [ __ ] I don't know how to explain
it, but yeah.
No, I'm just No, Dusty. I'm not talking
about that one. I'm talking about the
Christian one, bro. That was a That was
a proper pissake. No, that was worse,
bro. That one was worse. Way worse.
Because with with that one, bro, at
least with the the American one, you can
still say this is that this is why this
this is why that this person didn't live
in your country. If you actually look
back on it now, it's just what they did
wasn't very nice. But, you know,
no, that that one's worse, bro. That was worse.
But it still wasn't nice either way. But
no, that Christian one was worse than
the USA is now. That's probably the
worst I think.
That's the worst I think I've come across, bro.
Well, I don't want to make the other one
seem not as bad because it was still [ __ ] But
it was still [ __ ] It goes back to that
who are they to think that they don't
Oh, it's hard to explain it, bro. Like, yeah, pretty much.
Mixed messages, lad. Mixed messages.
That's all these people give is pe is
mixed messages. Then you're crying on
the voice though. Like you're the victim.
Bad. Bad. Bad. Bad. Bad.
It's [ __ ] up, lad. It's [ __ ] up.
You start losing hope in humanity, bro.
That's what you start doing. Losing hope in humanity.
That's all you do, bro. Yeah.
And then, like I said, when you hear
about some of these exes and what they do,
what the [ __ ] bro?
And you can tell they don't want a nice
person or a loyal person. You You know
they don't because if they did, they
would get with you. They'd give you a chance.
If they really wanted a lo a loyal
person, they would get with you. Sorry,
mate. You don't just get with someone
and they just cheat on you and have a
kid with someone.
I'm sorry, mate. Like, that just does
not happen. You know what I mean, bro? Like, so
it's pretty [ __ ] up. Pretty pretty
pretty bad, bro.
Yeah. And then she just turned out to be
a time wasting [ __ ] Bad bro. Mad
It's bad, is it, Stephen?
They can't be normal people, bro. They
can't be normal people.
That's that, you know.
So yeah, man.
They're sick in it. Sick.
Look at these people sick, lad. Yeah.
And she started being a [ __ ] I won't be
going out, lad.
Last time I went out, bro, I went into
the same bar I met Christian. Is he guy
was like, "Oh, um, yeah, can you change?
We don't allow tracksuits." And he was
proper trying to
intimidate me. No, I can't explain it.
Like, not intimidate. I don't think
that's the right word, but he was trying
to be like strict. I said, "Oh, okay. I
can change." Changed. Went back to the
bartender, bro. This black guy who was
just talking about stuff, bro. The guy
comes up and says, "Oh, yeah. You you're
banned on face recognition." What? For
for approaching three people months ago.
like proper trying to embarrass me and
[ __ ] So yeah, bro, [ __ ] that. I don't
know, man. But I don't really want to,
bro. To be honest with you, it's not
worth my time.
Oh, it's just not worth my time, lad.
You can't even approach people in places
without [ __ ] the risk of getting banned.
Um, so the the women are [ __ ] so I
mean the alcohol has a negative effect on you.
And I just don't really um see the point
in it, mate, to be honest.
Yeah. Serial cold approaching.
No, I only approached three people, bro.
It was three people, lad. It was months
ago. Months ago.
I think it was when I was back at the old house.
Maybe it was. I think it might have been
when I was back at I think it was. Yeah.
So, they want you to deal with [ __ ] women,
but then they don't even want to give
you the chance to find the a 1% person
that could be different.
This country just makes no sense at all,
does it? So, it's bad enough you got to
deal with [ __ ] ass women. 99.999999%
of them. And even if there's a small
bitty litty witty little chance that
there's someone that's not like that,
well, they're not going to let you meet
them because you get banned for [ __ ] approaching [ __ ]
What the [ __ ] bro? Seriously, I mean
Boy, that woman soon shut up when I was
talking about height, Grezy.
When she says, "Oh, it's bad to have a
boob preference." and I spoke about the
height preference and stuff. She didn't
know what to say
cuz it's the truth in it, Grezy.
People are not allowed a boob
preference, but you're allowed a you're
allowed a height preference.
Like, make it make sense, bro.
Men date below, women don't. remember that. And yeah,
but yeah, good luck in this day and age
finding someone greasy. You're going to
need it, lad. You're going to need it.
Yeah, but me having a boo preference is
probably is apparently the reason why
Christian Izzy done me over.
Just making stuff up. Just completely
making stuff up. We
Yeah, they definitely do.
Yeah, he does. Grieves. He does want someone
eventually he does. Of course he does.
He doesn't need someone, but I think he does want
No, I don't want a rel No, no, no,
Dusty. Dusty. No, I don't want a
relationship. Yeah, there's a big
difference. When I found someone Oh,
sorry. When I'm talking to someone who I
think is different, then obviously,
okay, I went out for a reason. If I met
someone then, you know, who I think's
normal, why why would why would I want
to see how it goes? I don't seek out for
stuff. I don't go out approaching.
Yeah, I moan about it when I've been
[ __ ] dead on for a month. Yeah, I
will moan about it cuz it's [ __ ] up.
Because all of it is [ __ ] up.
All of it is completely [ __ ] up.
The [ __ ] they do, the [ __ ] bar
management, the [ __ ] B, all of it's
[ __ ] up. All of it is so messed up.
It is. It is. It is. It is [ __ ] up,
lad. I don't go out approaching all the
time. Very, very rarely I go out.
I only drunk twice last week cuz I had
anxiety and stress and [ __ ]
I don't go out, bro. I'm not out today.
Why? I'm not out. I wasn't out
yesterday. Why? I've got the money
because I know it's always going to be
the same, lad.
But however, I went out don't approach.
If you're talking to someone who you
think is normal, well then yeah, it's a different story.
I don't put effort in. Dusty, I didn't
even get my haircut last time I went out.
I don't put effort in.
If I'm drinking, when I do and I see
someone, then I'll just go and do it in
it. [ __ ] it. I don't care.
I approached someone on [ __ ] Monday.
No, sorry. Wednesday. It weren't Monday.
It was Wednesday.
[ __ ] Yeah, I approached one person
Wednesday and that's it.
They are sick. Very, very sick.
That's what they are.
Like I said, it's fine if you don't know
anything about them.
It's completely fine, lad.
What they say they want is the opposite
to what they want. They don't want
normal, loyal people.
Trust me, they want abusive, drugdeing,
cheating bastards. That's what they
want. They don't want normal
for the most part.
Believe that, bro. Believe that.
They want the opposite of what they say
they want, lad. Cuz
how was your ex cheated on you and had a
child with someone?
Let me guess this [ __ ] started
off as a drug dealer. No, cuz there's
got to be more to it than that.
How do you always seem to make mistakes
with the same men? This is what I don't
understand. The same the same people, bro.
You know what I mean?
That is [ __ ] lad.
It's disgusting. But all of these things
that we list, all of these things,
you know, that we go on about, they're
just slaps in the faces.
That's what they are. They're just slaps
in the faces, bro.
Is that easy?
No, Christian Izzy is the worst, bro.
She's the worst.
She's, you know, I actually felt sorry
for her, you know, bro. I, you know, I
actually did I actually felt sorry for her.
But she obviously evidently seems to
like these people.
She evidence evidently seems to like
these people that do this.
So you should never feel sorry for like
women that have, you know, abusive exes
and stuff. They bring they like these
kind of people. I mean, there's people
that get with people whilst they're in prison, lad.
How are you explaining that one? Yeah.
Yeah. Like I said many times, false hope
is the worst, lad.
False hope is the worst.
That's how Isabelle started. But to be
fair, I can kind of blame YouTube for
the Izzy situation.
cuz people's messaging her and stuff.
So, we can't really we don't really know
how it would have ended if it wasn't for
YouTube. But these ones weren't because of YouTube.
You know what I'm saying? Let's be so
real right now, Grezy. These people
weren't YouTube. So, when you've always
always thought into your head, okay,
well, how about these people didn't know
about YouTube? How about these people on
YouTube never found these people? What
would have the [ __ ] result be? And it
would have been the same. Do you
understand? There's no YouTube to blame now, bro.
There's no YouTube to blame now, is there?
You know, at the end of the day, bro,
what's someone going to do? What's
someone going to say to me, bro?
What someone What is someone going to
try and say to a [ __ ] 28-year-old
man, bro, that's been up and down the
country deal that with thousands of
women over the past years? What is
someone really going to tell me?
You know, Damon always tells me that I
need to find God, bro. God ain't going
to tell me a damn thing. What could what
can God tell me, bro?
What could Allah tell me? Nothing. What
could What could they tell someone like
me, bro? Nothing.
You know, when it comes to this
had more women than you, Timmy, you're
still a virgin, lad. And that's the
funniest part about it. This also proves
I'm I'm biased.
This also proves I'm unbiased, lad. So,
what could [ __ ] what could what what
could Jesus Christ tell me? No offense.
Jesus can't even tell you nothing, bro.
That's how you know it's bad.
You know what I mean, bro?
No one's obsessing over lost women.
Greasy. We just don't like being led on,
lad. That's the difference. We just
don't like being led on. That's the big difference. Yeah.
So, yeah, bro. Like,
don't even know what you could say about it.
Yeah, Timmy, the only virgin is you,
lad. You've been on here for 15 years.
No one's ever seen you with a woman.
Nah, not even an insult, lad. It's just
facts. I know the truth hurts, bro. I
know the truth hurts, bro. But that's
just the way it is, man. I'd rather be
called an incel than be called a white
knight. However, but yeah,
an incel because they don't lick women's
asses. Do you want me to lie to you? I
can lie to you if you want me to. I can
tell you the truth.
At the end of the day, if the truth if
the truth makes someone an incel, then
you can keep calling me it, bro. But I'm
not going to sit here and lie to you.
Sorry, bro. I'm not a white knight. I'm
not a s.
I can't lie, bro. If you just, you know,
I've got every evidence to back up all
the stuff I say
about this person I'm speaking to right now.
That's why Triple H left.
Yeah, I'm a virgin, bro. Okay.
Jesus [ __ ] Christ, bro.
See, that's what I'm saying. If I knew
where some of these women lived, I would
grieve you. I hate to say it, bro, but I
might just go one of their doors, lad.
I'm not even joking, bro. I might I
might would have had to, bro.
I'm not I'll keep it real with you, bro.
I'll keep it real with you.
I'm actually I'm actually being real, bro.
Bro, I said half these [ __ ] are um mentally unstable.
Yeah, people know I'm a virgin.
Timmy, you you just look so stupid when
you say that. You do realize that when
you're saying that I'm a virgin. Do you
know how stupid you look?
You look so stupid.
I'm already asexual, bro. This wasn't
about sex. This wasn't about lust.
This is what I was trying to explain to
Gregy. This wasn't about sex. And this
wasn't about lust either.
It's about when you find if you meet
someone on stuff, [ __ ] you expect
them to do what they said that they were
going to do. Do you get it?
Just like when someone owes you money,
they say they're going to pay you money.
You expect them to give you the money to get it.
I'm pretty much already asexual anyways.
I don't have a sex drive, lad.
No baby hairs. So yeah,
[ __ ] mental, bro.
I don't find it funny though. Do I
agree? Is the dating game?
Nah, you know I don't. You It used to It
pisses me off and you know it does, bro.
I got three numbers. None of them
replied. I didn't give a [ __ ] bro.
I didn't care about it, lad.
Maybe you just want to find somebody
just to find somebody. Maybe you don't
care about sex. Maybe you don't care
about stuff like that. I didn't care about it.
I don't care about sex. I don't care
about any of that stuff, bro.
What if you just wanted to find someone
just for, you know, just to um
be with, bro, without that? But you
obviously clearly you can't. So
it's just abandoned, is it? You just get abandoned.
That's all that ever happens, bro. So,
but then when we call them evil, we're
incels. What are they then? What would
you like to call these people then?
Huh? What would you like to refer to
these people as?
people on the [ __ ] Reddit. Eh
Well, anyways, thank you whoever made
Tik Tok. Thank you whoever made Instagram.
You [ __ ] a lot of people's lives up.
You [ __ ] a lot of people's lives up, lad.
Thanks for that, matey.
I won't be live tomorrow. So,
we was just talking about [ __ ] Cory.
How [ __ ] evil they are, lad.
Like the [ __ ] they do, bro. It's sick.
was just saying that you should just go
gym and get money and that, bro, and leave
cuz these women are [ __ ] lad.
Really, really bad people, bro. Yep.
I can sleep now. Is it Greasy? Um Cory,
I can sleep now, bro. Past couple days
and that I weren't sleeping properly, lad.
It was taking me ages to go to sleep, man.
Stressed as [ __ ] bro. I was
No, I'm all right.
Yeah, it's gone down now, bro. It It's
just the whole date and stuff, bro. It
was stressful, man. People very people
underestimate how how stressful it actually is.
People underestimate how um stressful it is.
Yeah, I will do, bro. Don't worry, man.
I'm going have my steak tomorrow. Mama. M.
Do you want my opinion, Zippy?
Do you want my opinion, Zie? Uh. Uhhuh. Daryl [ __ ]
You want my opinion, Zippy?
Uhhuh. They're all [ __ ]
Oh, it's a banger, lad.
It's quite stressful, man.
Yeah, man. You can. No, Peter B can't
make content when Peter Benny's When
Peter Benny's stressed.
Man, I can't, bro.
What content you look after, lad? I
can't go out drinking
for my own mental sanity, lad.
You know what I mean? chaos.
Yeah. I'll go to Birmingham and knock him out. Yeah, man.
I want to go on just I want to go on
Timmy's door, bro.
That's what I want to do, bro.
I want to go on this cunt's [ __ ] door, mate.
We need to We need We need to play it
safe and steady, though, bro.
Yeah. I want to go on this cunt's door.
Trust me. Yeah.
be laughing it.
He won't tell me where he lives. I said,
"If you give me your I said if you give
me your address, I'll come and see you tomorrow."
I said, "I'll come and see you. I'll
come tomorrow." It
hard, bro, is it? Come on now.
I said I I will actually go on his door
tomorrow, bro. If he give if he gives me
his like address, I swear I won't dox
him, bro. I don't do that [ __ ] bro. I
don't dock people. I'll actually go on
the cunt's door, bro.
I'll buy a phone and I'll go live. I'll
just buy a phone and go live, lad. It's no problem.
So what you're saying is Timmy's got
anxiety. Steven Howard, is that what you're saying?
Uh yeah, I gambled. I won 20 pound on
the fog tea and then I've done some
football bets. I got let down by one team.
He wasn't taking the pitch. Yes, she was
taking a piss.
Oh. Oh, your grandma is one of the
reasons I don't want to date right now.
That's not taking a piss. Of course,
it's taking a piss. It's trolling.
No, no, no. Like I I know people hate to
believe this [ __ ] bro. But there are
these women that will do these things to
try to make people feel like [ __ ]
There are lad. That's an example. You know,
no, I wouldn't. No, there are women that
are that do do that, bro. They go, they
will do stuff to make people feel like [ __ ] So yeah.
No, I don't like
that LEG don't like that LEG. Sorry,
bro. I was typing something. Yeah. NG
You like that? Yeah.
No, not for me, lad. Yeah,
to be fair, it doesn't take much to be
the best looking on here, bro.
You know what I'm saying? [ __ ] hell.
You got a bad headache.
Why does it feel like [ __ ] bro?
I had a headache earlier. I just took
some pills, bro.
I was scared of the future. me.
If this is like this in 2026, then
[ __ ] hell, bro. Yeah,
it's quite scary, isn't it, mate?
Yeah, the future's scary, lad.
What the [ __ ]
One second. I'm drunk. One second.
Oh, Reddit's banned. Yeah.
All right, Ian. Will the dating game in
this country ever change, do you think?
But people on Reddit say that it's going
to change. Ian,
I was speaking to someone for a month.
Um Ian, they led me on and then when I
said, "Oh, let's meet." They started
making excuses and [ __ ] Ian,
shit's [ __ ] bro.
Shit's [ __ ] bro. Honestly, it's
People on Reddit say you'll meet someone.
Yeah. I don't know what what the problem is, Ian.
I look normal. I am normal. I don't know
what what the what the problem is, lad.
Why do I care? Cuz I don't like being
[ __ ] over, lad.
I don't care, bro.
They were laughing at you. [ __ ] you.
I love it, bro.
No, I'm not posting stuff on Reddit. I'm
messaging people. I don't post stuff on
Reddit. I just message people.
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro. That
Well, I don't get it. Takes them a while
to ban me, you know.
It takes them a while to ban me, lad.
These women are [ __ ] [ __ ] lad.
She doesn't know anything, lad. She
doesn't know anything.
She doesn't know anything, lad. So, she
doesn't have an opinion.
Oh, that Christian Izzy was a [ __ ] man.
Proper [ __ ] lad.
Well, I'm mockto now anyways, lad. I'm mockto,
if you know what that is.
If I knew where that Christian Izzy
lived, I'd go on a door, lad.
See, I'm that kind of [ __ ] that would do
it, bro. Like, I'm I'm not even joking,
bro. Like, workplace door.
I went on Isabelle's door.
I actually would do it, bro. That's the
thing. You don't I actually would do it,
though. That's the thing.
They did the worst type of [ __ ] I would
do it, bro. 100 100% I would do it, bro.
[ __ ] hell, man. Yeah,
I would do it. Be
I have done it, bro. I went on [ __ ]
Do you remember when I went on his door? Steven Howard.
Now ask her why she's leading people on
and giving people false hope and I've
got the messages to prove that. Yeah,
that's that's what I'd ask. Yeah.
And I'd ask why do you cry about your
why was you crying about your ex that
done X Y and Zed and asked why do you go
for the same X Y Z people just out of curiosity.
Yeah. Yeah. Those are the things. Yeah.
That's what I'll ask. Yeah. Yeah. Why do
you leave people on? Why do you play
games? Why do you use people of um why
do you use people as an emotional tampon?
No. Stop making excuses, lad. Stop
making excuses for them. They had no in
like I said, bro. Believe it or not,
believe it or not, try to imagine this,
bro. Some women are just out there to
[ __ ] with people just the way just the
way men are. I know it's hard to believe
cuz for some reason a lot of people
don't think people that's got a vagina
between their legs can do anything
wrong. But at the end of the day, lad
hope, but at the end of the day, um,
they're not innocent, lad. Hate to break
it to you, bro. Hate to be the bear of
the bad news, bro.
Big cheese. Listen, lad. You was the one
trolling Ant-Man. Yeah. 7 years ago,
Ant-Man went to the pub that you said
you'd meet him, and you didn't even turn
up, lad. Oh, anyone who doesn't know who
this big cheese is, this is the same guy
that was trolling Ant-Man. Now, you know
what I love? Yeah, bro. Yeah, this is
this is a prime example, right? Yeah. A
lot of people don't like Ant-Man. Yeah,
I get it. People don't like Ant-Man and
people can have their opinion on the on
the dude. That's fair enough. But look
at it, bro. Yeah, he he Look at him.
He's living in Thailand, bro. He done
something with his life, you know?
He he done something with his life, bro. Right.
You're still on YouTube trolling. You
was doing this to Ant-Man back when he
was 26. You sad [ __ ]
You were on Ant-Man's channel and you're
still doing the same thing. And my man's
living in Thailand now. Turn his life
around, bro. Does not even watch this
community anymore. Does that Does that
not give you [ __ ]
Does that not tell you something, lad?
If a weirdo, right, what you call him
has done that, what's your excuse?
You understand? What's your excuse? Hate
him, love him.
No, I'm not moving on about it, bro. I'm
not moving on about it. [ __ ] that, bro.
It's lucky I don't know where some of
these women live, bro. Trust me.
Cuz the point is, Stephen, now they
won't none of these women can lead you
on in real life. None of these women can
get lippy in real life.
You understand, bro? None of None of
them can, bro. None of them can.
And trust me, I will do it, bro. Trust
me. That's the thing. And I don't I
don't care who they live with. I don't
care what man they live with. You know,
you know what I mean, lad.
Man, you was [ __ ] with a bro.
How many people you Who are you [ __ ] with, lad?
You get me?
I just find it so funny how these women
go with these men that cheat on them.
How they end up right with the complete opposites
to what they say. That's what I find
funny, Stephen Howen. how they make the
same mistakes with with with the same end lad.
That's what makes me die, bro. That's
That's funny, bro. That's funny. That's funny, lad.
Then they moan and complain and winge.
That's what makes me laugh. They're absolutely
actually contradict themselves.
It's okay to like people, bro. Like that
do that stuff,
you know? It's okay. Like, you don't
need to you don't need to just say that
you like people that cheat. Just say
that you like people that sell drugs.
Like, no one's going to no one's going
to think think weird of it. But what
will think weird of it is when you say
people don't like these people, but you
end up with the same kind of person.
Think about it, bro.
[ __ ] off, bro. Yeah.
I hate talking about this, bro. It winds
me the [ __ ] up, lad.
I don't even know why I bring it up.
Yeah, this big cheese has been on
YouTube for years, lads. Years.
Yeah. All these women will do is
continuously seek out people to [ __ ] with.
That's what they do. They they they they
will get they will lead people on
for their own amusement. That's what they do.
And not one of these people are different.
Not one of them are different. And none
of them will ever be different.
And that's that, bro.
No, I wish Stephen Howard I never met
some of these women, lad.
I wish I never met some of these women, bro.
Seriously, bro. Like in the past. Yeah.
I wish I never wasted time. I wish I
never met some of these people. You know
that. Seriously, bro.
No, I'm not feeling sorry for myself.
I'm speaking facts, bro. I'm speaking actual facts.
It's not even feeling sorry for
yourself. It's talking the truth, lad.
And if you don't like the truth, lad.
Then that's on you, bro.
Yeah. Especially her, bro. She is a [ __ ] lad.
I'll bump into her again in central
London. Don't you worry, bro. I'll bump
into her again.
Trust me, it's a small world. I got a
friend that lives in Eden as well, bro. So, yeah.
Yeah. She's a nasty [ __ ] She's a nasty
Worse than USA is. I don't think you
could get worse than USA. Is he lad?
I don't think you can get worse, lad.
But there's always someone worse.
Yeah, there's always someone worse,
mate. There's always someone worse.
There's always someone worse, lad.
Yeah, there's always someone worse, bro.
You know, it's scary as you get older,
you know, bro. Yeah,
it's quite scary, bro.
And I never I never get anxiety, bro.
This is the maddest thing. These these
[ __ ] are big enough to trigger your
anxiety and [ __ ] bro. Yeah. Then [ __ ]
them, bro. Ain't it? If you know where
they live, you could just go on their
door, bro. Is it? [ __ ] it.
You know, they can trigger people's
anxiety and [ __ ] So, bro, like, but
face to face, they're not about it, bro.
Face to face, they're not about it.
Like, you don't understand. Like,
listen, bro. Yeah. It could be It could
be a grown man. It could be a boxer. It
could be anyone. No one's going to stop
me sticking it on a woman. Not one
person is going to stop me, bro. Yeah.
You should you should have just saw that
Arsenal Mark thing. I don't I don't care
if I'm going to lose, bro. Even if I'm
going to lose, I don't give a [ __ ] It's
like that Arsenal Mark thing. Do you
remember with Izzy? Yeah. When that
whole Arsenal Mark thing was going
around, Steven Howard back years ago
when I was younger. Um, this is my
opinion on Simpsons and White Knights.
And the thing is, lad, yeah. And the
thing is, right,
I didn't know, bro, what was going to
happen. You understand? I was in I was
in that park two times when this [ __ ]
didn't come out. I didn't even care,
bro. Do you understand? That's how much
I I don't like these white knights. I
don't like these simps,
you know? Like, do you get me?
Yeah. It doesn't matter what happened
with Timmy. Everyone knows what happened
with Timmy, bro. So what?
You know what I'm saying, bro? Like, [ __ ] me.
But if I knew where they lived, I would
if I knew how to get them, I would stalk them, bro.
Trust me, I would stalk them, bro. Trust
me. You don't know what I'm like. I
would. Yeah. And tell them about
themselves to their face.
Yeah. At the end of the day, bro, if you
don't want to talk to someone, whatever,
bro. Just don't walk away and that in it, bro.
Or just lock their lumber. You need
someone on, bro. That's
That's That's door type [ __ ] That's
going on someone's door type [ __ ] bro.
I don't care.
Yeah. Why did Timmy leave his cab as
well? His cab was down the road. I went
running up the road. He wasn't there.
Where was he, bro?
See, I thought I thought right by me
ignoring him, he would go away.
Then I thought, "Oh, shit."
Then he's on my he's he he's he's trying
to intimidate my mom. He's trying to
intimidate my mom. [ __ ] that. I went
first. I was straight in that black cab,
lad. Straight in that black cab.
No, he didn't pay for it. He bunked it.
Oh, that's the story as well with the
taxi. He bunked the taxi.
He bunkked the taxi. That's the story.
You see, he bunkked the taxi.
Yeah. I did nothing. I went back and he
ran into a field lad and I tried to meet
him several times after. Let's not twist
Let's not twist the narrative now. Yeah.
Yeah. Let's not twist the narrative,
Dusty. Cuz I was live when he was still
in the area. I was live in a pub that he
said he was in. Yeah. Let's not Let's
not start making up stuff now, lad.
Yeah. If you if you didn't run after 30
seconds, you would have known what would
have happened to you. If you didn't run
away after 30 seconds, you would have
known what would have happened. Simple.
You would have known what would have
happened, lad. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah. Okay.
You should be defending women anyways. Uh
and then who who's probably Terry? If if
someone wants to lead someone on, then
there's no whole bar. Simple.
If somebody wants to lead someone on,
then that's it.
[ __ ] them, bro. Is it?
Yeah, I hid him. I hid in my bedroom.
Okay, bro. Yeah. Yeah. I hid in my
bedroom. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Totally, bro.
Yeah. See, this is what I mean on this
community, Steven. They twist stuff.
They make up [ __ ] mad stuff, lad.
Yeah. It doesn't matter, lad. I I'll go
in your door. Well, no. It wasn't It
wasn't that she didn't want to talk.
That's not what started it.
She just didn't like the truth. It
wasn't even about talking. No, it wasn't
even about talking. And there that is a
big deal. And either way, either way it
is a big deal. Of course that's a big
deal, bro. You've had a whole month of
someone making you feel like [ __ ] Of
course that's a big [ __ ] deal. What
is a big deal in your eyes, lad? Tell me
what you think is a big deal in your
Come on, man.
What is a big deal in your eyes? And it
wasn't even just stop talking either.
That wasn't even that. But anyways, it
wasn't even that either way. Of course
that's a big deal, lad. Um, nothing
cuz I didn't believe he was actually
going to come.
And yes, it is a big deal when someone
is leading you on. Yes, it is a big
deal. And then she starts crying on voice notes
because I told the truth. Huh? [ __ ] off, man.
Yeah, cuz I started telling the truth,
bro. And then they started like
Yeah. Like, [ __ ] these [ __ ] bro.
[ __ ] them, bro.
You know, I swear to God, Stephen
Hardwood, bro, if I ever get a chance
again, I'm really going to do like these
people dirty, bro. Like, I'm really
really going to try to ruin one of these
people's lives, bro. If I ever get the
chance, you know, they're they're
turning me nasty now, bro. They're
actually turning me nasty.
They're actually turning me nasty now,
bro. You get me? Yeah.
And you know what I was going to do as
well with Timmy? If he didn't run across
that field, I was going to take his
phone off him as well, bro. Yeah.
You know what I mean? And
I I was going to take his [ __ ] phone
off him as well, bro, and smash it up.
I'm not even joking, bro. I swear to
God, I'm not even joking. And you know
when I told the cab driver the address,
it took them about a minute or two to
put it in. I said, "This is the address.
This is the address. Hurry up. Hurry up.
2 minutes." Bro, if they didn't take
that time, I would have bumped into him
100%, bro. I would have bumped into that
[ __ ] I told them address multiple
times. What the [ __ ] you waiting for?
You know what I mean, bro? So, yeah.
Okay then. Okay. Let me ask you this
So why was he not in the pub when I was
in the pub when they told me? Didn't you
people tell me to go to that pub? I went
to the pub and he wasn't there. Where was he?
One second. One second. One second. You
lot told me to go to that Weather
Spoons. When I was in the Weather
Spoons, where was he when I was live? Go
on. Go on. You told me to go there. So,
where was he? You know
where where where was he, lad? Where was
he? You lot told me to go to the pub. I
got the Uber to the pub. Where was he?
Where was he then? Where was he?
You know what I mean, lad?
hiding in a bedroom was not hiding in no
bedroom, big cheese. You're the one that
didn't shop for Ant-Man, lad. So, we
talk about how you were supposed to meet
Ant-Man in a pub and you bottled it. You
little [ __ ] house. I wasn't even in the
[ __ ] house and I've already proven
that. So, stop trying to reverse the
psychology. Secondly, you you you
bro his obligation. He got bullied by
the neighbor, bro, and ran into a field.
Yeah. Everybody, everybody saw it.
Yeah. Yeah. Anyways, bro, wasn't you
supposed to be Ant-Man, Big Cheese? Do
you want me to pull the video back up?
You little [ __ ] house.
No [ __ ] else, bro.
Yeah. And no, it won't end. Even if I go
to Birmingham, it won't end. Stephen
Howard, even if I go to Birmingham
tomorrow, the whole thing will just
start all over again.
That's why I don't Why do you think I
haven't gone, bro?
Why do you think I haven't gone?
Yeah. Funny how my mom was waiting for
him at the door. Maybe because she was watching LJ
and she was watching the whole thing.
You [ __ ] cuz she subscribed to LJ.
No, no, no, no. But no, no, no, no. But
Job is biased.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. There's a
few people on here that are biased. Joe, Nunchle Legs,
um, yeah, [ __ ] Red Star, LT. No, no,
no. There's a few people that are
biased. They started coming out with
their excuses the other day as well.
So, no, there were definitely people on
here that were biased, lad. People were
saying, "Oh, I'm quick enough to go back
for Timmy, but not LT." But hold on. You
said that Timmy beat me. So, which one
is it? What's going to happen? I tell
you exactly what's going to happen if if
I go to Birmingham, Steven Howard. I
will I will lock this [ __ ] out. Trust
me, he won't beat me, bro. Trust me, he
will not beat me. Yeah. So, I'm going to
go there or let's just say it draws or
whatever, right? And what's going to
happen is I'm going to come back. London
Taylor's going to start his [ __ ]
Timmy's going to start his [ __ ] again.
And then it's just going to go round and
round and round and round in circles.
That's what's going to happen. That's
why, bro, there's no point. There
generally is no point, lad. And that's
not even excuses. Trust me.
Trust me, bro. That's not even a joke,
bro. and London Taylor will get involved
somewhere along the line. Bet, bro. Bet.
I'm telling you.
100%, bro. 100%.
You get me, bro. So,
hate to say it, bro, but that's what
will happen. So, that that's not even
excuses, bro. I'm not even using that as
an excuse. I'm being bro. Seriously, it will.
Trust me, Timmy. I was seconds away from
you, lad. seconds away from you.
Seconds seconds away from you, lad.
You was going to get smashed up, bro.
It's not even a joke. I was going to
take your phone as well.
I was going to smash you up, bro. I take your phone.
Absolutely. Send it,
bro. I'm done with the dating, lad.
If you're talking about dating, I'm done
with it, lad.
Oh, I thought you meant with the dating, bro.
This dating things gave me um bad
anxiety for over the past week, lad.
And Peter Benny never gets anxiety, matey.
Bad, bro. Bad. [ __ ] the dating game,
man. I'm not sending nothing, bro.
[ __ ] that, bro.
Yeah. Okay, Lesie, you keep telling yourself that.
You know, as you get older, Stephen, how
would you realize you can't trust people?
You actually realize you can't trust people.
So Timmy said, "Fuck off, you naunt."
And then Timmy started running. That's a
true story, by the way. Not not [ __ ] lad.
Bro, they're [ __ ] [ __ ] you know.
You know what I think I would do now? If
I actually met a woman Ian, I think I
would just rob them.
You know what, bro? I actually think I
would do him one bad, bro. I'm not even joking.
I think I would actually just rob them
and [ __ ] them over Royale, bro. At this
point in my life, bro, for all this [ __ ]
that they've given me over the years, I
think I would just do it. I actually
genuinely think I would go down that
route, lad. I'm not even joking, bro.
Just like actually just [ __ ] them
royally over, bro. And I'm not even
joking. I swear to God I would, bro.
Yeah, they deserve it, bro. They're
[ __ ] scum of the earth, bro. Hey,
bro. They're [ __ ] They're [ __ ] little [ __ ]
Well, he [ __ ] was scared, mate. He
[ __ ] was scared cuz he soon [ __ ]
off and ditched the cab, didn't he?
But yeah, as you get older, you realize
you can't trust people. Um, Steven, like
me, bro, I hate people.
The only people I speak to is my mom, Ant-Man,
and sometimes a couple of people that
I've known for before. Like, I try to
stay away from people, bro.
This guy still owes me [ __ ] money. Like, h
what I'm saying, bro? Like, it's I
[ __ ] I I grew to hate people as I got
older, lad. As I got older, I did, bro.
I'm not even joking.
You start seeing people's true colors.
You don't see it at first.
You don't see it at first, lad.
But I I realized it. I realized it.
women even like some family member like
people in general. Yeah.
I just really hate people, bro. Like, I can't lie.
So I would actually [ __ ] someone over that.
I know he that's the only reason he went. Yeah.
I know that, bro. I know that. You know
Like I've got tenants. You know the
tenants that I used to rent the rooms
to? They live in Birmingham. They said I
can go over anytime. I can stay there a
couple of nights. They'll pick me up.
Like they said you can come anytime.
They don't know about this Timmy thing.
So I could easily go there, bro. Easily.
I have to pay for hotels. But I know
exactly what it's going to be.
That's the thing. I know. I know exactly
what it's going to be, bro. That's the thing.
I know exactly where it will