[sighs] Yo, bro.
Yeah, that's boring to be honest, bro. I
kind of woke up late to be honest.
What a boring Sunday. A boring Sunday,
bro. What a boring life, lad. Not a
boring Sunday. What a boring life.
I woke up in a vulgar mood.
No, that's a mistake later. Yeah. [ __ ]
Just chilling, bro.
That's what's going on. Just chilling.
Yeah, nothing much. We're just chilling.
No, I'm not joining monies, lad.
I can't be bothered, bro, with the drama
and that, bro. [ __ ] that. >> Yeah.
Had a stupid westernized [ __ ] [ __ ]
women woman dusty on Reddit say, "Bro,"
I said, "Listen, I'm not your bro."
Yeah. Don't try and talk to other people
about grammar when you're using the word bro lad. [ __ ] off.
Stop using Tik Tok. You westernized
[ __ ] That's what I said to him. You
[ __ ] westernized little [ __ ]
I'm going to tell you the west the rest
of what I said to her, bro.
[ __ ] burn it. Yeah, bro. Yeah. Do
Yeah. No, I'm not arguing, bro. Oh,
nah, bro. I'm just chilling, man.
I'm just chilling, lad.
I'd love to know where some of these
women lived up there. I'd love to know
where some of these [ __ ] live. Lad
banging on their door, bro. Do the Do
the frown upon thing. Do you get me?
Trust me, bro. Do the frown upon thing. Yeah.
Just chilling, bro.
Just hit him. [ __ ] bro.
Why do people on Reddit still keep
telling you you're going to find someone?
I thought, bro, you could be like six
day on your deathbed and they'd still be
telling you exactly the same [ __ ] thing, bro.
Telling you the same [ __ ] thing.
Like, do they just get like joys out
like knocking people or something? Nothing.
>> 14, 16, 18, 20, 21, 22, 25, 28, [ __ ]
30, 32, 34, 35. Bro, every time your age
goes up, bro, they'll be telling you the
same thing, bro. When you was a nipper,
they'd be telling you the exactly the
same thing, bro.
Is is is Okay. Okay. Put it this way. Is
is Tik Tok all of a sudden going to get
banned? Is Instagram going to get
banned? Are smartphones going to get
banned? No, they're not going to get
banned. These things are not going to
get banned. So, if they're not going to
get banned, how could it change?
If social media, right, well, these
certain apps are never going to stop.
They're never going to get banned.
Then how how is it going to change?
Like, how how how
So what I'm going to start doing, you
I'm going to start going out and [ __ ]
with people, bro. Yeah. You think I'm a
troll? I'm not trolling. I'm not
trolling, mate. Yeah. I'm I'm gonna I'm
just going to go out and just start
[ __ ] with people, bro. That's what
I'm That's what I'm going to start do.
Just going just going out and [ __ ]
with people for a lot. Yeah. Deadly
serious, bro. Deadly serious. You can
say that people are trolling. No, I'm
not trolling. No, I'm [ __ ] not
trolling at all.
I'm not trolling. You think everyone's
trolling, don't you, bro? All the time.
Yeah. You think everyone's trolling all
the time? I just going to start [ __ ]
with people, bro. Like, it's like a
drunk vlog. Yeah. Just start [ __ ]
with people. Seriously. Yeah. No. No.
No. No. Seriously. Seriously. Seriously, I will.
Seriously, lad. Seriously. Seriously.
Seriously. Seriously. I should have went
out yesterday to be honest with you. I
should have went out yesterday, but I
just couldn't be bothered. You know,
I might just steal someone's phone, be a
thug. That's what I might do. I might
just I might just approach someone and
steal someone's phone. I might just
start being a [ __ ] You know what I'm
saying, bro? Just like start going
around being a [ __ ] You might get more
respect for it. You might get more
respect for it, lad.
No, no, no. Seriously, you might
actually get more respect for it.
To be fair, thinking of it. No, I'm
being ser I'm being deadly serious.
No, I wasn't even nice to them. Anyways,
I [ __ ] hate them, bro. I [ __ ] hate
them [ __ ] [ __ ] I hate them little
you know? I'm not going to say what I
want to say. Obviously, bro, but I can
say it on different platforms. You know
what I mean? Not even that, bro. Not
even that, lad. The past few times I
went out, I went out for a reason, lad.
And it wasn't for [ __ ] them.
They're actual scum in the earth, bro.
They actually deserve They deserve every
They deserve every bad thing that
happens to them in the world. Every bad
thing that happens, bro. They deserve it.
They actually deserve it, lad. Like, I'm
not even joking, bro. Like, I'm actually
being deadly serious, lads. They
actually deserve every bad thing in the
world that happens to them. Every single
damn and last one of them. Every single
bad damn and last one of them. Like Yeah. 100%.
Every single one of them.
Every all. All because I know people
don't like the word all when you're
talking about it. Yeah. All of them.
You get me, lad?
Every single last one of them.
Do you understand? Simple.
They only started being [ __ ] in the 2000s.
Do you don't believe me, bro? like me
know like where people work and stuff. I
would go to their workplace, bro. I've
done it once. I'd do it again. And I've
also gone to where people have lived as
well. I don't give a [ __ ] Flying [ __ ] bro.
I don't give a flying [ __ ] UK asylum.
What What's the worst that can happen
that [ __ ] someone's someone's going
to get involved? Oh. Oh, well, it's me
or them, is it? It's me or them.
So, that's that. It's either me or them, lad. Simple.
Oh well, [ __ ] happens in it in this
life. You don't you die one way anyways,
isn't it? So that's that.
The update is I've not touched it.
There's not going to be no update.
I just bought the [ __ ] for the figures. Yeah.
>> [clears throat]
>> Oh yeah.
No, seriously, bro. I would. I don't
give a [ __ ] if it's a woman. So, you
think just cuz it's a woman, you're not
going to go on their door? No. Go on
their door every day, bro. Every day
I'll be a stalking little bastard. I'll
be a little pest. That's what I'll do.
I'll be a little pest like from pest control.
You ever played Runescape? You ever see
that thing called pest control? I'll be
the biggest stalking pest weirdo going.
I know White Knight and Synth is going
to do a damn thing about it, bro. They
have They'd have to kill me. Yeah,
they'd have to [ __ ] I'd be a dirty,
stinky pest. That's what I would do. Yeah.
I'm trying to find out if I can try and
find this person's area from what
they've sent me, what they've sent me,
and what they've shown me. But I'm
trying to see if I can find out.
I've seen the McDonald's they go to. So,
if I can find the McDonald's that they
go to, um, and if it is that McDonald's,
I I can link it to the train station,
link it to the bus stop, and try and
catch them slipping, bro. I don't give a
[ __ ] I'll go all the way to I'll go all
the way to West London, bro. I don't
give a [ __ ] Trust me. One second.
Yeah, bro. So if if that is the
McDonald's, I need to look up that McDonald's.
And if it is the McDonald's, then I'll
just I'll just start stalking him, bro.
Like Yeah. Simple.
I'll just start I'll just start talking.
I'll just start stalking him. Yeah.
Trust me, I'd smash her in her face as
well. That's what I do as well. Smash
the [ __ ] in her [ __ ] face, lad. If I
knew where this [ __ ] lived, I' i'd just
go and smash her in her face.
Trust me, bro. Yeah. That's not the
right attitude to have. That's the
attitude I have. I like that attitude. I
I like the attitude. I like an attitude.
G, I should have went out yesterday,
bro, and caused a madness.
Seriously, I should have went out
yesterday and called an absolute caused
an absolute madness, bro.
To be fair, I should have
like causing absolute madness,
but I just couldn't be bothered, bro, to be honest.
But if I thought about causing madness
yesterday, I would have went out, bro.
An absolute madness.
Yeah, trust me. You know there's going
to be a madness when Peter Belly's in town.
I start being homophobic. I'll start
being a [ __ ] Oh, just all the [ __ ] that
these women have gave me over the years,
all the bad experiences these little
[ __ ] have gave me over the years. Go
back into that place. Stop being homophobic.
And I don't care if I get nicked. I
don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah. Trust me.
Trust me, bro. Trust me. You You know
when you've had enough. You will know
when you've had enough, mate. Trust me.
Everyone's got Everyone's got different
like um everyone's got different um
you know, limits, you know. Everyone's
got different limits. You trust me. You
know when you've had enough. Trust me.
You know when you've had enough. Like trust me. That's it.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, they can't put him in his face,
bro. He's probably a mad bastard.
That's why That's why no one put That's
why no one puts him in his face, bro.
Cuz they know he's a mad bastard. >> Yeah. [clears throat]
Let me try and look up that McDonald's.
See where that is, bro. [clears throat]
I see where that [ __ ] McDonald's is,
bro. That's why I need to see where that
McDonald I would just start stalking the [ __ ]
That's what I would just I would just
stop me in a dirty stinky little
stalker. Trust me. Yeah.
I'll get a camping bag and just camp out there. Yeah.
What is it? Why have I got you looking at me?
>> There's nothing all of this. Why are you
look Why are you looking at me?
>> You're staring at me. [snorts]
You're just staring at me, mate. It's
[ __ ] quite weird, you know. >> [snorts]
>> No, you're just staring at me. I don't
know what what you're staring at me for.
>> I don't get in your face,
>> you know.
I [ __ ] will be. I will be [ __ ] going elsewhere.
Isn't that right, Grezy? I [ __ ] will
be. Damn right.
Damn right, Grizzy.
Yeah, I [ __ ] will be damn right.
Yeah, I [snorts] am Dusty. No one's
going to do anything about it either.
I'm going to look up this McDonald's in
a bit anyways and I'm going to try to
track like where trying to track their
steps. Trust me, bro. Trust me. Trust
me. I'll find this little [ __ ] bro. I
will find this little [ __ ]
I will find this little [ __ ] bro. Trust me. Yeah.
Let's see if any everyone any anyone's
got the same energy in person. Let's see
if they've got the same energy in person.
Some give it a good game, bro. But they
don't. They give it some might give it a good game, you know.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, they're not getting away, bro. I
will catch him, bro. Trust me, I will catch them.
Trust me, I will.
Where is this? Trust me, I will catch them.
Trust me, I will catch the [ __ ] Yeah.
And it's going to be worse than It's
going to be worse than It's going to
It's going to be worse than someone
cheating on you and having a kid with
someone else. It's going to be a lot
worse than that, Dusty. It's going to be
a lot worse than that. I I I'll You can
add You can add You can add another
negative experience to your collection.
You can add another bad experience to your collection.
You can have a worse experience. You'll
never forget me. How about that one?
[snorts] Yeah. How about that one?
No. Chilling, bro. I'm going to try and
track down this person. See, see their
steps and that. And
I'm trying to find them. No, I'm not
moving on. No way am I moving on. [ __ ]
this, bro. These people have tried to
take the piss out of me for way too long
now, bro. way way way way too long. Way
way way way too long now, bro. Yeah. Way too long.
They've been doing it way too long.
[snorts] Trust me, bro. To to to last me
a [ __ ] lifetime. Yeah.
Long enough to last me a [ __ ]
lifetime, lad. Yeah.
Trust me, bro. Trust me. Trust me.
They shouldn't get away with with what
they've done. They shouldn't get away
with their actions, bro. Do you
understand? I don't care. No one's
moving on. I'm not moving on from
nothing. Simple. They need to pay for
their actions just the same as I would
have to pay for my actions. It's as
simple as that.
That is it is as simple as that.
Someone on Reddit said that's not the
right attitude to have. I said it
[ __ ] well is a right attitude to
have. It's a lovely attitude to have.
It's a lovely attitude to have, lad.
You know, it's a lovely, lovely attitude
to have. I love it. Same as Grievy as
well. He loves it, too. We all love it.
Let me make you feel like [ __ ] in your
face. Let me come to your Let me come to
you and make you feel like [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? That's my
whole argument. Okay, fair enough. Let
me come and make you feel like [ __ ] to
your face. How about that one? You can
bring whoever you want. Any man you
want, cuz you know my opinions on white
knives. Let me let me make you feel [ __ ]
to your face.
Let me do it, man. Let me do it. Come
on. Come on. Give me that chance. Come
Absolutely. Come on.
No. Just we just trying to find a way to
get back at these women. Dr. Echo
just trying to find about trying to
trace this person's where they living at
or where they hang out basically or
where I can catch them.
I want a mad one, bro. I'm a mad one,
bro. Trust me. I want to make them feel that [ __ ]
I want to make them feel like [ __ ] I
want to I want to nick their phone as
well. I want to nick their phone and put
it down the drain, bro. Yeah, that's
what I want to do. A bit like how these
people try to cause misery in your life,
you cause misery in their life. It's as
simple as that.
Yeah. Nick their phone. That's what you
know, Steven would love that little
word, you know, Nick. It's the truth,
isn't it? It's the truth. Yeah.
street robbery. I don't think so, lad. I
don't think you're going to go to jail
for [ __ ] someone's phone.
And even if you did, I generally don't care.
I generally generally wouldn't even care.
Yeah. Okay. I'm not going to do
anything, bro. Like I didn't go on
Izzy's door. Like I didn't go to Kenji's
workplace. Yeah. I never I won't do
anything, bro. Just like I didn't stick
it in front of a woman in Weather
Spoons. Okay, bro. Just like I didn't
stick on a woman last Monday. Nah. No,
no, no, no, no. I don't do anything. Me, bro. N.
Yeah. No. No. No. No. I never do anything.
No. No. No. I never do anything, bro.
Me. N. Not me, man. Not me. Nah. Come
on, bro. Stop it now. Stop it now. Every
single encounter I've had with a woman,
I've told them about themselves. Even
Even when I pull it on YouTube as well,
I've put it on YouTube. I've told them
about themselves multiple times. I've
gone on one of their doors. Yeah. Made
them [ __ ] themselves. Get the police
involved. Let's not go down memory lane now, bro.
Let's not Let's not go Let's not go down
that uh Let's not go down that uh Let's
not go down that um that that road, lad.
Yeah, you can send it to the police all
you want, lad. No one cares.
Okay, good for you. See you later.
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] about the
police, bro. Oh my god. Nobody cares
about the police. You get mad, lad.
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] And I don't
have no court case either. But anyways. Yeah.
Yeah, that's that stupid Birmingham
[ __ ] is it, Dusty? Well, it might not
be the same one, but yeah,
that little [ __ ] that that the one
that lives in Birmingham. That Canadian
one. That little white knight. He's
another little white knight. Yeah, he
can slag me off all he wants, lad. I
don't care. He can slag me off all he
wants. I don't care. [snorts]
Yeah, he can slag me off all he wants,
mate. I really don't care, lad.
That's good, man.
Brilliant stuff, bro. Brilliant stuff.
Let me see.
Yeah, I don't care what he says, bro. I
really don't give a [ __ ] what he says. [sighs]
Honestly, I don't care what he says.
That's nice, bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying, Grezy?
Everybody knows that you're a crazy [ __ ]
Is that right, Ruby? Everybody knows
take your bro crazy [ __ ] Yeah, trust
me, I can get crazier, bro. Trust me, I
can get [ __ ] crazier. Yeah, I can get
crazier. I got a friend that lives in
Rein anyways, bro. So, I'll go and see him.
Um, I'll go and see him basically after.
Um, I'll do what I got to do, bro. Ain't
it simple? Well, so be it, lad. So be it.
So yeah, these [ __ ] need to pay, Dusty,
for all the [ __ ] that they all the
misery and [ __ ] that they've caused me
over the years. They really need to pay,
bro. They really need to pay.
Trust me. Trust me. They do need to pay.
I'm going out next week, lad. Watch. I'm
going out next week. You watch. What's
day today? Sunday [ __ ] today. Watch.
I'll be going out Thursday, lad.
Yeah. Oh, Wednesday. You watch. I'm
going to cause a [ __ ] madness, bro. >> [snorts]
>> I'm going to call I'm going to go back
to that place and and pick on that guy
for being gay,
right? I'm going to pick on him for
being a little dick sucker. And ain't no
one going to do a damn thing about it,
bro. And no one's going to do a damn
thing about it, bro.
Trust me. Watch. I'm I'll get nasty,
bro. Trust me. I'll get nasty. I'll get
really nasty, bro. Trust me. Yeah.
And that's what happens. These people
create a monster. Monsters are created
just like bears. Bears are created.
Yeah. Do you get me, lad? I don't give a
[ __ ] I'm the only one that's going to
be doing something about it. I'm the
only I'm not on bail, but okay. Uh
firstly, I'm not on bail, but okay. Um I
I that's not I I know I'm not the only
one, but I'm the I'm the only one that's
going to be doing something about it.
Simple. Simple as that. I'll be I'm
going to be the only one doing something about it.
Yeah. Monsters are created. Have you
ever heard Have you ever heard a saying
being cremated? Um being create a
monster being created.
Yeah, they they create monsters, lad.
They create monsters. They're [ __ ]
evil scum of the earth. And guess what,
bro? If any white knight and simps got
anything to say about it, they'll have
their say on Thursday, won't they?
They'll have their little say on Thursday. Simple,
lad. Simple. Yeah.
Cuz no one else is going to do it, are
they? So, I'm the one that's going to
have to do it. And what I'm going to do
as well, Greavvesy, I'm going to try as
well, lad. I'm going to try I'm going to
try to I'm going to what I'm going to
do, I'm going to be so narcissistic.
This is what I'm going to do, bro. Yeah,
they can protect all they want. They'll
get their face smashed in.
The boozers, they're not going to know
where I am. They're not going to know
what boozers I'm in. What I'm going to
do, I'm going to be so narcissistic,
bro. I'm going to approach about 100
people that day and I'm going to I'm
going to [ __ ] their life up, bro. That's
what I'm going to do. If one of them
meets me again, bro, trust me, I will
[ __ ] their life up. Trust me, I will. I
will. I'll give them a taste of their
own medicine, lad. Yeah.
Yeah, they can protect females, but I'll
just spit in their face. Yeah, they can
they can protect them, but I'll spit in
their face. If they think they're going
to show up in front of a woman to me,
I'll just spit in their face and throw a
drink all over them. So, at the end of
the day, bro, we will see, won't we?
You're not going to be protecting no
female in front of me, mate. You're not
going to be protecting no female in
front of me, mate. Cuz even if I need to
smash that glass over someone's neck,
you're not going to be protecting no
female in front of me. Trust me.
Trust me. You're not going to be you're
not going to be protecting no female in
front of me. You're not going to be no
calming down no situation in front of me
either. Yeah. That's that's something
that you're not going to be doing, bro.
Yeah. Don't forget, we're in an
establishment where there's glasses,
lad. Yeah. And if I need to defend
myself, I will I will defend myself.
I will break that glass and and and slam
it in their neck. Trust me, bro. Trust
me. You know how I feel about white
knights and simps and people defending
women. You know my opinions on it, bro.
And you already know what I'm like. I'm
going to be doing it the whole day on
Thursday anyways. Oh, they will allow
it, mate. They will allow it. Just like
they allowed it in the Weber Spoons just
like they allowed it out. They allowed
it outside when I told their women to
[ __ ] off and they done nothing about it.
This when I told their their women in
front of their men to [ __ ] off and they
couldn't even stand up. So, they will do
something about it.
You know, they they [ __ ] wouldn't.
Yeah. Okay, whatever, bro. Well, you'll
see all about it then, won't you?
Wednesday and f Wednesday or Thursday.
Probably Thursday, to be honest. Well,
you'll see all about it Thursday, then,
won't you? You will see what I'm not
about on Thursday.
You will see what I'm about on Thursday,
then, won't you?
I wants to get involved. Yeah. Okay.
I'll be in no show. Whatever, lad. Okay.
Like, I've not stuck. A lot of you
people in this community have got
selective memory. How many women have I
stuck it on? I've stuck it on women in
front of men. They ain't done nothing.
Multiple multiple times. Oh, they will
allow it. They'll have no choice. But if
they know what's good for them, they
will allow it. If they know what's good
for it for them. If these men know
what's good for them. Oh, they will allow
on Thursday. Anyways, lad. Bro, you can
doubt you can doubt me all you want.
Like I said, the you people in this
community's got selective memory, lad.
You people have got you people have got
selective memory, lad. So that's fine,
lad. You can say whatever you want, bro.
You people, you people. You people have
got selective memory, lad. You can say
what you want, bro. It's not going to
wind me up,
you know. Oh, yes. I'll be bullying
women on Thursday. I'll 100% be bullying
females in front of men as well. I'll be
doing it in front of men as well. If
they want to get involved, I'll be doing
it in front of them. Trust me, lad.
Yeah. I'm going to just nick someone's
phone as well.
Because I can, Leslie. Because I want to
and I can. Just like how you people have
got selective memory. Because I can and
I'll do what I want. Well, they Well,
they will allow me. They Well, they've
allowed me to do it in the past, Dusty.
They let me in the They allowed me in
the Weather Spoons. They allowed me to
speak to their women like that. They
They've allowed me in the past. I mean,
they people have allowed me in the past.
They allowed me on Monday. I mean, every
time I've stuck on a woman, these men
have allowed me in the past because
they've had no choice because they know
what's good for them. These people are
not stupid, bro. These people are not
stupid. They know what's good for them.
They know their targets. Trust me, they
know that I can speak to a woman how I
want and ain't no man going to stop
nothing when I'm around, lad.
Anyways, we're not going to get into
this cuz I know what you're trying to
do. It's not going to work. I'll be out
Thursday. I'll be doing a madness and
that's it. I know what you're trying to
do now. That's not going to work. But a
good try though, bro. Is it cuz you know
that I'm wound up. You know that I'm
wound up. You know that I'm wound up, bro. Yeah.
You know that I'm wound up, lad. Like he
obviously you know that I'm wound up. I
know what you're trying to do, bro. It's
it's it's a smart move, lad. It's a
smart Yeah, it's a smart move, lad.
It's a smart move, lad. You know, but
it's not going to work, bro. It's It's
not going to work. Trust me, I know what
I'll be doing on Thursday. You don't
need to worry about that, lad.
I already let the gay guy keep me out of
the spoons. Uh, firstly, no gay guy
kicked me out of anywhere and it wasn't
the spoons. But anyways, lad, you're not
going to get what you want. Nice try,
though, bro. Nice try, lad. Nice try.
It's not going to work. [snorts]
You know, I don't need to do I'll do
what I want, lad. I will do what I want.
That's the thing. I will do what I
[ __ ] want, lad.
I will do what I want. It's as simple as
that. You don't tell me who I can meet,
who I can't meet. No. No. No. No. No.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. Bro.
Nah, bro. [ __ ] that. Absolutely [ __ ]
that. They're big enough to play games.
They're big enough to [ __ ] with people.
They're big enough to try to cause
misery in people's lives. I'm doing I'm
doing the world a favor by doing this,
bro. I'm literally doing the world.
We've already been over this Timmy
thing, lad. I'm not going over it again.
Simple. So, I'm actually doing God's work, lad.
Yes. I'm like, well, we've already been
over this, lad. I'm not going over this
again. and it's not going to work. But
yeah, um we will see on Thursday anyways.
Yeah. Anyways, we will see on Thursday anyways, bro.
They're not big enough though. Really
greasy. Do you remember Do you remember
what I told you about in Waxies last
Monday? I said, "Come outside then." I
said, "Come outside then. Come on. Away
from these people, bro. Their jaw
dropped, bro. Their their jaw [ __ ]
dropped, lad. It's not even It's not
even a joke, bro. Their jaw [ __ ] dropped.
She said, "Oh, I can start getting
rude." I said, "Oh, really? Let's let's
let's hear it outside. Come on. Let's
get away from these people. Let's let's
hear how rude you are outside." And her
jaw dropped, mate. Yeah. You [ __ ]
little [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah. You're not even
You're not even big enough to do it in a
public land allowed outside. I would
have spot that [ __ ] out in front of any
man, bro. It's not even a joke. Trust
me. I would have spot that woman out in
front of any man while smiling about it
with my teeth. Trust me, bro. You don't
know how nasty and dirty I can get. I
can get really nasty, really dirty, bro.
Trust me. And And you don't even need to
be You don't even need to be a strong
person to be like this.
Yeah. Trust me, bro. Trust me. You don't
even need to be about it, bro. Anyone
can be like this. They don't have to be
strong. They don't have to be weak. They
can be anything.
Trust me, lad. I said, "Come outside
then." I said, "If you want to get rude,
I love that energy." Know that's nice.
Come outside. I said, "Now [ __ ] off."
That's what I said. And I went back to
the bar, tried to walk past me, didn't
say nothing. I said, "No, [ __ ] off."
Didn't even say anything back. Think
you're going to get rude to me cuz
there's a bunch of white knights here.
Let's go outside. When someone finally,
if someone has the balls to do this when
they're not with men, fair enough, bro.
I I rate it. I actually rate it, bro.
Like credit where credit is due. If you
want to start running up your mouth.
Yeah. And and you're and you're and
you're not in front of and you're not in
front of men. I rate it, bro. I I
respect it. But you can't do that. And
you know you can't do that. You know,
you know you get told about yourself.
Even in front of men, you'll get told about yourself.
You know what I'm saying, lad?
Yeah. Just know men. Like I said, Chico,
selective memory with you people.
Like I said, selective memory is a is is
is is a real thing. Selective memory,
which is what you people have got in this community.
We don't need to go over all of the
examples again. You know exactly who
what men have stuck it on many, many,
many, many times.
So that's that. Yeah. Well, we'll see
you on Thursday then, won't we, Dusty?
Well, lad, we'll see you on Thursday.
Never you mind, bro?
Oh, because of that Christian Izzy one,
bro. Because of that Christian Izzy one.
And trust me, after I'm done in central
London, I'll be going West London, bro.
I'll be going to England. Don't you
worry about that, lad. Don't you worry.
I'm never ever going to stop. Trust me.
I'm never going to stop now, bro. I'm
never ever ever going to stop.
Trust me. Trust me. I'm never ever going
to stop, lad. [gasps]
Trust me. Trust me. I'm never ever ever
ever going to stop.
Trust me, I'm worse, bro. I'm I'm I'm
I'm [ __ ] worse than any [ __ ] on here,
bro. Trust me, I'm worse than any [ __ ]
on here. And if any man thinks he's
going to get involved, then he's going
to get slapped in it. Simple. He's going
to get slapped in he
tell your uncle as well. Listen, you
know what I'm going to say to my friend?
Yeah. This uncle. This uncle. Yeah. This
uncle right of him. My friend gets beat
up by his uncle. Yeah. And his uncle
tries controlling him. You know what I'm
going to say? I'm going to say Tell your
uncle to [ __ ] off. Yeah. Tell your uncle
that he's not going to beat me up and
he's not going to make my [ __ ] face
[ __ ] bleed. You know what I'm going
to I'm going to start I'm I'm going to
start saying something, mate. I'm going
to start saying something because I went
to Manchester to see this guy a couple
of years ago. Yeah. His uncle didn't
[ __ ] come out. He bullies you, bro.
Cuz you're like 5'2. That's why he
bullies you. Yeah. punching people in
their faces and [ __ ] for no [ __ ]
reason. [ __ ] off, bro. I like to see the
[ __ ] do it to me. I like to see that
[ __ ] [ __ ] do it to me. Make my
[ __ ] face bleed. [ __ ] stupid little [ __ ]
Yeah. Don't make me start [ __ ] saying
something, bro. That's abuse what he's
doing. That [ __ ] That [ __ ] Yeah,
it's abuse, bro.
No, I never let things go. Dr. Echo.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Whatever. Yeah. Okay.
Like I like I Bro, like I said, selective memory.
Sun-kissed. Selective memory, lad.
Said it once. Say it again. Selective memory.
Yep, I do remember it.
Yeah. Selective memory, lad.
That's all I got to say. That's all you
got to say to these people. Selective memory.
That's it, bro. That's all you got to say.
You've got selective memory, lad.
There's videos of me sticking it on
plenty of men. Plenty of men. Uh I've
tried to meet plenty of men. Like I
said, selective memory.
Just like when you say you don't get
beat at the money game, you got beat.
Just like people call me a virgin when I
prove I've had sex. Selective memory,
bro. It's a real thing. That's all I'm
saying. But nice try though, bro. I am
wound up and you're trying to wind me
up. It's not going to work.
It's not going to work, lad. Yeah.
So, yeah. All I got to say is selecting
memory. That's it. [snorts]
Okay, bro. I'm not about it. Well, we'll
see you on Thursday then. Well, we'll
see you on Thursday then, won't we?
Well, we'll see you on Thursday, then, won't we?
Yeah. You don't even know what what
happened with that [ __ ] um with that
[ __ ] Polish bouncer. I've got it
recorded as well, you know, but I'm not
putting it on YouTube because you people
have got selective memory. I might send
it to I might send it to [ __ ] um
Greavvesy if he wants it, but I'm not
putting it on YouTube because you people
because you people have got selective memory,
bro. I Everybody heard it. Everybody
down that road was looking, bro.
Everybody right down that road was
looking, man. We're looking looking. I
won't upload it instantly. Not at all.
Because you people have got selective memory.
You people have got selective memory.
You [clears throat] people have got
selective memory, lad.
So yeah. Okay. I live in fantasy land. Okay, bro.
Okay. Keep thinking that. Well, I don't
know what I'll be doing Thursday anyways
and that's it. [gasps]
Okay, bro. Like I said, I'm not going to
go over all the W's I've took before,
bro, because we already know all of
them. So, I don't And you know all of
them. So, yeah. Yeah. 4 days until
Thursday. That's fine, bro. It couldn't
It's going to come fast.
That's good, bro. Four days.
Yeah, that's good, lad. That's good. I'm
going to cause absolute mayhem. I'm
going to approach people as well in
hopes that they meet me again so I can
[ __ ] their life up. Like this is like
pure like this is why I've got the
motivation to do this now, lad.
Yeah. Yeah. This is why I've got the
motivation to do this, you know, and I
will, bro. And I will not stop all day.
And I will not stop all day, bro, until
I [ __ ] get revenge on one of these
[ __ ] Trust me, bro. Rob them [ __ ]
something like that, bro. You know what
I mean? Yeah, they deserve it. [ __ ]
them, bro. [ __ ] them. Okay, don't
believe me then, lad. If you don't
believe me, then don't believe me. What
do you want me to say?
You people call people virgins even
though they prove they've had sex. You
people get beat at the money game. You
still think that you've won. Okay, don't
believe it, bro. I don't know what more
you want to say.
Biased people tend to not believe things
when they're proven wrong. That's just
the h that's just the way it is. You
people are just biased. Okay, don't
believe it. No one's forcing you to, lad.
It's going to be any woman. Yeah. Yeah.
It's going to be any woman. And then I'm
going to go to Elen and I'm going to I'm
going to I'm going to find this [ __ ]
bro. Trust me.
Do you know what I might do? Oh, and if
I can't find them Yeah, you are the
virgin, lad. Stop talking about
yourself. And if I can't find them, do
you know what I might do? Uh, posters.
Yes, I'm doing posters.
I'll be doing posters all over that
area, bro. Yeah. Oh yeah, cuz I know
what they look like. But I got posters, bro.
If I can't find them, which there's a
chance I won't be able to. Posters.
Same as what I done to [ __ ] launch
legs. They'll get posters done all over
him, lad. Yeah. Trust me, lad. Yeah.
Okay, bro. Whatever you say. Okay, lad.
Like I said, selective memory. Like I
said, selective bias memory, bro.
Whatever. And and obviously posters.
Yeah, I do posters, lad.
Oh, well, she didn't ghost me anyways,
but I'll just No, I'll just make up
stuff. Keile, na, everything. Yeah, put
it all over the train stations,
everything. Just like I knew. Oh, that's
another thing people forget, Grezy.
That's another thing they forget. They
forget um they forget the non legs
thing. Part of their selective memory.
Uh just think I bring that up now. Yeah,
they they also forget that uh due to
their very selective memory on this
community. So yeah, posters, posters, I
do posters, bus stops all around that
Elen area, bro.
Trust me. Like, trust me, I will do it,
bro, as well. You know, I'll do it as
well. I've done it before, bro. I'll do
it again. I don't give a [ __ ] Yeah. Say
that they were dirty pedophile nons.
Yeah. Everything. Trust me, bro. Trust me.
Yeah. I don't give a [ __ ] Dr. Echo. I
don't give a [ __ ] lad. I don't give a flying [ __ ]
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ]
I generally don't give a [ __ ] lad.
If there's no other way I'm going to
find them, then it's posters. But
posters are a last resort. You know,
posters are always a last resort. You
know, if you can't find someone or
they're not going to meet you, whatever,
then it's posters. It's straight up
So, and the posters has got nothing to
do with the court case, Dr. Eko. That's
got nothing to do with um that's got
nothing to do with that either. The
that's got nothing to do with any court
case, the posters.
He can record what he wants, mate. I've
got plenty of that. I've got plenty of
stuff on that Virgin as well. I've got
plenty of things of him harassing me.
I'm all good to I'm all good to go to
court, lad. If it goes to court, which
it won't go to court, I've got plenty of
harassment. I'm all good. Trust me. And
I've already spoke to my solicitor about
this, lad, which is why he's panicking.
Just worry about it when you're in
court, lad. Simple as that. Yeah. It
doesn't matter. Listen, Dr. Eko, I've
got evidence of him harassing me every
day. Don't worry about it, bro. The
courts will sort it. The courts will
sort it out, lad. If it goes to court,
you don't need to worry about it. They
will sort it out, lad.
They will sort out the skin virgin and
all the evidence that I've got on this
virgin. It's fine, lads. It's cool, bro.
Simple. Yeah. You I think you keep
forgetting, bro, that I've got about 200
pages of evidence of what this [ __ ] has
done. Trust me, it's all good, bro. You
don't need to worry about anything.
You have a lot of explaining to do. A
lot of explaining to do. Yeah. Simple.
Yeah. I made that.
And that's that, lad. Nah, no one's
allowed no women. [ __ ] that, bro. These
little [ __ ] gave me mad anxiety, you
know, the past week, bro. And I never
get anxiety, bro. I never even get
nervous. I had problems sleeping and
everything. Nah, no. Ain't allowing no women, bro.
Have they allowed me over the years?
Have they allowed me over the years,
bro? [ __ ] with me? No. No. No. I
ain't allowing no woman. [ __ ] that, bro.
Watch. Watch what I do on Thursday, bro.
You watch what I do on Thursday. You
watch what I do on Thursday. Yeah. You
watch. No, no, no. No one's allowing no
woman. They're big enough to try and
make people feel like [ __ ] I'll make
them feel like [ __ ] It's as simple as
that. [ __ ] that, bro. No, no, no, no,
no. [ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that.
I'll put that Christian Izzy all over
Elen and you know the area as well
Dusty. I've got I've got a friend in
I've got a friend in Redland. So it's
not it's not a problem bro. I'll just go
and meet them after. I'll just say that
they're a nons appeal. I'll just make up
I will make up stuff about them bro.
Simple. I'll just make up stuff about
them and embarrass them. It's as simple
as that. Yeah. Simple as that, lad.
I'm going to make sure that [ __ ] gets
humiliated. See how big they are then,
bro. They're all over the train station.
Yeah, that's the number one place you
want it in that train station, mate. So
when they try to walk in that train
station, they're [ __ ] Simple. Then
they're [ __ ] lad.
Yeah. Simple, lad.
Nah, it's not. It's nothing to do with
them. It's nothing to do with gambling
evil, lad. I've got money. I've got
plenty of money to do what I want when I
want. It's all because of this little [ __ ]
Yeah. No one cares. See you later, lad.
So yeah, that's that. No, no, no.
Nothing to do with gambling, bro.
Nothing to do with gambling at all. At
You get to a certain point in life where
you've just had enough of these [ __ ]
where you have generally just had enough
of them. You know that, you know, the
same thing happened with Ant-Man.
You know, him a lot well before me and
stuff. So, I mean, I'm I'm quite
patient. That's what happens. That's
what happens, bro. Happens to anyone.
There's only so much someone can take
any person. normal, not normal. You
know, everyone's human at the end of the
day. Everyone's got a breaking point.
Hence why people have mental breakdowns.
Why do you think so many people have
mental breakdowns? What? Because they
starting off mental, lad. [ __ ] that,
bro. No, I'm [ __ ] putting up posters
of them. [ __ ] that, lad.
I'm going to put up posters.
Yeah. You want to play games? I'll play
games with you. I'll [ __ ] with you in
your area. It's as simple as that.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, she will not be moving
on when there's posters. Nope. She ain't
moving on, mate. These people are not
moving on. You're not moving on with
your life [ __ ] with me. I'm going to
put post I'm going to make sure you get
[ __ ] battered as well, bro. Yeah. So,
we can either we can either do it the
normal way or the not nice way. It's as
simple as that. I'm going to make them
feel like [ __ ] It's about time you do
something to these little [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah. It doesn't matter. I don't give a
[ __ ] And I'm just going to be doing
posters of you. And I'm just gonna do
posters of you and make you [ __ ] and
make people mad at you, bro. Simple.
And I'm just going to humiliate you and
ruin your life. And I'm just going to do
it. Simple. Yeah. I don't give a [ __ ]
bro. I don't give a [ __ ] I'm going to
make you feel like [ __ ] I'm going to
make you look like a [ __ ] It's about
time, bro. Do you know what I'm saying?
It's about [ __ ] time with these
little [ __ ] weasels. Yeah. It's about
time with these little weasels, bro. Yeah,
let me [ __ ] with you. [ __ ] with you in
real life. You know, that's the that's
the difference. You know, when you take
when you take it to real life, that's a big difference.
No. How dare she lead somebody on for a
month and play games? Yes. How dare she?
How dare she play games and make people
feel like [ __ ] dusty? Yeah. How dare
someone do that, lad? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
How dare someone do that and play games
and try to make people feel like [ __ ]
Yeah. How dare they, Dusty. Poor them.
So innocent. Poor them. Leading people
on and messing with people, making
people feel like [ __ ] Oh, poor them.
They're innocent like babies, aren't
they, lad? They're innocent like babies,
aren't they? Well, trust me, I'll be
feeling a connection all the way to Eden
when I'm putting up posters. I feel the
connection cuz posters are going
everywhere, lad. I can feel that
connection, lad, to that train track
going all the way to [ __ ] Elen, bro.
I'm not leaving no one beat. I'm not
stopping, Dusty. I'm not going to stop,
bro. You can try to calm me down all you
want. I am not stopping. I will continue
doing it. I feel the connection and I'm
not leaving you alone. It's as simple as
that. And you're not going to you're not
going to you are not going you're going
to change your number as well. I'm going
to make you change your number, lad.
I feel that connection, lad.
I feel that connection all the way
there, bro. I can feel it, bro. You know
what I'm saying? [laughter]
Seriously, bro. Seriously, lad. I can I
can feel it, Greavves. I can actually
feel it, bro.
Stupid little [ __ ] Stupid little [ __ ]
bro. I'll give you I'll give you a I'll
give you another collection, bro. Yeah,
I'll give you another collection. Yeah,
simple as that, bro. This is going to stop, lad.
Yeah, this is going to stop, lad.
I don't give a [ __ ] if I don't care.
Uncle Andy, I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
Honestly, I don't give a [ __ ] lad.
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] Yeah,
I don't give a [ __ ] Don't come on my
phone for a month trying to make me feel
like [ __ ] Do you understand, Grezy?
Don't come on my phone for a month
trying to make me feel like [ __ ]
And they done it on purpose as well,
Grezy. Do you understand, lads? I don't
give a [ __ ] Leslie. I don't care to
remember. I don't care. Simple as that,
bro. Yeah. I don't care. What part of
someone not caring? Do you understand?
We're not like you little [ __ ] sat on
YouTube every day, bro. It should be Mr.
Ly as well. And they done it. And the
thing is, Ly, they done it on purpose as
well. It wasn't even that. And now all
of these people are feeling sorry when
I'm saying I'm going to put up posters
of this [ __ ] or I'm going to tell this
person about themselves. What the [ __ ]
bro? And then you got these people
feeling sorry for a [ __ ] You
understand, Ly? Like this is the world's
gone mad, bro. The world has gone the
world has gone mad, bro.
Seriously, the world the world has gone
mad, bro. And then you got people like
these and they done it on purpose as
well. a lot. I don't know who you are,
where you come from, but bro, like they
done it on purpose, so [ __ ] them in it. Simple.
They done it on purpose as well, bro.
You know what I'm saying? [ __ ] them,
bro. Telling me about their cheating
exes and all of this Ly. Oh, where's
this studying lot? Where's this going to
church when? Well, these people can't
have been that when they're cheating,
can they? [ __ ] [ __ ] Do you
understand, bro? Yeah. Where was Where
was all of this then, Grezy? Oh, bro.
I'm going to have fun with this club,
bro. Real real fun with this cub. Trust
me. I'm proper going to I love it when
people meet me cuz they meet their
match. I love that, you know, bro. I love that.
I absolutely love it, bro. I absolutely
love it. Yeah.
I don't give a [ __ ] I didn't get locked
up through posters anyways, mate. So,
get your facts right, lad. again.
Selective memory. You people need a CAT
scan, bro, cuz your brains obviously
don't work properly, mate. Yeah.
No, I'm not leaving no one alone. S
white knight, you're going to have to do
something about it. I am not leaving
nobody alone. I'm going to continue
doing it. Watch on Thursday, bro. Watch
on Thursday. Watch on Thursday. Just
watch on Thursday, lad. Yeah, just watch
on Thursday. I'm going to be doing a [ __ ] madness.
Yeah, that'll be the last time, bro.
That'll be the last time.
Trust me, it will just be the last time.
Yeah, I'm telling you, I'm not leaving
nobody alone and I'm telling you I'm not
doing it. So, yeah, [ __ ] off. Go and
have a wank, you silly [ __ ] Go and have
How about that one? Yeah, I don't give a
[ __ ] if she's a Christian. I don't give
a [ __ ] [snorts]
I don't give a [ __ ] I'm an atheist. I
don't give a [ __ ] Simple
as that. I don't care what you are.
Muslim, Christian, Catholic. I don't
give a [ __ ] You could be pink for all I
care. You understand?
Uh, she's not innocent, Leslie. I've
already explained the story. Leading
somebody on simp and playing games. You
deserve everything that you get, lad.
Nah, Joe. [ __ ] what I'm doing, bro.
I'm going to be doing I'm going to be
doing a madness on Thursday. Yeah. So,
this Christian Izzy has sent me pictures
and I'm trying to put two and two to
They live like around the West London
area, bro. I'm going to try and see if
that is exactly the same Donald. And I'm
just going to start stalking him, bro.
I'm just going to start stalking him,
[ __ ] with them. I'll be doing a
madness on Thursday. Anyways, I'll be on
the drink Thursday. So, I'll be doing an
absolute [ __ ] madness. I'm going to
be getting myself in madness, bro.
Madness all day. Trust me. Yeah. These
[ __ ] [ __ ] women need to pay, bro.
And I'll do it in front of any man. Just
like I have done [ __ ] two [ __ ]
months ago, [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. Simple as that. Yeah. [ __ ] damn
[ __ ] white. Right. Yeah. But you
people have got [ __ ] selective
memory, so you forget all of that stuff.
And bro, if I can't find them, posters
are going out, lad. Yeah. Didn't reject
me. Didn't reject me. I've already
explained the story, lad. Listen,
Leslie. White Knight simp. She didn't
reject me. That's not the reason. Again,
white knight. There's no point trying to
explain stuff to White Knights. They led
me on for a month. They made me feel
like [ __ ] Don't know how many times
they tried playing games. I'll put up
posters in their area. Simple. It will
be another launch legs. It will be
another launch leg scenario, lad. It's
as simple as that.
Stop defending women. They're not
innocent. Grezy will tell you the same
[ __ ] And me and Grezy complain about,
you know what I'm saying? Listen, Joe,
you will never do nothing, lad. You You
can't talk. You didn't meet LT. You
didn't meet me when I was up when I was
up north. You have never done nothing.
Baggot Ferrar, you have never done
nothing. You literally have never and
you will never do nothing. You won't
talk. You won't meet LT. You didn't meet
me when I went to leads. You will never
do nothing ever. You're just another red
star. You're another nodle legs. You are
the definition of nothing. That's your
middle name, lad. You ran away from
London Taylor. You ran away from me. You
can't talk. You will never do nothing.
That's your middle name, Mr. Joseph.
Nothing. [ __ ] Fur. You will never do
nothing. Same thing to you, lad. Same
thing to you, lad. Right. Same thing to
you, lad. Right. Stop doing post. Stop
winding yourself up cuz you your middle
name is nothing. Unlike me, lad. Do you understand, lad?
Yeah, bro. You You can come on the door
anytime you want. I will never stop. I
am not going to stop. I will never ever
ever ever ever stop. Never say never. I
will never stop. So if you want to come
on people's door, you can. But I'm
telling you that I'm going to continue
doing it. Thank you very much. And
you're not going to do nothing about it.
Simple as that. I'm going to continue
and you're going to do nothing just like
Joe's going to do nothing. How about that one?
So yeah, Greasy, bro. Like that's it,
bro. Like these [ __ ] these [ __ ]
deserve it, bro.
These [ __ ] deserve it, bro. Don't Don't
feel bad or anything, lad. Yeah. Don't
feel bad. Trust me, lad. I mean, I know
I only showed you some messages, Grezy.
Yeah, I know I only showed you some
messages, but um I only showed you some
messages, but bro, you don't know the
whole thing, bro. Like, it went on for
[ __ ] a whole month, bro. [ __ ] them,
bro. Don't feel sorry for them, bro.
Don't feel sorry for them little [ __ ]
They They purpose They done this on
purpose, lad. Yeah, they done it on they
done it on purpose, Squeezy. Yeah, which
is something that these people don't
seem to comprehend in their head. No,
I'm not leaving her alone. I'm not
Trust me. Did you leave me alone when
you was giving me [ __ ] mad anxiety
the past [ __ ] week? No. So, [ __ ] off.
You don't call the shots, do you, [ __ ]
You don't call the shots.
I'm going to continue doing it to a a
lass a lassie and you're not going to do
nothing. Yeah. If you're going to do
something about it, come on. Come on
Wednesday then cuz I'm going to I'm
going to show you where I am Thursday.
Sorry, not not Wednesday. Thursday. I'm
going to do it to a a lassilas and
you're going to do nothing. You bro, do
you want me to go live on Thursday?
Right. Cuz everyone's going to know
about this, right? I am going to keep
doing it. I'm not going to stop and
you're going to do nothing. There you
go, bro. You have got you have got four
days, right, notice. And I tell you, I
absolutely will be doing it. I'm telling
you, [ __ ] You understand?
Yeah. I'm telling you, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, bro. The part Yeah. About seven
days, bro. Yeah, it was bad. It was
pretty bad, bro. Pretty bad. I'm not
going to lie to you. It was bad, lad.
See, people don't need to people don't
need to lie about stuff on here, you
know, like Lord J saying, "No, I don't
have anxiety." But then the guy [ __ ]
himself in a [ __ ] pub, looking left,
right, up, down, bro. The guy was
nervous. Yeah, but bro, I never get
anxiety really to be fair. Not really,
lad. But yeah, the past seven days, uh,
seven days ago, I did. Yeah, bro. What
the [ __ ] All because of this dating thing.
Yeah, I drunk Monday, bro. I drunk
Wednesday. I [ __ ] even a couple days
before that, I had problems sleeping and
[ __ ] and everything, bro, because of
this little [ __ ] And then you got
people defending them. You know,
you know what I'm saying, bro? Just be
honest. I had it. I had it, bro. I I
swear to God, I had it, bro, a week ago.
But I never I never do get it. I never
do. Well, like I said, like I said,
Leslie, you'll know where I am on
Thursday, won't you?
You know where you'll know where I am on
Thursday. Yeah. This person caused me
mad anxiety, bro. It's not even a
[ __ ] joke. And now they're seeming to
be the innocent one, Grezy. This is what
these people do. Do you understand? Like
this is this is what I'm saying with
these white knights and these simps.
Yeah. These women are allowed to play
games, [ __ ] with people, do as they
want, and do as they please. But the
moment you stand up for yourself, oh
lassie, a woman. Do you understand, bro?
Do you understand what I'm saying, lad?
What are they, a baby? Are they Are they
a dog? Are they a dog, but they don't
know what they're doing? Are they
children that don't know what they're
doing? No, they're not. So why do you
people feel the need to defend them?
They're not going to let you [ __ ] them.
They don't like you. Women do not like
you and they're not going to sleep with
you, lad. So why do you keep doing this
to people that are [ __ ] It's pretty
much the what? Same thing that I said on
my two videos
or one of them at least on one of my dating videos.
Yeah, [ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] standing
up for that little [ __ ]
>> [clears throat] >> Yeah.
It's [ __ ] what I'm saying, lad.
Yeah. It gets rejected. Like I said,
twisting. Twisting the narrative. This
is what these people do, Greavvesy. They
twist things. They twist things. Do you
understand, lad? They like twisting
things. They're such virgins, Leslie.
The only one that's a virgin is you
defending women and they don't even like
you. What a loser. Any child, yeah, that
grows up to be a white knight sing
loser. I feel bad for them, lad.
You're defending women, but women don't
like you. Do you not get it in your
autistic brain, lad, that they're never
going to sleep with you. They're never
going to [ __ ] let you hit it. So,
stop stop defending them. Women don't
like you. You've had less women than me.
They don't like you, lad. And why? So,
why are you defending them?
You're a reject. They don't like you.
They don't. They're never going to sleep
with you. So why are you simply, bro?
You know what I mean? No woman wants
you. You're an ugly fat ma. No woman
will ever like you. Doesn't matter how
many times you defend them. You can
defend them till you're blue in the
face. And bro, they're not going to
sleep with you. They don't like you.
Just go on about your own Just go on
about your own business. They're not
going to sleep with you. They're not
going to like you. Trust me, bro. This
is the way you got to tell these this is
this is the way you got to tell these
people. Greavvesy, these are the way you
got to tell them. Bro, they don't like
you. Women don't like you. Stop
defending them. They don't like simps.
They don't [ __ ] with white knights. They
don't [ __ ] with simps. They laugh at
people like you. Laugh at ugly ass
people that's had less women than the
person that that's sticking it on them
like you. How like how many times does
someone have to explain it to someone
that's a dumbo? Women don't want you, so
stop defending them, bro.
Yes, 100%. 100%. Like I said, Joe, I'm
going to show everyone where I am on
Thursday, brother. I might have been
rejected, but guess what? I've had more
women than you. More women than you will
ever have. And I'm not licking no
women's ass, cuz I'm not a loser like
you. Yes. And says the guy who's had
more women than you will ever have,
despite how many times you said, "Women
don't like you." Yes. It's It's coming
from me, bro. Yeah. Because the fact
that you need to white night and the
fact that you need to s in the first
place, they're not going to sleep with
you. They're not going to give you their
body. Don't waste your time. It's not
worth it, bro. It's not worth it, lad.
Leslie, it's not worth it, bro. Listen.
Listen. Forget about me for a second.
Yeah. You're going to You're going to
You're going to What? One second. One
second. You're going to You're going to
defend a woman and potentially get your
head smashed in because you think
they're going to sleep with you? It's
embarrassing, bro. And I'm not even
talking about me. It could be anyone.
You You would put yourself in danger to
try to look good for women that don't
like you. Please tell me where it makes
sense. If you can explain to me where it
makes sense, I'll be happy.
Look what happened to that guy that
defended the woman on the train. He got
his head crushed in the [ __ ] door
trying to look good for women. When do
you people learn? They're not going to
sleep with you, lad. They're not going
to sleep with you. They're not going to
let you hit their anus with your dick.
It's not worth it. You're going to do it
to someone one day and then they're
going to seriously hurt you. You do
realize that. Trying to look good for
women, what a loser. You know, I could
understand people that are trying to
save the world, people that are trying
to, you know, whatever it is, but trying
to look good for women, what a [ __ ]
loser. I can't I can't figure and and
women are [ __ ] as well. Like, bro,
defend children. That's fine. Defend
children, defend babies, defend dogs,
defend cats, defend [ __ ] farm animal
pigs, bro. Defend anything that's
innocent. And I rate it. I 100% rate it.
I'll give you credit where credit due
with credit. But don't defend [ __ ]
evil little [ __ ] that [ __ ] try
playing mind games with people. They're
not the people to be defended. They're
not the people to be defended. [ __ ] me.
I don't know how many times we've gone over this.
They're nasty, nasty, nasty little
narcissists. That's what they are.
They're nasty, nasty, stinky little
narcissistic [ __ ] And guess what, bro?
Let me tell you something. If I knew
what they were like half them, I would
have robbed them, bro. And I would have
made sure they they never went back home.
Yeah, bro. No one's bullying women. It's
called standing up for yourself, you know.
Yeah. This is what I mean. Tiger. Tiger.
Bro, this Hey, bro. Yeah. I might seem
like a mad [ __ ] Yeah, I might seem like
a mad [ __ ] but bro, I don't really
care, bro. Because this person This
person's been [ __ ] leading me on for
a month. Yeah, this person's been
leading me on for a [ __ ] month. Yeah.
So, [ __ ] them, bro. Yeah, exactly.
They they they love defending women, lad.
They love defending women that are
[ __ ] It's it's their life. They think
they're going to sleep with them. They
think these women are going to sleep
with them, lad. You know,
it's not even morally correct. It's not
even morally correct. And do you know
the reason? Do you know the reason why I
don't I'm not bringing up the laney
thing with the neighbor because you're
taking out of context. I've already
explained it before.
No, I just woke up in a bad mood. It's
as simple as that. I just woke up in a
bad mood, lad.
Yeah. You know what she was doing,
Tiger? the tiger and they were trying to
make me feel [ __ ] on purpose. Yeah.
Listen, Tiger. Tiger. I was like, "Okay,
yeah. If you need to call me, call me."
Took things slow. I didn't even care,
bro. I didn't even want to be with them.
Yeah. I didn't even want to [ __ ] [ __ ]
them. I don't give a [ __ ] about that
[ __ ] like these white mites do. Yeah.
Saying about how we're going to meet,
how we're going to meet, and then say,
"No, you need to do this. You need to do
that." I was like, "Bro, did any of your
exes do that? Did any of your exes do
that?" Am I lying, bro? No, they didn't.
So, don't start expecting stuff from me,
bro. All I wanted to do was meet up and
I didn't even give a [ __ ] if anything
happened or not. But no, [ __ ] that, bro.
Simple. You want to start playing
[ __ ] games with people, being a
little [ __ ] for a month? [ __ ] off, man. Simple.
Simple. It's as simple as that, bro. I'm
pissed off, Tiger. I'm pissed off, lad.
And this Tiger Tiger is why you do not
take people's advice like Joe. Oh, speak
to them longer. Make them feel more
comfortable. Why? So they can [ __ ] you
over anyways. Cuz this is the thing,
Tiger. Tiger. They're going to [ __ ] you
over anyways, bro. Whether you speak to
them a day, a week, two weeks, a month,
two months, two years, these people have
got no problems with [ __ ] you over,
bro. Why do you think I keep myself a
distance from people now, lad? I know,
you know, we've not agreed with
everything in on everything in the past,
bro. You've been on this since I was 22,
bro. But why do you think I distance
myself from people, lad? Isn't it the
smart thing to do?
It's bad. That is, bro. Bad. Bad. Bad.
You know, like, you know, the games and
the [ __ ] and bro, it's mad, lads. It's mad.
They're not children. They're not
babies, lad. They They're not They're
not They're not No, no, no, no, no, no,
no. What I am going to do, Joe, I am
going to keep pursuing them and I'm
going to [ __ ] with them as well. I'm
going to be pursuing them to [ __ ] with
them now. Yeah, that's what I'm going to
be doing. I'm going to be pursuing so I
can try and get a date so I can just
ruin them on their lives. Yeah. Then
I'll be happy, bro. I'll be happy as
lamb. Yeah. Simple as that, bro. No,
I've had enough of this [ __ ] mate. I've
had enough of this [ __ ] Don't try to
make me feel like [ __ ] cuz you feel like
[ __ ] Don't come on my phone and try to
make me feel like [ __ ] Yeah.
Do you know what I'm saying, bro? No.
No. I'm not having that [ __ ] [ __ ] off.
No, bro. What's stopping the madness?
I'll be out Thursday anyways, bro.
People will know where I am. Defend a
baby. Defend a child. I rate it, lads.
Credit where credit's due. Don't defend
people that are worse than men. Don't
defend people that are worse than men, please.
Yeah. And and well, this [ __ ] gave me
anxiety for a week, lad.
Yeah. I don't give a [ __ ] if it ruins
her life. She had no problem [ __ ]
with me, trying to make me feel like
[ __ ] giving me [ __ ] anxiety. So,
[ __ ] her. Do I care? Good. Your life can
be ruined, can't it? And that will teach
you to stop being a [ __ ] to people, will it? Yeah.
Simple as that. madness, lad.
>> No, I'm not leaving nothing alone, lad.
I'm not leaving nothing alone. You don't
try and make me feel like [ __ ] You
don't try and make me feel like [ __ ]
lad. [ __ ] that.
And it's the way they were doing it as
well. Like, you can't, bro. You can't
even explain it, bro. You know the thing
is you can't even it's you can't even
explain these things to people though.
It's not even explain it's like trying
to explain a narcissist to someone. You
can't explain a narcissist.
You actually like you can't you can't
even explain it. Like cuz there's people
out there Yeah. that that's never that's
never met that's never met a narcissist.
You can't explain a narcissist, bro.
Like you can't explain like you know
what I'm saying? It's it's
inexplainable, bro. You get what I'm
saying? You can't explain it.
You can't explain it, bro.
You can't explain it, bro. You literally
can't explain. There's certain things
you can't explain. Like trying to
explain the game Moonscape,
you know, and then trying to talk about
your exes to make me feel like [ __ ]
Like, trust me, I know the game, bro.
Yeah. I've been in this game a very long
time now. A very, very long time now. I
know the game.
Yeah, I know the game, bro. I know the game.
You don't understand because you don't
deal with said people. So, you just
think people are mad. So, you think when
people react like this, they're mad, but
you don't understand it, bro.
You just don't understand it at all,
brother. You just think that they're all
innocent and that's it.
It's mad. It is actually mad, bro. You
you people should be sympathetic or empathize.
But you can't do that. You don't do
that. This is what I don't understand.
I swear to God. If I speak to someone,
they walk away. It's not a problem. It
is what it is. It is what it is, bro. If
I'm out, I don't care. You know, if
someone pretends they've got a
boyfriend, okay, [ __ ] it. I don't care,
bro. You know, I don't care about any of
that stuff. But when people are trying
to make me feel like [ __ ] Yeah. I'm I'm
not having it, bro. I'm not having it.
[ __ ] that. You know, simple. Yeah. I've
already explained what she's done. And
it wasn't [ __ ] rejection. I didn't
even [ __ ] want to date. I just wanted
to meet up.
You know, honestly, that's all I That's
all it was. I didn't even think about
sex once. That's the maddest thing about
it, bro. Come on. You know, you think
that's all people care about? Nah. Maybe
three, four years ago, but not now, lad.
Not now. My sex drive's gone way down,
bro. I don't give a [ __ ] about that.
Leading people, leading me on for a month, lad.
Giving me like false hope that we're
going to meet and that's it. Yeah, just
false hope, isn't it? And me and and
whatever. And I I was speaking to this
person every day for a month. Every day,
bro. voice noted a lot and look I still
got [ __ ] over. So [ __ ] talking to
people for a month. Stop trying to tell
people they it wasn't even it wasn't
even rejection lad. This is what I mean.
You can't say anything to you immature people.
You know you cuz you're think oh they
rejected bro. How many times how many
times do people get rejected when they
go out? Do we do you see us reacting
like this? No because I don't care.
And she was like, what was she was? She
was trying to um keep bringing her exes
up as well. She kept bringing her exes
up, exes up, exes up. Oh yeah, I've got
an Albanian. And this is the part that
was annoying me the most. Yeah, but I
didn't say anything until after. This is
the thing that was annoying me, right?
You You're asking me if I'm Albanian.
I'm not Albanian, but people think I'm
Albanian because I'm not fully white. So
I said, "No. Oh, I've got an Albanian
next. I've got an Albanian next." So
these people are similar to you. Hear me
out here. Just let me talk here. These
people are similar to you. Think about
it. They look that probably a lot of
people think I'm Armenian. So, they're
similar to you. These people, bro,
[ __ ] cheated on the person and then
they had a child with someone. I'm
sorry. Where were you meeting people like that?
Because they're not they haven't gone to
church. They haven't um they haven't
gone to church and they haven't they
haven't completed university. Yeah.
Do you know what I'm saying, lad?
No. Not at all, Leslie. Uh, not at all.
And then at the end of the day, lad.
Yeah. At the end of end of day at the
end of the day, lad. Yeah. Like this is
what annoys me. If you have got high
standards, I don't agree with it. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't agree with that. Yeah.
Obviously, you can have whatever you
want, but when you're trying to expect
something from another person whilst
the other people have not been like
that, [ __ ] off. Simple. You're just
trying to make people feel like [ __ ]
Simple. That's it, bro. Like, you're
just trying to make people feel like
[ __ ] and that's it.
So, yeah, it's just it's it's sickening, lad.
Yeah, it does. It does. Because the
thing is, Tiger, yeah, this is what
these people don't understand for
whatever reason that they don't
understand it, lad.
Listen, listen. Here's the thing. Yeah.
Here's the thing. Tiger. Tiger. Listen,
lad. Yeah. Here's the thing. Tiger.
Tiger. Yeah. If you listen to me, bro.
Yeah. If you approach someone, they say
they've got a boyfriend. Oh, you just It
is a bit annoying, but you just go on
the next. Someone says nothing, you just
go on the next. Or you message someone,
I I got free numbers. I got free
numbers. I got free numbers. Tiger
Tiger. Yeah. Last uh Monday they didn't
reply, I didn't really give a [ __ ] to be
honest. It's just oh same old England or
or if they reply for a day or two days
because you don't you don't even though
you don't know even this person you're
not you can't you don't know any
anything about them, right? So when you
when people are leading you on and
they're making you right and they're and
they're going and and and they're making
you believe stuff and you're [snorts]
knowing stuff about their exes because
you believe what people are saying. Bro,
that is disgusting, bro. I I haven't had
anxiety in a in a very long time, bro.
A very very very very very long time.
I've not had anxiety, bro. Until last
week. So, put like that, bro. People
think it's a minor thing. People think
it's a minor thing, bro. But it isn't.
It isn't a minor thing.
I couldn't sleep. Yeah. Again, it's not
to do with the rejection, and I've
already explained the story. She led me
on. She played games. She used me as an
emotional tampon. She tried to make me
feel like [ __ ] It's more than
rejection, lad. I didn't even I didn't
even want to be with her. I just wanted
to meet up. But this is what these
people are always going to say. Tiger
Tiger is old. They've just rejected you.
But it's more than that, you know? It's
more than that. It's a lot more than
what they do, bro. They make you feel
like [ __ ] That's what they do.
Yeah. She's horrible. She's horrible.
Tiger. Tiger. Listen, Tiger. I I was
speaking to them. Yeah.
Tiger, Tiger, listen, bro. Yeah. So, I
was speaking to them, speaking to them,
speaking to them. They said that I had
exams, so they couldn't meet. So, I was
like, "Okay, whatever." Yeah, you don't
have Okay, whatever. So, then after the
time period, we're still talking every
day. Whatever, bro. This why it doesn't
matter what you do, lad. Then then I
tried to meet them after the exams and
they start and then they started like I
said, "Oh, I'll let you know." I was
like, "Well, you obviously don't want to
meet me because you wouldn't be saying
I'll let you know." And then she started
coming up with madness and madness and
it just started going mad, bro. that one
day in in in the whole month. So, it's
like this is what I'm saying. Tiger
tiger, bro. People will have no problem
with [ __ ] you over. Even if they
spoke to you for a month, even though
they've wasted hours and hours. No one
has a problem with [ __ ] you over,
bro. Remember that. They don't think,
"Oh, oh, yeah, we're not going to do
this. We're not." They will do it, bro.
They don't care. People do not care
nowadays, lad. That's something that
you've got to understand. These these
these people are [ __ ] evil, lad. They
are evil. Yeah, they are very evil,
nasty people. And I'm not even just
saying that, bro. And do you know why I
went out that time? Tiger Tiger. Yeah,
because I was stressed as [ __ ] Not
anxiety, just this guy was pissing me
off. Not anxiety, but he was this guy
was pissing me off. Yes. So I thought,
oh, let me go out for a drink. Let me
have a piss up. And then I had I done a
couple of approaches on the way. And I
thought, okay, we're on to something
now, is it? First one of 2026,
everything happens for a reason. These
problems still keep happening. You get me, lad?
So that's the reason why I went out in
the first place to get me, bro.
So like it wasn't like I I I you know
what I mean, bro? That's why I don't go
out now, lad. It's very very rare I go
out. They're all the [ __ ] They are
all the same, bro. They are all the same, lad.
You know, people always try and make you
feel like [ __ ] tiger, tiger, and that's
it, bro. Yeah. I wouldn't mind if the
ex's were black. I wouldn't mind if the
ex's were white. I wouldn't mind if the
ex's were good people, but it's not.
They've made it seem, bro, you don't
understand this game playing. They tried
to make it seem like so similar to you.
This is the This is the whole game
playing, bro. Do you get it, lad?
Yeah. I don't have anything to offer.
Like, okay, whatever you say. And
they've got nothing to offer me either,
Gona. And they've got nothing to offer
me. Some of these women have got jobs in
McDonald's for [ __ ] sake. And they've
got nothing to offer me. And you know
what? I'm glad that because they've got
nothing to offer me but stress and
anxiety. That's the only thing that
they've got to offer us. No money, no no
stability. They're draining. They're
depressing and they give people anxiety.
That's the only thing that they offer
us. That's the only thing that they
offer us is anxiety. Yeah. Isn't that
right, lad? The only thing that they've
got to offer is anxiety and heartbreak.
Yeah. That's the only thing that they've
got to offer us. So actually there is
there is something that they have to
offer that. That's what they've got to
Yeah. They the only thing that they've
got to offer is anxiety and heartbreak.
Nothing else. And stupidity. That's the
only thing that they've got to offer us.
So they do have something more to offer
than me. Yeah. Yeah. That's I don't
approach I don't appro Yeah. And I don't
approach. The reason I went out last
time, there was a reason why I went out
last time. I don't approach. I've been
Bro, did you you should actually catch
up with my dating videos and you you understand it.
No, it's not about being rejected. I
don't care about being rejected. I don't
care about going up to someone and them
saying they've got a boyfriend. I don't
care. I don't I just I'm out. I'm
drinking. I don't care who says no. But
other when someone's trying to [ __ ]
lead me on and play games or whatever
and seeing these people make the same
mistakes, bro, what the [ __ ] What the
actual [ __ ] lad?
Yeah, it's not about rejection. I've
already explained the story, lad. You
can keep twisting it all you want.
And I mean it, Gona. I mean it, lad. I
actually mean it, lad. I mean it.
So church is out the question now, lads.
Even if you go to church, you might you
might come across the same people.
I want peace in my life, bro. Peace in
my life. That's what I want. Not
headaches, not dramas, not [ __ ] anxiety.
That is bad, lad. I can't remember the
last time I had anxiety, but then
long time, lad. Long time.
I don't really get anxiety, bro, to be
honest with you.
Yeah. Okay. I've got nothing to offer
women. Okay, bro. And they got nothing
to offer me, lad. They've got nothing to
offer me [gasps]
but headache, heartbreak, and games
and anxiety. That's the only thing
they've got to offer me, you know?
That's it, man.
So they do play games with people on
purpose to try to make them feel like
[ __ ] They do do that. Why does no one say anything?
No, I didn't get rejected. I got led on
and [ __ ] with. So yeah, big
difference, lad. Big difference. Big So yeah.
So that's it, lad. Explain this one. Go.
Right? If it's about how people
if she did nothing wrong, of course she
did nothing wrong. She's a woman, bro.
Okay, answer me this question, right? If
it's to do with what people have got to
offer, why do women go for people that
beat them? Why do women go for people
that are in prison? They've met them
whilst they were in prison. Let's hear
it. This guy used to always ask this
woman for money. Can I have some money?
Can I have some money? Bro, I never need
to lend money off anyone. Doesn't matter
what income I'm on. I I can't remember
the last time I needed to borrow money
from someone. Yeah, I'm my own person.
So, if it's really about this, can you
explain to me why so many women are with
so many bad people with nothing? Please
explain that one to me. I've got all
day. No one's getting blocked, you lads.
Come on. Explain to me why there's so
many women with people with nothing. No
personality, no money, horrible ass
people. Come on, lad. They got nothing.
They've got nothing. Some of them are
even in prison. Some If you look up
articles, there are people dating women
that dating men that are in prison.
Answer me, lad. Answer me. Answer me the
question then. You don't like it, do
you, bro? You don't like it.
Yeah. You don't like it, lad.
Yeah. You don't like it, bro. You don't
like it. Because you know I'm right. You
don't like it.
Yeah. That Listen, Tiger. Tiger, bro.
Listen. If I if I approach someone now,
right? If say I was, let's just say
hypothetically this was a Thursday,
right? And I approached someone and they
say they had a boyfriend. Yeah. Then
okay, whatever. Then I'll go on to the
next one. It doesn't like we're out
anyway. So we got we're going to get
numbers regardless. So it doesn't really
matter what anyone says. But it is after
if you do it sober for eight times and
it happens, it's a bit annoying for like
maybe 10 minutes and then you just go to
a bar, whatever. And there's a big
difference, lad. There's a big
difference because when when someone's
leading someone on, you start thinking
of, oh, this is going to happen. Oh, all
of these bad experiences. This is the
reason why this has happened. Now, we've
actually found someone that's not going
to do this. And then the more you talk,
the more you talk, the more they're
trying to you're trying to gain their
trust. Do you understand? And then bam.
Bro, just I'd rather just someone just
walk away, bro. And at the end of the
day, bro, I'd rather just someone just walk away.
No, she didn't make it clear. She said
that she was going to meet me. She said
that she was going to meet me. And
another thing, Tiger, Tiger, she was
asking how many women I slept with. She
was asking me personal questions as
well. At the very start, asking me
personal questions. And then they said
that they were going to meet. Whether it
went anywhere, whether it didn't go
anywhere, they said that they were going
to meet me several times. They were
asking me personal questions, bro, that
you don't ask someone that you've just met.
You don't ask people them questions just
like I wouldn't ask someone the them questions lad.
You know if I asked a woman a a body
count I'd get killed.
So that's it. Like it's horrible bro.
These women tiger tiger there. They're
[ __ ] horrible lad. They are horrible
bro. They are really really really really horrible. You know,
and what I'm saying, Tiger Tiger, is I
don't know what you look like, bro, but
when someone's trying to tell you about
people that look similar uh that look
similar to you, but they're scumbags and
you're thinking to yourself, hold on a
minute, why isn't they have done this?
Why? Do you understand what I'm trying
to say? It's all game playing. This is
what [ __ ] with the mind.
Do you understand?
Yeah, but you'd get called for it,
Greasy. Yeah, you could do, but they'd
call you for it. If you asked a woman at
body count, she'd she'd And it's like,
why does it matter how many people I've
been with anyways? Why are you asking me
these these questions? Why are you
asking me these questions?
Why are you asking me these questions? I
think that was really strange why people
asking me these questions.
Um, to be honest, but I thought it was
strange to be honest with you, lad. Cuz
look at your exes.
Like it can I can understand if they're
a highmaintenance person that goes for
highmaintenance people. But judging by
your exes and what you've told me, why
are you expecting something different
from me? Do you get what I'm saying? Tiger tiger.
Do you understand? Yeah. But she goes
for these people, Joe. There's I don't
have sympathy for Tiger. Tiger. Yeah. I
do not have sympathy for women that get
cheated on because they go for these
people. They choose these people. Yeah.
I'm sorry, mate. You have not just met
someone and they've just cheated on you
and had a baby with someone else. There
is no [ __ ] way. These women just run
into these people, lad. Yeah, sometimes.
Yeah. Okay. Sometimes you might come
across someone that tries to, but
there's no way, bro. They know exactly
the kind of people they're going for.
They know exactly these the reputation
that these people [ __ ] have. Do you
get me, lad?
Do you get me, bro?
So, I don't feel so I don't feel sorry
for people like that, bro. They they
they choose it. They choose themselves.
And and and the thing is And the thing
is, listen, here's another thing as
well, is that even if they get the
chance to go for say they've got someone in mind,
uh tiger, tiger, someone that don't
cheat, someone that this some you could
beat all of them things and they'd still
go back to the cheater. They'd still
choose the cheater lad. Do you understand?
They would still go for the cheating
bastard. So that's why there's no sympathy. Lad,
was she fit? No, not really. She's a bit
young to be honest as well. But the It's
the principle. It's the principle, lad.
Nope. Nothing to my sister's boyfriend.
I've met many women. I know the I know
the kind of guys that they like that
they go for. I know the kind of guys
that they go for, lad. So even when
they've got a chance to meet someone
that's not like that, they won't take
it. They'll go back to the cheater.
So it's like that's No. No way, bro. No.
No. They were all right, lad. Yeah. How many
um I have had women that have had
cheating exes, right? that have had
chances to get with somebody that isn't
like that, but they don't want to be
with someone like that. And then to
that, if they're honest at first, I'm
like, "Oh, I'm not really bothered." But
it's a shame because they moan about
men. They moan that they can't find
someone whatever that that doesn't do
these things. But then when they get
these chances, then they go back to the
cheater. So, it doesn't make sense. It's
a shame. I feel more for them when it's
like direct. I'm like, I feel more for
them to be honest with you, cuz they
bring it on themselves.
They really do bring it on. They They do
bring it on themselves,
mate. It was It was on no experience,
bro. There's been plenty of experiences.
Plenty of plenty of experiences,
right? And like I said, you can look it
up. There's women that date people in
prison. The [ __ ] are you doing with
someone in prison, bro? What the [ __ ]
So, no, there's been plenty of
experiences. This one right here,
there's been others in the past.
USA Izzy's uh ex was an abuser, and I
know this because I spoke to her, but
they always seem to go for these same
kind of guys. These same kind of dudes.
You know what I'm saying? And this is
what I I don't understand. They always
constantly go for these same kind of
dudes. You know, just say you like
scumbags. We're not going to judge you
for it. Like we know the truth out
there, lad. You know the [ __ ] you you
you just say these things. We we don't
mind, you know. Just just put it straight like.
So yeah, just admit that you uh it's
like L J. Like I was saying, bro, if you
got anxiety, bro, it's fine. I had
anxiety last week.
Nothing wrong with having anxiety, bro.
At periods in your life, you know,
there's nothing wrong with that.
You don't need to be so like, "Oh, I
ain't got this. Oh, I ain't got that,
bro." You know what I mean? So, yeah. [clears throat]
I thought at first it was the the
watching that video with that guy
getting smashed with a hammer, but I
don't even think it was that to be
honest. I think it was the dating thing.
I'll be waiting for a response back.
I'll be fiddling, bro. Twitching and everything, twitching,
like half awake where you're not sleeping properly.
All because of that. Um cuz I'm
thinking, "Oh, they're going to respond
or they're not going to respond." But
people just think this [ __ ] is normal.
They think dating is so easy. It's so
normal and it isn't. There's nothing
normal about it.
It sucks, lad. What I would do, what I
would give to be born in the 1980s.
Yeah. No, it isn't, lad. I go out all
the time. All the time. I'd actually
probably donate a kidney, bro. If I
could go, if I could be born in 1970,
I'd give a kidney, lad. I'm not even
joking. I would give a kidney, bro,
before all this Instagram, before all
this Tik Tok [ __ ] I'd actually donate
my I would donate my kid. My bro, you
know what I'm saying?
Well, I can do, bro, when I'm being led
on. Well, I can be when I'm being led Yeah.
I' I'd donate a kidney, bro. If I could
if I could be born in in in in 1970s,
1970s, be around in the 80s, '90s. Life
was a better place back then. I I would
actually I actually would. Yep.
But no, that anxiety was bad, bro. Last
week, it was really bad.
It was really bad,
bro. No one's desperate for nothing,
lad. I tried to get away from these
women multiple multiple multiple
multiple times because of what they're
like. Just cuz I went out once in three
months, bro, and thought, "Oh, I'll give
it a try." Doesn't mean I didn't give up.
I didn't go out yesterday. Why didn't I
go out yesterday? I've got money. I've
got money to go out. Why didn't I go on
Friday? I've got money to go out. I've
You know, I was playing pool yesterday.
Think about it, bro. If I generally had
hope. You don't understand, Gula. Yeah.
This is where your your your mind
doesn't work properly. Someone that's
got hope would do madnesses. They'd go
out every day. They'd go out. If they
had no money, they'd find ways to get
money. They would they would go out,
bro. Trust me. People with hope, when
when a man's got hope, they'd find a
way. They'd find a way. I've got money,
bro. I could go out. Yeah. You
understand? Why didn't I? Cuz I'm sick
and tired of it. You understand? I'm
sick and tired of their [ __ ] to last me a lifetime.
Something that you don't understand,
lad. Just because I come across someone
when I went out after 3 months and
someone seemed they were different and I
thought, "Okay, whatever." Does that
mean I'm not giving up, bro? Come on.
It's still giving I'd be out trying
today, you know? I'd be I would have
went out trying yesterday. I don't need
to try. Try what? They're all the same.
None of them are good. I don't need to
speak to any of them. They're not good.
None of them are good.
So, I don't need anxiety. I don't need
stress. I don't need negativity in my
life. Yeah. It's as simple as that. No one does.
I certainly don't, lad.
Yeah, simple, lad. Like, it's so bad.
Tiger Tigers, when I watch porn, I
shouldn't even be saying this. I watch I
watch porn from the 80s, you know. Why
do you think I watch porn from the 80s, lad?
I watch porn. I never watch new porn.
There's nothing new I watch. Actually,
if you think about it, lad. All the
horror movies are old. All the pornos.
Like, you laugh at it, bro. But it's
serious. It's serious [ __ ] I don't
watch Paul that much anyways, but when I
do, it's always old porn,
you know? Shouldn't even be saying that
live, but there you go. Certain people
are probably watching. But yeah,
simple. Yeah. And I will never approach
again. As simple as that. Yeah. I don't
need to, bro. I've had my curiosity
satisfied multiple times.
Yeah. Simple as that.
None of them are good. And none of them
can offer you anything. This is the
thing. None of them can offer you
nothing but a headache and anxiety, you know.
Then that's all they'll offer you, you know.
Okay, bro. The issue is me. Okay, you
keep thinking that, lad. I don't need to
come on here and explain anything. I put
up so many messages to prove that it was
them. I put up so many approaches to
prove that it was them. If you think
it's me, then the issue is me, bro.
That's it. We don't need to get into
debates. I've proved all I can prove.
And what the evidence shows is it's
them. Whether you want to admit it, whe
you don't want to admit it, that's on you, bro.
That's on you. But evidence don't lie.
Remember that. Videos don't lie.
Messages don't lie. You can make up
stuff all you like, bro. But you know
deep down it is them.
You know, most of the time.
I mean, what I don't understand Tiger
Tiger is that these people will say that
it's you. Okay. So, they've got their
opinion. Okay. So then you then you dist
then you distribute a approaching video
where you literally can't even finish
your sentence without saying that
they've got a boyfriend but apparently
it's you and you're the bad person and
you're this and you're that. Okay. And
then you get a number. Okay. So then you
agree to meet with someone and then they
come out with excuses. Oh, I'm getting
back with my ex. And it's happened
multiple times. But oh, it's you. You're
the bad person. You ain't got anything
to offer. You see, they always in this
day and age, people always like to make
excuses for these women. Whether you're
right, whether you're wrong, that's the
way it will always be. They they love
doing that. For some reason, they think
women are angels and they can't do anything wrong.
Even when you've shown evidence as well,
even when you have shown evidence. So,
yeah, that that ex thing has happened
multiple times actually as well. I
remember USA Izzy talking about her ex.
I remember that American I was supposed
to meet talking about her ex. It's
happened. It has happened multiple times.
So, that's another thing as well, lad.
So, no, news flash, women pretend
they've got boyfriends. Yeah. No, no,
women pretend they've got boyfriends,
which is what they mostly do. They they
they pretend they've got boyfriends. And
we're not having the same argument, bro,
because I know it and you know it.
You're just in denial. You're not even
believing what you're saying now. You're
just in denial.
And it doesn't matter about boyfriends.
That's one thing. What about the leading
on? What about the piss taking? What
about the attitude? That's one thing,
bro. Whenever you whenever you you say
stuff, it's one thing.
One thing, bro. Okay. They got
boyfriends. Okay. So, what about when
they leave people on? What about when
they play games? What about when they've
got a vile attitude? What about when
they try to be tumb to people? What
about them? What about that? That then?
Yeah, man. See you later, lad.
Yeah. See you later, mate.
So, I'm making up things even though I
put the messages out there.
So, I'm I'm making up things even though
I've provided black and white evidence.
But that's that's me making up things.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Yeah. That's that's
making up things even though I put the
evidence out there. Okay, bro.
You've never seen me led on? Well, the
only thing I can say to that uh Goona,
is go to Specs Savers and get your eyes
tested. Uh because if you which you have
seen my videos, you will see that I have
absolutely been led on multiple times.
Multiple most of the times it happens
when conversations go on. Most of the
time you get led on. But you can't see that.
You can't see that, lad.
Really? You've never seen it? Well, you
need your eyes tested, lad.
You need your eyes tested, lad. I'm
pretty sure if it was a man leading me
on, you'd have a lot to say about it,
and you would have all of a sudden um
forgot. Isn't that right, Gona? You
wouldn't have all of a sudden forgot then.
Nah. Nah. But soon as it's the woman,
apparently you act dumb. You're blind
all of a sudden. [ __ ] off, man. Come on.
It's pathetic. Very, very pathetic.
But yeah, I'm done anyways. I'm I'm I'm
done anyways, lad. I was out the I was
out the dating game months ago. >> [snorts]
>> just going to go out and do a madness.
Like I said,
mate, I don't need help. I need better
experiences. That's what I need, Harry.
I need better experiences.
Better experiences with better people,
lad. That's what I need.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
Okay, I'm not then. Okay, I'm not.
Whatever, lad. You say what you want.
Whatever. I don't care. Cuz
the more you keep with these women UK
signing, the more bad experiences you're
going to get. They're no different. None
of them are good. So the more you try
with these people, the more you're going
to you're going to it's just going to
keep happening and happening and
happening and you will just end up just
hurting someone one day. And it would
happen to anyone as well, bro. It would
happen to anyone.
That's why I don't [ __ ] That's why I
don't [ __ ] with them, bro.
People like to say things, but they
don't like to stick to their word. Do
you get me?
I'm off Thailand, bro. I swear I'm off
Thailand, bro. 100%. I was watching a
video of someone in Thailand earlier,
bro. You got a cheap ass flight. I'm
thinking, what? Told Adman about it. Out
of here, bro. [ __ ] that. Yeah.
Madness. Absolutely madness. Absolutely madness, bro.
I just woke up in a pissed-off mood
today. UK asylum. Just a pissed-off
mood. As you would, as you should do,
all the bad experiences you've had. As
you should do, you know, madness, bro.
I can't believe you can [snorts] speak
to someone for a month and they do that.
[ __ ] hell. Well, that's people's
advice is that that's people's advice contradicted.
That's people's advice contradicted, lad. Yep, [snorts]
pretty much, lad. Pretty much. Yeah.
And you know the maddest thing about it
UK signing, man, this is how life is
unfair. Yeah. Is that they can they can
do this to someone. They can be
narcissistic. They can be evil. And they
can just find someone else. They could
be the shittiest person what they are. a
lot of these people and they could just
find someone the next day. How mad is
that, bro? It's so [ __ ] up, bro. Like,
this this day and age is so [ __ ] up. I
I feel sorry for any kid. Yeah. That
that is born. I feel sorry for any baby
that is born cuz God knows what it's
going to be like when they're my age.
Going to be worse. I'd imagine it'd be
even worse, bro. God knows
cuz it will get worse. They'll think of
other stuff to bring out and that. You
know what I mean?
It's so unfair, bro.
Really, really unfair in so many ways, bro.
And you'll just keep having more bad experiences.
The more you try, the more you'll get
more bad experiences, lad.
So, that's why. And it's not going to
change. None of them are nice. None of
them are different, bro. Me, I can
safely say that now. Like I said, God
can't tell me nothing. Jesus can't tell
Yeah. Why am I going to go to church?
Why am I going to believe in Jesus
Christ when I'm not a believer, bro?
These these experiences have made me not
a believer in any kind of religion.
So, what what am I going to go to church
for to to believe something that um
that you know I don't believe in Jesus
Christ, bro? You know, they can't tell you nothing.
God, whatever. You know,
but then you say that people are
trolling, bro. I'm not even trolling.
I'm being serious.
I wish I never went out, bro.
That um that February, I think it was
the 4th of February or the 5th of Feb. I
wish I never went out. I I actually wish
I never went out, lad. Because here we
are again, you know, with the same
problem again, the same issue again. I
wish I never went out, bro. You know,
I hate this country, bro. I really hate
this country, bro. I can't I can't fret
to you enough how much I hate this country.
So bad. So bad.
I wish I never approached, lad. I wish I
never did. Seriously, I wish I never
did, bro. You know,
look at all these issues that it's caused, you know? Madness.
Is Monty still alive?
They always go for the same stereo
stereotypical people. UK, same
stereotypical man, same abuser, same cheater.
But you know the thing is UK I could
understand. Yeah. If he was ugly. Yeah.
If he was ugly, right, and these men
were good-looking, then bro, they're
going for like sex appeal, bro. These
men are sexy, bro. Like, could you
imagine like these sexy guys doing these
bad things and you're like Tim Eldridge?
Obviously, people are going to make
excuses not getting with you. I could
understand if you look like Tim
Eldridge. If you was a [ __ ] like him,
I could be like, "Fair play, bro. We
[clears throat] get it. These people
that are cheating obviously have got
some sex appeal in it. That's why people
keep going for these people, but it's
not even that, bro. Cuz what what
chances are you're probably better
looking than them, if not the same as
them. So, you know, I could understand
if you was born at Timmy Eldridge
or even like Rick Mace or ugly people
like that, bro. Then I could I could I
could understand it. I could be like,
"Okay, fair enough." But you can't even
say that, bro, cuz you're not fat.
You're not ugly. You're not broke.
You know, I've done the money thing
experiment. They just love being [ __ ]
That's what they are. That's what they
love being lad.
It doesn't matter though, UK signing
because they didn't even get to know me.
And the conversation was perfect. The
per the conversation was perfect, lad.
Perfect every day. So the what I'm
trying to the point I'm trying to make
is if they're making excuses not to get
with you, you could understand if if you
was ugly. you. That's the point I'm
trying to make. If you was ugly, then I
could understand the excuses.
But you're not. There's nothing wrong
with you. Like a lot of other of these
people, there's nothing wrong with them.
But yeah, sure. You might not be
perfect, but you're not. You're not No.
No. The vibe definitely was there. The
It's very personal, lad.
And you go by their ex's UK asylum.
That's the thing that makes it personal.
If they were black guys, okay, fair
enough. They go for black guys. If they
were white guys, oh for okay, they go
for white guys. Oh, they go for people
that actually do have their [ __ ]
together. 100%. Okay, fair enough. They
got their standard, bro. But when
they're trying to tell you what you
should be like when they've gone with
cheaters in the past, that was just
grinding on my mind, bro. I'm not even joking.
No, she didn't stop talking to me. She
just started making excuses.
It was about not meeting. She just she
just made excuses not to meet. She kept
talking and everything.
That's what was driving my mind mad,
bro. I'm not even joking. Like, that's,
you know, it's not like, you get what I
mean. And then it just contradicts the
whole thing that they're saying. So,
because why wouldn't they meet you? Why
wouldn't they give you a chance? What's
wrong with you? There's nothing wrong
with you. There's nothing wrong with the
way that you are. There's nothing wrong
with the way that you look. So, what
what's the problem? And you're telling
me that's not personal? It is personal.
All of it's personal.
So, you can go for cheat and ask
bastards. You know what they're like,
but you can't go for someone that's normal.
They ain't got more sex appeal than me,
bro. So what? You understand the point
I'm trying to make.
Madness, bro. Madness.
It was the It's just sick, bro. All it
is is just sick.
So what what is it? Are you Timmy or something, lad?
Are you [ __ ] Are you ugly like nods?
Are you ugly like Ricks? I don't think so.
They even said, "Oh, you look good."
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You look good. You're
good. Look. Yeah. So, what's the problem
then? What's the problem
now? I'm done with it, bro. I'm done.
I'm done, lad.
You see what I mean? [clears throat] UK
asylum, lad. So what is it? It is
personal. Of course it's personal.
So yeah, it is definitely personal lad. It's bad.
So that's that.
and my success has has not been as good
as it should have been UK asylum. Bro, I
should have had way more the effort that
I put in. But people don't see that.
People don't empathize. They don't care.
They just straight to defending the
woman. Don't care about this. They don't
care about that. They just go straight
to defending them. No matter what the
what the circumstances are,
they're just straight like straight
defending the woman.
straight sticking up for the woman.
They're bad bad people. It's so bad that
I would think I'd ever ever be even be
happy with one now, bro. Knowing what
they're like, I don't think I would ever
be happy with one.
I would just continuously be thinking of
ways to [ __ ] him over or like because of
what they've done where they've done so
much damage, bro. Like it's irreversible.
It's irreversible. You understand? If
that makes sense.
They've done so much [ __ ] so much damage. So yeah,
it's like being in a classroom as a kid
and being treated differently. Don't
know if anyone's ever had that yet. Like
when they used to go to school that it's
like you're being treated differently
than other people. Do you understand?
When why you're not Timmy Eldridge? You
don't look like Timmy Eldridge. You
don't look like Money Mike. You don't
look like Lo J. Why are you being
treated differently? You get me?
So, it's like going to school, right?
And then being treated differently. One
kid's allowed gum, the other kids not
allowed gum. You get what I'm saying, bro?
It's like people having three kids and
having favorites. You understand?
It's not good, bro. >> [snorts]
>> Is there any coke? I don't think so.
It's all about personality and mindset.
You keep telling yourself that, lad.
You're in for a bumpy work. You're in
for a bumpy ride, my man. You're in for
a bump bumpy ride.
Yeah, man. It was all It was all about
personality and mindset when I spoke to
someone for a month and they [ __ ] me over.
Yeah. You keep telling yourself that,
lad. Keep that faith going, bro. I'm
glad I'm happy if you believe that, bro,
because I certainly don't.
Well, if it works for you, lad. Good for you, man.
Good for you.
Good for you, then. If it works for you,
lad. Good for you.
It's bad, bro.
It's really bad, isn't it?
Can [snorts] smell a bad mindset. The
only thing they can smell is their
[ __ ] dirty, disgusting fanny.
That's the only thing they can smell is
their dirty, disgusting ass fanny
that they don't clean. That's the only
thing they can smell, lad. And the [ __ ]
coming out their ass cuz they're so full
of it. Full of [ __ ]
That's the only thing they can smell is
their shitty ass with all the lies they tell. [ __ ]
But then a part of me still wants to go
out and just like try to find one to [ __ ] over. Yeah,
he's slagging me off. Yeah.
That's good, bro. That's good, lad.
Bro, look how long my beard's gotten,
bro. Jesus Christ.
Look at my beard, bro. [ __ ] it.
I didn't have a shower yesterday, did I, bro?
Yep. Really, lad?
Yeah, cuz I don't give a [ __ ] lad.
That's why I don't give a [ __ ]
No, I don't.
I could just go out in the cold approach
people and just try to [ __ ] with them.
Yeah, I could never be happy with
anyone, bro. I'm too damaged. Too many
bad experiences. It's irreversible.
These women are real [ __ ] lad. Real
Yeah, bro. Irreversible damage, lad. It's irreversible. Nope. Madness, bro.
It's bad, Harry. Really bad.
Nah, I'm done with the dating [ __ ] lad.
I'm good, bro.
Oh, I've just sent that and I'll have to
do it all over again. [sighs and gasps] [ __ ] sake.
I sent that and now it's all over. All
over again, bro.
You're not evil, lad.
I say to myself, I I I would have told
that to my younger self, lad.
You know they're taking a piss, lad.
That's why I ignore it.
You know they're taking a piss. You've
seen everything I've done on this community, lad.
I'm sick, bro.
Sick to death for this [ __ ] lad.
I just don't want to talk about anymore,
bro. It's depressing, lad.
They drains your energy.
Don't want to talk about them, bro.
Them evil, nasty people. I don't want to
talk about them, lad.
One second. I'm trying to send something.
Oh, for God's sake. It's done the same thing again.
I'm trying to [ __ ] send something.
It's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
That's so annoying, bro.
It's not funny, bro. It's annoying, man.
I just sent this and [ __ ] I've had to
do it again. No. All
right, Pips Smoker, do Reddit mods.
I do Reddit mods. Um, like to control people.
No, I'm not sending it ever again, lad.
I'm done with it. I'm done with the
dating game, bro. I don't know how many
times I have to tell you this. I'm done
with this [ __ ]
I don't know how many times I have to
tell you, bro.
I'm done. I'm done. I'm done. And you
don't listen. I'm done, lad. It's over. It's finished.
The end, bro. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, but if that if that if that
[ __ ] uncle wants to keep talking
[ __ ] I'll go in Birmingham and smash
his face and mate. See if he'll [ __ ]
hit me, bro.
I said, "Oh, your uncle said, "Don't
speak to me anymore. Tell your uncle to
mind his own [ __ ] business." How
about that? Tell your uncle to mind his
own [ __ ] business.
Yeah, I mean Uh [clears throat] yeah, Sunday
I'll have my steak later.
Player number. You're a loser, lad. Go
back. Go back live on YouTube on
Christmas Day, you loser.
live on on YouTube Christmas Day. What a loser.
That's funny, lad. You was live on
Christmas Day with no family, no roast dinner.
Get a grip, lad. It's 2026. Get a grip,
Yeah, get a grip. [snorts]
Get yourself a little grip. [sighs] [gasps]
Yeah. You've never had a girlfriend,
lad. You're still a virgin. Yeah.
You've never had a girlfriend and you're
still a virgin. So, you're talking about yourself, lad.
It is funny to be fair. projecting your
life onto other people that you don't
know every day. It is kind of funny that
I found it funny as well. You've never
had a girlfriend and you're still a virgin. Yeah,
it's really funny. You got no family
either. You're sat on YouTube Christmas
Day. What a [ __ ] loser on YouTube Christmas.
That's funny, bro.
You're just all self-reflectives on this community, lads.
Your comments make me laugh.
>> [clears throat]
>> Oh, really? Yeah. That's nice, bro.
I know. I know, bro. You talk You talk
about yourself. If you people had a
woman, you wouldn't be sat on YouTube
every day talking about people that you
don't know. If you had a woman, you had
a girlfriend. So, it's just it's just
self-reflection of your [ __ ] lives.
That's why no one cares, lad.
because it's just self-reflection from
your own [ __ ] lives that you like to
self project that other people like onto other people. So yeah, [snorts]
Chicago Summers, [laughter]
that's your name. That's what Tibby
calls you, is it? Chicago Summers.
She called hers. [laughter] [clears throat]
It's [ __ ] hilarious.
in the women win.
>> Well, we won't on Thursday, but don't
you worry about that. We're causing mayhem, man. Absolute mayhem.
It's a pick you don't feel like this on
like the Thursdays, or the Fridays, or
the Saturdays. I fell on it on a Monday.
That's why I went on a madness on a Monday.
That's why, oh, it's a Monday. Should I
do a madness? And I thought, [ __ ] it.
But I saw the madness on the Monday.
Trust me, there will be a madness, lad.
I'm not [ __ ] stopping, bro. Bust. I'm
sick of these [ __ ] to last me a [ __ ] lifetime.
I'm sick of them, Chica. I'm sick of them.
I'm sick of these [ __ ] women, man.
Nothing [snorts and clears throat] lad.
Nothing much. Just the same old m. [snorts]
But I'm not trying to meet anyone on
Thursday. I'm just going on a madness. Chica,
it's not like I'll be going out to
what? Loads of birds with pretend
boyfriends. No thanks, lad.
I'll be dipping into central London.
I'll be going on a madness, bro.
Whiskeyedied a lot, lad. We're drinking
from the bottle, mate. Trust me. Yeah.
I'm going to cause a madness. Like a
proper proper proper madness.
Trust me, bro. Proper one. It was bad
enough Monday, even though it was a Monday.
Trust me, lad. Trust. Yeah.
I'm sick of these kind of women. Chico,
I'm sick of them. I hate him, bro. I
[ __ ] hate these little [ __ ]
I hate these little [ __ ] I hate these
little [ __ ] Trust me, bro. Watch.
Hate them, lad. Hate them.
going to go out in a bit. I need to go
for a walk, get some food, and then get
have the steak later. Yeah,
got some change here. Sir.
Yeah. Horn church. Why? Why? Why are you
saying go to horn church? It doesn't
matter where you go, lad.
They're just [ __ ] These women are just
[ __ ] It doesn't matter where you go.
Does not matter where you go, lad.
Do you get me, bro?
and it will be a madness cuz I've had
enough of it, bro. So, countdown them days, lad.
Countdown them [ __ ] days, bro. Cuz
it's going to be happening.
gonna be happening, mate. Trust me. Yeah. [snorts]
Other ways I'm going. I'll be back later. Yeah.