Oh, [ __ ] hell, man. Been laughing all
day. I have.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
Oh, some [ __ ] that away.
Some [ __ ] that away. [ __ ] Mom,
you've always been single, Trevor. Self-projecting, lad.
Talking about yourself, lad.
That's self-p projecting, buddy.
You're also disabled and you can't leave
the house as well.
Just like when I went to Middlesbr, bro,
and you didn't show up.
Won't get into that, lad. But yeah, you
know all about being single, lad.
Yeah, I'll let a few more people join, bro.
Talking about yourself, Trevor, lad.
That self projecting.
Yeah, we we have been through this. You
can get a timeout anyways, lad. See you later.
Yeah, we've been through this. I went to
Middlesbr when you didn't show up. See
you later, lad.
Well, I won £100 today on the FB TE's.
Yeah, I won £100 today on the FB TE's,
bro. Took out 100, got to 200.
That's towards Thursday, bro. When when
I go out on Thursdays. I'm sending it
Thursday, lad. I'm sending it, bro. hard. Yeah,
sending it hard, lad. Got the money here.
So, yeah. Still doing Thursday. It's
happening, lad. It's happening.
I got I got a bonus on Fishing Frenzy,
bro. Fishing Frenzy.
It was [ __ ] lad.
Yeah, I got a bonus on fishing frenzy,
bro. One pound. It paid [ __ ] like 37 quid.
Then I went on the roulette in it. So
yeah, I want 100. So
yeah, I got the 100 to 200. I took it.
So I'll use that for Thursday in it. I
need to get a haircut as well. So
nice winning money. It doesn't matter
how much it is taking money from them, eh? Lovely.
It's [ __ ] lovely taking money from
them in it.
So, I'll be out on uh I'll be sending it
Thursday anyways and that'll be it until
probably the 28th. Yeah.
Yeah. I had a curry anyways. I had an Indian.
Yeah, I had a curry.
I was trying to keep hitting it, but it
weren't having it. So, just took the
money in it. Yeah.
We'll put that towards the madness on Thursday. Yeah.
No, I don't care, lad. I won I won 100
pound today in the fy.
I'm out Thursday. I'm on the piss on Thursday. So,
um yeah. I kind of can't be bothered,
but I said I was going to do it. So,
yeah, I'm going in hard on Thursday, bro. Oh, wow.
Yeah, I put in 100. I got it to 200. So,
I need to get a haircut though. That
should pay for the haircut and the
drinking and that. Got more money anyways. Yeah,
should be good, bro. It should be good.
You know, I put 100. I basically just
double the money in it.
[ __ ] fishing frenzy is a [ __ ] bonus,
bro. [ __ ] bonus.
So, I could just use that to go out
drinking. See? Don't have to touch my
own money. So,
oh dear do me. Do we do we do we do me man?
Yeah, I just took it.
I need to go barbers.
I had an Indian. So,
I'll be curious to see how much I spend
on Thursday. Bob,
I want to see how much I'll spend. Be
interested in it. I bring my card with
me as well. I've got my money anyways,
but I want to see how much I'll spend.
Let me be be interested in it. Be interesting.
Depends though, you know, if you just
stick to Guinness, you ain't spending
more than60 if you're if you're just
sticking to Guinness, bro. That [ __ ]
you up, bro. You can't even They can't
even water it down.
So, haircut. So, I got £200 for the
haircut and the drinking.
So, we'll see if we exceed it. I've got
more money anyways, but I just want to see.
I reckon no. I reckon you'll I reckon
I'll just spend all of it to be honest.
But I don't think you'll need anymore.
But I think I will spend all of it.
How much do you reckon?
I reckon 80 to 120. I'm thinking
I'm thinking about 80 to 120. I'm spending
Oh, I won 100 pound in the FBI, bro. I
put £100 in, doubled it,
brought it to 200. And um I'm just using
that for Thursday, Thursday's content.
So, after I get a haircut, it should uh
leave me with 140
money. I've got more money obviously, so
we'll see. How much do you reckon we'll
be spending Steven Howard?
I reckon it's going to be 80 to about 120.
I don't mind anyways. I'm just curious,
bro. Like, I'm just wondering. I reckon. Yeah,
I might go out again Saturday. I don't know, bro.
How much you reckon we'll be spending?
Come on, bro. Let's let's let's hear it. 100. Yeah,
that this 200 pound needs to pay for the
haircut as well. The haircut and the drinking. So,
I got the money right here, bro. Not
showing it because that's what self
projectors do. Self projectors ask
people to show money.
No, I don't use escorts, bro.
200 to my name. I've got more than £200
to my name, mate. I've got more than 200
to my name. This is just money that I won.
200 to my name, bro. Are you serious?
Are you Are you actually serious?
200 I've got 200 to my name. No.
No, I don't think so. Yeah.
What do you think? 200 just on drinking?
Nah, you won't spend £200 just on drinking.
Dates, bro. Who gives a [ __ ] about
dates? What the [ __ ] are you on about?
Who cares about dates?
[ __ ] dates, lad.
Yeah, really. Well, I've got 200 right
next to me, but I'm not going to show you it.
Yeah, I got a lot more than £200, mate.
a lot more than that. It's lovely when
you don't know people, isn't it?
Oh, the joys of not knowing people.
Pretty much free spending money. Well,
£100, the haircut's going to cost 50.
Yeah, 50 will get you pissed. So,
yeah, it's a good chunk of it, bro. Yeah.
So I don't I don't have to touch my
money that I save which is good in it.
I've never been on a date. [ __ ] I don't
need to rely on anything, Trevor. I've
got more money than you, lad. You're the
disabled man, lad, that lets people go
to Middlesbrough and you don't show up.
You don't even leave your [ __ ] house,
you fat [ __ ]
You don't even leave your house, you fat
[ __ ] I've got more money than you'd
ever have. Why do you Why do you think
these Hey, Steven Howard, why do you
think I don't show these people money?
Because it's self-reflecting. Have you
noticed why I don't show I could show
these people 20 pound right now, they
can't double it. But I don't I don't
show self-reflecting projecting people
money. Do you get it?
Yeah. Listen, listen. The videos was
uploaded when I was there, lad. Yeah.
All you had to do was walk down the
road. Yeah. And it's just excuses with
you, Trevor. It's excuses. I' We've been
over this before. And no one agrees with
you. Literally, no one agrees with you,
mate. You're a fat old man in
Middlesbrough. You don't even leave your
house. Yeah. I was doing a video calling
you out. You didn't even try to meet me.
Everybody knew I was in Newcastle.
Everyone knew I was in Middlesbrough.
Shut up. You're boring, lad. You're
never going to meet no one. Shut up.
Just like Just like if I went to
Middlesbrough tomorrow, you wouldn't
come out. You would easily just walk up
the road to see if I was there or not.
But you didn't even do that. So shut up.
You can use all the excuses you want, lad.
Yeah, you can use any excuse that you
want, but it's silly.
So yeah. Anyway, Steven, man. So yeah,
it's free spending money. Yeah,
but I need to get a haircut as well. So
I can come up there anytime I want. Lad,
you don't know how much money I have.
That's the That's the joys of not
knowing what people have and what people
don't have. How can you doubt stuff when
you don't know what people have? You
don't know how much money people have.
You literally don't know how much money
people have. This is what I mean with
you people in this community. You base
you base your lives right on other
people. Sorry. You base your own lives
on other people, lads. That's what you people do.
You base your lives on other people's lives.
You think everyone lives the same life
as you. Got no money, no nothing. People
needs to rely on gambling. No. No. Would
have went out Thursday. Either way, I've got money.
I would have went out either way. I've
got money, but it's nice that I don't
have to spend my own money. You know
what I mean? Steven Howard, do you know
why it's good Steven Howard? Because I
know exactly what's going to happen
Thursday, but it's something to do
anyways. I know exactly what's going to
happen. So, it's good that I don't have
to spend my own money doing it, isn't it?
It's good that I don't have to spend my
own money doing it. You get it?
maybe 30 pound of it, but you know what I mean.
So, yeah, man.
Got it ready for Thursday anyways.
Yeah. Yeah. You can suspect what you
want, lad. You don't You don't know what
people have. You don't know what people
don't have. That's nice, man.
Doesn't matter, Trevor. I've had more
women than you, lad. You don't even
leave your house. You don't even leave
your house. And do you know what, Trevor
Dawson? I laugh at you people every day.
I get more laughs out of you than you
ever get out of me. Fat, ugly, lonely
people. Everyone laughs at you as well,
lad. We all have giggles out of you.
People on YouTube as well. 24/7 on
YouTube. We laugh at you people as well.
Sat on YouTube, no life. We get so many
giggles out of you, too. You don't even
believe. Hey, these people don't even
leave their houses.
These people like Trevor Dawson, bro,
they don't even leave the house. They're
just fat, ugly, miserable people sat on
the internet every day. I get bigger
laughs out of you than you get out of
me. Like, I get so many giggles out of
you people, right, than you will ever
get out of me.
So many giggles. Like, you don't
understand. You're what people don't
want to be like when they're older.
Anyways, we're going to put this clown
on time out now cuz he's ruining our
chat and he's trying to kill the vibe.
Yeah, lot. I'll be out sat I'll be out on um
I'll be out Thursday, bro. I won £100 on
the FBOT today. So, yeah.
Oh, look. I've just [ __ ] banned this
guy for no reason. This is what I mean,
bro. Look at these haters. They just
ruin everything, bro. They ruin the chat.
They just ruin the chat, bro. It's not
even funny, lad. It's [ __ ] annoying.
These fat, ugly self-reflectors.
One second, bro. I've just bobbed this
guy out. I just banned this guy.
Nope. I can afford to go out without
spending my own money. Yeah, it's
lovely, isn't it? Yeah, that's lovely,
isn't it? Oh, all in Rose. You do not
know how much money people have.
You do not know how much money people
have. You really don't. You don't know
anything. That's what makes it funny.
You don't know how much any You don't
know how much money people have.
I don't even know how to unblock people, lad.
I'm going out with I'm going out with
myself just like Lord Jen went out by
himself the other day.
But he's just a copycat. He tries to be
like me. But yeah. Yeah. Anyways,
sorry Bob. We had to block you by accident, lad.
I'm not playing a money game. That self project.
So yeah, it's going to be a madness
Thursday. Steven Howard, man. Madness.
And I might do Saturday, too.
Yeah. And just like you people, doggy,
right? Sat on YouTube 24/7, but you got
all this money and this perfect life,
right? We're going to start banning
these self-reflectors. Yeah, that's
that. Um, what I was saying is, uh,
yeah, just like you, doggy, all this
money, all this life that sat on YouTube 24/7
talking about people that you don't
know. Make it make sense. Hey, I was
busy all day today, Stephen Howard. I
went for a walk. I gambled. Um, I was
busy today, bro. That's why I hadn't
been on. And this is how you know these
people have got nothing because they're
sat on the internet every day talking
about people that they don't know.
They're sat on the internet all day
talking about people that they don't
know. Don't let them Don't let them try
and tell you that they've got anything.
All jokes aside, UK asylum. Yeah. Like,
jokes aside, yeah, no trolling. This is
serious. Do not let these people try to
tell you that you don't know them and
you're speculating. Bro, what they do on
here, it shows they've got nothing.
Trust me, no one would have that much
time on their hands. Trust me, they're
sat on YouTube with no one and nothing.
Trust me. That's why they That's why they self-reflect.
You understand, lad? They're on YouTube
because they got nothing. That's that in it.
Anyways, uh you get banned lads. See you
later. So yeah, I was going to go out
regardless. Win, didn't win, lose. I
would have went out regardless. I've got money. So yeah,
see you later. Self-reflector.
And that's that.
you get banned, lad.
I was actually tempted to go to
Birmingham today, you know, because it
does tempt you, you know. You know, when
you don't have to use your own money and
stuff, but we just know what it's always
going to be with these people. It's
always going to go around in circles and
no, waste of time, lad.
I'll be out Thursday like I said I was
going to. That's that. Yeah,
you watch my video on launch legs. Thank you, Captain.
But then we need to
Yeah, I might be out Saturday as well,
Stephen Hour. It depends. But I'll stay
local if I do on Saturday, but we're
going out out Thursday, bro.
I don't have the energy for it anymore, lads. So,
Thursday will be a madness though. Don't worry.
I had a curry, by the way. So,
no, I'm going out Thursday.
Yeah, I'm going I'm going out on Thursday, man.
I won £100 today, so yeah, it'll pay for
some of it. I was going to go out regardless
whether I won or lost anyways, so it don't matter.
Long time ago.
Yeah. 100 to 200. Got it here. Need to
get a haircut. Going to get on the
drink, get some food and [ __ ] That's
that. I don't need to spend any on my own money. Yep.
Yeah, it was roulette. Yeah.
Well, I got a bonus on fish and frenzy.
It paid [ __ ] £30. It was [ __ ] I just
went on the roulette. Yeah,
it's another self-reflector. See you
later. I just banned these self-reflectors,
self-projecting weirdos. They just get
banned. They just get kicked.
It is nowadays, isn't it?
Cuz it's so hard to win nowadays.
I know. So many jealous people, bro.
They They've been the same for years on
here, Ian. You just laugh at them.
They're just fat ugly old men. You just
laugh at them.
Haircut's going to cost 50 something.
That leaves me with 140.
Yeah, man. On for free, bro. But yeah.
Yeah, I want it on the bar. Roulette,
you're laughing. Like I said, you can
laugh, right? One second. You can laugh
about you can you can laugh when people
when people are calling you jealous but
you know deep down that you are jealous
cuz none of you people show your faces.
You people on here 24/7 talking about
people that you don't know. So yeah, you
are jealous. There's nothing to laugh
about what you are, lad. That guy's
right. You people are jealous. Most of
you people on here are fat and ugly. And
then you laughing when you call jealous.
Why you laughing when you call jealous, bro?
Most of you on here are fat and ugly and
you and you're laughing when people are
calling you jealous, bro. Come on. Most
of you pe most of you haters on here
don't even leave your house.
Yeah. And and you're laughing. Like it's farfetched.
Yeah, bro. Dusty, you can't use that
excuse, lad. We've already been over
this. We've already been over this, lad.
We've already been over this. I'm not
going over it again. We're talking about
other stuff. We're not talking about these people.
You know, we've been over this million
times, bro. Why is it escalating to this again? So, yeah.
And like I said, Stephen, I would I
might go out Saturday as well. Depends
if I can be bothered. So, Yeah,
this depends, man. V. Yeah,
I got my football bets paid for as well on Saturday. So, yeah. Yep.
I'm going to be [ __ ] bro, on Friday.
I'm going to be [ __ ] on Friday, lad. No, Thursday.
N Thursday, lad.
cuz it's Monday today. Is it? I'm not
going out Monday again. [ __ ] that. It's
going to be Thursday.
She's all right. Yeah,
that Christian Izzy was [ __ ] lunatic, bro.
Stephen, she's a [ __ ] lunatic, man.
Proper lunatic, in it.
I don't care about it anymore, bro. But yeah, man.
I can't be [ __ ] lad. I can't be
At the end of the day, these people
don't help themselves in it. So, just
leave them in it. They don't help themselves.
These people don't help themselves, lad.
You can't help people that don't help themselves.
So that's it, isn't it?
But we're still doing a madness on Thursday.
They just don't help themselves like
these people. And she was crying,
sending voice notes, crying and [ __ ]
Like what the [ __ ] bro? [ __ ]
mentally unstable as [ __ ] man. What the [ __ ] bro?
mad. You're [ __ ] You're actually
really off. But they don't help
themselves in it. So you can't feel
sorry for people that don't help
themselves. Really, these people have to
help themselves, but they don't. It's
[ __ ] mad, is it?
No, I think she's just too damaged.
She's just too far gone, lad. Damaged.
Do you know what made me laugh? Yeah.
She's like, "Don't get lippy with me." I
was dead. I was [ __ ] dead, bro. Don't
get lippy with me. Sorry, I banned you
by accident, bro. This [ __ ]
I was trying to ban someone else.
Yeah, man. I got my Spider-Man t-shirt
on today, bro. It's sick. I need to go
barbers. The reason I didn't go today is
cuz I ain't going out today.
Yeah, I was about this other [ __ ]
[ __ ] But um yeah,
don't know why she was crying at
Christian. I was even rude to her. What the [ __ ]
She's like, I can't believe you said that.
She must have had some
[ __ ] up experience, bro, with someone
that she's met or something. She's not
all there in her head, bro. Trust me.
Like a lot of these [ __ ]
I don't have a white coat, lad.
Don't have a white coat. So, yeah. Yeah,
it's cream. I don't know what I'm
wearing. Depends on the weather. It was
hot today. It was actually warm today. I
might wear my blazer with my Rit the
Bear trousers. I might wear the coat. I
don't know what I'm wearing.
Depends what the weather is saying.
You never had an Amazon coat in my life,
lad. You're just a hater, bro. Just go
back on L J's channel. You're just a hater.
So yeah, this money is going towards
finding a new mama.
And you know, do I really care about
going out Thursday? Not really. But I
don't want to deprive [ __ ] Greavesy
of content. The poor [ __ ]
especially when it's not coming out my own money.
So yeah, poor [ __ ]
He's already been through enough, you
know. Poor [ __ ]
Yeah, she's crazy, bro.
Definitely had mental issues, isn't it? Steven Howard
definitely had mental issues.
Yeah, she blocked me on um
Tuesday. Last Tuesday she blocked me. Yeah.
But I don't feel bad at the end of the
day. that these people tried to play the
victim and I know what their games are
so it doesn't work with me. Their little
games don't work with me, bro. Yeah. So, yeah.
Yeah. [ __ ] him anyways, bro.
No, no, no. Yeah.
Oh, Greavvesy. Okay. So, I went in um
I went into the bookies today. Uh I put
£100 in I got to 200 now and I took it
and obviously that's going towards
Thursday. Need to get a haircut and then
obviously get on the drink and stuff. Um
now Grevy obviously I don't really care
like about drinking anymore or going out
whatever. Could have just put the money
like with my other savings and stuff but
then I thought I can't deprive Greavvesy
of the of content. Poor [ __ ]
You know poor [ __ ] It's not it's not
[ __ ] it's not coming out of you know our money
you know £200 going to pay for the
haircut and the drinks isn't it? So poor
poor [ __ ] greasy poor [ __ ]
It was quite hot today. Greavvesy quite warm.
Yeah, we're going uh we're doing it.
We're doing it Thursday. greasy and if
you're lucky I might even go out
Saturday as well.
Okay with you, boss.
What I do to give you [ __ ]
what I do to to give you content, eh?
Yeah, bro. I'm just going to get on the
piss and send it. Yeah.
So, I put this I'm I'm going to I'm
going to use this money
I'm going to use this money to find a
new mama. It's going to be toward It's
going to be towards finding a new mama.
Dusty, dusty, dusty, dusty, dusty. What
else am I going to be doing on Thursday? H
What else am I going to be doing on Thursday?
It's a mama fund. Yeah. Literally. Yeah.
Yeah. What else am I going to be doing,
bro? It's not coming out of my money, so
I don't give a [ __ ] What else am I
going to be doing? So
I have given up, bro. I have given up. I
need to get a haircut anyways. So
yeah, £100 on a FBI.
Yeah. 100 pound on a FBI. Yeah,
I thought Let me try. Yeah,
I don't give a [ __ ] if I pull. I don't
pull, lad. I just want to get pissed. I
don't give a [ __ ]
I won't give it back a more, lad. I
won't give it back a more. Trust me, I'm
smart. I know what I'm doing.
Trust me, I know what I'm doing, lad. I
know it wasn't. It was normal roulette.
Well, not normal roulette, but the the
one with the zeros.
I won't give it back. I'm all that. Trust me.
I know what I'm doing, bro. Yeah,
I'll be pissed on Thursday, bro.
There's nothing else to do, so I might
as well leave Laney in peace for a day.
I'm going everywhere.
Do I like drinking? No, not really.
It's just something to do.
If it was out coming out of my money,
Greavves, I'd think maybe twice about it.
I don't need I don't need to drink to
have confidence, bro. I'm confident already.
Drink doesn't give me confidence either. Cuz
you remember what I was saying about
like you getting banned, Greasy. Yeah,
you getting banned. Listen to me, bro.
Yeah, he didn't get me borrowed from
Waxies. I was in Waxies last Monday, lad.
I was in Waxies last Monday. Got a
couple of numbers there. So, we
definitely didn't cuz I was in Waxies
last Monday, lad.
Anyways, Grezy, listen. Uh,
so you know how they ban like they b
they try to ban you for no reason.
That's why I didn't want to give them my
money, but you know that's obviously
good because you win money. Then I don't
give a [ __ ] You get it, lad?
No, Mother's Day is already sorted, lad.
It's next Sunday.
Yeah, it's next Sunday. Yeah.
So yeah, I was in I was in waxies last Monday, lad.
I was in waxies last Monday.
Promise you I was. Last Monday I was in
Maxis. No one said nothing. Trust me. So
went by myself.
Went by myself.
If I get a wide ride Thursday, you It's
not going to happen.
You're not going to get a ride. You're
not even going to get a date, lad.
You're living on law. You're living
You're living in La La Land.
Nope. I don't need mates, bro. When I'm
going out trying to trying to meet a
woman, I'm not going to go out with
mates, am I? I'm I'm going to go out by myself.
I got loads of friends I can go out with
on Thursday. I was speaking to my friend
today from Reen. I don't want to. I want
to go out by myself. Simple as that.
I can easily get someone to meet me
Thursday. I know loads of people. I want
to go out by myself. Simple as that.
Cuz I don't need to rely on No, brother.
Is that right, Grezy?
Never had a problem before, lad. I've
pulled loads of times by myself.
Sometimes I go out with people, but I
prefer to go out by myself.
See LJ trying to trying to be me. Um,
greasy. The little copycat.
the little copycat.
With a bit of luck, you might get lucky.
No, you of course you're not going to
get lucky. It's not about luck, lad.
It's never going to change. It's always
going to be the same. But it's something
to do in it.
You're not going to get lucky. It's
always going to be the same. I just
don't want to deprive Greaves of
content. The poor [ __ ] It will never
ever ever be different.
But Laney gets the house before they I
get to do something. Yeah, it's fine,
isn't it? I at least get my haircut anyway. So,
there's like you've got Well, saying
that you've got a 1% chance.
You've got a 1% chance,
but I wouldn't bank on it. You got a 1% chance. Yeah.
To get drunk
and collect some numbers. Is that right, Greavvesy? Yeah.
You've probably got about
It's probably about one in
realistically it's probably about one in 20,000 lad.
I've not I've not tried hard enough.
Good one Leslie lad. Good one.
Nope. I don't drink full of confidence.
I'm confident. Completely sober lad. I
do approaches sober. I go out once
sober. Nope. Must be talking about yourself, lad.
I don't need drink to make me confident.
I can approach sober. Sober, drunk,
anywhere, train, I don't give a [ __ ]
where. Nope. I don't need drink to give me confidence. So,
you know that ain't it, Grezy? You've
seen a million approaches sober.
Yeah, that's self projecting. Check 121.
That's self projecting. Yeah, please.
You need to get another one. Is it really?
Oh, I've plugged it. I've unplugged it.
>> Yeah, we're going to ban these people anyways. Yeah.
We're going to ban these self projectors.
All right. You know what? I noticed
every time I go drinking that Kin always
comes back on my channel.
Have you noticed that?
Have you noticed that Grezy? Whenever I
come back drinking, he's always there in it.
See you later, lad. God, man. What the
[ __ ] So many bitter old projectors.
They must be jealous cuz I won 100 pound
or something cuz I'm going out Thursday
and I'm giving Grezy some content. Isn't
that right, Grezy?
I think these people are getting
jealous, Stephen. I would lad. Yeah,
I think these people are getting jealous, man.
Definitely getting jealous again, is it?
These lavry mongs are very weird, Steven
Howard. Very, very weird.
Greasy Christy Lizzy said, "Don't get lippy.
Don't get lippy with me."
Oh, bro, I was dead. Don't get lippy.
Now, you know what that means?
Do you know what that means?
I will lad. I will.
Yeah. See you later, lad. You get a time out. Mom,
do you know what don't get lippy means?
I said, do you know what don't get lippy means?
I'm a I'm a cheeky monkey.
Oh, I remember before. Yeah, I was
reporting something to the police before
and this black police was like, "Oh,
don't get um don't get He said, "Don't
get cheeky." I said, "I'm a cheeky
monkey." I get I said, "I'll get as
cheeky. I'll get as cheeky as I want.
I'm a cheeky monkey. Don't tell me what
to do, you [ __ ] silly [ __ ] in a
shitty little uniform. You don't have no
[ __ ] all furry over me, you [ __ ] eating [ __ ]
You know what I mean? That's all police
are [ __ ] eating [ __ ]
Pigs. That's all they [ __ ] are.
[ __ ] tell me what to do cuz you wear
a shitty little uniform. Got no [ __ ]
authority over me. You're not no [ __ ] judge. Piggies. Yeah.
Oh, that's funny, bro.
Nope. I'll never no more.
Yeah, that tenant was definitely trying
to scam me in it. Definitely trying it,
was it? He was definitely trying to scam
me, wasn't he, Dusty?
In it. Yeah.
Definitely in it.
Mom, that tenant was definitely trying
to scam. Is it?
They must think you're stupid, isn't it? Cheeky [ __ ]
cheeky [ __ ] pies.
That's what they are. Cheeky [ __ ] py
That's what they [ __ ] are.
>> Yeah, that's what they Thursday is definitely happening.
Just cuz you can't imagine doing it, lad.
Just cuz you can't imagine doing it.
Don't uh don't [ __ ] don't don't don't
self project that you're [ __ ] onto me. I
know what I'm doing. Thursday. I'm a man
on a mission UK asylum. And I've got the mama fund.
Yeah. To find my mama.
Peter Belly can't get attached anymore
because he's already found his mama. UK
asylum. He's already found his mama.
Cuz he's already found his mama. Yeah.
It's happening, lad. It's [ __ ] happening.
It's [ __ ] happening, mate. You know.
Oh gosh. I'm going to have a can of Coke
in a minute. Oh gosh.
Is that Vindaloo? It dries your mouth out, man.
Now, I'm not autistic like you and LJ, lad.
When I say I'm going to do something, I
deliver. I I [ __ ] deliver, lad.
Yeah, I got a [ __ ] bonus on fishing
frenzy. I only paid 30 something pound,
dusty one pound steak.
What a load of balls.
Yeah, definitely. Definitely sure.
Oh, do you know what I might do? Yeah, I
might I might flip a coin and be like,
"Okay, I either go out sending it in
London or I go to Birmingham and knock
Timmy Elders out." Like, flip a coin.
Like, flip a coin in it.
What do you think?
Yeah. I just flip just flip flip a coin
in it. Yeah.
No, but they call you something though.
They do. They call you something though.
Players number. They call you the loner
on YouTube Christmas Day.
They say, "Look at that player's number.
The little [ __ ] with no girlfriend on
YouTube Christmas Day. Sat on YouTube.
No life. I've heard that. There's a
rumor going around about you, lad. I
don't know if it's true, but they're
like, "Oh, look at that loser sat on
YouTube Christmas Day, no family."
Again, I'm not [ __ ] you know what I
mean? I'm not I'm not saying anything,
bro. But that's the rumor going around, you know?
So, Greavvesy, what did you think of LJ
drinking in the pub and going live?
What's your opinion on that?
What's your opinion on that, Greavvesy?
H what's your opinion on that? >> Yeah.
Oh, well, basically he was going live in
the Weather Spoons.
The thing is, Grezy, I've done that a
lot. I've gone out drinking live and now
he's doing it. He's he he's kind of
doing the same thing as me. No,
he's a little copycat.
You a little copycat?
No, I heard about it.
I didn't see it, but I heard about it.
Yeah, I heard about it. Yeah. Are you a little coffee?
Yeah, I need to get a phone to be
honest, bro. That's not blocked, but I
can't be bothered right now.
I'll go live in the places, bro. It's
fine, isn't it?
You can use it anywhere. I mean, there's
Wi-Fi everywhere, so yeah. Yeah.
Are you looking forward to um Thursday greasy?
Oh, I might go to Birmingham. I don't
know, bro. Cuz you know what is Grezy?
Yeah, I was walking earlier. Yeah, just
walking. Uh cuz I went to get some food
and I couldn't stop thinking in my head.
I just couldn't stop thinking in my head, lad.
Them Birmingham [ __ ] were laughing at
you, mocking you. And you know when when
and when stuff like that happens, bro.
Yeah. You really don't care where you
go. You don't care about the distance.
Laughing at you. Mocking you. Seriously, bro.
I think we can let it lie, lad. We might
have We might have to do We might have
to do the coin flip.
We might have to do a coin flip. Greasy. Yeah.
Mocking you. Yeah.
You know why he got he went to Marley
Bone? Because his anxiety is so bad. He
can't he can't go to Houston. Houston's
a massive train station. Why do you
think he went to Marley Bone?
Uh, it's from Ant-Man.
Them [ __ ] were laughing at you.
[ __ ] you. You remember that come back
someone and started saying that.
What do you think of the Do you want to
add to the mama fund, Greavesy?
Do you want to add to the mama fund? Huh?
I'll be look I'll be look smacking on
Thursday as well.
Oh, it doesn't matter anyways. We've got enough.
So, how much money do you reckon I'm
going to have left from the 200 GBsy
after I get my haircut and go drinking?
How much do you think? How much do you
think I'm going to have less?
I think zero, mate. Abs. I think zero. Yeah,
maybe. Maybe £60. Maybe, bro.
No, I need to get a haircut.
So, it's going to be £140 I have left.
Well, that's that though. I've got my
own money anyways, but of that. So,
no. I think we'll spend about 100.
No, no, no, no, no.
It depends. Look, when I went out on
Monday, I only spent £50.
I spent £50, bro.
No, I'm not super rich. I wish I [ __ ] was rich.
I'm just careful and I just save money.
Nothing rich about me, lad.
None of them mas reply to me. Um, Grezy,
but it's all just a bit of fun, eh?
No, just earlier when I won that £100.
If you want to show me 10 grand, you can.
That must have took you about a year to
save that 10 grand in it.
That must have took you [ __ ]
But like you don't really go out and
spend money though, do you?
You don't really go out and spend money, do you? So
that's good, is it?
Yeah. Still going out, mate. I won £100
today. We're putting it towards the day.
We're putting it towards Thursday.
Yeah. See, if I if I stayed for a couple
of months, bro, I would have had a lot
more. But obviously, I went out drinking
and [ __ ] so
I can't stay in that long [ __ ]
I can't do that. I know people do it. I
look at [ __ ] Virgin Boy. He's missed
out on a lot of life experiences for the
sake of [ __ ] bum a bum chains amount of money.
That will never be me, bro. You You only live once.
You only live once. So you could die tomorrow. So
I might get some more Lego Greavesy. Yeah.
I'm going to I might get the SP I'm
going to get the Spider-Man one. Greasy.
Do I get Greasy when I go out and collect mumas?
You like it when I go out and collect mums.
Yeah, I need to find a new mama. Every
single mama I find [ __ ] abandons me. The [ __ ]
Yeah, life's more peaceful that way.
Greavves, you don't get your heart broken.
You don't get your heart broke that way.
Have you noticed, Greavves? I'm normal
now. I'm calm and stuff. No anxiety like
I was getting last week. That [ __ ]
Christian Izzy was giving me anxiety,
bro. What the [ __ ] No, no.
You can also get vitamins from bananas,
too, and milkshakes.
Oh gosh, I fancy a milkshake, actually. Oh gosh.
I actually fancy a milkshake, you know.
No, I fancy a [ __ ] milkshake.
Dude, dude, I want a Five Guys one.
Yeah, who is he? Mate, we just ignore
Timmy Aldridge. Timmy Aldridge is a [ __ ]
We just ignore that [ __ ]
don't we, Grezy?
Nah, bro. I'm not going to get it, bro.
Just going to have a coke.
I'll get a milkshake tomorrow. Yes, sir.
soon to be Robert the Bear. Greasy.
Soon to be Rbert to bear.
So what you're saying, Grezy?
So what you're saying, Grezy, if I go to
if I go to Birmingham, right, and put it
on YouTube and call it the madness.
What? So what you're basically saying is
that's the same website you can watch Elmo on.
The same website you can watch Elmo on.
that visits the form.
Is that what you're saying?
Is that what you're basically saying, lad?
>> Mhm. That makes me want to do it even more.
That makes me want to do it even more, lad.
That makes me want to do it even more.
You see, that makes me want to do it even more
cuz it's exciting. It's fun, you know. Crazy.
Look, I'm going to get my I might get my
outfit uh ready for um for Thursday actually.
Right, let's have a little look. Let's
have a little gander. Okay. Oh gosh.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. Look,
these are my Robert the Bear trousers.
Oh gosh, you can't even see it. Oh gosh, look.
These are the Robert the Bear trousers.
I'm going to wear a blazer and a nice
little turtleneck top.
You like them? They're Robert the Bear trousers.
And I've got a boss belt to go with it, too.
I think that's [ __ ] sexy. Me, bro.
Yeah. Look, I got this.
Tell it. Look. Yeah.
With a nice little blazer.
I'm going to wear with a blazer.
Lovely, lovely stuff. Oh gosh.
So, I go to Birmingham with them
trousers. No, I've not got Scooby-D.
This is my favorite thing. Yeah, bro. I
love this. I can't remember the last
time I wore it. Look. 200 pound.
200. This is
Yeah. Don't know. I might just wear that
with like the Vapor or something. I
don't know. I don't know what I'm
wearing, bro. [ __ ]
But then I could just wear that Saturday.
Might just wear the blazer on that
Thursday and then Saturday just wear
more something more casual if I go out in it.
I'm wearing my Spider-Man top. Easy.
The westernity took over.
The Westinity took over, lads.
Did it take over
the the took over?
Where you mama? Why you mom?
I've had your milkshake, mama.
Well, it's too cold now. You silly goose.
Why do you want one?
You want me to go all the way and get a [ __ ] milkshake? [ __ ] that.
A [ __ ] that. No, no,
no, no, no, no. That's [ __ ] That's long.
That's long. That is long. No.
No. You can order us.
No, [ __ ] that. I like a banana and a
milkshake. I'm not going out. [ __ ] that, bro. Tired, man. Oh gosh.
Crazy. Oh gosh. Coca-Cola.
What do you get out of trolling on
YouTube, Grezy? Why do you troll people?
Mhm. What do you get out of it, man? Serious.
You know that whole Timmy thing lady was
watching it as it was happening like she
was watching it live from where he was
until we come under VZ.
You couldn't make it up in it. You
like from the time where he was right
until he come and got so she she was
waiting for him. She was waiting for him
all on the same website you could watch
Spider-Man on. No.
No, mate. That's [ __ ] Huh? Oh gosh.
Uh uh uh uh uh
uh uh uh uh.
Because he's already found his mama. Oh gosh.
So, what are we predicting for Thursday?
>> I think you need to chill out.
Is that right?
>> Yeah. Everybody knows. Everybody knows
that you're a crazy [ __ ]
Everybody knows that you're a crazy [ __ ]
No, I ain't staying there, mate. I'm
[ __ ] sending it, you [ __ ] That's
what I'm [ __ ] doing. I'm [ __ ]
going to send it. I'm going to find a
new mama and then [ __ ] off. I'm going to
find a new mama.
No, serious. I'm going out
cuz it's probably going to be one of the
last times I do to be fair, bro.
Then we're on it. We need to stack
money. We need to leave. So
yeah, but I know what I'm going to end
up doing. I'm probably going to end up
[ __ ] drinking. Yeah, I'm probably
going to end up [ __ ] drinking and
[ __ ] messaging that Christian is
I know what I'm like, mate. I know what
with these smartphones.
You know what I'm saying? I know what
I'm like, mate. Going to stop [ __ ]
Well, you know, I like you little [ __ ]
Come on, you [ __ ] Come on, you [ __ ]
I love laughing, you know.
So Laney was waiting for him to come
by the when he was there right from when
he was there all the way to when he come
in the door. She was watching the live
stream. She was watching it live
all on the same website. Root the Bears
on. You couldn't make it up. Steven Howard,
why waste 200, bro? Cuz we've got 200 to waste, bro.
You got money, bro. It's fine.
You never know. Pending. It could be different.
It could be different this time, lad. Yeah,
she did. Yeah,
to be fair. N
I've done my clothes. I put clothes wash
on Steven Howard.
Ready to get into my nice fresh clothes
when I come in on Thursday after my
little night out and stuff. Oh gosh.
Don't get lippy. Christian said don't
Don't get lippy with me.
It was the neighbor, bro. It was the neighbor.
Yeah, the label M
don't get liy with me. She don't get liy.
I kind of I don't feel sorry for her
though, bro. Even though she got bad
anxiety and [ __ ] like [ __ ] That's
your choice, man. You know, you go you
go for these people. [ __ ] I mean, you
go for these people. So,
what do you expect? You know what I'm saying?
So, these people are so weird.
And I'll be approaching as well um on um
Thursday and I'll be doing it in front
of that game manager as well.
I'll be doing it in front of him.
Trust me though, madness will be uh
don't even know why she blocked me to come.
Yeah. So, if he comes up on um if he
comes up to me on Thursday, I'll just do
an approach in front of him
and I'll make fun out of him with the
person that I'm I'm approaching.
Yeah, I was watching Launch Legs's video.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, I was watching Launch Legs's
response. Steven Howard.
Eene, is that you? Eileen,
don't think I'll actually go to
Birmingham, do you, Steven Howard?
You don't think I'd actually do it, do you?
I will, mate. Trust me, I will, mate.
You don't believe me, do you?
Well, you don't think I would go?
You don't think I would go, lad? Oh gosh. Who's that? Use that.
You don't go. Of course I will, lad. Of
course I will. Of course I would.
Do you remember that video where Timmy's
going mad saying to Monty, "Come here
now. Come to Chelmsley Wood. I was dead.
I was dead, bro." He's like, "Come to
Chelmsley Wood then. Come to Chelmsley Wood,
bro. What the [ __ ]
Come to Chelmsley Wood.
Do you remember that grieving?
Sorry. Um, Dusty. Oh gosh.
Yeah. I'm not speaking to Christian, is he anymore?
I used to like talking to her, you know.
We used to speak every day and stuff.
It's nice to have someone to talk to, you know. Oh, no. No. Yeah, probably.
What was the point of me? What's the
point of sending loads of messages to
then delete the messages?
I got some of it because I was out and
then I come back. It's like, "Oh, you're
delusional. You're scary." And that,
"Oh, you're delusional. You're scary."
Mad, bro. Madness.
I think she had a screw loose, lad.
Steven Howard, I think she had a screw loose. Yeah.
No, not at all, lad. Not at all.
I actually didn't.
I actually didn't, lad.
I was just drinking on a Monday. I said,
"Oh, let's meet up in it. Let's talk." Yeah.
No, I actually didn't. No, bro.
She thinks you're actually scary. How am
I scared? She know you're actually scary. Steven
Howard, you said I dodged the bullet
though, is it?
Yeah. I scared her by saying, "Oh, let's
meet up and talk." Yeah, that scared her. Yeah.
And that's how I got blocked.
Well, you think she's unstable?
I think she's unstable, lad.
I think she's unstable now.
I don't know why she was crying on the
voice notes all cuz I said you're not
going to ever find anyone as good as me.
Yeah, I didn't mean to.
Yeah, I didn't mean to, bro. I didn't
say anything bad.
I'd never message her again on another
number or anything.
Never, lad. I would never do that. Never
ever would I do that. I don't that with
USA is he? I would never do that again, bro.
It's not that lad.
I got too much respect for myself.
No, obviously not.
I didn't even say anything bad. I don't
know why she was crying though. I didn't
even say anything bad, bro.
Sad, isn't it?
I don't like hearing people cry, bro. I feel bad.
I didn't say anything bad. That's what
I'm trying to say. That's what I'm
trying to say, lad.
I don't know why she was crying though, bro.
All I wanted to do was meet up.
All I wanted to do is meet up Steven Howard
and be a friend and stuff. Do you know
what I mean?
And look at what it caused.
But people like that don't help
themselves. You know what I'm saying?
People like that don't want to be helped.
You get me?
They don't help themselves. They don't
want to be helped.
No, I didn't. I actually never.
I love it. Pips smoker. I love it. I actually didn't.
I actually really didn't. That's the thing.
I just said, "Oh, let's meet up and talk
in it. I'll come to where you like your
area and that.
I'll come to the five guys and that."
You know what I mean?
That's all I said. Yeah.
I actually did say about this
Yeah, I'm crazy when I'm drunk. But I
didn't say anything bad, bro. I've got
the voice not still there. No. No,
I just basically said if you want an
apology, meet me in it. >> Yeah.
She was playing games before that
anyway. Stephen Hardwood lad, she
deleted my number. Oh, why'd you delete
my number? She said, "Oh, I didn't. I
didn't." So, she was playing games anyways. I mean,
trust me, nothing was nothing bad was said, lad.
It all started when I asked her to meet.
I said, "Oh, your exams are finished.
Let's meet next week." And then she was
like making excuses. And then obviously
there's me thinking like, "You just
spoke to someone for a whole month.
They're making excuses now not to meet
you." I'm thinking like, "Oh, like I
basically said I basically said, "Oh,
like well, you're obviously not going to
let me know, are you? Because why can't
you just meet up like as a friend? They
don't understand what the problem is.
You said you was going to meet, so why
didn't you meet him?
Um, you know, and that's how it all
started 3 weeks after basically.
So, yeah. And obviously people would get
pissed off. If someone's been speaking
to someone for a month, of course you're
going to get pissed off. Anyone would. So, yeah. Yeah.
But Steven Howard for a whole month.
Speaking to someone for a whole month. That's mad.
just to do that. Yeah. For a whole
month. That is [ __ ]
That was crazy, bro.
She could have actually been with a
really like normal person that didn't do
all of these things that she told me her
ex has done. So, at the end of the day,
it's their loss, Steven Howard, with
these people. It's their loss. It's no
one else's loss.
Do you know what I'm saying? So in the
end, it's always their loss. You get me.
If you look up uh chat GBT, it will say
the same thing. You want to try and meet
people with well chat GBT says 3 to 7
days. I say 4 to seven days.
Yeah, you should try to meet somebody
within 4 to seven days.
How do you know she was flaking? Steven Howard.
Yeah. As soon as someone says I let you know, bro, [ __ ]
it's over, lad. Simple as that.
Yeah, she didn't delete the pic, bro.
She deleted my number and she tried
saying that she never. She showed me
that she had she still had me saved, but
there's no way you definitely delete my
number because the the symbol removed
itself as well. So, I know she
definitely deleted my number.
She said that she removed it, but no, no
way cuz the status got removed as well.
So, no, no, no, no, no.
She definitely delete my number.
What do you think? Delete the picture.
Steen Alor deleting my number.
Definitely the real one.
Mad people though bro. Mad people
are mad in it.
Yeah, you already know, bro. 100%.
No, no, no, no. What probably happened was
he probably got back with her ex.
That's more than likely what happened. Nah,
I reckon she just got back with her ex.
Cuz when someone mentions their ex, bro,
if you ever if you're ever with someone
and they mention their ex, that's what
tends to happen.
You understand when people mention their ex?
Yeah. They always just go back with him.
So yeah, that's what happened. I I reckon. Yeah.
when I started it.
What else can you say? Yeah. Yeah, man.
But anyway, Stephen, I tried to meet
them ASAP and they were using [ __ ]
exams as an excuse. So, at the end of
the day, I'd done all I could do really.
I done all I could do.
So I tried I did try to meet them, bro.
a couple of times. So yeah, it's nothing
I can do, bro. They don't meet. They
don't meet in it. Yeah. [ __ ]
No. No. The thing is though, Stephen
Hour, the only reason I gave them the
benefit of the doubt. Yeah. Is cuz
[ __ ] um they were talking every day,
all day, every day. And when they
messaged me, they were they they they
were almost crying. Some of the times
when they messaged me, they were almost
crying. So I thought, "Oh, I'll just
give them the benefit of the doubt." and
it if they're talking every day, they're
still talking. They were seeming like
they were stressed as [ __ ] So, I
thought, "Okay, I'll allow it in it.
[ __ ] it. Try and meet them after a
couple of weeks. See if they're still
coming out with excuses."
So, I just went with that, bro. I went
with the safest option.
and where they were still replying all
the time. I thought, "Yeah,
you get what I'm saying."
So I just I just thought, "Oh, [ __ ] it."
I mean a way they were still replying back. Yeah,
pretty much. Yeah.
pretty much. Yeah,
it's [ __ ] up, isn't it?
Yeah. Well, she was only 22 anyways,
bro. So, probably a good thing it didn't
go anywhere, you know.
No, she gave more than a little bit of
hope, bro. She gave mixed messages.
There was more mixed messages, if that makes sense.
Yeah, she gave mixed messages.
No, she was all right, bro. Nah, no.
But the deleting the number was weird,
isn't it, Steven Howard?
That was really weird, isn't it?
Cuz normally you just block someone.
UK biggest nonser. Let me see
what's his channel.
Well, no then because she's not stinking.
Well, no. No, it wasn't.
Bro, none of these people know any women
I speak to. I don't know how many times
I have to tell you this. They don't know
any women I speak to, and they'll never
know any woman I speak to.
What's the red flag, Stephen Howard?
No, bro. They don't know anyone I speak
to. They're never going to know anyone I
speak to cuz all the people I meet, I
get their numbers. So, no one on here
will ever find them.
Trust me, it will never happen. You know?
Yeah. I don't speak to no woman on Instagram, lad.
Yeah. Yeah. I noticed her her her uh picture disappeared
and I was like, "Oh, did you delete my
number?" She was like, "Oh, no, no, no."
I thought she blocked me in it cuz we
was talking and Yeah.
I'm kind of over it now, bro. But uh
yeah, it was bad last week. I was bad
last week, lad.
No, it's not her, lad. I don't speak to
no woman on Instagram.
I don't speak to no woman on Instagram, bro.
Yeah, the number thing was weird, in it, Stephen Howard.
Yeah, that's weird, bro.
Here's fake. They don't know any woman I speak to.
They don't know any woman I speak to, lad.
She was tapped in the head in it. Steen
now with Captain Ned.
Yeah, I'm glad she's blocked me, bro.
That's good, isn't it?
That's good that she's blocked me in it, bro.
Yeah, I got a lot of stalkers on here.
Palace, lad. A lot of stalkers.
Yeah, there's a lot of I got a lot of
stalkers on here, lad.
A lot of people obsessed with me, lad.
Yeah, that question is is mad.
I think the [ __ ] was trolling me, bro.
I think I think she was trolling, didn't it?
She was trolling me, lad.
Trolling me hard.
Trolling me hard, man. Yeah.
Yeah. But she said that she would meet
me. She did say that she was going to
meet and whatnot. And she was asking me
questions that you'd only ask people if
you're potentially going to date them.
So, they were giving me mixed messages
cuz the way she had it is like she's not
looking for anyone right now because
obviously what happened to her with her
ex and stuff, but she was still prepared
to meet and stuff. So, she was she was
given mixed messages. Yeah. So
in in a roundabout way. So
then they go back to the same people
that do the same [ __ ] So
that's the story how it is here, lad. Yeah.
I wonder what results we're going to get
on Thursday. Steven Howard.
Same as always.
Nope. None of that weird chat. There was
nothing weird said, lad.
I don't know why you keep thinking that there is.
What do you think of that Christian? Is
he Bob Bills?
She's quite weird, isn't it? Strange character.
Oh, just the one I was speaking to for a
month that disappeared.
It's a bit too young for me anyways. 22
is a bit too young for me
to be fair.
It wasn't long distance, lad. They live in London.
They live in London, bro. It's not long distance.
I kind of feel like I don't want a
woman, bro. I actually feel like I've
been put off, lad. I feel like I'm allergic
because all the [ __ ] they doing that.
Yeah, I'm not going to put her pictures
out there, bro.
She's all right, bro. Yeah, but she just
looked a bit she's a bit young.
You never know, these people might find
her through her pictures and start
messaging her and that. So,
I'm allergic. I'm allergic. Bro,
I don't understand that palace. Why
speak to someone for a month? Say you're
going to meet and then don't.
I don't understand that, Palace. I
really don't understand that.
And then start playing victim.
This madness, it lad
was the point of it.
I was speaking to them every day for a
month, palace. Every day, lad. Voice not in messages.
Then she just randomly deleted my
number, then denied it, added me back. I
said, "Oh, your exams are finished now.
Let's meet up." She said, "Oh, I'll let
you know." I was like, "What do you mean
you'll let me know? Obviously, you don't
want to meet. So, what was the point of
saying you was going to meet?" And
that's how it all started. It's [ __ ]
bro. It's [ __ ] up, lad. Yeah.
What do you think of that situation,
palace? And I was drunk. I messaged her.
I said, "Oh, we should meet up. Let's
talk. If you want this apology so badly,
what people need to apologize for. Why
don't you meet? Let's meet up."
And then she just sent me like 13
messages, deleted most them, then just
blocked me. Huh.
Funny as [ __ ] bro.
Come in, fellas.
They do it.
They do it to make people feel like
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
They do it to make people feel like [ __ ]
What do I rate? Is he a What? This one?
Maybe a seven.
She had big boobs though. But she she
looks quite young. So
not uh notch legs. Minus one.
Minus one out of 10. She's [ __ ] stinking son.
Faky stinking son. Yeah. But yeah,
Palace. Yeah. Um
that's where we're at basically. Um,
no, I'm not showing you her lad in case
people found find her.
Stop messaging her. I know she's blocked
me here, but still, you know,
I actually thought she was genuine,
palace. I thought she was genuine
because she didn't know how long she was
messaging me for and stuff. That's the only reason.
But yeah, that's why I try to meet
people within days, lad.
So anyways, we'll be out Thursday.
Nah, not sex. No, we never done any of that stuff.
No, no, none of that stuff, bro.
Yes, we can do something sometime. No problem. Yeah. Mhm.
It's a madness, palace. It's a madness.
No, we didn't talk about sex or anything
like that, bro.
I don't care about that [ __ ] that sex
and all that. I don't care about that, bro, anymore.
No, I would never do that, lad.
I was trying to meet this person. This
Christian Izzy, man. The [ __ ]
I would never do that, bro, if I was with someone
to be honest. Yeah.
Well, yeah. Palace, I'll be out on Thursday, lad.
Here in the I've got a boyfriend. Oh, no.
Nah, it's not that bad, bro. You just
expect it now, is it? You just expect it.
You expect it in this country now, is it?
She's like, "No, I don't want to talk."
And then she started crying. Bro, what
the [ __ ] No, I don't want to talk right now.
Yeah, basically. Well, I put £100 in. I
got to 200. So,
my haircut's going to cost me 50, but
yeah, I'm sure you could drink with £50, bro.
It's about £8 a Guinness, but
I mean, I only have six. Well,
it it gets you on your merry way in it.
It gets you on your merry way. So,
yeah, cuz I wouldn't I don't think I
would, man. I I wouldn't want to.
You get banned from approach. You get
banned in places now if you approach women palace.
You heard that story I told you. So I
don't really want to be giving them my
money. You know what I mean? I don't
mind [ __ ] about with a little bit of
money that I won, but I don't really
want to be giving them my money. And
I've got money, bro. Like it's not it's
not a problem, bro. But I don't want to
be giving them I don't want to be giving these
That's the whole point of the Thursday,
bro. We're just going to do a madness and um
yeah, we're kind of going to have to
leave after that, lad. So yeah,
we need to save um maybe a month or so
and then we can [ __ ] get out of here,
bro. So yeah, like
yeah, I just Yeah, man.
you a drink tonight?
Yeah, I drunk I drunk last week cuz I
was getting anxiety palace from this
Christian Izzy, bro. Was giving me anxiety, bro.
I had really bad anxiety.
It's kind of gone now. Lasted like a week.
I was having trouble sleeping and that,
but now it's better. So, yeah.
Yeah, I drunk twice last week, lad. Not good.
No, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, I know, bro.
And I felt bad for them cuz they was
telling me what their ex done to them
and [ __ ] and she seemed like very
stressed and that.
So I felt bad in it. So um
yeah they they like I said palace I
never I don't like the thing is what I'm
saying bro is that I don't get anxiety
really. I don't get anxiety. So for that
to have triggered anx so for that to
have triggered anxiety in me bro that's crazy.
That's crazy man.
They do [ __ ] with your minds
when they lead people on. They do [ __ ]
with your minds, bro. Because they make
you think like
like Yeah. There something. Yeah. Basically,
yeah, it's bad. Laney.
Well, obviously Palace. What the [ __ ]
You've been speaking to someone [ __ ]
for that time, bro. And you and when
they tell you something, you you know,
[ __ ] you like you believe it in it.
So, well, I believe it anyways.
So, obviously, lad
it took him like two days to respond. I
was getting anxiety, bro. And then when
I finally said, "Oh, shit." They
respond. Yeah, bro. Cuz that's what they
do. You know, this is why palace I say
you try to meet people as soon as
possible because the more you speak, the
more you, you know, you can um
the more you can get invested.
It's not good, bro. It really [ __ ] with
your mind, bro. And I watched a video of
a guy getting his head smashed him with
a hammer as well.
H that was pretty sick.
Sure, everyone's watched it. But yeah,
which one? There's been loads of different iszies.
I don't know, bro.
Plan is we're going to go outside. Uh
we're going to go out Thursday and send it
with the winnings. So yeah.
So yeah, Palace, it just gives you
Yeah, I went on roulette earlier in the bookies.
I got a bonus on fishing frenzy. It paid [ __ ]
Yeah, that Christian is he's gone, bro.
She is gone. Finished.
Yeah. And then I and I met the last
conversation I had at Palace. I was
drunk here. I said, "Oh, we should meet
up. Let's meet up and talk." sent me 30
messages, deleted most of the messages,
then just blocked me, bro. She said,
"Oh, you're scary and that trying to
play victim in that." What the [ __ ] bro?
These people really know how to play the
victim, don't they?
Yeah, it's mad, bro. Yeah.
You think it's funny, is it? This dating thing. Nah,
I don't know how anyone can find it funny. Lad,
you actually think it's funny in it, Palace?
I don't find it funny, mate.
I don't think you should because I don't. Did I mad, bro?
No, it isn't funny, bro. It isn't funny.
It's [ __ ] weird, bro.
Can't I can't even
Bro, you can't even count on one hand
how many times you've actually been led on
USA. Is he led me on as well? Is he led
me on? Christian. Is he led me on? They
all lead you on.
They lead you on, bro.
Okay. Why is this not working?
Oh, what's going on here, bro?
Yeah, but they don't care, Dusty. That's
the thing. They don't care. People like
Christian is he
people like um USA.
Why is this not what is wrong with this? Yeah.
Who do you think the worst one is,
Dusty? Who do you think the worst one is?
No. What is going on here, lad?
Yeah, but Christian Izzy's is quite bad, too.
She's quite bad as well, to be fair.
She's quite bad too, lad. They're all bad.
Yeah, it's not good, lad.
What do you expect from a 22y old lad?
That was USA, is he?
She didn't say we'll get tattoos. She
said that you can um you can come with
me when I get my tattoo.
I'm getting a milkshake from McDonald's.
Yeah. She said um she said
she said I was her type and everything,
but this Christian one's
I don't know, bro. Cuz the thing is,
yeah, like the other one lives in
America. This one don't live in America.
This one could have easily met me again,
bro. Know what I mean?
But you know this one could have easily
meant me again, Huh?
I should have coward as well.
But this one's quite bad as well, isn't she?
This one's quite bad as well, is it? Yeah,
USA is he palace.
She has some big tits.
She had some big tits, bro.
Yeah, I'm going to haircut on Thursday. Yeah.
Yeah. On Thursday. Yeah.
I just ordered a milkshake. [ __ ] £8
it cost me. [ __ ] hell, man. No, McDonald's.
But I might go to Birmingham. I don't
know yet. I don't know. But I'm
definitely doing something Thursday.
It's not deliveroo, but uh yeah,
because why why do I feel like going to Birmingham Grezy?
Why do I feel like going there?
Yeah, I feel that [ __ ] bro. Yeah, to be fair,
cuz you go and you're walking.
You're walking. Yeah.
And all you can think of is them bra
[ __ ] were laughing at you. Mocking you.
[ __ ] you. It's only It's only It's
only a train ride away, bro. You know
what I'm saying? But even still, [ __ ] you. mocking you.
Laney was watching the whole thing,
Grevy, from the time he was in Romford
all the way to the door. It was on Lord
Jay, isn't it? Laney was watching the whole thing. Yeah,
Lady was watching the whole thing. That's mad.
That's [ __ ] mad.
On the same website, you can watch the
bear in the big blue house.
Oh, 16 minutes away. Why?
Hopefully, it's all right. It should be
We'll see. Do this.
laughing at you.
It depends. Greasy, which one would you
prefer to see? Me calls Chaos in London
or me calls Chaos in Birmingham?
Cuz I will knock him out. Trust me, Bob
Bills, I will knock him out.
Yeah, I will knock him out.
He tried it with me before. They tried
kicking me, bro. I was dodging every
single [ __ ] kick. I will knock him
out. Trust me. Yeah,
I will knock him out. Yeah.
Just hate being led on, you know, Dusty.
I hate being led on.
False hope. That's the worst. Cuz
that's what happens before you meet someone.
You know, the same stuff happens. They
give you hope and then that's how you
meet people. You see? So, you don't know
if people are being genuine or they're
leading you on. Madness, bro.
Oh, bless you. You got a mad address this time.
Where the [ __ ] is
17 minutes away?
Definitely going to come running then, isn't it?
Yeah, the Vindaloo earlier. Hopefully not.
But it probably will be to be fair.
Have you ever been led on dusty? Would
you know how to tell the signs? No.
At least with USA, I got her body.
Well, that's not the point really, is it?
It's not the point.
All that stuff's irrelevant, bro.
And I got Yeah. So what, bro? £40. It
only cost me £40.
£45. I got myself a steak meal, too.
So I got a body in it. So yeah. Yeah.
It was a lovely steak meal. Do you
remember it, Dusty?
I sure did. Yeah,
I was beginning to like this Christian
Izzy, bro. And then she [ __ ] me over,
man. [ __ ] sake.
These people don't help themselves, bro.
We can't feel We can't feel sorry for
these people. They actually [ __ ]
They don't help themselves, bro. [ __ ]
them in it.
Yeah. Temporary nutrition.
Do you like going drinking in Romford, Dusty?
Is that a good place to go drinking and
approaching in in Romford, Dusty? Yeah,
I done it a couple months ago. It was
okay, but it's not as good as central London.
Yeah, it's okay, but it's not as good as central.
It's not too bad,
but not as good as central.
How come central London's busier than Rockford, Dusty?
No, I haven't.
How come it's like Tottenham Court Road
is busier to drink than Romford?
Tottenham Court Road is rat. That's why
I met Christianiz Oxford Circus.
What's Monty going to do if he ever gets um
What's Monty going to do if Natalie G
ever breaks up with him?
He's [ __ ] in it.
No, he's actually [ __ ] in it.
Yeah, he's actually [ __ ] in it.
Yeah. If N ever breaks something, he he
would never got over it. I don't think
he'd ever got over it.
after he would never got over it, would he?
I might try again to the O'Neils
tomorrow, Dusty. See what happens. Nah,
no way, lad.
No, [ __ ] that, bro.
I say no, you're not allowed here.
Have you seen Have you seen it? Have you
Have you seen the management there,
Dusty? Have you seen the manager?
He's like an Indian guy. Indian heritage. Horrible [ __ ]
I don't even know why I kissed her. What
the [ __ ] I must have been really drunk, bro.
Still better than Nlex's girlfriend, though.
Dusty, how come USA didn't let me sleep over?
You know, like a sleepover.
You know, when I live in castle, I just
I didn't sleep over. Just done what I
done and left, bro. Look,
you're like sleepover.
That's like a sleepover.
You don't You don't like a sleepover?
No. Like when she was in London. That's deep.
Am I well traveled somewhat? Yeah.
No, I mean in London when she was in London. Dusty. Yeah.
laughing at you. Mo,
Dusty, remember when she said she went
to the police?
Get a [ __ ] life, you [ __ ]
Dusty. Hey, do you remember the Snapchat, Dusty? Yep. Yeah, dude.
You'd bang USA in it. In it, Dusty.
You'd bang USA is
you would bang her ear
or at least accept a [ __ ]
How about a [ __ ] Dusty?
Would you date her? A chicken.
Oh, [ __ ] bro. Would you date her?
You know there's people Dusty that's
killed themselves over breakups and stuff
ascending utter madness. Yes.
You know there's people that's killed
there's been a lot of people that's
killed himself over it. Yeah.
I think Monty would kill himself if
Natalie G broke up with him. I reckon
he'd kill himself. Yeah.
Who was the root cause? Hey, you know
when you know hey Dusty, you know when
like LT was messaging USA Izzy and he
was trying to wall hero and calm it down
on that. Who was who was the root cause of that?
Like the root cause like in the middle
of all of it? Huh?
Who do you reckon the root cause was?
Yeah, I demo.
That's what he calls it, is it?
The toxic sapler. It's your toxic saber.
But who is the root cause of that?
UK asylum. Do you still think I'm Do you
still think that I'm a troll? What?
>> Do you still think I'm a troll? Like,
nah, I'm not, man.
It's the toxic sector. Yeah, that's a
banger, bro. That that saying's a
banger, bro. I'm going to lick it.
Let's see what this milkshake's like.
I'm going to lick that, bro. 6
man, you good? Yeah, man. >> 16.
Oh, this man probably
No, it's all right to be back.
>> Yeah, man. Ready?
Is this the toxic sector?
That's funny, isn't it? This little toxic sector.
Did you hear him say then? Yeah.
Did you actually hear that?
It's I agree. He said it's the toxic sector.
I love it. Yeah,
he said that these people are energy vampires.
I think this guy's trolling, isn't it?
This LT guy is trolling, isn't it?
Yeah, I think he's trolling.
I got a lovely banana milkshake.
That's yummy. I only like the banana one.
Christian Izzy said, "Don't get don't
get don't get lippy with me."
Creamy. She's like, "Don't get lippy with me.
Don't get Don't get with me,
bro. That's funny, man. That's funny.
It's a toxic sector.
But you know this community, Grezy,
who's caused most of this [ __ ] on here?
Like would you say it's Cosmic Kitty?
Would you say it's Ricks? Like who's
caused the most [ __ ] on here?
Maybe Rick is it? Yeah. Yeah,
but but people say that I'm the root
cause to a lot of this stuff. Greasy. Yeah.
Don't get lippy with me, darling. She
greasy. She said, "Don't get lippy with
me, darling." I was dead, didn't it?
Hey, bro. I was dead.
Look, I'm getting my vitamins. Boozy. Lovely vitamins.
Nah, bro. I've had the worst. What you
talking about, bro? I had my house
smashed into. I could have got killed if
I was in that day. I might I might have been killed.
I've had it worse than him, lads.
I've had it worse. I could have got
killed. It's not even That's not even a
joke, bro. Like, that's not even a joke. M
I had people stalking me, waiting
outside the door for me.
No, I had it worse, bro. I could I would
have I think I would have been dead. I
think I would have got killed.
What do you think, Dusty? I would I
could have got killed if I was in that day.
I knew not I knew not to go back to that
house, bro. [ __ ] that. No, [ __ ] that,
bro. I knew not to go back to that
house. You see? Uh-uh.
No. No. That's not even a joke, bro.
That's not even a joke, bro. Someone
could have got seriously hurt. Seriously,
it's not funny, you know. Someone could
have got seriously seriously hurt.
It's not even a joke. That's not even a
joke. The windows went in. Yeah,
that's not a joke. That's not even a
joke. What do you reckon would have
happened if I was in that day, Dusty?
You reckon I would have got killed? I
would have been woken up to I would have
woke up to a [ __ ] beating, isn't it?
Like you're half asleep. Yeah. And
you're getting attacked whilst you're
sleeping. That's [ __ ] mad. That is
What do you think would have happened, Dusty?
That's quite scary, bro. If you think about it. M.
This is yummy.
I'm enjoying this lovely milkshake, Grezy.
I could have got killed. I knew to stay
away from that house, bro. I knew to
stay away from that house. Trust me, we
Yeah, I could have got I could have got killed, bro.
The windows went in.
Yeah, the windows went in and everything, bro.
Is that the same website you can watch
the Bear on? Greavesy.
That's actually scary, bro.
That's actually really scary. Yeah.
I remember after that, bro, when I went
back to the house, I was sleeping next
to a knife and [ __ ] bro. I'm not even
joking. I was sleeping next to a knife.
I swear to God, I was I was sleeping
next to a knife, bro. Yeah.
Did I go back to the house? I must have
went back to the house. Yeah.
I must have went back there. Yeah. I
don't know. I was staying there. I think so.
No, it's not funny though.
They were trying to hurt me, Grezy. They
were trying to kill me.
They were trying to kill me over YouTube.
No, like we could laugh. We shouldn't
even laugh at it now to be honest
because it was serious. But they were
trying to kill me over YouTube. Gym. Oh.
Oh, I got my little mama fund. Greavvesy. £200.
Should be plenty for Thursday, won't it?
Oh, yeah. Do you know what Monty said,
Greavves? He said, "You know what? I
wonder every day. I wonder why you got
me on this community. This is something
that I wonder every day.
I'm just having this milkshake."
He said, "This is what I wonder every
day. Why you got me on this shitty community?" Yeah.
That's what Monty wonders every day,
Greavvesy. Why I got him on this community?
But he doesn't understand that the
people done [ __ ] to him before they done
it to me.
I didn't think that all that stuff was
going to happen. I'm not even joking. I
didn't think all of that stuff was going
to happen, bro.
To be fair, cuz a lot of people come on
here, Greavves, and a lot of people just
left like other people. So I didn't
think he was going to jump I mean
this is a toxic sector. Yeah
I would have left bro if I was going to
be meeting that Christian Izzy. was
going to leave
now. He'll come back, Grezy. He'll come
back. He will come back.
He's probably met someone or he's at
work or something. He'll come back. He
will come back.
Trust me. I would have met I would have left, bro.
Oh, I'll go back on on the other channel
and stuff, but I would I was going to
go, bro. Seriously, that's why I wasn't
on here much.
He will come back, bro.
He will come back, bro. Even if it's six months.
Oh, you're waiting. Are you Are you
awaiting his arrival? Grezy, are you
awaiting his little arrival? Bless you.
You miss his little voice, Grezy. Well, I
Well, I Pete. So, get So, get in there,
Pete. That's how we talk, isn't it?
Laughing at you, Grezy. Mocking you.
Just as you told me, yeah, that she had
these guy friends that said like, "If
you don't love me, I'm going to kill
myself." And apparently she told them off.
She's trolling, isn't it? Ah, you're
trolling, isn't it? I get it. Yeah, I
get it. Yeah, I get it. It's funny, is it?
Somebody's going to get Yeah.
Yeah. Oh yeah, I get it now. Yeah, you
going to get hurt.
No, Grezy. I'm going to that same place
that game manager is. And if he thinks
he's gonna if he thinks he's going to
try and kick me out again, he's got
another thing coming, lad. No, no, no.
He will get another thing coming, lad. I
will call it for you if you want. I will
record it for you if you want. No, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, bro.
Bro, I'm going there on Thursday,
right? And I I will record it for you.
If he comes, then I will record it.
Um, then yeah, I will I would just say
exactly what I said I was going to say
about Grinder, the gay pride.
Yeah, I will. I will, bro. Yeah. M, you know.
No, I'll just say to him, can I can I
have your phone so I can delete Grinder?
Can I stop Can I stop the gay pride?
Because you're trying to bring my energy
down. You're trying to stop me meeting
people. So, let me stop let me stop you
meeting people. How about that, Grezy?
Do you like that? Do you like that talk?
You want to try and kill my vibe? I'll
kill your vibe.
Simple as that.
Yeah. You want to try and interfere with
what I'm doing? Yeah. You don't even own
this place. Okay. I'll interfere with
what you're doing then. How about that? You know? Mhm. Mhm.
Maybe I don't like the fact that you you
suck guys dicks, but you don't see me
complain about it. You don't see me cry
about it, Grievy.
You know what I'm saying?
I I'll tell him to go back to Kent and
take his attitude with him. Just because
you work in London, mate, it doesn't
mean you're better than anyone. This is
what these people need to uh need to
realize, Greavves, like you are not from
You could tell the guy's from Kent.
Yeah. go back to where you come from and
bring your attitude with you and leave
it there. Don't think that because you
work in London you're prestige because
you're not, mate. You're [ __ ] well
not. And that's what a lot of people
need to understand. Just cuz you work in
London, bro, just cuz you're in London,
you're not better than no [ __ ] You understand?
You're not better than no [ __ ] If you
want to walk around and not speak to
people and you're in a rush, you do you,
bro. If you want to do that, you can do
what you want. But don't stop acting
like you're better than people.
Uh cuz I tell you to sling your hook,
you [ __ ] [ __ ] right? I'm a single
guy. I'm allowed to go and speak to
people. I'm allowed to make friends. I'm
allowed to try and um find myself a a
future baby mama. Right? So, and I will
say all of that stuff. That's none of
your business. Don't try and tell me
where I can go. Show me the deeds to the
place. Show me that you own this place.
Show me your name and the deeds on it.
Then I'll listen to you.
And I will say it, bro. I will say it
because it's the truth. It is the truth,
lad. Why do you think, Greavves? Yeah, I
don't want to waste my own money on this
on Thursday cuz I know what it's going
to be. Obviously, I won that £100. Yeah.
It's going to pay for most of it.
Whatever. Yeah. Why do you think I don't
I don't want to waste my own money on
it, bro? Cuz because of these people.
But I'll give you content, poor [ __ ]
I said I was going to go out Thursday.
And I say, "Fuck back to where you come
from, Kent. The guy's a white guy. Stop
trying to act like you're something
you're not cuz you're working in London,
bro. It don't suit you. Drop your attitude."
Yeah. Giving us a bad name, bro. Giving
us a bad name. That's what all these
people in London do. They give us a bad name.
You know what I mean, lad?
You tried to embarrass me in front of
that bartender. I'll embarrass you. Let
me embarrass you, bro. Let me come to
one of your little gay boys and
embarrass you, lad. No, he sounds gay.
He's gay, bro. The guy's gay. He is gay.
You can tell by the way he talks. He's
gay. Let me come to one of your little
gay boys and embarrass you. How about
that one? Give me a chance to embarrass you, bro. like,
you know, let me cramp your style. Yeah.
Do you know what I'm saying, Grezy? Let
me cramp your style. How about that?
trying to trying to it's it's all about
you know what a lot of these people have
been you know what a lot of these people
are like Greavvesy a lot of these people
that are managers for London they've
been bullied in life why do you think
they like the power it's called it's
like a bit like Reddit moderators it's
it's they're just bully victims that um
basically want power
they like the power you get
And I'm going to say, why don't you move
me out the Why don't you move? Why don't
you move me? Why don't one of you pe Why
don't one of you and these little
bouncers move me? And we'll see what
they've got to say to that. They won't
do that, though. They'll try and call
the police. Trust me. You know, I know
what they're like, bro. They'll try and
call the police, Greasy. Trust me.
Trust me, lad. That's what they'll do.
You don't get banned for approach to
people, bro. You're supposed to talk to
people in a bar, in a club, and stuff,
whatever you call a place. You're
allowed to. You know, it's not It's a
free country. You're allowed to do that.
There's nothing against that. As long as
you ain't sexually assaulted anyone or
beat anyone up or whatever, you're fine, bro.
Do you get me?
Easy. As long as you ain't done any of
that. And this is how you know it's
[ __ ] as well. No one complained.
Because if someone complained, this is
what would happen. Yeah.
Um if somebody complained, what would happen is
you would um they firstly this is how it
would work. Yeah. They'd come up to you
and say, "Can you stop?" Whatever.
Whatever. Okay. And then the next thing
that would happen is they'd probably ban
you for a month or two months or three
months. So they would just ban you and
then they say, "Oh, come back another
time." That's what happens in certain
establishments. There's no way, mate,
that you've approached three people and
you've just been banned for life. So
what's the story?
Like what is No. No. What the [ __ ] is
going on? Cuz a you do not get banned
for that period. And even and and and
they wouldn't just ban you. They'd come
up and and and basically tell you to
just just to not do it.
Do you understand? It's a power trip. Do
you understand, Greavvesy? It's it's a
it's an ego trip for these people. Do
you get it?
Weird, is it?
Very, very weird. But you you're all
right in pubs. In pubs, you're all
right. Yeah. In pubs, you're completely fine.
You don't get these problems. But yeah,
how can you get banned for talking to people? Yeah.
I don't want to go back to that place
though. Really, bro? It just reminds me
of Christine, Izzy, lad,
where she was sat down, didn't it, with
her little mates.
Greavves. I approached her with in front
of her little mates.
There's four of them in it. I was like,
"Fuck it. Let's just hit it, bro." And
it [ __ ] it.
In front of her and her little mates.
Yeah. I thought, "Fucking. Let's hit it, bro." Yeah.
Love it, bro. I love it. Oh, [ __ ] man.
I don't know who he is, bro. But
and if he doesn't, I'm going to approach
someone in front of him as well. If he
stops me Thursday, I'm going to I'm if
he tries to come come to me on Thursday,
I'm going to approach someone in front of him
and take the piss out of him. If I'm
going to do that, yeah. Yeah.
Mhm. What have you said to him? What
would have you said to the gay? What
would you say to the gay guy? Greasy.
Don't try and tell me I can't I can't
come in here and approach women, mate.
[ __ ] off, you little gay [ __ ]
Don't try and [ __ ] annoy me, bro.
No one's going to do it, lad. Trust me.
No one's going to do it. Believe me.
Believe you me.
Yeah, but you you would know how to react, you know? Yeah.
How can you have a bar? How can you have
an environment, right, and then when
somebody goes over and approaches people
normally, you decide to ban them
forever? That's corrupt, lad. That's
literally what you call corrupt. You
know when you say corrupt talk about
maybe it was because of the bouncer. No,
no. Do you know what it was with the b?
No, no, no. It's cuz maybe it was cuz
the bouncer or something like cuz I
weren't going to let him like put his
hands on me cuz I fought back. That's
maybe I mean what did you want me to do?
No. What he said was no. Oh go. And then
he comes up to me and says
I said oh that's just stupid and that
man. Then he's like, "Oh, if you give me
attitude, I'm going to snatch the drink
out of your hand." I said, "You're
[ __ ] not going to take no drink out
of my [ __ ] hand. Don't know who you
think you're [ __ ] talking to." Then
he tried pulling it and there was a
little bit left and then I pulled it
back and then the glass and then the
glass fell and then I just started being
like mad racist to him like you polish
this, you polish that. Come around the
corner. Yeah. And I think the [ __ ] took
the piss uh he took a picture out of me
and then that's what what it was. Yeah.
Something like that. Well, don't get
rude then. Simple, bro. Who you talking
to about you're going to snatch drinks
out of people's hands? Who the [ __ ] are you, bro?
Come on, man. Like, you are you Who are
you talking to?
You're no You're no [ __ ] You're in no
position to to to think you can start
talking to people like that.
You know what I mean?
They are swearing at him, call him out,
bro. Like, yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
He's a [ __ ]
And they got my picture as well. So,
yeah, that's what happens. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
No, it wasn't a dream, bro. It was like
It was almost finished, but it's not the point.
It was like a spirit. It was almost
finished, but obviously you're not going
to snatch no drink out of my hand.
And you're not snatching no drink out of
my hand, mate.
Well, have you been when you said the
same thing, Greavvesy?
I should go to church and do a cold
approach in church.
What do you think? We
No, mate. After [ __ ] Christian is
I've been put off [ __ ] Christians,
bro. I've been put off Christians. Nah, they're toxic.
No, they're toxic, Grezy. They're very toxic.
Is that what Christians do then, Grezy?
Lead people on.
Is that what they do? Lead people on. Is it? Huh? Yep.
They do lead people, don't they, Greavvesy?
So what you're saying, Greavesy, is this
[ __ ] you you what you're saying is
this Christian is he's innocent. Nah.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Not really, bro.
Bezy, I'm not going to no church after
that, mate. [ __ ] that.
And I'm not [ __ ] with no Muslim evil, lad. Yeah,
a screw loose.
Yeah, [ __ ] hell.
That USA is he had a screw loose as well.
But I wouldn't have went church anyways
to be honest. I I I don't think I would
have done that anyways.
What you said,
me, Christian, Izzy, and
Um, king and church.
Imagine that. And King in church as well. Greasy.
Nah, I've been to Canary Wolf, but not
for a drink.
You spelled Canary Wolf wrong as well, lad. Yeah.
How much was that Spider-Man game, Grezy?
I think this phone's packing up, lad.
The screen. I thought the screen just
went there. Lad,
I might start delivering for money
again. Uh delivering food for money again. Dusty.
I got this uh Hungry Panda app.
Might give it a whirl.
So, if you don't see me, Grievous, I'll
be at work.
Yeah. These bad experiences with women
drove me to the gambling.
Yeah, that's what it's called. Hungry
Panda. Have you heard of it, Grezy? Oh, boy.
A screw loose.
Do you know what she said to me? Oh my
god, sausages. I love sausages. I am a
sausages biggest fan.
That's what Christian Izy said to me. I
am a sausages biggest fan.
Hey, trust me, bro. On Thursday. Yeah,
we're not going to let these [ __ ] women
win. Do you remember agree with you that
account? Don't let them cing women win.
Yeah, we won't, lads. Don't worry,
there'll be some content. Yep.
I don't have a screw loose, do I?
Grievy, I think you need to chill out.
Yeah, everybody knows that you're a crazy [ __ ]
What Christian is he? Voice notes. No,
I'm not playing. I'm not playing them, lad. No,
>> I think you need to chill out. Is that right?
>> Yeah. Everybody knows that you're a
crazy [ __ ] I want I want you to say
that on Thursday. Um, Grezy, everybody
knows that you're a crazy [ __ ]
A good old Alf Stewart, Dusty. Good old Alf Stewart.
Good old elf do it.
I'm going to find my mama. Mama
with a h. Mama.
Is that right, Grezy?
I wonder who my mama's going to be on Thursday. Yeah.
No, there's no point in playing the
messages, bro. I'm not doing a video. I
can't be bothered,
man. [ __ ] bro.
Don't get lippy with me, Dusty. Don't
get lippy with me, darling.
Don't get lippy with me, darling.
Don't get limp with me, darling.
Why are all these [ __ ] crazy, man?
All Why are all Why are all these [ __ ] crazy?
Grecy, I'm talking to you, Grezy.
All right. One sec. Darling
Grey living with me. Oh,
someone's bossy, isn't it? Greasy, huh?
Oh gosh. Now I find shea
li with me darling with me.
But I ain't heard that saying in [ __ ]
years. That's an greasy
grievy. Listen, like um so Grievy, like
I haven't heard that saying in years.
That's old, bro. So what you're saying
is that Laney was watching Timmy Eldridge, right?
Like the whole stream of where he was
until we come on the door and that's the
same website you can watch Andre the Giant on
when he's when he's strangling that old
man. Is that what you're basically saying, Greasy?
Is that what you're basically saying?
Wow. That's [ __ ] mad, isn't it?
This is the toxic sector. Crazy.
LG calls it the toxic sector.
Bro, I'll never forget when LT said Jay.
He said, "I'm going to light up your battleship."
I was dead, bro. I was dead. I agree
with you. Do you remember that? I'm
going to light up your battleship.
Where the [ __ ] does he come up with these things?
Imagine saying that to someone. I'm
going to come there. Yeah.
Indigo, stop it. You're getting to me.
Stop it. Stop it.
Yeah. Same website, is it? Same website.
Yeah. Same website, lads. Same website.
Yeah, same website.
Don't get lippy with me, darling.
So, grievy. So, on Thursday, do you want
me to do do you want me to go for a
drink or do you want me to do it bad? Do
you want me to do it dirty? Like, what
what what do you want? It's up to you
and it I can either just go for a drink
normally or do it bad.
Stop it. Stop it. You're getting to me.
Stop it, bro. That kill that that kills
me every day when I think about that,
you know. Yeah. It's mad, isn't it? It's mad.
It's [ __ ] madness.
This [ __ ] needs to be monitored, Grezy.
And what makes me laugh, Greavves, is
everyone knows each other's channels.
You know, I go on Timmy's channel, I see Monty Pumington.
How do they know each other's channels?
You know what I mean?
You know what I'm saying?
Don't let these [ __ ] women win. Indigo,
now I fancy Coca-Cola, but it's [ __ ] Oh gosh, oh gosh.
I ain't going out, lad.
Oh, do you want to do it bad?
Do you want to do it bad, Grezy?
Do you want to do it bad?
Oh, I love your little telly, Greavesy.
I love your little telly. I've just gone
back on that picture. God bless.
Lady said to me, "What do you even want
a woman for?" Grezy,
I know, Indigo, it's crazy, isn't it?
Yeah. Elani said, "What do you even want
a woman for, Greavvesy?"
She said, "For what reason?"
That's what Laney said, Greavvesy.
I don't know. Just to be in control, Greavvesy.
You know, just to be in control, you know?
That makes sense, don't it, Griezy?
You remember that comment on um Reddit,
Greavves? He stayed the hell away from
us. From that woman, stayed the hell
away from us.
You know what I used to say? Yeah. I
said, "Oh, I'm starting to hate all
women on the student room form, Greasy."
And they'd said, "Yeah, good. We hate you, too.
We hate you, too."
Yeah, we hate you, too.
That's what they say. They have
meetings. Women have meetings about me. Grievy
USA is that they all have meetings every
Tuesday at at 10:00 a.m.
They have meetings. Rezy,
what do you think about that?
No, I just want to be in control,
you know. No, no problem with that.
I just like to be in control. Oh gosh.
I've had more [ __ ] than you, Grezy.
And it wasn't from women that weren't It
was from women that weren't escorts.
And I'm talking about not escorts. I'm
talking about normal women. Greavves.
It's an achievement. My little collection, you know.
Well, I was going to get with Christian. Izzy, Greavesy.
I think she had maybe like um
anxiety and split personality disorder. Grievy.
She says, "No, I don't want to talk. You
just made me cry.
What the [ __ ] I didn't even say anything, bro.
That was funny though, the way she said
it. Not the crying part that I don't
like to see anyone cry, but she says,
"No, I don't want to talk.
These [ __ ] are cray, bro. H.
Is that right, Gregy? Is that right, lad? Indigo,
why is why was I watching the bear in
the big blue house
um on the same website that Timmy
Aldridge come on my road on?
That's a bit weird, isn't it?
That's a bit old, isn't it, lad?
Same website, Indigo. Same website.
You can't handle it. Why? No,
I agree. Easy. Look at Indigo's
comments. It's true. It's true though. I
love it. Yeah, it's true. It's true.
Yeah, the Harry Potter one's the funniest. Yeah,
they're interviewing him as a kid. Yeah.
And then the next thing Yeah. What the
[ __ ] is going on, Grezy? This site needs
to be monitored. Uhhuh.
Mhm. It's true though, isn't it? Yeah.
That's bad, is it? Grezy. Oh gosh.
So, you reckon if I found someone I
would cheat, Greavvesy?
100% I would. Yeah.
Actually, I think I would.
If I got with Christian Easy, I wouldn't
have cuz of her past and stuff. That's
cruel. But like a normal woman. Oh yeah,
100% I would. Yeah.
Yeah, I would cheat.
100% I would cheat, bro. Every as soon
as I could.
I' I'd get with escorts.
I'd get with escorts. I'll do anything.
I wouldn't care. I would cheat.
Yeah, cheating's fun.
Is it Grezy? Cheating's fun.
You remember that whole thing that was
going on with that USA? Do you know what
I wanted to do, Grezy? when all of that
stuff was going on. Do you really want
to know how I would have got her her back?
I would have I would I wanted to get her
sister pregnant. Grezy,
let me have a look.
Yeah, she is a loony. What the [ __ ]
Oh gosh, Grezy, listen. That that's the
best way to do it. If you if you're ever
with a woman and she [ __ ] you over or
whatever or does or you want to get
revenge or she's cheated or whatever,
you should get their sister pregnant.
That is what you call a lovely sight.
Stephen Hour, that is absolutely beautiful.
So, you had one sister and then now the
other sister's having a baby and she's
going to be an auntie to that baby. Yeah.
[ __ ] lovely. You ask me, Grezy. Absolutely lovely. Yep.
Oh gosh. Indigo.
Oh, imagine. Imagine I found out where
she worked, Greavesy. And I went to her workplace
like I done with that Kenji Grezy. You
loved that, didn't you? With that,
Kenji, you was pissing me off. Yeah, I
went all the way there, didn't I?
I went to his [ __ ] workplace to [ __ ]
Yeah. Do you remember crazy? Yep.
That was my Isabelle. No one else's.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
Indigo, I love you, man. I watched it.
I've already watched it, Grezy.
Oh, I love you, Indigo. You're an animal.
Who? What question is his mom grieves? A
you know when she was crying Greavvesy I
just wanted to give her a big hug you
know and tell her everything's going to be okay.
How cute is that? Grezy.
She was crying and stuff. I felt bad. I
don't like people crying and stuff.
How cute is that?
Do you remember that person I went on a
date with when I come back from Belgium?
Greavesy, the Portuguese one from the dating app.
She wouldn't [ __ ] me on a second date,
so I had to ditch her. [ __ ] pitic.
>> Yeah. Why am I an angel?
>> No, she was crying and stuff. I felt
bad, bro. I didn't I don't like to hear
people cry, you know.
I wanted to give her a little hug.
Don't like seeing people cry, you know.
It's not nice.
I cry sometimes, but I always hide it.
No one ever knows. Rezy, no one ever
knows when I've been crying. Oh gosh. You know.
Yeah. Have you ever Do you cry, Grievy?
Do you ever cry grievy?
Have you cried?
Hey Bob Bills,
have you watched that uh Three Guys One Hammer yet?
We was talking about this the other day.
Did you watch it?
I'm going to send it to Greavvesy one
day. I'm going to screen record it and
send it to Greavvesy. He's not going to
know what it is until it's too late.
And once it's seen, Greavvesy, it can't be unseen.
Once it's been seen, Grezy, it can't be unseen.
So, you're going to be [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah, you you're [ __ ] then, Grezy.
Nightmares for you, dead. And you live
by yourself. Yeah.
Oh, watch it.
I am very naughty. I am very naughty.
Oh, look it up. Uh, Bob Bills, go and
watch it. It's uh 7 minutes long. Yeah.
And you're going to And you're going to
get nightmares. GZ
never heard of it. I've never heard of that, bro. Uh, Indigo,
how comes I can see Timmy Aldridge on YouTube?
How comes I can see Timmy Aldridge on YouTube?
I am in my 20ies, you silly goose.
I watch porn today. Actually, I watch
some vintage [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. I want some lovely vintage. Yep. Oh gosh.
Do you reckon I'm going to find my mama
on Thursday? Grievy,
we got some money to go out with.
Hopefully I find my mom.
Yeah. USA was my mom for 2 years.
I even found her YouTube channel.
Once you meet me, I'm with you for life.
Is that right, Grevy? Once someone meets
me, I'm with them for life.
Oh, get rid of me, lad. Yes sir.
Well, USA is he left me indigo
after giving me nutrients.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
Gave me nutrients and ditched me.
What was the point of that?
taking a baby away from its mama.
Greavvesy taking a baby away from its mama.
Did you like that little saying,
Greavvesy? From its mama. Huh?
I got my little mama fund here. I can't wait.
I can't wait to go and find a new mama.
One that will love me and take care of me. Grievy.
Oh, that question is he left me. Bob Bills.
I miss her sometimes.
Why don't you like that saying, Grezy?
I love it. Really? Taking the baby away
from its mama. I remember when I first
said that, people kept repeating it. Do
you remember, Grezy?
People kept repeating it.
Joe F is one of the brothers. Steven Howard
is that right? Greavves you. Joe F is
one of the brothers.
I might give him the new channel.
So, um, so Steven Howard, what happened
between um Britney and Lunch Legs?
What was the story there?
All I listen Grezy, you know, like June,
July, it was good. The banana milk say
was good. You know, June, July, bro, I
might have to um go to a colder country.
I can't deal with the heat. I don't know
about you, Greavves. I can't deal with
the heat, lad.
It was hot. It was hot. I don't like the
heat, lad. To be fair.
I don't really like the heat when it's
that bad. I don't know about you, but I
don't really like it. I kind of
hibernate in the summer.
I kind of like hibernate.
I kind of just like I obviously I go out
and stuff, but like within peak hours, I
don't like the heat.
Normally I like March, but it's quite
hot already. Even though it's March,
it's quite hot.
Do you remember when I went to the beach
by myself, Grey,
during the summer?
Yeah, after April it's just unbearable,
bro. The weather. I don't like it like that, man.
I like October,
I guess. I don't know, bro.
So, will I get some numbers on Thursday then, Greavesy? Yep.
Are you doing a football bet Saturday, Stephen?
Dodge your [ __ ] lad.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Greavves is so obsessed with women.
Grez is obsessed with women. Steven Howard,
I'm not obsessed.
Yeah, same. £10. Yeah.
Oh, bless you, Grey. If you want to have
a little gamble then
with your little stockpool accent. Oh, bless.
How cute is that? Oh, bless you
with your little stockpool accent.
Oh, Steven Allen, I done a correct
score, you know, last week, last
Saturday, nil nil. And they like I done
a correct score on nil nil and then
[ __ ] they started scoring and [ __ ]
the bet up.
Yeah, I done a correct score of nil nil
and£10 returned hundreds but yeah they
scored. So we need to start doing these
correct scores. Steven Howard lad. Let's
try to predict
the scores on two games. Yeah.
What do you think, Steven Howard?
It's hard to pull it off, but if you do,
you're in the money, aren't you, lad?
You're in the money.
You're in the money if you do.
You know you are in it. Just two games,
bro. All you need is two games.
I need a new mama. Greavvesy.
I need a new mom.
Is that cute? Greavesy. I need a new mama.
Somebody that will love me for me. Grieves.
I've noticed a lot of these women I've
been with have got mental health
problems. The 19year-old had mental health problems.
Uh the one in Nottingham, they all like
self harm and stuff. Grievy, they've got
mental health problems.
A lot of them doing it. Greasy.
Yeah, I was 26 at the time, bro.
Well, she's not 90 now. She's 21 now.
Yeah, she's 21 now.
Yeah, she was 19 and I was 26.
She used to give me [ __ ] and stuff. So yeah,
I used to get my dick out greasy and she
used to put it in her mouth.
Yeah, good couple of times, but then I
just prefer the [ __ ] Lovely. Yeah,
Christian Izzy is 22 even. That's a bit
young now. I mean, I'm 29 this year, so
that's a bit young, too, is it?
Yeah, 19 was young to be fair, but
I didn't give a [ __ ]
Pass legal in it.
Yeah, banged her. She
sucked my willie.
It's nice to have your witty sucked,
ain't it, Greasy?
Yeah, it's all right.
Nothing nice nicer than putting your
dirty dick in someone's mouth, Grezy.
Your dirty penis in someone's mouth. Lovely.
Is that right? Greasy.
I'm so sleepy.
So yeah, I am going to cheat. If I ever
do find someone grieves, I will be cheating.
I will definitely be cheating
and I don't care.
Is that all right, Greg with you if I cheat?
I already had an Indian earlier. That
was my dindons.
That was my dend.
Yeah, I would cheat. I don't care.
Like I said many times, yeah, I love curry pasta.
Yeah. The reason you should cheat on
women is because a they're going to
cheat on you and b it's like going to
the cinema and getting a pick a mix and
only having one suite.
You're not going to do that, are you? So
why would you stay with one woman? That's boring.
You need to try out new ones,
see which one's better at giving you
vitamins and stuff. Like
I told that woman I was speaking to on
Tinder about Christian Izzy and then she
blocked me grievously. She actually
blocked me. What a selfish [ __ ]
I said, "Why are you telling me this?"
Don't know what it is with these women.
They're so jealous. It's like women I've
been on dates with before. I told them
about other women and they started acting weird.
What you think the world revolves around
you or something, Missy?
You know, I don't understand what's
what's wrong with them. Greasy.
Well, this woman I was speaking to on
Tinder, I got her on WhatsApp. Grezy.
and I told her about Christian Izzy and
then she blocked me.
That's weird, isn't it?
No, I don't lead people on.
I'm a lovely fellow. Yeah.
So hopefully on Thursday, Greavvesy, we
don't get the I've got a boyfriend [ __ ] will we?
We're not going to get that I've got a
boyfriend [ __ ] are we, lad? Fingers crossed. Nah, nah, bro. Yeah.
So, do you reckon if I was So, do you
reckon if me and USA Izzy was together,
do you reckon I would I would have
cheated on her then, Greavesy?
Like if we were like dating and stuff on there.
No, but why would I do that? cuz I've
already got the nutrients we've
No, I wouldn't cheat on Christian though.
I would have done that, bro. Honestly,
after what she told me happened and stuff,
if she was trying to change and find
somebody that wasn't like that, I
wouldn't have done that, bro. Trust me, I wouldn't.
with USA Izzy like well I got the
nutrients in it so why would I cheat
it just depends Greavvesy you know
I felt safe under her arms Greavvesy
you know I felt I felt safe
that you Greavvesy
where we was hugging and kissing and stuff.
I just felt safe, you know,
that cute greasy
cuz that's what they do. You know, you
know, if a baby's if if a baby's with
its mama, it feels safe, isn't it? It's
the same thing with puppies and stuff. grievy.
I felt safe
and then when I got abandoned, oh wow, I got depressed,
you know, got left and abandoned.
Left wondering what happened, you know,
horrible, horrible person. Oh gosh.
Why would I cheat on USA? Izzy though,
Greavesy. You actually think I would do that? Nah.
I wasn't I I wasn't going to cheat on
people back then.
You remember the Do you remember the
delivery job Greavvesy? It kept taking
me to Elephant and Castle Greavvesy.
A lot of history for Peter Belly in
Elephant and Castle Greavvesy. Yeah.
Oh gosh. Steven Howard.
This where I met my mama. Why?
Is that you, Greavvesy?
That's where we had some fun.
I don't know.
Maybe cuz I'm a loony myself.
Um, it's where I had fun with someone
and I latched on to their boobies. Isn't
that right, Grezy?
I just want someone to hugle onto
Greavesy and and kiss, you know?
That's all I want, Grezy.
Good thing I got Crash Bandicut in it.
Good thing I got Crash Bandicoot.
I want someone to hugle up to, Grezy.
So, how comes when when me and USA was
kissing and doing stuff, I felt safe? Greasy,
why do I feel safe? Huh?
I was touching her on the sofa. Greasy.
I was touching her body parts and she
liked it. Greasy. She liked it a lot actually.
Virgin boy said, "It's lucky we don't
have guns or I'd be the next Elliot Rogers."
I mean, it's very easy to get a gun in this country.
Very easy to get guns. Very easy. I
mean, you don't need a gun to do anything.
There's knives. There's hammers.
Why does Nons legs call me an incel,
Steven? Is it cuz he's an insult himself?
I'm not sure yet, but I'm definitely
going out Thursday.
Maybe 5:00 p.m.
Why does nonsense call me an incel? Is
it cuz he's an incel?
I'm going to make myself a glass of milk
in a minute, Grezy. Is that okay with you?
I don't know what I want a woman for,
Greavvesy. I don't really care about
sex. I'm not lustful anymore.
I don't actually know why I want one greasy.
I'm not too sure.
Just for the fun of it.
I'm not sure. I don't care
about sex or anything like that anymore. So,
I just want I just want to be treated
like a baby.
grieves you. I just want them to like
lie me down on their tummy and tell me
that I'm the best ever.
I want one to put me to sleep every day,
read me a bedtime story. You know how
they do to um you know how Elma gets uh
read a bedtime story.
Greavesy, that's what I want. I want to
be put to sleep every day, you know.
I just want a mom basically, you know.
I have to go out. I have to go out on Thursday.
I have to go out on Thursday cuz if I
don't go out Thursday, Greavvesy will
block me and never speak to me again.
Isn't that right, Greavvesy?
It's [ __ ] hot tonight, mate. Oh, it
is hot today, bro.
Yeah, I have to
can't [ __ ] deprive Grezy. Poor [ __ ]
No, I just want one to like lay me on
their belly and tell me that I'm the
best in the world, Grezy.
I want to be huggled and kissed.
Sorry lady, I'm going to have to I'm
going to have to drink all this. Lady's
going to hate me in the morning, mate,
for this. But I'm drinking all the milk.
Oh, no. There is no there is still some
milk left. But yeah. Oh gosh.
Why would you say Why are you asking me
if I've lost it, Pip? Laney's sleeping. Laney's asleep.
Oh, I need to go wee wee.
Can you hold your pee in Grezy?
Oh, I can't.
Yeah. As you get older, your your
bladder gets weaker.
Um, Grezy, Grezy. Uh, Grezy,
Grezy, I like shovel Gy. I like shovel carsy.
I like Cheryl Cole Grezy.
No, but seriously, man. Lord J was
trying to be like me the other day.
Weber spoons drinking and that, putting
his camera on. That's the [ __ ] I used to
do. He's a copycat. And now he's showing
his dick on YouTube as well. He's a copycat.
No, he's being a Hey. Hey, LJ's a copycat.
LJ copies me. Why can't I do anything
without anyone [ __ ] copying, bro?
[ __ ] Sony's dick and [ __ ] bro.
Everything I do, someone copies Greasy.
Is that why you call it a copycat community?
He showed his dick. He went drinking in
Weather Spoons and stuff.
Yeah. Why do you think he's not on
YouTube? He showed his dick. There's
like a video of it, bro.
Is it a copycat community? Uh,
Greavvesy. Timmy's just done a new uh YouTube video
and I was literally watching the side men earlier.
Uh, you got some explaining to do, lad.
Why is this Timmy keep appearing on YouTube, lad?
I was watching the Sideman earlier.
I like London Taylor. Steven Howard.
London Taylor is one of the brothers.
I like London Taylor.
At least with And at least with London
Taylor, he's not on YouTube much either.
See, that guy's got a life. LT's got a
life. He doesn't come on YouTube much.
He's a cool guy, man.
Yeah, he doesn't come on YouTube much.
Yeah, he is. What do you mean he's not?
Of course he's one of the brothers. He's
a cool guy.
Why wouldn't he be a Why wouldn't he be
one of the brothers?
I quite like him. I think he's a cool
guy. I think he's a lovely little fellow.
Nah, he's he's a cool guy, man.
He's a lovely little fellow.
Oh, Groovy. What a lovely little fellow.
Yeah, Bob. I want a woman to put me to
sleep every night and lie me on her
belly and tell me that I'm the best ever.
Yeah, you always take L Timmy Eldrid.
See you later.
If you don't stop it, I'm going to come
to Birmingham on Thursday and sort you out, lad.
Don't make me do it.
Do not make me [ __ ] come to Birmingham, lad,
cuz I love you all.
Remember that one? No, I don't say it to
them. I keep it to myself, Bob.
No, obviously I keep it to myself and
stuff. Is it
No, obviously I keep it to myself, but yeah,
I do like to be treated like a baby.
You understand, Bob? I like to be like
motherthered and stuff.
I've always had I always have.
I've always associated like women with
like mums and stuff. So, I just thought,
yeah, it's my mom, you know, I've always
been like that, Bob.
So, I don't know why, but yeah,
always have. So, yeah. Well,
I'm both. I'm a man and a kid.
Well, I'm a man and a kid. I need to be fed.
I need to I need to suck on boobs, Bob.
I need my vitamins. If I don't get my
vitamins, I get very ill, very groggy, very depressed.
So, obviously, I need my vitamins,
nutrients, and stuff.
So, and when I'm deprived of it or took
away from it. Yeah.
Yeah. UK signing. What I was saying is I
want a woman to treat me like a baby, you know?
Um, I want I want a woman to treat me
like a baby.
No, Bob. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
They don't have to be pregnant.
Trust me, they don't have to be pregnant.
There's nutrients and calcium in the
boobs without them being pregnant.
Trust me, bro. No, no, no, no, no.
They've got milk and vitamins
without being pregnant. Trust me.
Cuz USA is
there was there was boot there was stuff
coming out of it
when I was when I was sucking on her
breasticles. There was stuff coming out of it.
So yeah, there must have been
I'm guessing there was. So,
yeah. UK asylum. I want to be treated
like a baby.
I want to be I want I want a woman to
lie me down on her stomach and tell me
I'm the best in the world. UK asylum.
I want them to say, "Oh, you cute poor little thing."
And give me loads of kisses. UK asylum.
That would be the dream,
you know. Yep. Lovely.
And to find someone on Thursday to be my mama.
It's not gross.
It's not gross at all.
If I got someone pregnant in UK asylum,
I'd nick all the milk.
I'd have all the milk and there'd be
none left for the baby.
What's your opinion on that? UK asylum.
I'd want it all to myself. Yep.
Ah, I'm so selfish. I agree. Uh, UK asylum. Yeah.
No, no, no, no. This is what you call a
hobby, Greavesy. You know how you got
hobbies and stuff like this is a hobby.
This is a hobby, lad.
A real hobby, you know.
Oh, Christian is he
Christian is he left me. Oh,
she left me, man.
I can't believe she left me.
All I wanted to do was be her friend. UK asylum.
She left me. Oh gosh. Oh. Oh,
Stephen. How do these women play games?
They definitely play games with women,
don't they? Yeah.
I don't want games.
I just want to be loved. You know,
I just want to be loved, baby. is Babies. Oh gosh.
I hope you're looking forward to uh Thursday, lad.
I hope you're looking forward to it. Yep.
Am I ever going to find someone that
loves me? Greavvesy.
Someone that loves me for me.
Someone that will stay with me. What?
What if I have a baby? Greasy.
Maybe I could have a baby.
Where is he? Oh gosh.
Without Peter Belly Greaves, you would
die in it. Without Peter Belly content,
you would die, lad.
Oh, I don't like that Ricks. I don't
like Rick squeezy.
I don't like Ricks. Do you?
I can't believe. Is that good enough for
you, Greavvesy? A 42 in TV. I would have
thought you would have bought a bigger
TV, Grezy, with all that money that you got, lad. Oh,
I would have thought you would have got
a bigger one, lad.
Yeah, makes sense.
Imagine playing it in the cinema,
Greezy. No, that's too big, is it?
That's too big. That is scary, bro.
No, that's scary. Is it?
My TV is a 55 in, but it's it's good enough.
But Grezy, imagine playing it in the
cinema. Nah, that's scary, bro.
That's scary, isn't it?
That gives me anxiety, bro, thinking about it.
I see someone play Xbox 360 in the cinema before
I've seen it before, lad.
I have seen it before.
I put it on a projector, Grezy. In the
old house, I had a projector. We put the
PlayStation 3 on a projector. It was all
right, you know.
It's not 32 in. It's a 55 in.
On Thursday when I go approaching, I'm
going to ask if any of these women could
be my mama. Greavvesy.
What do you think about that?
I'm going to ask them. Yeah.
Yeah. I say I f with my family. I don't
speak to my mom anymore.
Would you be my mama?
Yeah, I will. Yeah.
I just want to be treated like a baby. What door?
Don't get lippy.
But why is that being a weirdo greasy?
But I do want them to treat me like a baby.
The way USA is. She treated me like a baby. Greasy.
I said, "Can I see your boobies now?
It's feeding time."
And then she got them out, grievy. She
pulled her top up.
I said, "Great.
I didn't want to be treated like a baby.
That's what they're there for, to to to
to look after you and stuff and treat you nice." Grezy,
I'm going to I'm going to buy a crown.
I'm going to buy a crown and put it on my head
and say, "Yep, I'm the king." Boozy.
Yeah. I said I said to her, "Oh, can I
see your boobs now?" And then she put
and then she lifted her top up and then
I started feeding.
Maybe I've already got thousands and
thousand Bob bills. You never know, lad.
You don't know how much money I've got.
Is that cute? Greavvesy. She fed me.
I fed her and she fed me. Lovely. Greasy.
How cute is that? Greasy.
That's so cute. Ain't it Greasy?
I've already fed them it before. My I've
already fed my sperm to them before.
It's nice seeing them swallow it.
swallow your babies. So, yeah,
I think I've had it three times where
they swallowed it.
It's funny watching it.
Yeah, it's only protein for them, isn't
it, Greavvesy? It's good for them.
Sperm, when they swallow it, it's good
for them, is it, Grezy?
Yeah. You're just feeding them in it and
they feed you. So, everyone's happy.
Yeah, I got a [ __ ] in the al anyway by Bills.
I was about to pass out. It felt so good.
It was this American chick.
I put my penis in her mouth. Yeah.
I can't I can't remember if I came or
not. I can't even remember.
I can't remember. I can't remember.
But she kept coming on to me. So
I said, "Okay, if you want it that bad, then
we'll go around the corner and do it
dirty." And we did. So yeah,
if you want to do it dirty, we'll go
around the corner.
Lovely, isn't it, Bob?
Nothing better than sticking your not
your your your dirty penis in someone's mouth.
I can't think of a more satisfying thing.
Nope. It happened in real life, lad.
None of the stories that I I say are are fake, lad.
Everything I say is the truth.
Don't have to lie about anything, lad.
It was two years ago.
I can't believe she sucked my dick
without like washing it or anything.
That's kind of hot. Steven Howard,
she just put it in her mouth.
I could have My dick could have been anywhere.
That's kind of hot.
More chance of pig flying. Bob bills.
More chance of pigs flying, lad.
More chance of pig flying. But it will
be a laugh nonetheless.
What do you mean selfwashing?
I fingered her and I put my dick in her
mouth. Well, I took my trousers down and
she just started sucking my dick. So, yeah,
it's kind of hot. Yeah,
that was hot, man. That was really hot.
She kept coming on to me. She was drunk.
I was drunk as well. So, I thought,
"Okay, [ __ ] it.
I'm not going to say no, am I?" So,
I was also drunk as well, so yeah.
Put my penis in her mouth.
Yeah, that sounds rapey, bro.
That is weird.
This American kept coming on to me
saying, "I really want you. I really
want you." And kept kissing me. So, I
thought, "Okay, [ __ ] it.
I'll take her around the corner."
She started on me. She kept like coming
on to me. Okay, fine.
Yeah, that's not going to happen in this
country, Bob Bills, lad.
So, you're not you're not going to be
hearing it cuz it's not going to happen.
So, you got more chance of GTA 6 coming
out next month than uh getting a shag in this country.
You got more chance of GTA 6 coming out next month.
So yeah, lad.
Yeah, I didn't pray on this one. She
just kept coming on to me. So I thought,
"Oh, okay, fine.
You can show me how bad you really want me."
And she did by giving me a [ __ ] So yeah.
What do you think about that, Greavvesy?
She was cleaning my dick with her mouth.
That's lovely, isn't it, Greavvesy? In the alleyway.
I wonder how it tasted greasy
cuz obviously I clean my dick and stuff
but I didn't wipe it which is a hot
thing. That's really hot.
Yeah, that's really hot. Grezy,
that 19year-old, I asked her like, "Do
you know why she fell out with me?" I
said to her, "How did my dick taste?"
And um I want to get you pregnant.
No, I think Yeah, I think I said, "Can I
get you pregnant?" and stuff. And she
said, "What the fuck?"
And I asked her how my dick tasted and
stuff. I'm curious.
That's lovely. Is it Grezy?
What do you think of that? Grezy.
I said, did it taste nice? Lovely. Yeah. All
right, I'm going to sleep. I'm tired.
See you later.