because he's already found his mama.
I can sing. I can
Lovely bit of Pepsi in the morning.
What more could you want, eh?
What more could you want? Yeah, man.
No, no, no, no, no. Oh, gosh. What are
you doing here? Few
days until the madness. I've been
looking forward to this.
I've actually been looking forward to
this, bro. Actually have
been looking forward to this. Yeah.
Yeah. Just having a little breakfast.
We're waiting for our breakfast.
I want to do a madness, bro. A madness.
Madness. They do. Just an approaching
madness, bro. That's all. Just getting
drunk and doing a [ __ ] madness
on Thursday, man. I went out Monday last
week. It wasn't even that bad for Monday.
It weren't even that bad.
Yeah, that as well.
>> Yeah, bro. I was scrolling up messages.
Yeah, when I uh earlier, bro, between me
and Christian Izzy. She is an actual
[ __ ] you know, bro. I was listening to
them properly. Yeah. Like, oh my god,
these [ __ ] are so entitled, bro.
They're so entitled. I'm thinking, what
am I actually hear? Am I actually
hearing right, lads? What the [ __ ]
Bro, they're actual [ __ ] I told
Ant-Man as well.
I told Antman, bro. Actually told Antman. Madness.
These people deserve every everything
they get like cheating and all of that
stuff. Like people that cheat on them.
They deserve it, bro. Trust me. They
actually deserve this [ __ ] But the
[ __ ] they get, they deserve, lad.
Oh, there's a new film on in the cinema.
I was thinking of going there, bro.
Yeah, they actually deserve it. They're mad.
Yeah, same. Timmy pop up popped up to me
with me today as well, bro.
Same with me.
So, I need to get my haircut on
Thursday. I'd get my haircut today, but
I'm going out Thursday. So,
yeah, I'm going out Thursday,
so I'll just go just get a Thursday.
Not tomorrow the next day. Get up. Yeah.
Fact, that's what people used to say,
bro. When they were counting down as a
kid, you're counting down till
Christmas. Not tomorrow the next day.
But that always used to like always just
happen, bro. You say not tomorrow the
next day, not tomorrow the next day
and you're counting down the days to Christmas.
Oh well, bro. Oh well.
about, oh, you're not going to waste
your breath on someone you don't care
about. Like, like you haven't sent
people for five um voice messages like,
"Are you mad?" And then these people
wonder why they get cheated on. [ __ ] off, bro.
They're mad. And then they wonder why
people cheat on them. How mad is that? Thank you. Cheers.
There we go.
Look at that,
mate. Look at that. Been wanting this,
you know, for the past two weeks.
Just a nice spoons breakfast.
I don't like that, though. Look,
look, there's no yolk.
I can't be bothered to tell him to
change it to be fair. I can't be [ __ ]
like this. Good old suicide mark.
Yeah, they give you fried eggs, but
they're [ __ ] more like boiled.
There's no yolks.
You know, I'm not drinking till Thursday, man.
I'm not drinking until Thursday. I don't
when I when I've set a day to go out, I
detox until the day I go out.
No, don't be on further.
>> Yeah, she's a [ __ ] bro. Sending voice
notes like that about you're not wasting
your breath on something you don't care
about, yet you're the one [ __ ]
sending me 23 messages.
These [ __ ] are cheeky, uncle. These
these these [ __ ] are cheeky, lad. Oh, that's
what the [ __ ]
I don't drink. I don't drink that much.
I'm not alcohol.
And that'll be it. After Thursday, that
will be it. So, yeah,
it'll be interesting, eh?
All right, Indigo. Uh, this thing popped up. Yeah.
On YouTube. I think it was Red Star.
And I'm thinking, bro, [ __ ] me.
Do you not get bored of stalking men in 2026?
Stalking men for four every day for four
or five years. I couldn't do it, bro.
I take my hats off to anyone that's got
um that that amount of time on their hands.
That is mad.
I could never like ever
be able to justify why would someone sit
on the internet for 4 years stalking men. But
I drunk twice last week to be fair which
was bad. It was only Guinness. Not that
it makes it any better, but I drunk
twice last last week.
cuz the whole dating thing was
depressing me, bro. So, I just run here.
Yeah, it was depressing as [ __ ] bro.
But, um, yeah.
I only drink Guinness anyways. So
I people can sit on the internet for
years stalking men. Uncle Andy,
you would sit on the internet stalking
women for years.
I don't understand how they can do it in though.
How they can sit on the internet for
years stalking men but claim they're
straight and claim they're not jealous.
all in the same sentence. That's mad.
They must be I think they're lying to
themselves at this point.
I think they're lying to themselves when
they're saying that they're not jealous
or something or they're not gay.
That is mental. You couldn't even stalk
a woman for 6 months, let alone stalk a
man for 4 years.
That is [ __ ] mental, bro. That is
insane. really really insane.
Couldn't even imagine it, bro. Couldn't
even imagine doing it.
So that must mean they sit
Oh, [ __ ] That must mean that they sit
on on YouTube, right?
That must mean that they sit on YouTube.
the time they wake up
to the time they go to bed recording
stuff. Uncle Andy,
that is mad.
From the time they wake up to the time
they go bed stalking people,
stalking men. That is [ __ ] weird, bro.
Tells you everything you need to know
about these people.
I don't have channels dedicated to
people. I don't record people every day. [ __ ] bad.
Yeah, they got nothing, guys. If they
had anything, they wouldn't be on there
doing what they do. Simple.
You know, and I know it.
Most of them probably got [ __ ]
agophobia. They don't even believe their house.
Most of them.
If you're talking about yourself, lad.
No self-reflectors on this channel.
Trying to bring the energy down.
Go self-reflect on another channel, lad.
We don't have time for self-reflectors.
Negative self-reflectors on this channel.
Go back to Ly's channel. You mong. See
you later, lad. Get kicked.
You know what it is with the people there?
Did you see yesterday when I said, "Oh,
I want money and I'm going to be going
out Thursday." You see the amount of
people I had to ban? Remember the amount
of people I had to block?
Do good, man.
Did you see the amount of people I had
to ban and block yesterday?
And you're another self-reflector. You
get a timeout, you little weirdo. See
you later, lad.
And then we actually self-projecting
people. There was a lot of people
yesterday. And do you know what the
reason for that was? It's because
you've got a life.
Unlike these people. These people are
sat at home lonely skin, no life,
nothing going for themselves, no family.
That's why they're on this tech this
sector day in day out, day in day out,
day in day out. So when they're here and
someone's doing something that they
could never do because a they ain't got
no money, b they got no confidence, they
they can't do any of that stuff. They
come on here and hate. That's where a
lot of this comes from. Hate, jealousy.
Um and you noticed it yesterday as well,
bro. Cuz I already told people what my
plans were. So
they're just sad, fat, ugly people just
wasted sat on YouTube all day every day.
Nothing going for themselves, you know?
And that's what these people are like on
this community, bro.
They're just jealous, obsessed, weird. Yeah, losers.
I don't know what else. Just losers.
Yeah, that's it, bro.
This is nice, bro. Oh, now it's kind of
You can see it
this band. Lad,
listen to me. If you don't shut up, I'm
going to come to Birmingham. I'm going
to knock the [ __ ] out of you. You come.
Self projecting, lad. Sit down. Timmy,
the only reason I didn't go to [ __ ] Birmingham.
Een, stop me. Een was like, "Oh, no.
Don't go. Don't go."
Timmy, I missed you by a hair's breath,
mate. I missed you by a hair's breath
for you. I was I was I would have
knocked you the [ __ ] out. Yeah. Everyone
know that you ran in that field.
Everyone know that you ran in that
field. Yeah. Everyone know that you
ditched the the the cab that was down
the road I walked past. You're a [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
You're a [ __ ] I've got some money at
home in cash. Not showing you it though,
Timmy. That's self projecting. You still
need to show me £2,600 lad.
You show me £2,600. Come back to me.
Simple. I got some money at home, by the
way. I'm not showing you it, though. Yeah.
Next time if you're going to do
something, don't run away and say in a
pub that you said you was going to be. Yeah.
Yeah. Of course you
just a [ __ ] That's all you are.
Oh, [ __ ] Just in the pub having a breakfast.
That's why Greavves is not here.
Timmy, stop embarrassing yourself.
You don't You're not getting [ __ ] off.
Give me a time out, lad. Until you learn
how to act normal, you got to time out. invited. Man,
>> sorry, Uncle. I just don't want to be
arguing with these spastics.
I just don't want to be arguing with
these utter spastics, lad. Sorry, man. Yeah.
Do you see how many haters I got
yesterday? Uncle Andy,
I mean, did you see how many people I
had to block yesterday?
Did you not see how many people I had to
block yesterday, bro?
[ __ ] hell. So many, bro. So many.
Yeah, that's a block. So many bugs.
These people in this community are absolute wasters.
A lot of them, bro. There some white
people in this community, but a lot of
these people here are absolute wasters.
I hate to agree with um
LT, bro, cuz I don't like the guy, but
this is I think this is true, you know,
about energy and he's biased as well,
but energy vampires.
To be honest, it's true because look how
much they tried to bring the energy
energy down yesterday. These alcoholic,
fat, ugly people that don't leave their
houses. Look how many times they tried
to drag the they tried to bring the
energy down yesterday, bro. when we was
going on a madness because their skin
cuz they got no life cuz they got
nothing going for themselves.
You understand, bro? They tried to put
the energy. They tried to drive the
energy out so much.
They actually did, bro.
They're [ __ ] just fat alcoholic
wasters. That's what they are, bro.
with no life, nothing going for
themselves. So, their goal is to bring
you down to their level.
Do you understand what I'm saying? Their
goal was to bring other people down to their level.
Try to bring people down to their level.
One second. But I need to listen to this voice. Y
I just need to sign. But yeah.
Yeah. These people try to bring the
energy down so much.
I feel bad for these people, bro. I do
feel bad for the people in this community.
At the end, you just feel you just end
up feeling bad for him, to be honest.
No, no, no. Yeah, bro. Anyways,
I'm gone. Yeah, be back later.