[Music] Yeah,
man. God, that's what's mongos and law
is like that's literally Yeah. I swear
to God, bro. That's the [ __ ] side of
YouTube. That's literally the [ __ ] side of
YouTube. It's the [ __ ]
side. It's crazy, bro. But um what I'm
going to do, yeah, after this live
stream, I'm going to take one week off
of YouTube. So, Tuesday to Tuesday.
Yeah. And when I come back, I don't want
to see any of these people on
YouTube. I don't want to see I'm going
to look every day from Tuesday when I
come back. And I don't want to see any
of these people on
YouTube because remember, we're the
skinn ones. We're the muners. We're
this, we're that, we're all these
negative things. So surely to God if we
have all these things these people won't
be on YouTube will they
simple and then when I come
back then I see all these people I'm
just going to scream no live for the
YouTube that's literally what I'm going to
scream as honest to God what I'm going
to [ __ ] scream I'm going to be like
no life for
YouTube as loud as I can because these
people wife on L J's. I'm telling you, I
was speaking to my friend um yesterday
and he was
saying that um you used to be a um
psychologist because we were speaking
about like celebrities and stuff. He
said, "Oh, you used to be a
psychologist." He says, "Uh you you know
your stuff." I was like, "Yeah." It's
like it's even like Nor J's followers.
They're all fat. They're all ugly.
They're all in their 40s. Nothing going
for themselves, which is why they're on
him every day. Most of them are on
benefits. Never had a job in their life.
So they just come on here and project
cuz they got nothing better to do.
That's literally what these people do on
this community. Literally, that is what
they do. They have nothing in their
lives. That's why they stalk people and
gossip every single day without failure,
without hesitation cuz they got
nothing. These are the real life
bunters. I'm telling you, they are the
real These people are the real life
muners. the biggest month is ever known
to man mankind. I'm telling you
because they call people this, they call
people that, they call people this, they
call people that. Yeah. They're the ones
that are stuck on YouTube every day
waiting for people to go live to hate.
Doesn't Doesn't look good, does it? It
really really doesn't look
good, you know.
Same spastics every
day. It's weird, man. It's a weird
community. Weird community,
lad. They haven't found me. They don't
know where I live. And even if they did
know where I live, uh that's not where I
live. And even if they did know where I
live, they still wouldn't do anything.
So, I mean, that was the whole point. I
was I was going to do a video about
this, but I didn't. I was like, it's all
well and good stalking somebody and
trying No one knocked my door because
you don't know where I live. Um, and uh
it's all well and good knowing trying to
find where someone lives. So, let's say
by the off chance you find where someone
lives, okay? And what you going to do?
You're not going to come on the door.
You're not going to do anything to
anyone. So, why would you even try to
find where out where someone lives?
because you're never going to do
anything. So, what I'm saying is, do you
want my ass? Like, do you do you want my
dick or something? Like, do do you want
to [ __ ] me or something? Like, or you
want to do something in it and you don't
know where I live. And that's why I'm
prepared to stay live. And if you really
really think that I live there, if you
really really really think Yeah. that I
live there, then
um yeah, bro, send send what you want.
Do what you want. You don't know where I
live. You will never know where I live. So keep
trying. So keep
trying. Keep trying, lad. You people
don't ruin no one. And you will never
ruin anyone. Even if you knew where
people lived. Yeah. Simple.