Yeah.
Yeah. Did anyone win their football
bets? I didn't win any of mine, bro.
Not even a single chance.
Not even a single [ __ ] winner
on any of mine. I don't know about you.
What a buzz kill.
What an What an energy kill. What a mood killer.
Don't know about any of you people. That
is a [ __ ] mood killer. That's enough
to get anyone depressed. I only put I
only put £10 on bets, lad.
I only put£10 on bets, bro.
It's [ __ ] depressing. I don't know
about anyone else that put any football
bets on that. It's depressing, bro.
What a vibe killer. What a buzz kill.
Imagine you was Imagine you were going
out drinking, bro. Yeah. and you and and
you put £510 on the football and it
lost. That is a buzz kill.
Proves I'm right all along with what I
was saying. Is it Oh Yeah,
that is [ __ ] depressing, bro. An 8
pound bet and a two pound bet. That is
[ __ ] depressing, bro.
That is actually depressing, man. Yeah.
See, with gambling, it determines
Gambling determines your mood, lad.
Gambling determines your mood. If I
lose, I feel like killing myself,
whether it's £5,10,
or killing someone. And if I win, it
doesn't matter how much it is. It's the
opposite. That's how gambling works with
me. But I'm aware it doesn't work like
I'm aware it doesn't work like that with
most people. But it works like that with
me, bro. Even if it's like£10, I don't
like losing. You're playing to win.
You're you're playing to win, not
playing to lose. Yeah, I put 10 pound
worth of football bets on to win, not lose.
Yeah, that's the whole point of it for
me. Don't know about anyone else.
It's a vibe killer, lad. It's a vibe killer.
It's a [ __ ] vibe killer. Yeah, bro.
I'm not in the mood, bro. I'm seriously
not in the mood.
I feel like seriously seriously harming
someone, bro. I'm not even joking. This
is how I get I feel like doing someone
dirty, bro. proper proper dirty. I'm not
even laughing. I'm saying it.
Yeah. Don't know about anyone else. When
they lose, I think I'm the only way. I'm
the only one. Yeah.
No, that's depressing as [ __ ] bro. That
is depressing as [ __ ] lad. I don't have no disability.
Well, you know what I mean by that. You know,
no, that's depressing, bro. I'll
probably be in bed all day tomorrow.
That is [ __ ] depressing.
That is absolutely depressing, bro.
I'm not even joking. That is [ __ ]
depressing as [ __ ] And that was only
£10 worth of football bets. That is
depressing as [ __ ]
No. No. You just simply don't like
losing. You just simply don't like
losing. You're You're gambling to win.
You're not gambling to lose.
Yeah, losing a football bet is
depressing as well. I lost two of them.
An 8 pound one and a two pound one.
That's depressing. Bad experiences with
women is depressing, but you don't see
me crying about it. You don't see me
[ __ ] crying about it, do you?
So, you shouldn't either. Yeah.
Yeah, just 10 pound, bro. It lost. Now
I'm [ __ ] depressed as [ __ ] Don't
want to get out of bed, bro.
>> Yeah. See you later, lad.
See you later, lad. See you later. Yeah,
it was only £10.
Yeah, it was only £10, but still.
No,£10 is not a lot to lose.
See, I don't give a [ __ ] mate. You got
money. I don't give a [ __ ]
Doesn't mean anything.
You have money. It doesn't mean anything, lad.
Doesn't mean nothing.
Losing is depressing, bro.
Losing is very depressing. Whether it's
£5,10, doesn't matter what the amount
is, doesn't matter what you have left.
It's depressing along with all the other
issues we have to deal with.
Depressing. I can't think of of a more depressing thing. At
least we can pray we don't wake up tomorrow Morning.
Yeah. Hopefully we can die in our sleep.
That'd be lovely.
Yeah, that'd be lovely, bro.
That is what you would call That is what
would be called lush. That's [ __ ]
depressing as [ __ ] Along with all the
other things as well, bro.
No. Hopefully I die tomorrow, bro. I die
in my sleep so there will be no Thursday.
Yeah. I think that's the only thing I
ain't got the balls to do is kill myself.
I think that's the only thing I ain't
got the balls to do.
But one day, bro, trust me, one day I [ __ ] will.
I'll just stop coming online and that'll be it.
No joke, bro. You laugh at it, but
you'll see one day, mate. You'll see one
day when I pluck the courage.
When I pluck up the courage, you'll see
what will happen, bro. That's that.
I don't know what happens.
Yeah, I just lost a£10 bet. Steven Howard.
Yeah, another 10 pound football lost.
One way to bring the vibe down.
They're bringing the vibe right now.
Depressing, isn't it?
Yeah. It be lovely just to die in your sleep. Yeah,
we die in the end anyways, lad.
We live, we get bad experiences, and we die.
That's all that ever happens.
You live, you get bad experiences, you
die. The end. Yeah.
You don't even know what my favorite
saying is. Nothing ever happens and
nothing ever changes.
I think that's a good quote. I made it myself.
Nothing happens and nothing changes.
Do I know anyone who's on alive themselves?
Yes, a few people.
And they're smart people. They shouldn't
be They shouldn't be known as cowards,
bro. They should be known as smart people.
I'm surprised more people don't do it to be honest.
Cuz nothing ever happens and nothing ever changes.
Nothing ever happens and nothing ever changes. Yeah. Sorry. Sad.
Wrong place. The [ __ ] are you talking about?
Nothing happens and nothing changes.
Do you like it?
We've already lost human in the human
race. We've already lost faith in the
human race. We've already lost faith in humanity.
Do you know what I mean?
>> No, it's not funny, bro. You're not
going to make me laugh. I'm pissed off, bro.
All I want to do is go outside and just
hurt someone, bro.
Really badly. Really, really badly, bro.
You can't make me laugh, lad. It's
annoying as [ __ ]
It's really bad, bro. Oh, well.
Yeah. Don't remind me. Thursday. More
bad experiences to come. Grievy. [ __ ]
hell. I think this this I think the next
one would actually kill me, bro. I think
the next bad experience would actually
kill me. I think that will be me finished.
This one already gave me crippling
[ __ ] anxiety for God knows how long
or a week. I'm going to be finished now, bro.
Anything like that, I I'll be completely finished.
Trust me, bro.
more bad experiences to come on Thursday.
It's like what I said to Ant-Man
earlier. I said you've got more chance of winning
uh for team correct score than you do
meeting a woman that's normal in this country.
Like think of how mad that is. You've
got more chance of winning a correct
score on four games
and people don't do their bets. So what I mean?
Yeah, definitely. Bro, you got more chance.
just fed up with it to be honest with
you. I'm just sick of it.
Well, I'm the one that said it to him.
So, I mean, it come for me, didn't it? Yeah.
I'm bit fed up to be honest with you.
And I'm going to be the same tomorrow as well.
Not good, bro.
I might die in my sleep, lad. So there
might not be a Thursday.
There might not be a Thursday if I die
in my sleep,
which with a bit like I do, that is
depressing as [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
Nothing happens and nothing changes.
So, like I said, um I'm only going out
Thursday cuz I said I was going to, but
the damage is irreversible.
You can't even meet You can't even meet
anyone now, Greezy, because the damage
is literally irreversible
what these people have done over the years. So,
you're pretty much [ __ ]
So that's my take on it anyways. Yeah.
It's bad, isn't it?
You ever think the older you get,
Greasy, you think what do you actually
like? Life's pretty [ __ ] at 28. I'm
the same age as you. I feel like you
didn't care when you was like 23, 24.
I feel like life is scary, is it? As you get older,
I don't know.
laughing at you, mocking you.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
Hopefully I die in my sleep. Lad,
if you think about a UK as silent,
nothing's changed in like 3 years.
If you think from 3 to 4 years,
literally nothing has changed and
nothing will ever change.
You just get more bad experiences
and gambling's harder to win. I don't
know who ever said it life was going to
change, but they were they were they were mistaken.
Nah, change is never possible in this country.
Never. Absolutely no way.
No, change is never possible. It will
always be the same here.
Dating, women, gambling, it will always
be the same. And it's been and it's been
the same for years as well. It's been
exactly the same way for years. I'm not
I'm not even trolling. It's actually got
worse. It's got worse. I say it's been
the same. It's got worse.
You can speak to people now [ __ ]
every day for a month with no intentions
of meeting you. Now, that wasn't a thing
back in the day.
Back in the day, that never really
happened. If you met someone in person,
it's got worse and worse and worse.
Everything has gotten worse. Nothing
ever changes ever.
How could it?
They're not banning Tik Tok. They're not banning Instagram.
>> How are they b How is it changing, bro?
No, I'm good, bro.
>> What do you mean it's better to have
hope and stay positive? There's nothing
to be positive about. Why are you lying
to yourself, bro?
Be positive to be let down. Why would
you do that? You Why would you give
yourself false hope when there's no
hope? If you expect the worst, then
you're not going to be disappointed.
Literally, if you expected the worst,
why would you be positive when you know
nothing's going to change?
going by the going by your going by your
um going by your history. It's it's
simple. It's simple as that. Why would
you be positive
when you know nothing's going to change?
It don't make sense. At least if you
accept your situation as [ __ ] then you
you know what it is. There ultimately is no hope.
There is literally no hope. I don't know
how people keep telling people that
there is telling people like me that there is.
It's not changing.
It will never change. So
never ever ever. So
best way is just to die, I think.
My experiences makes me not want to wake
up tomorrow. How about that one? UK asylum.
Not my mindset. My experiences.
So yeah, my experiences
rightfully so. If you I don't know how
I've not ended up killing myself
or having a severe severe severe mental breakdown
like them people that just don't leave
the house for like 10 years. I'm
surprised to be honest with you how
that's not happened. I don't give a [ __ ]
about other people. Some people have got
worse lives. Some people have got better
lives. If they don't want to kill
themselves, that's them, lad. If people
don't want to kill themselves, that's
that's on them.
Good for them, bro. I'm happy for them. Nah, bro.
You know, I don't smoke.
I don't I don't smoke, lad.
But if they want to stay alive, bro,
that's on them, man. There's homeless
people that stay alive, but that's on
them. I don't give a [ __ ]
Nothing's going to change. So, that's
that. That's facts. Nothing will ever
change. And that's certain
on the Bible.
Doesn't matter. It doesn't matter, does it? Greasy.
Tomorrow should there be no [ __ ] um
there'll be no Thursday.
That's my slogan, lad.
Nothing happens and nothing changes.
Blind people don't learn sign language, you [ __ ]
Deaf people do.
Oh, I was just going to go out drinking lad
and sending it, but I'm not sure if I'm
going to now, bro. I can't be bothered. Too depressed.
That's depressing, bro.
Just want to stay in bed, bro. You know
what I mean? Not move.
It's depressing, man.
It's [ __ ] depressing, is it?
Proper depressing, lad.
Proper proper depressing.
Not interested, Cory. Lad, not interested.
Not interested, bro.
probably just give up with life again. I reckon
just like a couple of months ago. Hey um hey Grezy
Sorry about that, bro.
No, I was on I'm on Reddit, lad.
I really just want to strangle someone, you know?
Just strangle someone to their [ __ ]
eyes pop out.
You know, you don't even know, mate.
Like, just strangle someone till their
eyes pop out, bro. You really don't understand.
Seriously, just just throttle them.
Yeah. Well, I'm saying it again, lad. I
said it the other day and guess what?
I'm saying it again.
So, if you don't like it, [ __ ] off.
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] about jail, lad. H
I'll be in bed tomorrow and I'll
probably be in bed Thursday.
Nothing happens and nothing changes.
That's my little saying, lad. Nothing
happens and nothing changes.
Simple as that.
It's the truth, don't it?
Nothing happens and nothing changes.
It's true that
I would get that. I would get that
tattooed. It's a good saying, bro.
a bad mood all day tomorrow as well.
All day Thursday
2026, same problems.
Same problems as 2022.
Four years of [ __ ]
Four years of constant [ __ ]
Nothing ever happens and nothing ever changes.
Simple as that. Yeah,
I was watching Green Street G Here's a
Yeah, I was watching some Green Street clips. Squeezy.
Them bill [ __ ] were laughing at us and
I just [ __ ] snapped.
It was funny at the time, bro. But I
can't even laugh at it now.
You can't even laugh at it, bro. It's
depressing as [ __ ]
These football bets are depressing, is it?
I mean, what could possibly change, Grezy? Um,
the damage is irreversible
that I've had over the years.
So, I mean, it's irreversible.
It's irreversible damage. It's like
having brain damage is irreversible.
So, what are you actually expecting is
going to change?
Like, [ __ ] hell, bro. Like, let's be real.
Let's be real about it. Nothing
Nothing happens and nothing changes.
It's as simple as that. Yeah.
We live, we get bad experiences and then we die.
That's all that happens. UK asylum. You live
you get kicked lad. See you later. Yeah,
bro. But you're not you're not going to
meet anyone on Thursday.
You're just going out to socialize.
You're just going out to uh talk to
people, in it.
That's what me and Antman was saying.
They said, "Uh, you just go out to
socialize, isn't it?"
Because me and you, we know deep down
that there is no chance here. There's no
chance it's ever going to change.
That's one of the reasons why I don't
really go out anymore because you know
that like it's never going to change. So
you just go out when you're kind of bored,
really bored. But deep down you know
it's never going to change. In 2026, you
can safely say that. You can safely say
you're not going to meet someone that's
different. No one's different.
Same as what Ant-Man says. It's just
it's the truth.
Nothing ever happens and nothing ever changes.
You live, you get bad experiences, you die.
die. The end.
I saw my sister today. Don't care.
Simply just don't care.
I simply just don't care.
None of my sisters have ever been with
London Taylor. But yeah, No,
nothing happens. And it's so mad that
like you know exactly what's going to
happen if you go out on Thursday, Grezy.
Is that mad like you know exactly what's
going to happen?
Isn't that mad?
Do you know exactly what's going to
happen? That's mad.
It's like you can predict the future at this point.
More bad experiences. More bad
experiences. More bad experiences
forever and always. Is that right, Grezy?
What do you think, Grezy? What do you
think it will be? Huh?
Yeah, is he? That's good for him, bro.
No one cares.
No one cares about that [ __ ]
type lying down. All right.
Yeah, I will.
So mad to think that you could actually
go out on Thursday, send it, and you'd
still you'd still be in the same situation.
Is that mad when you think about it?
Like you could actually go out, you can
actually go out Saturday.
Sorry, you could actually go out
Thursday and you'd still be in the same position.
That is madness, isn't it? That's perfect.
Nothing happens. Nothing changes.
Rey Antman said it's always going to be
the same day. You know this.
He's talking about England.
Yeah, he's right, isn't it?
Yeah, he's obviously right. It is always
going to be the same. Yeah,
it's always going to be the same here.
He's right in it, Grezy.
Bro, no one cares about Timmy, bro.
So, stop bringing it up, lad. No one
cares about that [ __ ]
I fancy some nuggets.
I'm too defeated, but I don't want any
more bad experiences. Literally, man.
This is the This is the toxic sector.
Is that right, Grezy? Yep. M
I feel defeated. Greasy.
It's not a nice way to feel defeated, is it?
Yeah, but Yeah, but En Legs Enlegs is a virgin.
Yeah, but Alex is an absolute virgin.
That's the difference. And leg is a virgin. Like
Yeah, Stephen, how you say what you want
about Ant-Man, but he's right, though,
in it. He's right.
It will always be the same here. I might
watch some incel videos. Well, they
don't class themselves as incelss, but
they just complain about women.
I'm feeling like that now. We need some nice toxicity,
some nice negativity before bed. Lovely.
Just before Betty buys. Lovely, man. I
want to watch some of their videos.
I always fall asleep to some of their videos.
I've had so many bad experiences,
Greavvesy. So many bad experiences. It's
It's They're irreversible.
It's literally irreversible. Like all jokes aside,
we're not even joking. We're being
serious now. It's irreversible.
The damage is done with so many
experiences over the years, bro.
And knowing how corrupt and [ __ ]
people are, it's over, bro. is done. Yeah,
I was done with this [ __ ] a long time
ago, bro. A long time ago. Mad,
this area is so depressing. This house
is so depressing as well.
[ __ ] low. [ __ ] low.
No, I just don't like it here. Like, cuz
it's so isolated.
I don't like living with Laney. And I
wouldn't like living by myself either.
I enjoy living with the other people in it.
I would get nuggets, but I can't be
bothered to eat Grimsy.
Life is [ __ ] Gre. Life is really [ __ ] Yeah.
I'm going to be in bed depressed tomorrow.
I want to be the world I want to be the
world's fat I'm going to be the world's
fattest person in like a month, lad.
The dating game makes you depressed as well.
The dating game is depressing, Greezy.
being sold a dream.
Very very depressing. Anyways,
I'm going. Yeah. See you later.