Yo yo yo yo yo.
Laughing at you. Moing you.
There we go.
There you go, Monty.
No, but you you see what I'm saying
though, is it UK? No, Grezy, you see
what I'm saying? Is it
like I went to Birmingham to bail this
[ __ ] out and and helped him with the Natalie thing?
And who have I got? No one
in a real life crisis.
Oh, Joker. Oh, that Rick needs to shut
his mouth as well, bro. He's getting on
my nerves. That Ricks
little batty man, bro. I hate that com.
I never liked him, you know. I never
like that Ricks.
Never like that Ricks, you know.
I think this is the fake Monty, but yeah,
>> fake multi yourself. Fake multi. Well,
why was you trying to get me to code
approach when you knew I was had
feelings Natalie? If you was a mate
got me cold approach, would you?
>> Well, let me answer you then. You ask me
a question. You don't let me answer it.
>> So, basically, uh because what if she
never come back and then you met the
love of your life on the night out with me?
>> Well, it well, it didn't matter if they
didn't come back to me or if she did
come back to me. It's a matter of
responsibility. It's like you didn't
give Natalie a chance to come back to me.
>> What do you mean? I didn't What do you
mean? What do you mean I didn't give her games?
>> No, she was playing games.
>> Who were playing games?
>> Natalie, you said she was playing games. What?
>> So, so how was Natalie playing games? In
what way was Natalie playing games?
>> Because she she was she was playing
games. She blocked she blocked you and
you were trying to reach out to her.
>> So, so, so hang on a minute. Hang on a
minute. So, what was my fault? Um, pause
arguments between me and Natalie from
Natalie to break up with me.
And that's Natalie playing games. Is it
for Natalie wanting to have that
thinking to get away?
>> You wouldn't give option. Well, well, she did.
>> It doesn't matter if she didn't give me
answers or not. He was she she was angry
at that time. So why the [ __ ] is she
going to talk to me when she was angry?
>> Well, she might have Yeah, but what I'm
saying is she might have never come back.
>> I know what you're saying. I agree for
what what what you were saying. Yeah,
she should have talked to me, but people
would differently. PJ,
>> you know what I mean?
>> So either way, why would you go why
would you get me to go call the potion
if if you was looking out for me? You
know what I mean? And you know
>> to take to take your mind off of it is
>> but you being there with me just having
a drink with me
mind it. Why would the [ __ ] would I want
to go out called approach from some
woman to take my mind off a woman if I love?
>> Don't make sense PJ.
>> Yeah but it was fun in it. It was a fun
night out there.
>> I'm not saying it was a fun night out
because it were fun night out. Yeah.
Yeah. It was fun.
>> Where was you? Where was you? Where was
you the other day when I was sobbing?
Where was you?
>> Yeah. Where was you? Where was you?
>> I'm not your mate, am I? So I don't
curve yourself, PJ. I'm a user. Like you said,
>> you wasn't there, was you?
>> I'm a user. Just like you said, PJ, just
like you said.
>> No, you was you was laughing at me.
>> Yeah, of course. I'm a PJ. That's what
users do in it. They usually laugh at
you when you know.
>> Yeah. And I helped you with all that
[ __ ] Timmy Eldridge [ __ ] as well.
>> I don't care to be honest with you. The
man's just bastic. The man's tapped out.
The man thinks The man thinks him
arguing with everybody's going to get
everybody to meet him.
>> All right, listen, Monty. Yeah. Do you
remember when you said Do you remember
what you said to me the other day?
>> You said to me, you said to me, All
right, listen, Monty. You said to me,
"Yeah, you wonder to yourself every day
why I got you on this community, in it." >> What?
>> You said that you wonder to yourself
every day why I got you on this
community. Is it?
>> Yeah. Go on. Why did you get me onto the this community?
>> But it's it's a fun little sector, isn't it?
>> This is this is the toxic sector.
And once you run it, you can't leave.
That's the thing. It's like a tra just
it's a little toxic sector.
Don't you like it? Just community. Um money
>> we don't you like this community
obviously you like this community or
else you wouldn't be here looking for
attention of this community or crying about your
listen I don't need I talked to
Greavvesy and Steven
>> I'm not being funny on these people yeah
I'm not being funny these little clowns
in this community but all these clowns
are single just like yourself
Monty, this is no ugly as [ __ ] These
are these are
>> Wait, he said alcoholic shakers and that's it,
>> you know. Yeah, but Monty, people can
still have a good life and be single.
They can go out and have fun.
>> Yeah, but PJ, these are like you. These
are why they all watch you. These people
in this in this side of the community,
they all the [ __ ] all being by that ugly stick.
>> Yeah, but I'm going out tomorrow and
having some fun.
>> Yeah, but you know what's going to
happen there, PJ?
I don't give a [ __ ] Yeah, but this and
body I don't like I would never get with
Natalie G. So you can't even use that
against me. And I'm not I'm not saying
anything. I'm just saying. I'm just
>> Hang on. Hang on. Hang on. Why do you
just ching out of this name up in all?
>> Because I know cuz I know what you're
trying to do. I don't know what you're
trying to do and it's not going to work.
>> What have we tried to do?
>> Listen, these people in this community
that are single, they fancy that energy.
I don't fancy that energy.
>> Yeah, I'm not being funny, but these are
more ugly than [ __ ] Timmy for [ __ ]
sake. This is why they so want sex with
every [ __ ] woman on this YouTube. But
[ __ ] hell, man. These are the kind of
people who will will shag G and cosmic
kitty for [ __ ] sake.
>> Yeah, but that's not me. I wouldn't I
don't care about any woman on this
community. Look, I argue with that
Autumn Rose. I don't like her. I don't
like any woman on this community.
You know that?
>> No, but you're you're out of order. You
are. You're out of order. You are.
>> Think of it, Monty. Yeah. when you was
going through that thing in Birmingham.
I'm the one that come. Not not your mate
Craig. No one from Manchester. They
could have easily come to you. They're
[ __ ] too far from someone talking to
Craig then at that time.
>> Yeah, but you must have other friends.
>> Yeah, I've got loads of mates. >> Yeah.
>> Met a couple of my mate
>> and you just you just throw me under the
bus every time.
>> Yeah. Not good getting touched under the
bus though. You're not in the best
feeling ever. That was supposed to be
nice feeling it getting ted under the bus. >> No,
>> was it not a nice feeling?
>> And we also had plans to go to the
pictures. Do you remember?
>> [ __ ] off. For [ __ ] off.
>> You think I sit next to you in the
pictures and hold your hand around and
share some popcorn with you? PJ,
>> not hold hands, but yeah.
>> No, I know. [ __ ] you.
>> Listen, listen, listen. Okay, fair
enough. Money. You got me I got you on
this community just like you got me on
the PlayStation community. Fair is fair. Is it?
>> Fair. PJ.
>> Yeah. You got me on the PlayStation
community. Yeah. So,
>> yeah, but the community what I got you
into on play on PlayStation's nothing
like this. Okay then. Okay then, PJ,
which community would you rather be in?
Yeah. This [ __ ] Tor community. Yeah.
All the community on on PlayStation.
>> Yeah. But PlayStation, but I got bullied
by Aaron Cox. >> Yeah.
>> I was I was young. I was I was 16 and he
he used to bully me.
>> Well, there you go. You you just said it.
>> Yeah, but Aaron Cox used to bully me and
you used to watch it
and I was six. I was like 17, bro.
>> Yeah. So So what you know that's what
what the community was about arguing
like you know.
>> No, it was funny to be fair. I actually
No, I actually did like that community.
It was actually funny, man. To be fair.
>> No, that's what it was about. It was a
good community back there. Better than
this shitty one here. These are nothing
on here. These are just ugly ass [ __ ]
old pens old pensioners. These ones are
the same age as my mom for [ __ ] sake.
>> Yeah, that's a good question. That's
good though, is it? Yeah. The community
that you just can't seem to leave, Monty.
>> Yeah, it's true. Why can't you leave it
then if you don't like it?
>> Well, I have left. Do I go live? Do I um
go live often these days? Have I been live today? like
I being lied these days. No, because who's
that's very nice, man. That's a [ __ ]
lovely thing. That's a That's a lovely fact. >> Course
I don't go live anymore like for these
people anymore. You know what I mean?
There's nothing to go live for these
days. Oh, I'd be going live now, would I?
>> Obviously, I'm live now.
>> You go live sometimes. Sometimes you do it
>> sometimes. Yeah, sometimes. But not not
often like I used to. What's the point
for the same shitty people to write the
same shitty comments? I thought if I
give him a break from saying the same
comments and come back next week, it'd
be gone irrelevant writing the same
comments over again.
>> More like more like slug skin.
>> All of it. All of it.
I'm sure that they they only can write
certain words and
>> maybe maybe they're robots and not real
people in it.
>> No, man. They ain't got no m
>> How can Yeah, but how can they write the
same stuff every day? Like they like
robots, isn't it?
>> It's cuz they only It's cuz that's only
what they can spell obviously. Cuz it's
only what they can think of for [ __ ] sake.
>> Do you remember? I agree with you. Do
remember it's the same repeating people
Monty. That's what you used to say the
same repeated people.
>> It used to say repeated people every
day. Same [ __ ] Mongle your skin. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. And obviously of course you are.
Of course you are.
>> No. Yeah. But it's weird. Yeah. But they
are they are obsessed with money on this community.
Monty. They're really obsessed with
money on this community. Yeah,
cuz I know what these are.
I wonder what these are are gamblers.
They ain't got no life. They just
gamblers spend the money and that's it
on [ __ ] fruit machines. Do me elders
do the clap on the head and that and they lose. >> Yeah,
>> they call people mongos in here because
they in a matter of fact is like worse
than what we are. Yeah.
>> Money a drug addict. >> Nah.
>> Oh, that's another thing. You've got
that wrong as well. Drug addict. What?
What? What's drugs, people? Is cannabis
really drugs? Nah, peeps. It's really
not. Is it? Cannabis is not drugs.
Cannabis is actually a herb.
It's a herb. And I'm a pthead. That is
totally different on a crackhead. I'm a
pot head in it. Different is from a pot
compared to a crackhead.
>> Yeah. You love weed in it.
>> Yeah. So, it's obviously they don't know
a crackhead from a pthead. It's
obviously You know what I mean?
>> Pick drugs over your kids. Nah, I don't
I don't believe that, bro.
>> Definitely not, lads. Definitely not.
What is it with you people and my
children anyways? Is it a bit weird either way?
Either way, you all know why my kids got
talk of me. You know why. And we don't
have to bring that situation up with you
little clowns. What you already know.
>> I don't talk about your I don't talk
about your kids.
>> No, no, no. Leave them to. If they do,
they're more welcome to I won't be
giving them I won't be reacting back to
these little clown comments what they
write. Either way, either way, they just
sad little lonely peace without kids.
>> I wonder why I wonder why that red star
goes for me all the time and never you.
You're lucky, man. You're actually lucky, Monty.
>> Yeah, red star goes for you cuz you're irrelevant.
>> Well, that doesn't make any sense, but okay.
>> For you because you're relevant towards
women. It's what you do towards women.
>> Yeah, but bro, this guy doesn't even
have a woman.
Even if he doesn't have a woman or not,
he's doing a good job on you in it.
>> No, he's just wasting his life on me. Really?
>> That's all he's doing.
>> Yeah, of course, bro. You stalking a man
all day every day for four years. You're
wasting your life, not mine.
>> PJ PJ Bit PJ, but but you obviously love
the attention of these little clowns in
this community either way for
>> actually. Oh, well, actually,
I think he's very weird, but Okay.
>> No, no, no, no. But you actually like it
either way. Well, you don't have him
blocked. That's a bit weird on your
>> I do have him blocked. I do have him
>> Yeah, but still still knowing that that
you're going to go up player on his
channel. Do you still talk about the
same [ __ ] Why he's going to record you
and put you up on?
>> But do you not think it's weird like sat
there recording men all day? Do you not
find that bit weird?
>> They haven't got a live. That's why they
do it. Riff no live. Um Bits, no live.
him no life. How How do you think that
they can sit there 24 hours watching
everybody and recording everybody? No life. >> Yeah.
>> You You got a life in it, Monty?
>> Yeah, I've got life. I've got a lovely
Mes who loves me. You know, I've got my
two I've got my two daughters who I go
and see every two months.
If anyone is a narcissist on here, it's funny.
>> The biggest narcissist in this community
is you people sat behind that keyboard.
You are the biggest narcissist. Bro,
stop talking about yourselves. Either way, >> I
do you know um you know chat DBT?
>> No, but go on.
Well, it's it's a good thing you should
use chat. I've been using it a lot. Chat DBT.
>> What is it?
>> It's just a site basically where you ask
questions and um they answer it accurately.
>> Have you asked it? Will you ever get
laid one day, PJ?
>> I've already been laid more times than
you've had hot dinners. >> Sorry, >> PJ.
I've been laid more times than you've
had hot. Listen, Monty, you've only been
with two women ever.
>> I've never been with two women. I
haven't been with Oh, you've been with
no women then.
>> Oh, no. No. Yeah. Yeah, man. I'm sort of
burying me. PJ Mon, listen. You've only
had Natalie and Kaye. That's literally
all you've ever had.
>> No, I've had more meeting my girlfriends
than Natalie and Kaye.
>> No, listen. How long you How long you
No, no, no. How long was you with Kaye?
I was with K for 10 years.
>> Yeah, they there you go then.
>> Yeah, that me being with her for 10
years don't mean that I haven't had no relationship.
>> You lost You lost your virginity to Kaye.
>> Did I? [ __ ]
>> You lost your virginity. Don't lie,
Monty. Don't lie.
>> My two children. No, I I did not lose my virginity to
>> Yes, you [ __ ] did.
>> Thank you s bringing her up. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Oh, well, we will listen. Monty.
Monty. Monty, you was a You was a virgin on PlayStation.
>> Okay, PG. I was a virgin on PlayStation.
All right. Okay. Okay.
>> I used to talk to you all day every day. You was
>> Yeah, because I come out only why I was
on PlayStation, PJ, cuz I come out of a a relationship
where I ended up going to a house
wanting to tie a lad up and stab him
with a gun. That was on that piece of paper.
>> My record. I went to the house. I wanted
decided that up cuz you were cheating on
me. That's when I decided to [ __ ] all
women up and I got with [ __ ] wheelie.
Now I'm with Natalie.
>> You watch a lot of weird stuff though,
Monty. Come on, man.
>> What do you mean weird stuff?
>> Like that hammer with that hammer with a
guy on the bike. You shouldn't be
watching stuff like that. You're sick, man.
>> Yeah. I watch. Do you want to see what I actually watch?
>> No. But why did you watch that?
>> Here. Come here, PJ. Watch this. Yeah.
>> Why did you watch Three Guys One Hammer though?
>> Because it's because think it's good to watch.
>> Dusty, did you ever watch it? Three
Guys, One Hammer.
>> Yeah, Dusty's watching it.
Well, your connection's [ __ ]
Yeah, PJ. PJ, it's not [ __ ] I'm
putting a link in the background for
you. Have you got Instagram?
>> Yeah, but you're going to have to guess my name.
>> I don't need a guess.
>> Yeah, go on.
Are you ready for the link, PJ? Yeah. >> Mhm.
>> Oh, I don't think that will let me put
that up. Well, it won't let me, but I'll
put it in chat then. Yeah. Are you ready
for this? Yeah, you can call me sick
then after you watch the send. Yeah.
>> What is it?
>> No, I'm scared it's child. [ __ ] that.
>> That's what PG I'm not a [ __ ] nons prick.
>> No, but I'm just saying is it I don't
like clicking random links and it
>> Yeah. No, no, this ain't this ain't I
[ __ ] This is P. I won't send you
anything for [ __ ] sake, man.
>> Okay. What? Okay. What is it? >> Just click it.
>> Okay. One second.
>> [ __ ] funny [ __ ] One sec.
Right. I'm watching it. Yeah.
Right. What is it? It's just someone aiming something. >> Yeah.
>> Okay. I'm watching it.
>> Yeah. Got shot. >> Okay.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. I send you some better
ones then. Yeah.
>> Uh, okay.
I'm going to send greasy three guys, one hammer.
Do you know what? I might I might put on
my live stream
and just put the camera on for Greasy to watch.
Is that okay with you, Grezy?
No, that's not okay with me, boss.
Well, you will be watching it because I
I'll just stream it. I'll just stream.
Come on, Grezy. Watch it.
I'll put it on. Greasy.
My mom's got another phone. I'll just
put it on it.
Dusty can watch it as well. They just
knock some random guy off the bike, bro.
It's sick. It's actually proper sick.
I'm sorry. There's a lot of us out
there. What sets? Yeah.
>> Is this the toxic Is this the toxic sector, Grezy?
Is Is this the toxic sector?
He was a He was a He He just survived cancer, bro.
He was He was an old man.
I can see the westernity in their eyes.
You can see the westernity in their eyes. Hello, Ken.
>> Who's that link?
>> All right, Ken.
>> What? Did you watch that one just shoot
yourself in the face? Did you?
>> Yeah, that's not that bad.
>> No, you see the ones where they get
blown up where the where the bulking
heads get blown?
>> You sent me You just sent me the same link.
>> Did I one sec? >> Yeah. You [ __ ]
I'm going to put the three guys. One
hammer on. What do you think?
And you're going to watch it, Grezy. And
you're going to like it.
And you're going to like it, Grezy.
This is the toxic sector.
Grievy. The toxic sector. So, what is
all the other sectors normal? Grezy
or they just normal
>> EP do this one.
That's nothing though, Monty.
>> What shin? It's nothing.
>> I'm watching it.
>> No, that hammer thing's worse.
>> Yeah, the what? With the hammer. The man
get his ass blew off and his head blew off. >> Yeah,
>> that Yeah, the worse than get getting
your head blown up.
You you don't even remember that thing, do you?
>> Yeah, of course. A man was driving his
pedal bike. Lads dragged him off his
bike, dragged him through the woods,
started stabbing him up and in the woods.
>> Yeah. You think it was funny, is it?
>> Put it on then, PJ.
>> I've watched it.
>> Put it on now.
>> What? The hammer on?
>> Yeah. Let everybody watch it. Okay,
>> I'll put it on for Natalie as well. No,
no, not watch.
>> Can you Can you Can you Can you put it on?
>> No, I'm not going on.
>> Go on. Go on.
>> I know. I'm not going on.
>> Come on, Greavves. Come on, Monty. I'll
give you a Scooby snack.
>> Yeah, I'm not going on score, my lad.
>> I'll go. Go on, man. I'll give you I'll
give you a Scooby snack.
>> Yeah, I'm not going on no B score
[ __ ] [ __ ] Are you [ __ ] No, I'm
all right watching.
>> I'm all about watching my war stuff,
watching people get blown up.
>> I'm not going on.
>> You can try,
>> Laney. I have to warn Laney to look away.
And you know what? They're going to look
as well because there there's no way
they can't look.
>> Just put it on.
>> One second. Let me get the other phone, man.
>> Watch this. He watching it now.
into the woods.
>> I don't have another phone, man. One
second. Let me charge it up.
>> Let me see.
>> [ __ ] stick it on.
>> Oh, here's a phone. I'm not using my
mom's a good phone for that. I'm going
to have to use an old one.
>> You're No, you can't close your eyes.
You're going to have to watch it and
you're going to like it.
>> One second. Let the phone charge up a bit.
Yeah, I'm not using my I could use my
mom's phone to do it, but I'm not I want
to use the old one, not the new one in it.
Do you want to Oh, do you want to see it?
>> Yeah. Stick it on. Put it on.
>> Yeah. I wouldn't let this one charge in it.
Can't you just put it on?
>> I can't. I've only got one phone.
>> No, seriously.
Seriously, I've only got one phone. I
can't put it on. >> Really?
>> You're a [ __ ] One sec.
Why do you want the lights off? For [ __ ] sake.
>> Yes. Yeah. Turn the lights off and all
that. Make it dark watching it.
>> You two make me laugh. One minute
arguing then you want babies together.
[ __ ] off, can't
>> Why do you think I'm PJ? Small dicks,
mate. I'm a [ __ ]
>> You gotick.
>> So, what PJ? Don't tell these that I've
got a small dick. Please, man.
>> No, I can't. The other phone's not
charging. I'm not using my mama's new
phone to do it.
>> Well, just use your mom's new phone. She won't
go and use it.
>> No, but she's going to I'll wait. She
has to go sleep. I'll wait till she's
sleeping. I wait till she's sleeping on it.
>> No, just say, "Mom, can I use your phone
for 1 minute for a video and you can
have it back?"
>> No, but it's sick. It's sicky. It's
actually sick, isn't it?
>> Yeah. But what? So, what you're saying
is it's going to be the same website.
You can watch Spider-Man on Greezy.
>> Watch Spiderman on it. Yeah. [ __ ]
>> On YouTube, you can. On YouTube, you
>> Yeah. On YouTube, you can. Yeah, but not
not on best score.
Yeah, but it's the same website like this YouTube.
>> How did you find How did you find out
about Besar anywhere?
>> Cuz I I searched the three guys one hammer.
>> You searched up three guys, one hammer.
>> Yeah, I found it
>> on Besar. >> Yeah.
>> You like that site, is it? You love it,
is it? Everyone knows.
>> Yeah. No, no, I do love Bes. It is
actually good. You're sick. You're actually sick.
>> You're sick, isn't it?
>> No. Why? Why am I sick? What? So you you
couldn't do any of that to anybody? Yeah.
>> No. Not smash someone's face with a hammer, bro.
>> Why not?
>> It's sick, isn't it?
>> No. Not that.
>> So you could?
>> Of course I could. PJ, my mate. I've
know someone I know someone who's done it already.
>> Yeah, you told me. But it's sick. It is
sick, isn't it?
>> It is, but it is it depends if you need
to or don't need to.
>> Yeah, but they didn't need to. That was
That was a random person, is it?
>> Yeah, they did it. Let Right. Okay, let
let them out. They did it for fame. Yeah.
>> Yeah, they're sick of it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. That's only the reason why
they did it. They didn't do it for no
excuse but fame. When they got sent down
that the car said, "Why did you do it?"
Because they only wanted fame.
That's only what them wanted. They
didn't want nothing more. They didn't
want to kill anybody. They just wanted the fame.
>> What do you mean they didn't want to
kill anyone? Of course, bro. They
smashed the guy's [ __ ] head.
>> Yes. Yes. Yes. For fame.
For fame. To be known. To be known.
>> Yeah. But do you do you remember the
whole video? The whole of it?
>> I watched it happen years and years and years ago.
I didn't even know score was still
working to be honest with you.
>> Okay, so how how did he get knocked out
to begin with? >> What?
>> How did he get knocked out to begin with?
>> It was ages ago, PJ.
>> No, but what I'm saying is they hit him
off the bike here and then they dragged him.
>> Yeah, that's only what I can't remember.
Like I said, it was years ago. Only what
I can remember is him getting dragged
into the woods and getting battered.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it was sick. Yeah, it was
sick, buddy. It was sick.
>> So, we don't So, yeah.
>> Has anyone else watched it? Has anyone
else watched that video?
>> A lot of people are a lot of people.
Okay, PJ, here's another video for you.
Yeah. One man one GR. Why don't you watch that?
>> No, I'm not watching any more [ __ ]
Why not? Why? Why? Why don't you want to
watch one man one?
>> Cuz No. [ __ ] that, bro.
>> Why not? You watch that?
>> No. [ __ ] that, bro.
>> So, what makes you search for one guy,
one hammer? I mean,
>> yeah. Someone said one man, one jaw is
mental. Yeah. Some Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, why don't you watch that then,
P? Yeah. Go on. right here.
>> In fact, even better. Even better. Have
you got a laptop player or something?
>> I'll watch it. I'll watch it. I'll watch
it. I'll watch it if you put the thing
on. If you put uh >> AJ,
so you're getting worse than me even
though I can watch it all. I sit here
now watching people get blown up.
>> I agree. Monty said all he can remember
is the man getting drugged into the
woods and getting battered. That's
funny, isn't it? Is it funny, Monty?
>> EGL were young when he when it happened.
>> Yeah, he got battered in it.
>> He got batted and he started stabbing
him with the screwdriver and whacking
him over the head with the hammer.
>> Yeah, that's what Yeah, that's what
happened. Yeah, it's not
>> stabbing him in his belly and all that.
Look, with the screwdriver. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, yeah. I've seen it. PJ, I know what it is.
They whacked him off his bike. They
knocked him off it with the hammer.
Whacked him off the bike.
>> But how? Yeah, but you know when they
whacked him off the hammer once yet. He
wasn't dead. He was just unconscious, isn't it?
>> Yeah, he was unc No, he weren't even
unconscious. He was still He's still
alive. He's still awake going through it.
>> Yeah, but he couldn't. Why? So, why
didn't he run away then? Because he he
he's just being waxed over here with a
[ __ ] hammer. For [ __ ] sake, you're
not going to be able to run.
>> Yeah, but of course you said he's still
alive. So like if you were still alive,
>> he's still alive. But he's dazed, didn't
he? He's going to be dazed out of his
head. The guy's not going to remember [ __ ] up,
>> you know.
>> So So what if they So what if they just
left him there? He would have just he
would have just got up eventually in it.
He would have got up or he would have
died or [ __ ] um blood clots to the
brain or something hemorrhage to the brain.
>> Yeah, they just give him one whack off
that off the bike in it. It was sick, isn't it?
>> Yeah. So either way, he would have died
anyway because if the hammer would have
[ __ ] put clocks in his brain anyways,
he would have his skull. He would have had
gold and all that. Look.
>> Yeah. What? Wait until you see the
video, Grezy. It's even more sick.
I can't believe you like this stuff,
Monty. You're mad.
I'm into it, man. I'm [ __ ]
Yeah, I've tried doing it myself to someone. So,
yo, we we should do that to Timmy Aldridge.
>> I'm not doing nothing to nobody, PJ.
That's why I said you these is a big big
mistake to find out where these live. Big mistake.
>> No, you're sick, man.
>> Not being sick. It's being [ __ ] what?
>> No. Seriously. >> Seriously.
What do you think happened to the last guy,
man? I nothing happened to him because
he got looking at the police come and I got arrested.
>> Monty, you'll do nothing. You monk.
>> Yeah, I know. Like I just said, I'm I'm
not going to do nothing.
>> You said I was going to do stuff.
Did I say I was going to do anything? PJ,
>> does money mike um bother you still or not?
>> No. PJ, do you know what? These clowns
can call me out. They can they can say
say come on meet me now. They can I'm
not going to meet anybody.
>> Yeah, I'm not I'm not even at this point.
>> I'm not going to even leave my front
door to entertain them. They can I let
them up on my panel. I call them to [ __ ]
my panel and if they come and tell me
he'll come meet cuz even if you meet
them cuz even if you meet them it goes
in circles isn't it?
>> Either way. Even if it doesn't go in
circles either way. I'm not meeting
nobody else out of this. You know you
know. Hey, but you know you and Timmy.
Yeah. Hey, Monty. Monty, but listen, you
know you and Timmy, you know, you've
basically been having the same argument
for six years, isn't it?
>> I'm going to say this once. Yeah. Once
only. Yeah. What you want to do? Yeah.
>> What you want to do? Yeah. Is just
shouting me out. Yeah. And just [ __ ]
bang him and then just [ __ ] up back home because
>> No, no. Listen. Why the [ __ ] have you
let him off? come to your front door and
let him know you can because he he
threat he threatened your mom. You know
what I mean? He come to your door
kicking off like your mom and all that
lot on your street
and the and the neighbor told him
>> to [ __ ] off the neighbor said the
neighbor said the neighbor said [ __ ] off you nuns.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But it's just the
responsibility of that that's your mom
who he who he chat his [ __ ] to. Do you
know what I mean? My mom was My mom
wasn't even scared.
>> Yeah, I know. She weren't scared. It's
your responsibility, in it.
>> You know what I'm saying?
>> We chatted to your mom. Know me chatted
to my mom like that and she told me to
leave it. I won't believe it. What the [ __ ]
>> I would go and kicking his head in
it to my mom, not behind my mom's face or
>> I went back I went back for him and he was gone.
>> Yeah. Well, go to Birmingham and shout
him out. I went back for him. He was
gone. And then people told me to go to
this Weather Spoons pub. I went to this
Weather Spoons pub. He wasn't there.
>> Yeah, he just couldn't go to Birmingham
and shout him out.
>> So, so ask yourself the question, Monty.
Where was he?
>> Obviously, he [ __ ] off.
>> You shouldn't have hid upstairs. I
wasn't upstairs. I wasn't even in the
house, lad. And I've already proved I
wasn't in the house.
>> But anyways, like, yeah, he No, what he
done, Monty, you was hiding in the
field. That's what he was doing. me.
You fed me some [ __ ] man.
>> Come on, PJ. What?
>> Um, I was saying that he probably ran
into a field, bro.
>> Yeah. No, what you want to do? Yeah, I'm
not involved in this. Yeah, but if you
need me to come with you, just in case
he bring little money or anything. Yeah,
>> bro. What's your What's Money M going to
do, bro? Come on.
>> Obviously nothing. But still, I reckon
that you should go to Birmingham and
slap Timothy for what he done to your
mom. Now, if that were me, I would have
done it. I would have done it hands down
cuz it's not on YouTube. That's real life.
>> Yeah, but you should have helped.
>> Why the [ __ ] am I going to help PJ
one? One, the man's a weasel. Two, I've
already slapped him twice.
I don't have to prove myself.
>> Do you not think it's pathetic? Listen,
do you not think it's pathetic how you
two have been having the same argument
for 6 years?
>> This community's been having the same
argument for [ __ ] 12 years.
>> 15 years. 15, I think. 15 years.
>> 15 years. I've only been in this
community six years. And these have been
here for Wow. It just shows me you need
to actually get off YouTube. These clowns.
>> 15 years, buddy. 15 years.
>> These do need to get off YouTube. Six 15
years and still sat on YouTube doing the
same. They said use [ __ ] sweaters. >> What?
>> That's just weird, isn't it?
>> No, it is. It is. But Scia, you need to
get your ass out and sorting me out.
>> He's a [ __ ] man. He's a [ __ ]
>> It doesn't matter if he's a [ __ ] or
not. Responsibility of him snagging your
mom off, going to your mom and starting
on your mom on the doorsteping away.
Does it matter if your mom wasn't scared
of him or not?
>> But doesn't he have anxiety to me?
>> Yeah, cuz he's got anxiety when it comes
to certain people. I'm not being funny.
>> But how? Yeah. But how did he come to
London if he's got anxiety then?
>> He hasn't got anxiety because it's you.
He thinks you're some little soft ass
who who gets battered and runs off from
everybody. That's what he thinks.
>> You know I beat you know I beat you know
I beat Timmy the first time isn't it?
Like when he come?
>> Yeah. It don't really matter. The man's
the man thinks. So
>> he tried he tried kicking me like 10
times where he missed every time.
>> Yeah. Yeah. What? What? He swings his
leg around, don't he? And tries kicking.
>> He tried. He tried. He's a [ __ ]
>> No, I can't keep [ __ ] He missed me
every kick. Every I would laugh.
>> I would laugh him even when money.
>> You know when you met You know when you
met him last time? Yeah.
Yeah. Was you Was you taller than him this time?
>> Taller than him. I'm the same size as
him with more or less.
>> Yeah. He said, "Hey, do you remember
what he said, Monty?" He says, "No, but
to be honest, Monty, I'm not even trying
to [ __ ] sty, bro." But you did look a
bit scared. I'm not going to lie.
>> You scared, Jimmy.
>> No, you No, you No, you looked a bit scared.
>> I didn't look scared
>> because you punched him in it. Yeah. And
then he and and Mike was he said if Mike
didn't hold um hold him he would have
knocked you out.
>> Money M didn't hold anyone.
Money M didn't hold me. He didn't even
hold Timmy. I was laughing at Timmy's
kicks. I want what Money M was saying,
"Oh, come on. It's going. I'll fight
you." But he's laughing at Money Mike as well.
>> Yeah. You Where did you punch him in his face?
>> Yeah, I tapped him. I only tapped him.
He says I'm going to knock him out.
That's what he said, isn't it?
>> Yeah, he only tapped him.
>> Why? Why did you only tap him?
>> Cuz he's a [ __ ] in it. Look, the
biggest [ __ ] of what I am calls me
the [ __ ] but he's the biggest [ __ ]
>> He said, he said he said turn the camera
off, isn't it?
>> Turn the camera off. Yeah.
>> And then you turn it off, in it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And then what
happened after that? You just made up.
>> No, we went for a drink and that money
were getting cocky. So I told him I keep
getting cocky and I'm just going to jump
over the table and burn him in his face.
>> Yeah. Yeah. We're bad every night. All
night they were both Mike was actually
just [ __ ] threatening everybody out on
the street. He nearly got battered and that
from guys come over to me and ask me,
"Oh, do you need help with him? Do you
need help with him?" Meaning, do you
want me do you want out kicking his head
in him because he thought I was having
trouble? Said, "Nah, no, no. I'm good. I'm good."
You reckon you would have took both of
them at the same time? Yeah.
>> Yeah. Both. Easy.
>> He's short in it, Money, M. He's shorting it.
>> Yeah. Both of Yeah.
>> He's a He's a Is that Is that true about
Mike? like vaping someone. Money, did
you hear about that?
>> Well, well, Money Mike was telling me
when I was out that night that he's
getting in trouble by the police and
that um something to do with like fraud
fraud or something like that, but then
he mentioned something to do with a
woman included as well,
>> but he didn't mention anything to do
with rape or anything like that.
Yeah, that's Yeah, people's been been
talking about that, bro. People's been
talking about it.
>> Good. I hope he get signed down and gets
bummed in person five times over.
>> Yeah, he used to always tell me he's
done fraud and that. >> Yeah,
>> Monty, it's not funny fraud. You go to
prison for that. You know that.
>> No, no, I know. I know you can.
what they were doing fraud and he did
mention something about a woman.
>> Yeah. Apparently he raped like he raped
like he sexually like like
>> if I knew that that time and then money
might have been standing I would have
dropped him off the balcony while we was on. >> Yeah.
>> I would if I knew that then he would
have been over the balcony
talking to like a bus stop and that did
he say what fraud he done? What
>> did he say? What kind of fraud he done?
>> No, no, just that um he he done some
kind of fer or something like that.
>> But he he weren't saying what he done or
anything like that. He just mentioned
that he done he's getting cuz I were
talking about that might get be getting sent down before caught.
>> Yeah. and that because she actually got
caught in Birmingham. My first time in
court when when everyone thought it was
my sentencing, but it wasn't my sentencing.
>> Why did you Why did you rape a woman?
Why did you rape a woman? L1.
>> But why is How can Money Mike rape a
Ramen man? He's got a He's got a maggot.
>> He's got a little dick. He's got a He's
got a same size dick as Money Lord. Yeah.
Lord J the same size as Money Mike small.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I don't know why he done
that though. That is weird.
Yeah. Timmy said it as well, you know.
Hey, I'm not even telling I'm not even
lying. But if I look like money or
Timmy, I'd kill myself. I'd kill if I
was them. I'd kill myself, bro. I can't even lie. >> What?
>> I said if I look like Money Mike or
Timmy, I'd kill myself. Would
you dream on here?
>> If I look like him.
>> Yeah. Like or say you was Timmy. I'd
kill myself, bro. 100%.
>> 100%. 100%. Both of them. I kill myself.
I wouldn't want to look like any of them.
>> No. [ __ ] that. [ __ ] that.
>> To be honest with you, I wouldn't even
want to look like you to be honest with
you, man. You have difficulty getting laid, too.
>> I'm I'm better looking than you.
>> So why why can't I get women?
>> Money. What women have you had? Natalie,
G and Kaye. What? What? Come on, bro.
What women have you had?
>> Come on. Okay then. Okay then. So,
what's wrong with Natalie then? KJ,
>> there's no there's nothing wrong with that.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no. What's wrong
with Natalie, PJ?
>> Well, she's not my type.
>> Come on, man. She was your type a couple
of months back.
>> A couple of A couple of years back.
>> Couple of year back. She were your type
22 and I didn't meet her.
Yeah, but Okay, let me ask you. Okay,
let me ask you this. Has any of the
women I've been with been your fight?
The ones I put up that that I've met up with.
>> No, they've been too skinny for me.
>> But how many have you seen?
>> None. I've never seen you with none.
>> You have?
>> I've never seen you with a woman.
>> Oh, come on.
>> Have you ever seen PJ with a woman? That
>> Yes, she has.
So, you've never seen me with a woman yet?
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Maybe one woman.
Yeah. That That was
>> nah. I knew he was going to say that as
well. I knew he was going to say. Okay.
Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Whatever.
>> Well, I do not remember. Yeah.
>> That was years ago, bro. And you like
you like yourself.
You fancy dizzy.
>> Hey, I'm going to have to go in a minute. Yeah.
>> Okay. I was saying that you fancy dizzy. >> What?
>> I said that you fancy.
>> Who's it? Isabelle.
I don't even know. Who is it? object.
>> Okay. Yeah. >> What?
>> Did you ever see that American that I met?
>> Yeah. You didn't want you either.
>> No. The one I banned.
>> Want you battered her?
>> No, I banned her.
>> What do you mean you banned her?
>> I banned her, bro.
>> Where did you ban her from?
Oh, [ __ ] sake. [ __ ] off, man. I banged her.
>> Oh, what? Where? Where? Where? How did
you ban her from? What? What? What?
What? What shop?
>> I [ __ ] her.
>> What do you mean you [ __ ] her? You
[ __ ] her off.
>> No, I [ __ ] her in a mini.
>> What? She's got a mini has
>> What kind of mini has she got?
A smelly one.
>> A smelly mini. Does the sun move come
off it? And that? >> No.
>> No. No. There's some move. So
>> you you said you said Natalie G has
black flaps. So you can't say anything.
>> Yeah. Natalie has got black flaps.
>> So you can't say it. Yeah. So how you
you can't take the piercing it?
>> Well, what's up with that? You know, you
know, he doesn't even have that. But
yeah, go on.
>> He was the one saying it. Yeah, she
asked. But go on.
>> Nothing. I'm just saying that you That's
what you said. >> Mhm.
>> Well, what's up with black flaps?
>> This is weird, isn't it?
>> What's weird?
>> You know what's really weird? >> What?
>> That every time you're kissing that G,
your tasty money stick.
That's funny to me. But sorry, you had
to, man. I had to.
>> No, no, no. He's right. He's right. She
never She's never sucked money in my cough. Small.
Every time she tried to eat, she was
sucking on a pube.
>> How do you know that?
>> You told me.
>> No, seriously.
>> Yeah. Seriously, she told me every time
she tries to clean him off, she ends up
on a p.
>> Do you remember that? Hey, no. Do you
know what made me laugh, Monty? Yeah. Do
you remember that time you were staying
at that place in Birmingham and there
was a guy that kept coming on the door?
The guy that kept knocking on the door.
>> No guy kept on coming on the door. A guy
come on the door open once.
>> That's funny though. It
>> is funny.
>> It was the mate downstairs. But why did
he come back anyways? He was he living
there. We told him to do it.
>> Oh jeez, mate. told him to do it.
>> That's weird though, Monty. Don't you think?
>> No, it's not weird.
>> It's a bit weirder.
>> Why? Natalie wasn't living there when he come round.
>> Did you just ignore it?
>> No, I opened the door told him to [ __ ] off.
>> No, seriously.
>> Yeah, seriously. What the [ __ ]
You're a funny [ __ ] You are.
>> You're not. No, not Natalie's not here.
>> Yes, she is.
>> No, I do not know. I'm on the phone to her.
>> Are you still there, Grezy? No, Ginsby's gone. >> Where?
>> Back to Grimby.
>> How do you know?
>> That's enough Tik Tok for today.
>> Have you seen that meme, Monty? >> What?
>> They were laughing at you, mocking you.
All right. Ser, do you know what we need
to do on this community? Everyone just
needs to make up.
>> Hey, come too far for that with these
little clouds, man. These clouds belong
in the circus, believe it or not. Best
job for them. >> Really? >> Yeah.
These do well in the circus. They all
[ __ ] clowns, lad. >> Really?
One. They all repeat the same jokes.
just say, "Yeah, cuz I got nothing."
They obviously because I got no new
content. So what?
>> What's your job anyways, PJ?
>> Um, I deliver food.
>> You thought, man, you're just a wanker,
mate. That's your That's your job.
>> Nah. What's your job? >> [ __ ] >> Really?
>> Really? [ __ ] Yeah.
I've never had a [ __ ] What does it feel like?
>> Oh, it makes your toes tingle.
It makes you go.
It makes it makes you go cockeyed.
It makes you laugh.
>> I've never had a [ __ ]
>> Have you not? So cute for lad. sort from
>> I'm a I'm a virgin.
>> What do you mean you're a virgin?
>> I'm a virgin.
>> What's it like being a virgin, PJ? I've
never been one before.
>> It sucks.
>> It does, don't it? I'm so a virgin, too. >> Really?
>> We sing that song together like a virgin. Yeah. >> Yeah.
What what network are you within?
>> Um I'm with three.
>> Oh, you're free. We're free. Are you? >> Mhm.
>> I can't believe you've cried. I can't
believe though you've cried over women.
>> Wait. Wait. So you're only on free is because
you're sick of being a third, so you
just rather just go free now? Yeah. >> Nice.
>> I can't believe you cried over women.
>> I cry over women all the time, PJ. You
know what I mean? It's just it's called
love. I don't think you've been in love.
>> No, I've never been in love. >> Never.
>> I think you're a s.
>> I am a s. I simply most of the times >> really
>> most of the times. Yeah.
>> Have you simp before PG? >> No.
>> Well, you never know how it feels then. Would you?
>> No, I don't s that.
>> I don't see pee only when it's over a
gorgeous woman like Natal.
really a good one. A good one at that.
He's amazing. Pedia, you know what, man?
I couldn't ask for a better woman. I
really couldn't. You know what? Jesus
Christ give me a [ __ ] angel.
He [ __ ] did.
>> Yeah. Not that angel who fell from the
heavens and hell.
You know them three angels who is it the
three angels what got kicked out of heaven?
the pre dark. This person said that
you're sad and pathetic.
>> Well, he must be more sadder, more
pathetic and watching in it. >> Really?
>> Do you remember when you was living in
the tent? That was [ __ ] weird, isn't it, bro?
>> That was so weird, isn't it?
>> Yeah, it was weird.
He was he was living in a [ __ ] tent.
That's [ __ ] bro.
>> Yeah, PG. You You won't even be able to
manage living in a tent.
>> Of course I would.
>> Would you
>> How was you How was you charging your phone?
>> I was charging my phone.
>> He special needed this guy in there.
>> I had all the equipment, PJ, to do that.
So, was that So, when you was living in
the tent, was that over YouTube? Nah,
>> partially. Partly not.
>> [ __ ] off. No, it weren't over YouTube on
here. Come on.
>> Partly partially not.
>> How? How? How? There's no way. That
sounds bad, doesn't it? It won't YouTube
who got me for homeless who put me in
town. It won't let me done that. They
weren't even the course of that. Yeah,
I brought I brought you on here over CO
if I remember. Yeah, it was co >> what?
>> I brought you on here on in CO, isn't it?
>> Through COVID lockdown. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Because you were getting bullied. P.
Yeah, you thought I completed
>> this community. This community was good
in lockdown because there was nothing to
do in it.
>> Monty, do you think Yeah. there's a
weirder community than this on YouTube
or do you think this is the weirdest?
No, no, no. Natalie never use wet wipes.
Sher co is called a shower.
We all We both had showers.
This is the thing, peeps. You're stupid,
aren't we? I I've got my own outdoor
shower, peeps. I'll show you all my
equipment when I get it home. I've got a
outdoor shower, meaning I can have a
shower outdoors, anywhere where I want.
Um, I've got um electrical charging power ports
so I can put my plugs in and play my
PlayStation and watch TV outside in the
tent. I can even charge my phone so I
power in the tent.
I've got all sorts [ __ ] Come on, peace, man.
I've even got [ __ ] central heating
now in my tents.
Monty, everybody knows that you're a crazy [ __ ]
>> I'm not crazy.
>> You're a crazy [ __ ] in it.
>> You're a bit crazy in it.
>> No. No. I didn't I didn't I didn't have
all that equipment in my last 10. No, I
didn't. only what I had in my last 10
is my son panel light. Um, and that was
charging up my phone and that that's
only what I had there is my son panel um
light bulb light bulbs
with my so with my torch where I used to
take diesel out and that was like solo
panel lighting and all that. So I had
that. I had son up and up in my yard back then.
>> No, I don't think Mont is a monk. I
think he he pretends to be stupid, but I
don't think he is stupid.
>> Yeah, Natalie's even saying exactly the
same thing as stupid. Yeah, even when he
might said it as well in person, you're
totally different. You're actually more
glued on and what? Yeah, Natalie's even
said that I'm not stupid, am I? No,
>> you know, you know, you know Timmy can't spell.
>> A lot of these in this community can't
spell. Like, come on, man. He s the piss
because you ain't got nothing else
better to do with their lives. They s
more bored than what we have for [ __ ]
sake. You know what I mean? This is why
they watch. This is what what they do
for us to bring them more play.
>> Have you noticed when you go live? Yeah.
They want it within like 20 seconds. 20
seconds. They're straight on it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. They're straight on it.
>> I noticed that to be fair. I did know. I
actually noticed that to be fair.
>> Because they're live is surrounding by
YouTube and other people on YouTube and
then they tell you why you on here. Why
you on here? Why you on here? Why Why
are these on here? Because
>> why can't they just go Why can't they
just go out for a drink or something? It
is because they can't socialize in the
real world. These people are not
socialized with all people. These people
cannot socialize with anybody. >> Yeah.
>> And one of the people who they can um
socialize with is people online. So they
come online and bully online. I'm not
being funny, but I was right about um
John West when I said that that John
West is some old
>> DJ. You come on live. One second, PJ.
You come on live within 20 minutes of
you waking up. No way. What are you
talking about, you [ __ ] When I woke
up today, I went out. I didn't even look
on YouTube. Okay.
>> Well, I'm not being funny. I'm not being
funny on all you be. So, you must be up
all night waiting to see you go live.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
That's what I'm saying.
So you must be all there looking at your
phones 24 hours just to see you going live. >> Yeah.
I want speedy awesome.
>> And there's another thing Monty is that
even when I come off of YouTube for like
two weeks, I won't go on YouTube for two
weeks. As soon as I come back, they're
there straight away.
>> Not even that. people who who who go
live and that and who has been live. Me
and Natalie, we don't even watch him nearly.
>> The diff the difference is one second.
The difference is you are broadcasting.
Yes. But you are on here watching me though.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You are on here writing at
me re read your name out for your name to
>> No, no, no, no. People watching are just
watching. Big difference. But is it
though? Because you're still typing.
>> You're still involved. You're still
involved in it.
Either way, even though you're writing,
but this is what what they're doing.
Yeah. They're writing [ __ ] Yeah. For
you to read. Yeah.
>> When you when you read their comment
out, they feel special that that you're
reading the comment out. So, they write
another comment for you to read that
comment and then there's the conversation.
Monty used to go
>> Monty used to go live 40 times a day.
No, I can't remember that.
No man, it weren't 40 times a day. It
was at least about 50 times a day, maybe
80 times a day.
>> So I want to understand if if all of
these people have got all this money in
this life, what are they doing on here every day?
>> AJ, my god, man. They they on benefits,
but they [ __ ] ashamed of saying it.
But and they tell people to get a job.
What what jobs they've got on YouTube 24/7?
>> They haven't got a job. PJ starts on
YouTube telling people to get a job
because they [ __ ] feel sorry that
they've never had a job in their lives.
So they obviously giving people IDs. Go
get a job. You don't want to be this
sad, lonely, fat, [ __ ] old man like I am
now that on YouTube crispering up. Yeah.
You're the best YouTuber on here.
>> Who is? >> Yeah.
>> Am I the best YouTuber?
>> You just are, man. Not the best
YouTuber. No. Do you think I'm one of
the best YouTubers? No.
No. Can I tell you why, PJ? Cuz it's pathetic.
It's pathetic. It's [ __ ] weird.
It is weird for going outside. These
>> people Well, these people in this
community are weird. Yeah.
>> Not just them.
>> Me and you included. >> Really?
>> Really? They're just as weird as us.
They have more they they sitting here
now saying, "Why are me and you live?
Why you live? Why you live?" Why the
[ __ ] are they watching for one 24/7 of
the live [ __ ] in greed? What's going on? Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Even if it's arguing or no arguing.
Yeah. Even you know they still involved
in it. They ain't got a life just as
same as you. Cuz the same as me. They
they still involved.
>> Yeah. But no but no but money I have got
a life. I go out and I do go out. I
don't sit in all day.
>> Well you a life. Yeah. Going out going
cold approaching is not alive. Like
that's a ration stalking women.
>> Okay. But the Okay. Well no no no. One
second. One second. But what do these
people do? Sit in all day.
>> These people sit in all day drinking a
bottle of [ __ ] beer, regretting their
lives, shaking, and going back on
alcohol because you got [ __ ]
I go out when I win on properties. Not
at all, lad. I rarely gamble. And this
is another thing, Monty. Right. This is
another thing. These people seem to
think they know how much money people
have and how much money people don't
have. It's really weird.
Monty, it's weird, isn't it?
You don't know how much money people have.
>> It doesn't matter. What? What? What?
This is what I mean about you little
[ __ ] in this community. Same as
yourself. Yeah. Why do you say about
money to use?
>> They bring it up. They're the ones that
>> What the [ __ ] money got to do with
anything in the world, man? This is
where it comes to with these [ __ ]
clowns. These all they think about money
every day because they ain't got [ __ ] money.
>> You know what I mean? This is why they
[ __ ] bring it up. Talk about this.
Talk about money. They got money.
>> You said PJ, you said you couldn't
afford to buy GTA 5 the other day. Uh,
have you heard of sarcasm and taking a
piss? That's another thing these people
don't seem to know when you're joking. Money.
>> You can pick 25. You can pick GTA 5 up
for 25 quid. these days. It's not even
much regard [ __ ] CX or something like that.
>> Uh I was taking a piss.
>> No, no, it doesn't matter if you're
taking a piss or if you weren't taking a piss on money
you need to sort theelves out.
>> They're [ __ ] They're retards. They
just they just give you brain damage in
it. I kind of give the cell brain damage
to be honest with you. PJ
or being Timmy's Timmy's another one
that calls people skin cuz he's skin.
He's another one.
>> No, these are these are basically
mongos. Bigger mongos on me and you cuz
they do they do repeat the PT but yeah
not being for this. Yeah, they're older
and us. A lot of these are older us. Yeah,
>> they are. They are
>> more uglier to be honest with you.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I know. Oh, no. You know
what I say, Monty? Monty, listen. No,
no. I say to these people, "Yeah, you
can say I'm ugly. You can say I'm this.
That's fine. But show yourself." They
can't do it. And then they say, "Monty,
oh, because we don't show our faces
because we'll get doxed." But no, it's
[ __ ] because how many people has
faced been out there and how many people
have been docked, Monty? Not a lot.
>> Be funny. No, not these people I've
learned either way. These people look at
um who's he called now? John West. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Look at John West. Yeah. He was arguing
with everyone, calling everybody to pug. Yeah.
>> As soon as his face got put out there
that it's some old man who wears
glasses, fat as [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> He ran off. He ran off.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? Pat Mustard look
like a [ __ ] plastic scene men.
>> You know what I mean? That's what I
mean. He ran off. He's hiding in
somewhere in the background.
>> Why Monty? Do you do you go do you go
piss um every morning when you wake up?
You're doing it.
>> You're doing it, Monty.
>> No, I have a wank when I wake up. PJ,
>> you ever have to piss off? Do you have a wank? Yeah,
>> I'm always joking. I don't really wank.
I don't need to perfect good woman here.
>> No, but do you pee every time like you
you wake up? Every time you wake up, is
it? I think everybody goes toilet when
they wake up or pee. Yeah.
>> I've had to go pee before before getting
a [ __ ] buddy. I was about to get a
[ __ ] and I had to pee in it before.
Have you ever had that?
>> Yeah, but I just carry on just suck my
dick knowing I need a piss.
>> No. [ __ ] that. [ __ ] that.
>> It goes away. It goes away. It blocks
it. You can't piss. It blocks it. That's
what it mean. You don't need a piss. It blocks it.
>> Come on.
>> No, bro. seriously.
>> AJ, you're the man. Yeah. When you're
you're shagging a woman. Yeah. Your dick
goes soft soon as you come. >> Yeah.
>> No, that's you.
>> Is that me? >> No.
>> Not me. 100% not.
>> You used to fight over women on PlayStation.
>> I still do. I wake up sweating crying over [ __ ]
um she only long legs sex misses.
That was a job by the way.
Well, we showed it on leg from him for a
couple of days with you PJ.
>> I don't know. He's your mate.
>> PJ, he's your mate. You and him always argue together.
No, I know him.
>> Yeah. Do you know what PJ to actually
piss you up? He actually might come back
to me showing online.
>> Well, he I met him I met him through you. So,
>> did you [ __ ] meet him through me? You
met him through the community.
>> You used to No, but to be honest though,
on a real talk, yeah, you and him was
mates at the start and you know you was.
Don't even lie, Marty.
>> On a real talk, me real talk. I swear
down dead now. I'm not even going to say
my two girls. Yeah. Because there's a
certain people who reaches them up
reaches on limit every [ __ ] day. But
I'm going to swear no dead on my
brother's dead body. Yeah. Yeah. That
I've never been mates with Johnny legs.
Yeah. I'll swear my dead brother's gra.
I've never been mates with.
>> Do you remember? Do you remember? Do you
remember the Do you remember the first
chat you met him in? Like the first like
the actual first first cuz I
>> I think it was Dean I think Dean it was
Dean who introduced me to Sean.
>> Yeah that Dean man he never ever met him
you know Dean and they used to talk all
the time and that just shows you it
>> Dean who used to choose us to show but I
used to get piss out of him because of
his health his pictures and that and you
could hear his at him all the time in
the background and that. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Back in the day and night. Yeah.
I've never been m never ever ever ever
ever be made with him. I can swear down
on my two girls now. And I can swear
down I'm dead on my mom's life. I can
swear down my dead brother's grave and
another dead brother's grave and my best mate's grave.
Do you remember that uh gay guy? What's
it not? Took the other one. Oh, I forget
the name, bro.
>> The one
used to Anna and used to say, "Ha, it's
okay if you get changed in front of me. I'm gay." >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Annoying, is it?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> You fancy down. You
do that. [ __ ] I don't like her, bro.
That's a used to
Yeah. No, you fancy dirt.
>> But think of it like this, Monty. Yeah.
Listen, think of it like this, right? If
you actually think about it. Yeah. That
just shows you that Aaron never got any
[ __ ] Because think of it. Yeah. If he
did, why would he care about some girl
on PlayStation? It's the same with the
people in this community. Why do they
obsess over women on this community if
they could just go out and meet someone?
Think about it.
I thought that Hannah Harris was ugly.
No, I don't think she was ugly. She
weren't my type or anything like that,
but no, she weren't ugly or anything.
>> I don't I don't really like
>> She was full of herself.
>> That's what I didn't like about her.
Like, she was full of herself. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I didn't like blonde women, bro. I
don't like blonde women. >> What?
I don't really like blonde women.
>> Oh, blonde.
Is that a real color though or died?
>> I think it was real. I'm
>> not sure. I'm not sure. I'm not sure.
>> I think it was a real not too sure myself >> really. Okay.
So, uh, what are you doing tomorrow?
>> Getting married tomorrow. My wedding day >> Really? >> Yeah. Tomorrow.
>> Can I come and visit you?
>> Me and Natalie got engaged and
everything. We got engaged last week.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah. Yeah, we got engaged last week.
Yeah. He post to me.
>> Can I come and visit you?
>> No. Can you [ __ ] >> Why?
>> You be expecting to s my dick again.
>> [ __ ] off.
>> So, are you are you f Have you made up
with Ricks now?
>> No. No. The man the man's the man.
That one's actually gorgeous. No, the
man's a bit too dodly to be honest with
you. The man's lost his brain.
>> I remember your birthday.
>> When's my birthday?
>> It's the 16th of October.
>> Oh, wow. Wow. Do you want a badge,
please? Yeah. Want a badge? You're gay.
Yeah, man. You know me.
>> You know my birthday, too. the second >> of >> January. >> No,
>> exactly. I don't know. But it's the
second though. Yeah. >> No,
>> there you go then. I don't know your
birthday, PJ. PJ, have you got a pair of
>> No one knows. No one No one No one knows
my birthday. Your knickers.
AJ, have you got a pair of knickers on
your bedroom floor? Huh?
>> Have you got a pair of knickers on your radiator? >> No.
>> No, I do. >> Really?
>> Really? Yeah. Yeah. I'm already
>> You like the number 16? It's a horrible number.
>> What? It's like a de It's a devil number.
>> 16's a devil number.
>> I like No, it's not. 16 is not the devil number. It >> is.
>> No, it's not.
>> You sure?
>> I'm sure the devil's number is got
>> When did When did I come to When did I
come to Birmingham? It was October,
wasn't it? I think last year. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. October, wasn't it?
>> Something like that.
>> Yeah, cuz it was just before your
birthday. It was before your birthday
and my birthday. Remember
>> the devil's number has always got to
beginning with a six. You can't put a
one before the six on the devil's
number. It's always got to be a number
six. Either way, it's number
I I still don't know how we drunk how we
drunk on an empty stomach. That's mad,
isn't it? No, not really. Natalie does
it all the time.
>> No, seriously. >> What? >> Okay.
>> Not only wants me to go down on a PJ
something what you can't do.
>> I would never I I wouldn't go down on a
woman. That's what simps do,
>> man. You've never Oh, you never go on a woman. >> Nah, >> never.
>> Nah. I receive, but I don't give. >> Monty,
>> man, why not?
>> I don't I don't even give. I I don't
even like to get to receive. >> What? >> Sorry.
No, it's it's disgusting, bro.
>> It's quite disgusting, Monty.
>> What is
>> licking mini?
>> Is it What the [ __ ] man? Going down and
just going, "Oh, man." Pulling back up
and then you got that wet stringy bit
coming up your mouth. That was right.
[ __ ] delish, man.
I remember I remember when you used to
get led on
not less me on [ __ ]
>> No, before that.
>> Yeah, I don't mind getting le on. >> Really?
>> No, I don't mind getting le on. I'm
getting something out of it. >> Yeah.
>> Well, you like get led on.
>> Yeah, it's nice.
I guess I said there you go then.
>> You don't know what that means playing
games, is it?
>> Yeah, women play games with you all the time.
>> And you?
>> Not with me. No.
>> Yeah, they do.
>> EJ, the difference between me and you
get it's like a game of Kirby. You miss
the curb where I always hit the curb.
>> Never. Always. >> Always.
Oh, does that place is a game of
>> No, seriously. >> Seriously,
>> Monty, you're a bit anxious.
>> I'm never anxious.
>> You are.
So if you have you ever gone down on a
woman for a while? >> No.
>> Be honest with you. I've only basically
gone down on N. She's only a woman you
really gone down on. Really? >> Never. >> No.
>> So you don't know what it tastes like.
No. You don't know what to go up on. No. >> No.
>> I'm a virgin mate.
>> The best is the bubble. PJ will you lick that bubble?
That's it. That's the best.
>> So So what you're basically saying is
you're licking money Mike's [ __ ]
>> Obviously not. Obviously not.
>> Is that what you're basically saying, Money?
>> Obviously not.
>> That's what you're basically saying.
Hey, I know I know I know I know a movie
that could make you laugh. >> Yeah. >> What?
>> I know a movie that could make you laugh.
>> Go on then. Watch the movie.
>> It's called Green Street.
>> I've watched it. >> Huh?
>> It made you laugh, isn't it?
>> No, not really.
>> Okay. So, what happened then?
He gets his head kept in a tunnel.
>> No, but what's the what's the thing about?
>> What thing?
>> The movie. What's the movie about? >> Football.
>> Yeah. When did you last watch it?
>> Ages ago.
>> Really? you really.
>> It's funny, eh?
>> I'm going to jump off, mate. >> Okay.
>> Yeah. Yeah, man. I've got um I've got a
a minute to attend to. It's got some um
that's missing on it, so I need to sort that out.
>> Will you come back?
>> No, no, no, no.
I just need to sort this cuz I need to
sort this mini out.
>> You mini gobbler.
>> All right, everyone. Monty's a mini
gobbler. Are you a mini gobler?
>> Mini gobbler.
>> Do you know what you're s man?
>> I'm a s
>> because you cry over women and stuff.
And I say you out for going down on a woman.
>> AJ, you want to watch? Yeah. >> No.
>> You want to watch it? I can go on camera
now. Yo, peeps. Pop one if you want to watch.
>> You think everything's funny?
>> Yo, put if you want to watch. Yeah. Put
one. Put one. Look, you only got one leg up.
I' only got one leg up, so I'll pop.
>> You're [ __ ] bold, man. >> Yeah,
>> it's cold [ __ ] again. B, is it pop one? Yeah. Oh,
>> [ __ ] money, man.
>> You think everything's funny.
>> What's funny?
>> Nothing. You think everything's funny, is it?
No, I don't think anything's going to appe.
Yeah. You never laugh at anything in it. >> What?
>> You You don't think anything's funny, do you?
>> Tell me your joke, PJ.
>> Your life.
>> That's the best chalk ever. That
>> Yeah. Do you like that? Do you like it?
Yeah, I love it. >> Yeah,
better life than yours.
>> Is it?
>> Yeah, I'm homeless, but at least I'm not
leaving with mommy. >> Seriously? in it.
>> He said my life's a joke.
>> So he said if my life's a joke
>> and it's not as I'm happy with my life being nor
he's still living with his mom and no matter
someone says why do I talk to you? You're snake
>> in PJ Snake. No. >> Yeah. >> No.
>> Molly, can you sort some I've got some
women problems. Can you sort them out for me?
>> Nah, you can sort your own problems out.
I've got my own woman to sort out in a minute.
I'll be going in a second to sort out my lady.
>> No, seriously. money. >> What?
>> You need to help me with some these women problems.
>> What? What problems do you want me to
sort out for your pas? Yeah.
>> You need to message someone some people.
>> Do you don't know if Izzy remember you
me Izzy for it in it?
>> Yes. So what? You told me to text her.
So I text her for you.
>> Yeah. Do you remember what she said?
You were cheating on you. She was
shagging some next guy. Met you went
outside and took the next guy up.
>> You took this guy out when he was crying
over Natalie G. I know. Don't remind me, man.
>> Yeah, this guy [ __ ]
things are turned on him.
>> Yeah, you was crying like a [ __ ] in it.
I'm cry. At least I can cry over a
woman. At least I've got a woman to cry
over in it. But you was crying like a
[ __ ] in it.
DJ ever was crying. What?
>> What? At least haven't got a woman to cry over.
>> I don't I've never cried over a woman, bro.
>> Yeah, because you've never had a woman
to cry over.
>> No, I've never cried over a woman. M.
>> Only what woman you cried over is your
mom when she shouts at you. >> Really? >> Yeah.
I think you fancy legs as a woman.
>> I'm sure you I'm sure you I'm in love
with Sha Long Legs.
>> Yeah, but you you're in love with this woman.
>> So, whatever. I am in love with this woman.
>> Do you like her?
>> I [ __ ] like her. I don't even know her.
>> And you seen her?
>> I'm not being funny, but I'm not. Why
can Sean get a girlfriend and you can't?
cuz he dates disabled and I don't
>> Yeah. Yeah. It don't matter if he's
disabled or not. He still can pull a
girl, can you?
>> I'd rather have no girl than be have a disabled girl.
>> I'm saying that shed on leg can pull kids included.
>> You and him both.
>> Definitely not.
>> You know all about that. It bro
>> No, but listen, it is No, but you two
you two are quite weird though, bro. In
all seriousness, you are quite weird.
>> He did. Do you know what? I I really
like my weirdness to be honest with you.
>> I know my weirdness. At least it's not
the same weirdness as Sean. >> Really?
The thing about man, I've got a
disability. Was Well, you know, Sean's
obviously got disabilities, but he knows
what he's doing.
>> Yeah. He's got he's got he's he's
autistic, isn't it?
>> Yeah, but you you met the actual pedophile.
>> Yeah, but I didn't know he was a pedophile.
>> It doesn't matter.
>> Yeah, but what do you mean it doesn't
matter if I don't know what someone is?
>> You've met Sha Long Legs more times than
you met me.
>> Yeah, I've only met you twice.
>> Three times. Twice.
>> How is it three times?
>> Is it three times?
>> It's twice. London and Birmingham, is it?
>> I'm sure it's three times.
>> No, London and Birmingham.
>> Okay. London and Birmingham
>> with Kayie in it. I met you and Kaye
with Kaye in it. in London and then
[ __ ] I went Birmingham.
>> I came I I went to I went to Birmingham
to pick up the pieces. Do you know what that means?
>> Oh, pick up what? PJ, you said you
>> you don't know what I mean, do you?
>> You asked if you could come come to me.
You said, "Do you want me to come to
you?" I said, "Come on then." I said to
you, "I don't have no money." You said,
"It's fine. I've got you." You're the
one who You're the one who started to
get me try and ceer approach women. I
told you no. I'm in love with Natalie
and all that, but I was telling you on
live that I just want Natalie.
>> I'm in love with
you pushing me to come go on cold approach. Don't know.
in love with a stripper. Yo,
>> either way, you could have [ __ ] it up
with me completely with Natalie.
>> Yeah, but Molly, you was looking forward
to this, weren't you?
>> I was I was looking for a night out with
a friend. Yeah.
>> A good old piss up like
>> Yeah. Yeah. P I'm going to have to jump
off in a minute to app Yeah. Really?
>> 11 I'm going. >> Really?
It's that now. Is it?
Five more minutes we're going. >> Yeah.
Oh, four more minutes now.
Money couldn't handle rejection. Yeah. >> Rejection, people.
When I went over to that girl in a pub
when PJ was recording,
I told her to walk off.
I've never been rejected.
>> Not that assected.
>> Not likeed.
Not like you being rejected.
>> Yeah, because you haven't cold
approached cuz you you ain't got the balls.
>> Yeah. So, how the [ __ ] have I been
rejected when you haven't called
approach? No one
>> on PlayStation. >> Never.
Can I tell you something? >> Yeah.
>> You you you can be in a relationship on
PlayStation or YouTube. Yeah.
But it's not relation. It's not a
relationship until you meet that person.
You can't say, "Yeah, yeah, I'm in a
relationship." Look at Yorkie and that
um girl from Ireland. Them two say that
they in a relationship, but they've
never met each other. They've never
kissed each other. They've never cuddled
each other. They've never done anything.
So, how the [ __ ] can it be in a relationship?
They don't make no sense whatsoever.
>> They don't make no sense. Huh?
>> It don't make sense.
>> Okay then. So, so, so can you have a PlayStation girlfriend?
>> Oh, that question that Christian bird
didn't mug me off, bro. I told her about
herself. What are you talking about,
lad? Sorry, Monty. Yeah, I told her
about her [ __ ] self.
>> So what, bro? I'm not a s I'm not a simp
like Monty. You understand?
>> S, you're the biggest s in this
community p yet. You can't even go
Birmingham to Timmy Eldridge who [ __ ]
come to your doorstep and I go at your mom.
>> I don't need you this door going.
>> I don't need you.
>> You don't. Exactly. Cuz you're not you
ain't got no respect for your mom.
>> Okay. I ain't got respect for my mom.
>> Obviously not. Cuz if that if that was
Timmy at my door that shouting at my mom
and the dead man, I'd be the first one
meeting him in town center. I be the
first one caping his face in.
>> Okay, Monty, put it this way. Yeah. What
would you do if Monty? What would you do
if a woman got rude to you?
>> If a woman got rude to me? Nothing. What?
>> You wouldn't defend yourself?
>> No. But no, not really.
>> Why? You wouldn't say anything at all?
>> No, not really. I I argue back, but I
won't do nothing back.
>> That's what I mean. You say something,
you wouldn't say anything back now.
>> No, not really. No.
>> Why not?
>> Cuz I'm better than you, PJ. >> Really?
>> That's why I can pull.
>> But you can't pull though. That's the thing.
You can't pull, can you?
Okay. I don't know. I'm single peas. Yeah.
>> No, but you can't pull [ __ ] You know
what I mean?
>> I can't pull everyone. Obviously not.
That be being big beheaded. Obviously close,
>> you know. I think anyone can pull but
you. You can.
>> You can't pull,
>> man. How many years has it been?
>> 6 months.
>> Add the add the years.
No. 6 months. You You don't How How old
are you? You're 36. And you you go on
about sex like a [ __ ] 10-year-old.
You don't How pathetic you sound.
>> Is it me?
>> It's you, PJ. Talking about
>> No, no, no. It's actually you.
>> It's actually talking about sex, PJ. I'm
talking about you can't get
>> because you've not had It's because
you've not had you've not had a lot of
sex in your life. Like, this is You know
what I mean? Okay. Yeah. Yeah, sure. >> PJ,
I'll leave you I'll leave you up to PJ. Yeah.
>> Yeah, man. Yeah.
>> Just remember this. Yeah. I'm the one
with the two kids. Yeah. Obviously, I
don't really see them much. And I'm And
I'm with a woman now. Yeah.
>> Yeah. You've been with two women.
>> And I'm the And I'm the same. Yeah. I see that.
>> Yeah. You've been with two women. Yeah.
Oh my [ __ ] god, bro. I've been with
way more than two women.
That Christian is he's a scumbag, isn't it?
And whatever. I might need to stick on
her some more.
I already stuck on her, but I might have
to. I might have to pit 100%.
So I'm not a simp like Monty. You
understand me? I'm not a simp like Monty.
Monty's a reg.
Who do you think's more of a sia? Monty
or the virgin?
The beds virgin.
already had a girlfriend, lad. Something
that you will never have and you're
banned. See you later, self projector. I
saw you a comment the other day.
No self-reflectors on my channel trying
to bring the energy down.
You've never had a girlfriend and you've
never had sex. Go self-reflect on
another channel, lad.
Early lad. Early
Just Christian tried to mug it, bro.
Yeah, I approach all the time, bro. Sober, drunk.
Yeah, I don't do it much anymore, but I
just can't be bothered. But yeah,
to be honest with you, bro,
why can't you do it? Can't you approach?
I take you can't do it now.
Yeah, right, Bob. Yeah, right.
That Christian needs a hide. Bob bills.
Jeez, are hiding lad.
She needs a good telling about herself.
Yeah, damn right I am. And that'll be me
done, bro. That'll be it.
Yeah, that'll be it, lad.
Yeah, that [ __ ] Christian Izzy didn't
mug me off, bro. She sent me like 13
messages, deleted it, then blocked me. I
told her I told her about herself, bro.
No one's ever loved me off.
I did 100%, bro.
Yeah, it's not going to be no different
tomorrow. Like, I I hope you know that. Anyways,
I hope you're aware
I hope you're aware that it will be the
same tomorrow, lad. because I know it
will, but I'm still doing it anyways.
Right. I'm going go on and start Anyways,
I'm going to sleep. Yeah. See you later.