Oh,
no. Indonesian fellow tomorrow.
That's not good, is it?
[ __ ] hell, man.
The people in this community need to get
a [ __ ] life.
They get a [ __ ] life, mate.
That's what they need. A [ __ ] life.
And it's not F you, it's FA.
They need to get a [ __ ] life. The
people this bloody community, lads.
They definitely need to get a life, bro. Another
that's okay. I'll just wait.
You'll wait. Yes. Until they get a lie.
You know, seriously, but
I clicked on that Lord J. You see the
same people every [ __ ] day.
I've been got my haircut. I was busy today, bro.
Some people got a life.
And it's clear that like most people in
this community haven't got a life.
See the same people typing the same [ __ ] every day. Madness.
I'm ready for tomorrow, bro. Ready as
I'll ever be. I'll just
wait your way.
>> Yes. So I get a life community.
That's what I'll do.
a [ __ ] rude [ __ ]
>> Nah, bro.
>> About You're not going to get with
someone who's got [ __ ] higher body than five.
>> Who the [ __ ] do these people think they are, bro? Yeah.
I'll be out here tomorrow, bro. out
here. Absolutely out here, bro.
I'm going to be going to that same spot.
I'll be [ __ ] hitting the same spot, bro.
Yeah, I'll be hitting it up. Trust me.
I'll be hitting the [ __ ] spot up.
Don't you worry about that. The same
spot. And you know why, pastor?
Cuz I'm not scared of you. That's why.
Yeah. Scared. No.
No. Nothing, bro. Just went out today.
Got my haircut. Be out tomorrow. Well,
be out tomorrow, bro. Yeah.
I just went to get my haircut earlier.
Big day tomorrow. Big day ahead of us. Yeah.
And that will be me done.
We're going to leave with a bang.
Yeah, rap boy. Them, you know, I was
thinking, no, no, no, don't go out
tomorrow. Don't go out tomorrow. But
then I was like, but then I was like,
them [ __ ] started laughing at us that way.
Oh, just this, bro.
I just went natural. I'm not going to
style my hair, bro. Just like this. I
ain't going to style it.
I'm going to like curl it. Yeah, bro.
It's sick, though. I like it. Looking
fresh, bro. Yeah. I'm just going to
style it. Um I'm just going to brush it.
Maybe curl it or something, lad.
>> Don't put extra. I'm not putting extra
effort in. [ __ ] that. I'm clean. I'm
good. That's it. [ __ ] off. Simple. Simple, mate.
Yeah, that's it, lad.
Hey, bro. I was I was so tempted. Yeah.
To text that [ __ ]
Christian uh Christian Izzy on NMS.
I'll put you in your [ __ ] place, bro.
Yeah. The more I read the more I read
stuff. Yeah. The more it like pisses me
off. Like don't don't make me put you in
your [ __ ] place, [ __ ]
I will do it. I'm the kind of [ __ ] that
And I hope tomorrow, bro, and let me
tell you something. I hope tomorrow I'll
be hitting up the same place. I'll be
hitting at that same place tomorrow.
Why? Cuz I tell you it's a free country.
Simple as that. How about that?
And no [ __ ] no one's going to be
telling me nothing. Trust me. I might
record it. I might actually record it. I
might actually do an approach there and
just record it for the Lord. Yep.
You know, bro, you know. >> Yeah.
Tomorrow. We're getting it, lad. And I'm
done. Rat boy, for yeah, a couple
months, I think. After tomorrow. All
right, boy. You know, the only reason
I'm going out yet
is cuz uh is cuz uh
is cuz um
is cuz I won like £100, lad. You can't
[ __ ] you can't even justify it.
Whether you work for the money, whether
you save for the money, you can't
actually justify it unless you win it.
You can't justify it, bro.
Yeah. You know, Breezy, you actually
can't justify it whether you work for
it. Like you actually can't even justify
it, bro. Because the country is so [ __ ]
You can't justify it, bro.
100 pound might be nothing. It's nothing
to me. I've got more money than that.
But pays for a haircut and it pays for
loads of Guinnesses. So that's the way I
saw it, bro. That's the way I saw it,
Rat Boy. It pays for It doesn't matter.
Look, say Guinness is £8 a pipe. Yeah.
How many Guinnesses can you get with £50?
Think about it like that, bro. You'll be
crashed after three. Okay, we'll put
that money towards towards the mama fund.
No, I'm not going to see that come out,
man. I'm not going to see that. You
might do. I mean, it has happened,
Grezy. Someone that I approached before,
they was ignoring and hey, this is
actually a funny story, Grezy. This
person was ignoring, ignoring, ignoring,
ignoring, ignoring. Right. They kept
ignor Not not like not ignoring, but
like they were like trying to play games
in it. I went to approach someone I saw
and it turned out to be them and they
was talking to me like it was normal. So
I mean it's a small world but is it? So
but it's central London at the end of
the [ __ ] day. It's big in it. So you
know but yeah you might do you might just do
you know I'll [ __ ] I'll [ __ ] tell
them about their [ __ ] self bro.
It's a harsh lesson.
You know who who you know that's another
thing as well about I was I was
listening to this [ __ ] about oh if it's
over five you'll cut so what people
people are not allowed to sleep with
five people says who says who bro what
if you're what what if what if you're
one of these people that never that that
never founded something at a young age.
You see there's people out there you
know that's only slept with one or two
people cuz they've been with the same
people since since young so they just
stayed with them. So what bro? Maybe
maybe you know you could have got used
for sex. At the end of the day, bro,
people people could have used you for
sex or you know you just come across you
might have been in five relationship,
six relationships. Who the [ __ ] knows,
bro? Like you're people, bro. You Oh my
god, bro. Like where did they even come
out with this [ __ ]
Like where do they even come out with
this [ __ ] bro? Five. You think five
You think a five body? No, bro. No,
that's that is that is mad, bro. These
these people are so entitled. Like they
need to know their level. They need to
know their level before trying to come
up with all these unrealistic
expectations. They need to know their
lane, bro. You understand, Grezy? They
need to know their lane. They actually
do need to know their lane, bro.
They need to know their lane.
And that's the thing. And that's the
thing with London, bro. People think
they're better than they are. It gives
us a bad name. We call it the [ __ ] city.
Yeah. It gives us a bad [ __ ] name,
bro. It actually gives us a bad name
with these wankers.
>> I'll be hitting up my case tomorrow as
well, dude. I've been recording the whole thing.
No [ __ ] gay [ __ ] is going to [ __ ]
tell me where I can [ __ ] go. I'll
tell you that, mate.
I'm not going to Birmingham.
Hello. I'm not going to Birmingham.
Why am I going Birmingham, bro?
>> But I don't waste my time on sping. So yeah,
[ __ ] that one in Nottingham. I got
you like 20. She had a body count of 10.
Who are we to say, Grezy? Who are we to
say what people's body counts are?
It's none of your [ __ ] business.
If you had my thrift group, it's none of
your [ __ ] business.
If you if someone
is having these expectations,
they better be [ __ ] perfect.
Yeah, Grezy, but they better Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. But they were basically saying
Greavvesy. I don't care anyways, but I'm
just I'm just putting this into
perspective. Listen, bro. Yeah. What do
you mean if someone I I if someone's got
higher than five? Five is nothing, bro.
People with five people is nothing.
You know, you don't know people's
circumstances. You That's why it's
unfair to judge people. Some people have
one, some people have two, some people have six.
What What's like what what do they expect?
Not everyone's been in a long-term
relationship for 10, 15 years.
I don't understand some of these the the
standards. I was talking to my bar about
this and say [ __ ] and I talking to him
about this, bro. Some of them don't make
sense. They really really really don't.
You can't come with all these. What are
you bringing to the table? What have you
got? You know, that's what I'm asking.
If people if people have got these
expectations, what have they got, bro?
These are probably the same people
working at [ __ ] McDonald's that are
trying to, you know, like you have to
have something yourself.
Like you better have a lot of [ __ ]
like you better have a lot of money and
have a really good [ __ ] job, right? A
really good [ __ ] job to be having
these expectations. That's what I'm
saying, Grezy. That's what I'm saying.
Okay, Greasy. Okay. Okay. So, what if
you what if you come across what if you
come across somebody that was 29 20 30
uh 2930 and they come at you and say,
"Oh, yeah. I've been with um I've been
with seven people." What would you what
would you do? Would you would you get
with them or not?
Oh, she only had three.
But that's not the point, bro. That's
not the point. I said three even though
it's six. Mine's six, but I said three
inwards. I don't have to explain myself
to people. At the end of the day, I
don't need to explain myself to people.
I think it's unfair to judge people on
that because you don't know people's circumstances.
Mine's six, but I said free. It
said free before then because it's none
it's none of their business, isn't it?
Well, she said free to me. No, no, I
think I think Yeah.
No, I don't think so, bro.
It doesn't matter anyways. I don't [ __ ]
No, that's weird, bro.
That's a No,
I don't think so, bro.
But it's all funny until people bump
into each other, lad. Yeah, I did. It's
all funny until people bump into each
other, then they'll start [ __ ]
themselves. Is it?
No, I don't think they've got 16. Yeah,
I don't think they've got What do you
think their body count is, Bezy?
What would you guess?
No, I don't think so, bro.
Nah. Yeah, they might lie. Not really
cuz thingy told me 25.
No, I'm not having dark one, but I'm
just going to stick to Guinness. I mean,
I don't know what. No, they don't use that.
The one in Nottingham said 20. I think
it was 20 or something mad. It was some
It was a mad number. I can't remember.
25 is thingy. So, I don't think so. I
don't think they lie, bro.
What do you think, Greg? You think they
lie about their body count?
I don't know, bro. I don't know.
No. For people to have these kind of
standards, bro, they need to um they
need to be something themselves.
It's as simple as that. They need to be
something themselves. That's the way I see it.
And if they're not solving themselves, that then
don't go having these um unrealistic
[ __ ] stupid things like anyone. I'm
talking anyone in general.
Not show up in here, bro.
What do you think, Greg? Do you think
people are about body counts?
Why would I be like Timmy anyways if I
if I don't gambling? Why is that? I
don't gamble much.
Yeah, you've gone your whole life
without any indigo lads. You're sat on
YouTube every day. You ain't even got a life.
I'll be cutting anyways, but I'll be
cutting after tomorrow, bro. I got some
stuff to do. I need to go to the gym and
[ __ ] and I need to Yeah, I got things to
be doing, bro, for a little bit. So, um
yeah. So, after tomorrow's content, I'll
be cut. I'll be dipping, bro. So,
I will seriously I will be I'll be
dipping for a bit, bro. But I'll be back
some point, obviously.
I won't leave. Okay, bro. Watch me. Like
I said, we can I I can take a day off of
YouTube, bro. You people can't. Remember that.
Yeah, remember that, bro. Already done
it before, many times, and I'll do it
again. I wasn't gone most today. I was busy.
I've got stuff to be doing, lad.
I got stuff to be doing, something that
you people should be doing. But just
YouTube every day. That's your choice, you know. Yeah.
laughing at you and then we kind of
started laughing at us.
I love it, bro. Absolutely love it, man. >> Yeah,
you me you watch.
Yeah, I'm sure that army constitution
was trying to mock me in it.
Yeah, there was a black guy. Do you
remember? And he was smiling when I told
him greasy. He was smiling.
Greasy. He was smiling, bro. You remember
Yeah. That attitude is bad, bro.
That attitude is [ __ ] bad, bro. Who
you [ __ ] talking to, you [ __ ] c.
Yeah, these [ __ ] need telling about himself, bro.
properly in it.
>> Yeah. So, she slept with more people at
22 than I did when I was at [ __ ] 25.
How mad is that, bro? Yeah,
I reckon. What do you think, L11? I
reckon if you started off nowadays,
you'll probably be a virgin. I reckon in
the next 5 10 years,
there's going to be a lot more virgins
because you're not going to be able to
meet anyone. What do you think?
I reckon it's going to increase.
The numbers will increase within 5 to 10 years
I reckon. Well, now but definitely 5 to 10 years.
What do you think?
You can't even meet people that are actually normal.
So, you're not going to
be able to um Yeah.
the [ __ ] bro. I really hope I bump into
No, I probably don't want to do that to
be honest with you. Probably start
[ __ ] crying again and playing victim. No thanks.
No off thanks lad.
Oh that person on Reddit was [ __ ]
white nighting greasy.
They were white nighting.
They were saying women are better than
men. Women are better than men.
I said bro
that's like one of the last messages he
sent. You know I was like bro
they're not going to [ __ ] you.
They're not they're not going to let you hit it.
He had the women. Yeah. Laughing. [ __ ] hell.
Right. Top of t time. last
looking cute little base. Lovely and groomed. Oh, [ __ ] Mama,
how do you people sit on YouTube all day
in the summer?
How the [ __ ] are you [ __ ] out?
How are you every day, bro?
That's how you know you [ __ ]
ain't got no life.
You just like the Virgin [ __ ]
the Kent Wanker. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Even in the summer use sat on
here. Was it
mate? I was out all summer last year on
the bike. I was going to again.
No. Why? No. I don't gamble, bro. It's
not It's not a habit for me.
I took that £100 I'm using it to go out with tomorrow.
I'll probably end up messing that [ __ ]
tomorrow when I'm drunk, bro. Putting
them in their face.
[ __ ] tell you about your [ __ ]
self, [ __ ] Yeah.
All I need to do is tell them about himself.
So that three That's basically double
your That's basically double your body
count. I'll [ __ ] tell you about your
[ __ ] self, man. For real? Yeah.
I try not to cuz I know pointless
arguing and that bro I probably will.
So yeah, bro, there's no point asking me
if there's any gambling because I don't
do it like that, bro.
And when I do gamble was£10 on the football.
I think I done it the other day cuz I
was pissed off.
I was just pissed off. [ __ ] off, bro.
I was happy with £100. So, yeah.
Got a big day tomorrow, Bob.
Man, I think I should just give that
£100 I want to Laney.
I could give it to Laney.
It's such a waste of money in it. But we
live for toxicity, don't we? music. We
live for toxicness. Yeah.
But I understand. I do understand
to be honest. I do understand like
someone saying, "Oh, let's go to church
together." And stuff. I think that is
like I don't think that's bad. But
asking people to have a lower body count
than five and you're asking
These people are are nothing to be
having these standards.
They're nothing themselves to be having
these standards, bro. Like for somebody
to have these standards, I want them to
be [ __ ] over. I want them to have been
[ __ ] over many times. I want them to
be making 10 grand a month and
being like high class in order for
somebody to have these these these expectations.
Um, don't think just cuz your family's
rich or you got uh, you know, you got
rich parents, it doesn't mean nothing.
See, that's the misconception. People in
London think they're better than they
are. Greasy. If you ever visit London,
it's the most westernized place you
could ever visit. And the people are just [ __ ]
Trust me. I don't know if you've ever
been to London. I don't think you have,
but yeah, they're just they're absolute
[ __ ] But I give you a new place, lad.
Yeah, you you you're missing the point
I'm making, lad. I mean, the point I'm
trying to make,
yeah, she is a proper proper snob trying
to say that she wouldn't talk to someone
if they've slept with more than five
people. Why? You could sleep with six
people, you could still be a normal
person. Why is that, bro? Like it.
The point I'm trying to make is like,
bro, like you need to be something
yourself to have these expectations,
bro. You need more than a a rich mommy
and daddy. You understand? You need a
rich You need more than a rich mommy and
daddy. Because the thing is with these
people, they probably ain't even got 100
pound in their [ __ ] account.
You understand? They ain't probably a
even got 100 pound in their [ __ ] account, bro.
You can't expect more than what you are.
That's my argument, Grezy. You can't be
working in McDonald's saying that you
want a man with [ __ ] a million pounds
who drives. You understand what I'm
trying to say, lad?
No, I don't care. But you're missing the
point I'm trying to make, bro. Like, you can't expect
cuz what is it? They they they have they
can say they can say
what they want, bro. But the thing is
Yeah. What have they got to offer?
What have they got to offer us?
What have they What have they got to offer us?
You know what I'm saying?
I don't have it. I don't have
unrealistic standards, bro. All
someone's got to do is not cheat and not be boring and Yeah.
You know what I mean? I don't have un
Yeah, her expectations. She's serious
about them as well. She's Bro, you ain't
finding that. Trust me, you're not
Somebody that's got a degree, somebody
that's got less than like that's very specific.
And they say that women ain't got
unrealistic standards. What the [ __ ]
But yeah, no, like they can't expect
more than what they are. Greedy. That's
what I'm trying to say. They can't
expect more than what they are. That
doesn't make sense.
You know what I'm saying?
That's my argument, bro. But that's all
that also gets into the whole argument
about the double standards. You understand?
Yeah, you can see in a minute, bro.
She's a nasty bastard. I I hope I bump
into her tomorrow, bro. I'll just tell
her about herself straight. Like, it's
it's not even a joke, bro.
That is [ __ ] bro. Like, oh my god, it
pisses me off, bro. I swear to God, it
pisses me off just thinking about it.
She said, "Oh, you need a degree and
anyone that's got a higher body count
than five, she doesn't speak to." which
I told her I slept with three people in it.
You've got some very um Yeah, there's no
point doing all of that stuff, bro. She
just walked in her head in it. Yeah,
there's no point doing all of that stuff.
What is the point of all of it, bro?
Like, serious. But you you're w you're
actually walked in your head.
No, I told her only three, but it's actually six.
And and even if it was only three,
that's not a madness, bro. We live in
the West where you can't even get a
conversation out of a woman. Only only
three. It's actually six. But even if it
was free, I lied to her. Um, even if it
was only three, I mean, anyone that's 28
that slept with three people nowadays,
congratulations. Cuz you can't even
barely get a conversation out of
someone. So, is it is it really a madness?
Not at all. It's actually quite
believable in 5 to 10 years when pe if
people come and start telling me that
they're virgins, I'll be like, "Oh,
okay." Yeah. It wouldn't even surprise me
because I know the truth, bro. This
isn't this isn't Reddit. This is real
life. But no, it's actually six.
She was saying, and she was being
serious. No, she was basically saying
like she wants someone um to go to
church with her, which I think that's
not as bad. But then she's saying that
she wants somebody to get a degree and
obviously the body count thing. So the
body count thing and the degree is
snobby. I don't think the church thing is
really but the other two is definitely
definitely that is and that's what I'm
trying to say. It's it's all London is
it? So they all think they're better than everyone.
Yeah. We'll send it hard to mind.
Nothing's going to happen anyways.
But yeah, you're not going to meet anyone anyways.
Why is a body count of three? Why is a
body count of three mad anyways? Even if
it was free,
you're not going to meet anyone. So, you
can't even get a date nowadays. So, why?
I don't think that's bad. I think that's the norm.
I generally think that's the norm.
Yeah. It doesn't matter anyways, pastor.
I'm not going to meet anyone anyways.
But yeah, like that is mad. Yeah. Agree.
Yeah. Agree. Yeah.
Yeah. A degree.
Has anyone in this community got a
degree? You know what I mean? But it's
not even that. She was trying to get
rude as well.
She was trying to get rude as well.
Yeah. She was trying to get rude like
saying, "Oh, I'm not going to raise my
breath from someone I don't care about."
I was like, "Do you know how much you've
contradicted yourself? You literally
sent me about 10 minutes voice notes every day.
So it's like that when you don't fall,
this is what they do. Yeah. When you
don't fall for their games and they
can't no longer manipulate you, they
switch cuz I think it's because they're
so used to Well, it is greasy. I think
they're so used to Yeah. dealing with
these white knights and simps so they
can walk all over that like when
So it's like an act. So what they do is
like an act. It's like fake. They're
fake in it. So when you realize that
like when they realize that you're like
smarter than them, they that's when they
switch. Does that make Does that make sense?
Hopefully it does make sense. So they
Yeah. So that's it.
I'm surprised you've got any friends,
bro. The way you're [ __ ] The way you
speak to people, that is that is [ __ ] disgusting.
That is really vile. Yeah,
that's a madness.
Yeah. So basically um Yeah. Does that
make sense? Grezy,
stop watching me. It's annoying. I can hear myself.
So, I'm speaking to Laneies. You don't
need to watch me, Laney. There's other
communities on YouTube.
[ __ ] hell. She can hear it cuz I'm
I'm She can hear me saying it. It's
going down to her phone.
There's other communities, one ones that
are more suitable for you.
You know what I'm saying? [ __ ] hell, man.
Do you know what's so funny? Lady was
watching the live stream. Grezy from
when he got off the train all the way to the door.
That kills me, bro. That actually kills me.
Oh, that kills me, bro. like from the
start to the finish
and I was just chilling watching Spider-Man.
I was just sat there watching Spider-Man
on the same website.
No, I was just chilling, but I weren't
even watching it. I was just watching
Spider-Man on another community.
Yeah, I was watching Spider-Man though.
Yeah, I was in the pub watching Spider-Man
and then all of a sudden Timmy Eldridge popped up.
Yeah, and then Timmy Elid popped up.
Yeah, I was out drinking watching Spider-Man
and then Timmy Eldridge popped up.
I slipped up, bro. Everybody knows I
wasn't in the house. I've already proved
I wasn't in the house.
So, how have I slipped up when I've
literally proved I wasn't in the house?
I literally proved like multiple times I
wasn't even in the house. But, okay,
bro. I slipped up anyways.
Okay, bro. Okay, listen, bro. If it
sounds fishy, I'll tell you what you
want to hear. I was sat in the house
scared to death, [ __ ] my pants, and I
was so scared. Is that what you want to
hear? If you want to hear it, I'll say
it, bro. If that's if that's what you
want to hear, I I'll tell you what you
want to hear.
I was so scared, bro.
>> Terrified, bro.
>> Like, oh my god. I was like shaking and
everything. Yeah. I'll just tell you
what you want to hear, bro. Because
that's the best thing. Just agree with these people
because I like Spider-Man. Duh. And then
Timmy L just popped up.
Yeah. And then
to be old just [ __ ] up.
>> But yeah, listen, bro. Um,
>> yeah, my trim my trim looks sick. >> Yep.
Yeah, I got a sick trim, bro. I like my
trim. And I got the mama fund white. I
got the mama fund right here. But
obviously we're not going to be showing
money because we don't we don't show
self projectors money, do we, Grezy?
Yeah, that's that's the toxic sector.
>> Yeah, they do that. They do that on the
on the toxic sector.
This is the toxic sector.
Yeah, it's the toxic sector.
>> Yeah, man. So, yeah. [ __ ] um
Yeah. What was we talking about? Um
yeah, basically unrealistic uh expectations. Uh-huh.
Bless bless you, Grezy. You're too
You're too short today, aren't you? And
it could even if it's not stuff like
that, it could be something like it
could be something like um
um Yeah, I used to patrol the area. Do
you remember that Grezy? I used to
patrol the area.
Yeah, I used to patrol the area. Do you remember Grezy?
Um so yeah, I mean it could be something
like so so yeah, it might not even be
anything physical, but sometimes it can
be stuff. Sometimes it can be physical.
Sometimes it could just be um you know
you're too short even though you're like
510 5 [ __ ] 11. Like it could be it
could be many many different things. See
the thing is what you hear on the
internet Greavesy is not what happens in real life.
Do you understand? There's a big there's
a big difference between what people say
online and real life. Do you understand?
There's a fine um line between the two.
There's a fine line,
especially London as well,
which you'll find out sooner or later,
Grezy, when you start dating. Bless you.
Are you scared? Be honest with me,
Greavves. Are you scared?
to start this dating thing after like
seeing like my experiences. That's
that's Do you know what? I wonder that
every day, you know, Greavvesy.
I do wonder that every day. Does does it
does it put you off a little bit?
Cuz you're going to be dealing with this as well, poor [ __ ] Yeah,
well, you poor [ __ ]
Yeah. I don't know why Laneany watches me.
It's kind of kind of weird,
but I got a feeling I will bump into
this [ __ ] you know, bro, like within a
month. I don't know what it is, bro.
Because I've already bumped into some I
have done it. It has actually happened a
few times, to be honest.
I bumped into this guy in Weather
Spoons. I think I was bad mouthing him
in it. I was bad mouthing him on on WhatsApp
and I see him again, but he didn't try
anything or anything. I'm sure I was bad
mouthing him. I can't remember what I
said, but I was bad mouthing them.
Greavves in it. And you know how you
just troll someone, you badmouth them
and you don't think you're going to see
them again. But you didn't try anything.
Yeah, it has happened. It has happened.
You can easily like the thing is dusty.
Yeah. You think that London Yeah.
because it's big, but trust me, you will
you will bump into people. Trust me, you
will. It has happened. It has definitely
definitely definitely happened. It's
happened a couple of times. I was
telling someone about this yesterday, right?
You know that nightclub, Dusty, that
they closed in um Romford.
Do you remember that that they closed
that that place they closed down in
Romford? Now, a couple of years ago when
I met that John on YouTube, right, I hit
this place up around about that time and
I see this guy, bro, and he was
Albanian, right? And I said, "Oh, like,
do you want to just do you want to just
hit it together, bro? Like, [ __ ] just
like send it hard in it." So, then I got
the guy on Instagram. This was about 4
years ago. Then I see the guy again, bro.
Um, in central London, the most random
place. Where was it? I see him a couple
times. I see him a couple times. I see
him in this bar. I said, "Oh, I know you
from somewhere, bro. I know I know you
from somewhere." You know, when
someone's got a familiar face and I see
him and then I see him again outside the
pub. So, just it might be London, bro,
but trust me, uh you could easily bump
into people like especially if people
around that area. If someone lives in
West London, bro, you can bump into
them, bro. Trust me. Trust me. And it's
happened. It's happened a couple of
times. So, yeah, I'll be live tomorrow
for a little bit. Yeah.
Then I'll be off here for a bit, lad,
cuz I got stuff to do. So, yeah. But
yeah, you can bump into people. It has
happened. It's like the army lads. I
used to keep bumping into them.
And they're still [ __ ] laughing.
They're still laughing at us. Yeah, it
happens. You'll bump into people, bro. Trust me.
We already found your mama.
But yeah, what do you do if you bump
into I just [ __ ] tell him, bro,
straight about himself. I would, bro.
Obviously, I'm doing approaching, bro.
I'm going out drinking. Of course I'm
going to go out approaching and then I'm
done. But I'm doing it DH10. I'm doing
it for the sake of it. It doesn't even
make sense why I'm doing it to be
honest. It don't make sense cuz there is
no hope. But I said I was going to do it
so I'm going to do it. So simple as
that. Why I'm doing it, I don't know. It
doesn't even make any sense. Me and
Ant-Man was talking about this. It
doesn't really make any sense
cuz it's always going to be the same
here. But uh something to do in it.
Yeah, I am.
Yeah, I'm going to go back into that
place and if that game manager comes,
I'm going to I will I'm going to I'm
going to tell him about himself, bro.
This time I will tell him to mind his own business.
I will. I told him about himself last
time as well, but I I'll take it to the
extreme this time.
It's a free country, lad. I don't need
to put up with any of your [ __ ]
And I'm not going to be intentionally
trying to annoy people. No. No. [ __ ]
him, bro. He likes to try to kick people
out of places for no reason. [ __ ] off.
You leave me alone. Simple as that.
Leave me alone.
As simple as that, bro. [ __ ] off.
Well, yeah. They didn't throw me out.
They just basically said, "Oh yeah, you
got to leave." I said, "Thanks for
understanding." So, I don't understand.
It doesn't even make any sense. So, what
I'm basically going to do tomorrow
grievy is I'm going to stay there until
I get an explanation.
That's what I'm going to do. I'm going
to be a very awkward bastard tomorrow if
they come. If they don't I'm not going
to intentionally look for trouble, bro.
I'm not I'm not looking for trouble.
That's not what I'm here to do. But, you
know, I will um really want to get the
answers to this question, lad.
Uh no, nothing to do with that either.
I'll be I'll be an awkward bastard. I
will be awkward tomorrow. Trust me, I
will be. But I'm not going out. Um, I'm
not going out for a trouble, bro. I'm
not looking for trouble. But, um, at the
same time, like I want to know like,
yeah, basically basically what I've said.
I said, make it make sense, bro. You've
got an establishment where people speak
to men, where people speak to women,
right? And then you're trying to tell
people they can't do it. So, what do you
want people to do? Sit in a in a corner
by themselves or with people that they
go out with and just talk to no one?
Like, it don't make sense, bro. So, if
you can actually give an explanation and
help me understand, it'd be nice.
Um, so yeah, I don't want to hear. Yeah,
it's just it's like respectfully, bro. you know,
um I'm going to say basically uh I'll
just say grievously
I'll just say like and and you know, to
be honest with you, um respectfully,
life's hard enough dealing with women
than having some gay guy trying to tell
you what you can or can't do. No
offense. So, I'm not going to like start
um going out
specifically looking for trouble, but if
I come across any white or any I'll tell
them about themselves and if I see
Christian Izzy, I'll tell her about
herself as well. I got I got some weird
feeling I'm going to bump into her
tomorrow, bro. I don't know what it is,
bro. But I've got this feeling, bro. I
swear to God.
I swear to God, bro. I've got this
because it's happened before.
Yeah. But you don't think I'll say
anything though, is it? This is the
thing with you, Greasy. You don't think
I'll say anything? I will, mate. Trust
me, I [ __ ] will. Yeah.
I don't know, bro. I'm not going to go
out [ __ ] intentionally like um
looking for trouble, but I'm not I don't
do that ever, bro.
But I will I will do, bro. Just tell
them about themselves.
You remember? Do you remember the one I
had go? Do you remember the one I had
going to waxis? Do you remember the one
I had going to waxies? We
So, do you remember the one I had going
to waxies? [ __ ] just stood the [ __ ] up.
There was a reason for that.
They done stuff to me, bro. So, [ __ ]
them in it. That weren't an innocent person.
But she was being a [ __ ] bro. weren't
an innocent person. They were trying to
be a [ __ ] They were proper trying to be
Yeah, she was being a [ __ ] though, bro.
So, it wasn't just some innocent person.
They were being a [ __ ] trying to like
patronize patronize me and [ __ ] So,
[ __ ] them in it, bro.
Yep. So, we'll see you tomorrow, bro.
We're going to hit We're going to hit
Grezy. We're going to hit it, bro.
Yeah. So, they're all bad in different ways really.
Yeah. You need to whenever you start
dating Greavesy. Yeah.
Just ask them. Just ask them. Uh,
Just ask them. Um, what have they got to offer you?
Like in a roundabout way. Just ask them
what have they got to offer you.
Um, what what about Okay, you're saying
leave women and gays out of it. What
about What about if I wanted to pick on
innocent men, Dusty? Would that be fine?
So, it's okay to go for innocent men,
but it's not okay to go for innocent
women. That's not fair, is it?
Because, as Greavvesy will tell you, as
women aren't angels. So, so it'll be
okay if I go for innocent men then.
That's not really fair, is it, dusty? Poor [ __ ]
So you can go for innocent men
even though women are worse than men and that's fine.
Seriously, bro. Come on.
Imagine you see how she was with a man
who white night. Oh, bro. I'd call
madness. I'm I'm I'm I'm
going prison. Simple as that. Like write
me off. Greasy. If you don't see if you
don't see me for a year, you know where
I am, bro. I'm in I'm in I'm in I'm in
the pen. I'm in a pen. But I just can't
I just can't, bro. I can't get over Monday.
Just have the whole thing played out.
Just have the whole thing played out, Grezy.
[ __ ] You're bored at home. You're b
You're bored at home, bro. Oh, I'm just
going to go walk to the mall. Just go
for a little stroll. Get out the house. Bus ride.
Okay, let me go to this place. I'm not
drinking. Oh, I have a Coke. Yeah, but
I'm not drinking. Oh, get on the
Guinness. I'm not drinking.
Oh, [ __ ] it. One Guinness isn't going
one Guinness ain't going to is not going
to hurt anyone.
Drunk the Guinness about what, six sips
in cuz it's quite thick, you see. And
all I can remember is them [ __ ] started
laughing at us.
You see, they started laughing at us.
Give me another Guinness.
Down the down the Guinness. Down the
down the kids, bro.
Went back home. Went back home, changed,
went straight on that tube into the
city. Yeah, I don't [ __ ] I don't [ __ ] about
them started laughing at us. See, that's
what I'm saying. It could it could it
could escalate in it. I love it. I love
I love this. I love this toxicity,
Grezy. I love this toxicity.
It's great, isn't it? It's great. Yeah.
You shouldn't even make jokes though,
seriously, about bumping into people cuz
it probably will happen.
It's not even funny, bro. It probably would happen.
Laughing at Yeah. UK asylum. I couldn't
stop. After I had like four sips of Guinness,
I had it in my head that them [ __ ]
started laughing at us.
They started laughing at us.
Yeah. Mocking us. Yeah. [ __ ] that, bro.
Yeah. You can't You can't And you can't
let Couldn't let it lie.
Do you remember? Couldn't let it lie.
No, it's But you would know, bro. If you
know, you know.
Yeah. mocking you, laughing at you.
Yeah. Yeah. We'll see. We'll be mocking
you tomorrow, mate.
Yeah. There'll be a white knight getting
involved as well. I tell him to [ __ ] off.
You remember Greasy? Do you want to go
for it, mate? That's what I say. Do you
want to go for it, mate?
The neighbor. Greasy.
The neighbor. Greasy. There's a black
guy that got arrested. You want to go
for it, mate?
It's always people. It's always people
that are trying to stand up for other
people and they and they get in trouble.
You know what I mean? Greasy. Yeah.
[ __ ] bastards, man. Bastards, bro. Bastards.
So, yeah. Anyways, Greasy, it's a
serious question. When they're asking
stuff from you, ask them what they can
give you. How can someone that's what
can someone like you that's damaged give
me? That's more the question. What can a
damaged person like you give me? Um long term
nothing. So [ __ ] off.
In other words, in it, bro. [ __ ] off,
man. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
It's the truth, bro.
It is the truth.
Damaged ass [ __ ] people, bro.
You don't know what I was going to do
that day as well, bro. I was going to
Yeah. Go out here and pull someone even
though it was a Monday. I got free
numbers. I was good for a Monday. And I
was going to send them the videos.
Greasy. I was going to send them the
videos. And if it failed, then I was
going to send like other one pre, bro. I
was going to show me getting a [ __ ]
bro. I'm not even I'm not even joking,
but I was going to show me get a
[ __ ] bro. I've got like I've got
like other videos. Creamsy.
Creepsy. Yeah, I was going to, bro. I
was going to be a madness, bro. Trust
me. You don't you don't know me, bro.
You don't know me. That's what I'm
saying, bro. This this this this
Guinness. Yeah, this Guinness is a is a
killer, bro. It's an absolute killer. I
can't only have one, Grezy. I can't just have one.
I can't only have one Guinness Griezy,
you know. I can't only have one. I can't
just have a pint or whatever. You know,
I try to behave myself and stuff, but
one thing just just Yeah. You can't just
have one, bro.
Peer belly can't just have one, can he? Greasy. No.
Oh gosh. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. It's true, isn't it? It's the
truth, bro. It is the [ __ ] truth. new.
Yeah, I was I was going to send her some
mad videos, bro.
You think I'm joking, is it, Grezy?
It's like, you know, when these crazy
people meet me, Grezy, it's like they've
met their match, isn't it?
Grezy, it's like they they they've met
their match in it. They And you know
what they do? This is another thing,
Grezy. Yeah. They take your Do you know
what they do? I was actually thinking
about this in the kitchen. Do you know
what they do? They they take your
kindness and then they use it against
you. Have you noticed that? Like they
don't not taking your kindness for
weakness, but they they try to then use
it against you.
So it's basically a trait of narcissism
because they're they're basically using
it against you. Does that make sense?
You know, like, oh, I'm not the one
sending good morning texts. I sent you a
good morning text because you were
stressed and you was [ __ ] crying and
you was almost killing yourself and then
they they're trying to use your kindness
and they're trying to use it against
you. How does how is that even possible?
You know, if someone's if someone's if
someone's at uni, yeah, these people are
supposed to be intelligent. How? So,
yeah, they will use your they'll use it
against you. That's what they do. They
use it against you and basically
um yeah just just yeah they just it's
basically they're using it against you
and what they do Greavves is then they
then start contradicting themsel
like you're telling me oh yeah just be
confident and then you're telling me oh
where did I get this confidence from so
like make up your mind like you're
constantly contradicting yourself
yeah I told her about herself as well
bro don't don't get it twisted I told
her about herself
You know, I told her straight about herself, bro.
Straight told her straight up about herself, bro.
Trust me. Like, you're you're supposed
to be I don't deem myself as
intelligent, but how am I more
intelligent than you? Come on. You
should be more intelligent than me. So,
yeah, they use it. They will use it
against you. That's why you need to be
care. It's like what you the problem
that you had, Grezy.
It's like that like I was messaging you
cuz you had issues. Do you know what I'm
saying? Like and now and now people care
and now you're trying to use it against
them. How is that possible, bro?
Doesn't even make sense.
[ __ ] [ __ ] man.
No. No. No. No. No. How's your narcissist going?
Yeah, I think that's got to be the worst
one I've come across now. I I reckon
that replaces USA is I can't lie.
I'm not even joking. I think that one's
I think that one's worse.
Yeah, that one's actually walked. I I
actually think so, bro. I think so.
Yeah, I think that's the worst one now.
So you Yeah, they they're actually worse.
They're actually worse.
They are actually worse. That is That is
crazy, bro. I never thought I'd see today.
Yeah, that's like me, bro. I want to
message them on SMS. I could easily
message them on SMS, but I'm not going
to do it, bro, cuz I just can't be [ __ ] Like,
so it seems similar to your thing, to be
honest with you.
Like they were saying that they've got
anxiety and stuff like I messaged them
because I felt sorry for them, bro.
So, how are you then going to try and
use it against people?
That is mad, Grezy. You know, the more
you actually think about it, that annoys
me, bro. That actually does annoy me.
Yeah, don't bother, bro.
Don't message them, bro. But I'm saying
that's they just use it. They use it against you.
So that's [ __ ] up, bro.
Cuz this person was generally mentally
ill. Like they weren't even trolling.
They were mentally ill.
They're obviously mentally ill in it. So
And then they trying to use it as um
Yeah, they're [ __ ] bro. They're
[ __ ] in their head, bro. They're
actually tapped. I'm not even joking, bro.
Yeah. So that's basically what happened
to you as well and it agrees. Yeah. I
see what you mean now. I see what you mean.
So they're not using your They're not
They're not taking your kindness for reason.
You They're not taking their kindness
for weakness. They're actually using it
against you. That's actually what
they're doing. That's actually what
If I've got some mentally ill person on
my phone, they're concerning me in it.
So, don't don't try and use it against people, you know.
Like I said, Grezy, this is what I'm
trying to say to you. They're so used to
talking to white knights and simps that
they can walk all over because you, how
do I explain it? There's two sides to to
me anyways. Yeah. Like, I'm normal and
nice, but I'm not going to let someone
take the piss out of me. So they will
act fake. This is what these people do.
They like to act fake. Yeah. Until they
realize you're not a [ __ ] And then they
their true colors come out. Do you get
it? Does that make sense?
[ __ ] weird. It's weird. It's it's
very weird, bro.
And they've probably done it to so many
people, but where people most people are
white knights and simps, obviously they
don't get that reaction. You get it? And
then when they meet their match, they
play victim. It happens every time. But
you said your one's a guy, Greasy. You
said your narcissist's a guy in it. Yeah.
I think I think more
I think more narcissists are women.
Greezy, to be honest with you,
I actually think more narcissists are
women. From my experience, I don't know about you.
I actually think here that like
more I actually think here
that more most more of them more women
from my experience anyways.
I generally think like honestly bro I'm
actually I actually believe that bro I
don't know about you I don't know who
you've met but I think more narcissists are women
from all of my 28 years of meeting
people I would say majority of them most are women
seriously greasy because if you meet you
know like not in a gay way yeah but when
you meet men Yeah like not in a gay way
but like say like that guy I met from Red and
and other people. You get you meet some
lovely people. Not in a gay way, bro. As
a normal way, like you meet so many
down to earth like people. Not in a gay
way, of course. You don't meet women
that are like that. Yeah. Men couldn't
Women are more heartless than men. Do
you get it? They're more They Oh, how do
I explain it? But like a man wouldn't
just block you.
Oh, it's hard to explain it. Like they
don't do the same things women do.
So obviously there were narcissist
narcissistic men. Of course there is,
bro. But majority of the ones I've come
across are women.
Nah, definitely not bisexual, bro. But
yeah, they're they're definitely um you
don't meet good women. You'll meet
normal men, but you won't meet good
women cuz they don't exist. It's like
what Antman said. But no, seriously,
most of most narcissists are women.
I could never block people and leave
people without closure. That's me. I
don't know about you, Grezy. I could
never do it. And I've ditched people in
the past. I'm saying generally. I'm
saying generally, bro. I'm not talking
about one or two or three. I couldn't do
it, bro. I generally couldn't do it.
I couldn't, bro. I I just couldn't do
it. Simple. Like that. I couldn't do it.
And I don't know many other men that
that can do it as well. So that's it.
And I'm not being biased, bro. I'm
telling you how it is. I generally don't
give a [ __ ]
They don't care if you're crying, dying.
They don't care, grievy. They'll they'll
get someone else to message you. They'll
get someone else to be the messenger. Do
you understand the point I'm trying to
make? They'll get someone else. They
don't they don't give a [ __ ] if you're
you're yelling, crying. They don't give
a [ __ ] bro.
That's how [ __ ] they are. They actually
are tapped in their head, bro.
I know two um two two guys, bro. They're
cool. You know, that guy from Redin and
that guy I met in Cardiff. And they're
actually cool people, bro. They actually
are cool people.
They're actually cool people, bro.
They're the only two people I know that
are really cool. But yeah, more
narcissists are women than men. Definitely. Cuz
the thing is, Greasy, right? They say
that women are supposed to be innocent
and all of this, but they're the mo
they're the most heartless people.
That's the bit I don't understand.
That's the bit I've never understood is
they say that, oh, all women are
innocent. They're all loving, but
they're the ones that are
like the the the most heartless with the
stuff that they do. So, it just doesn't
really make any sense to me.
That has just never made sense to me as well.
They're supposed to be the caring ones
and like not do what they do, but but
clearly they do. So, you know,
they don't care. Like me,
when this person sent me a voice note of
them crying, Greavves, I felt bad like
before like I actually I actually felt bad, bro.
Like I actually No, seriously. No, I
felt bad, Grezy. I genuinely felt bad
even though I I didn't do anything or
say anything. I'm thinking like, are you
are you okay? Whatever. Clearly, the
person don't have anyone to speak to.
And then there was someone else before
Griezy. Yeah. I said I was speaking to
this person from Scotland and I said to
them I was going to beat them up as a
joke and then they had like trauma with
their dad beating them up. I didn't know
this obviously and then I didn't know
any of this before I said it. And I
found out all that stuff, bro. I felt
bad, bro. The whole day I had to message
them. You see the difference? them. They
don't give a [ __ ] They generally don't
care about anyone but themselves.
People could cry. They could be dying.
They don't care. Simply do not care.
Um if all they had to do was give
someone closure and it took 10 seconds,
they wouldn't do it. Greasy. Doesn't
matter what um
what if someone was crying. It doesn't
matter what. They they don't care.
That's how you know they're heartless.
That's the truth, bro. As well, I can
back it up with evidence as well. You know,
there that is really really heartless,
bro. Like all it's like that whole I
hate to bring it up again, bro, but if
we if you want to use examples, bro,
like this whole um this whole USA easy
thing, it shouldn't be her friend
talking to me on the phone for 5 hours.
Just write something and dip.
What the [ __ ] So, this is another thing
you need to This is another point you
need to bring up, Grezy.
This is another thing that you have to
bring up to these white knights and
stuff when you're trying to put your point across.
The hold on a minute. You're saying that
all of these people are innocent. All
Okay. What about this that, this, that, this, that?
um this that this that this that this
that you obviously that's the point the
point you have to you know what I'm
saying and yeah they don't they wouldn't
give a [ __ ] if someone's crying or poems
and they wouldn't care bro they don't
give a [ __ ] so whereas men would I know I would
but I mean I mean but
and this is why this is what I don't
understand about why people defend You know,
now when I ditched them, remember when I
ditched them people, bro, when I was on
a date and that and there was a reason
why I ditched them, I explained myself.
I never ghosted ever.
I never ever ghosted or left people um
wondering. It's mad. It's It's [ __ ] up, bro.
But yeah, when the person um was crying
the other day, I felt bad. I'm thinking,
why are they crying, bro? What the [ __ ]
I didn't even I didn't even say
anything. They were just crying for no
reason. All I said is, "Oh yeah, you're
not going to meet anyone as good as me."
Which is the truth. That isn't That's
not even trying to manipulate you.
That's being the truth. And then someone
starts crying. What the [ __ ]
Like the only reason I was speaking to
him for a month to be honest is cuz I
felt sorry for them as well.
I don't care about sex. Like I said,
bro, I'm 28. I'm not lustful, bro. I
don't give a [ __ ] about that stuff.
Why do you think I don't go to escorts?
Because, bro, I don't need to. I don't I
can live about sex, bro. I really don't
care. I barely watch porn anymore. Like,
you you're missing the point of what I'm
trying to say, bro.
Um, they are very heartless. It would be
very it'd be very hard nowadays to find
some that someone that isn't like that.
Even Nons to be honest with you, bro.
You know when that you know when all of
that stuff was coming about with Izzy? Yeah. Yeah.
You know when all that stuff was going
on with the first Izzy? Do you remember?
And I was I don't know if you remember
this. You might have not been watching
me, but um
this is what I'm trying to say. They are mostly narcissists.
And I'm not even, bro. They Do you
remember when all that Izzy stuff was
going on with the Craig Goodston? Oh,
maybe you wasn't aware aware of my
channel back then, but when we was going
back and back and forth and back and
forth and back and forth and back and
forth. Yeah. Listen to me, bro. Yeah. I
don't know if he was This was when Cai
Mark was back on YouTube. Yeah. He
messaged me, bro, saying, "Oh, um, yeah,
like don't do anything bad. Don't kill yourself."
I'm thinking, "What the fuck?" So, we
were beefing, bro. And obviously, like
he just messaged me saying, "Oh, yeah.
Don't do anything stupid." And bear in
mind, bro, we're like enemies. We hate each other.
So, I mean,
that's [ __ ] This is what I'm trying
to say. You'd never get a woman doing
that, bro. Never ever get a woman doing that.
This is what I'm saying. This is a point
you need to bring up as well.
Maybe I'll do a video on it sometime
when I come back on YouTube. Um,
but yeah, I do remember that, bro. But
then it didn't make any sense though
because Steven Howard Yeah, he wrote
that. Yeah, he said, "Oh, don't kill
yourself over someone and stuff. He
messes he messages me on WhatsApp
because he had my number just launch."
But then it never made sense because
then when I met her, he started getting all jealous.
But the point I'm trying to make is,
bro, like I don't know how many people,
bro, have have have, you know, um, you
know, I don't know how many people have
seen me cry and ret and they just didn't care.
They simply didn't give a [ __ ] So
that's that, bro.
You know, I still do it now. You know,
if I've had bad a bad experience, I'll cry, bro.
Simple as that. I actually did, bro, the
other day. Then the other day again. I
was stressed as [ __ ] bro. But now I'm good. So,
no one cares. And that's very worrying,
lad. That's very, very worrying.
So So yeah,
men shouldn't be more
thoughtful than women. It shouldn't be
that way. It should be the other way
around. They're supposed to be the
feminine ones. They're supposed to be
the caring ones.
So you would think, right?
So you would actually think
that is just so mad to me, bro.
But yeah, and then when when Yeah. But
that that's what I found kind of weird, bro. Yeah,
I don't think I've ever found a woman
that was not like that, bro. Coming to
think of it.
All right, I me, you know, when all that
USA is thing happened, the first person
I messaged was London Taylor. Greasy.
The f the first person I messaged was
London Taylor. I said, "Oh."
I said, "This little yank broke my
heart." He was pissing himself laughing.
He said he remembers it to this day.
Yeah. He remembers the message.
It doesn't matter, bro. It doesn't matter.
So, we'll be on it all night, bro. So,
yeah. Yeah, I remember on a date with
this Indian and she never.
But yeah, that Christian Izzy is well
out of order, bro.
Well, it's actually £150 now because I
got a haircut. But yeah,
that's mad, bro.
That's actually [ __ ]
No, I'm not doing shots. [ __ ] off. I'm
not doing shots. Maybe I'll have some
baby shots. I'm not having shots, bro. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, I got a haircut earlier. I was
going to get one tomorrow, but I thought
might as well get it today. Saves me
[ __ ] around tomorrow.
Yeah. [ __ ] hell.
Nah, bro. Still got 150 of it.
I left it on the side. And I've still
got 150 on it, bro. 150. And then after
tomorrow, we're saving hard, bro. And I
won't be on it cuz I need to do stuff.
So, uh, yeah, I'll be I'll be gone for a
while, but I'll be back.
What do you say, Greavves? He shoved the
McDonald's nuggets down. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. And then after that, we have
to save. I could go out every week if I
wanted to. Can get a haircut every week
if I wanted to, but I'm not going to do
that, bro. I need to save, bro. I went
out last Monday. I got free numbers. So,
Thursday will be Yeah, I don't I don't
care about it, bro.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, they are heartless [ __ ]
Can how can they use
people's kindness against them?
But then they're very stupid because
then at the same time greasy they can't
win an argument. That's the thing is
they can't win an argument cuz I'll
wreck them. I'll wreck them. See they
deem you as below them. You see because
you're not a [ __ ] from the get- go. But
so they deem you as as not intelligent.
They deem you as somebody that they can
win an argument with, but they can't
really, bro. Because soon as you step
up, they're actually quite stupid, really.
Cuz like I said, there they don't they
don't know people have got a different
side to them. And everyone should have
this side to them as well.
They'll take the they'll do it in
different ways as well. [ __ ] they're
just [ __ ] idiots, bro.
They're actually quite sick. Really?
Yeah, that is actually quite thickening, bro.
So, why do you want to message on
narcissist? I thought it's all over. Anyways, greasy.
Yeah, I thought it was all over.
Anyone with a higher body count than five.
So, how many people do you expect a
28-year-old to sleep with?
Do you know what I want these [ __ ]
bro? In the future, the the the the
future people that I meet, like I said,
I'm going to ask them, "What have you
got to offer?"
That's what I'm going to ask. I'm going
to ask these people, Steven Howard, what
have you got to offer?
That's that's that's a good question, is
it? We hear all about the men offering
this. We all We hear all about the man
offering this, bro. Let's Let's see what
these [ __ ] have got to offer us.
That' be a good question. Yeah,
that's a good question. Yeah,
he was live earlier, bro.
Me, me, me.
laughing at you. Looking you mocking you. Um, yeah,
I was tempted to gamble today, but I didn't.
It's so tempting, you know, once your
bank once you do it, bro, you you know,
you win a little bit money, they they
try to hook you in again in it. But it
never happened, bro.
It never happened. Sure
will do. Captain,
are you messaging this narcissist? Are
you doing it via email?
I'll [ __ ] message the [ __ ] But my
ego's my ego is too big to do that, bro.
My ego is too big to do that, lad. Even
though I could put them in their place,
my ego is too big for that.
And there was little signs there as
well, bro. There was little signs there as well.
But I just ignored them in it, Grezy. I
just thought, ah, like they're
westernized, isn't it? But there was
little things there, but I just kind of
ignored it and just played it off.
Does that make sense? Like
maybe I'll do the Carolina Reaper Burger
tomorrow, Grezy. But only if that's okay
with you, boss.
Yeah, there were little bruh.
You know when you meet when you meet a
woman Greg and she starts saying bruh,
you know they're just westernized [ __ ]
You know, you know what I'm saying? When
they say bro, you just know they're westernized.
They were trying to talk about my
spelling as well.
They were trying to talk about like my
spelling and stuff. Like not spelling,
but my grammar and stuff. But we got a
smart ass over here.
Bro, do you not understand lingo?
They were westernized as [ __ ] bro. Like
watching Love Island. But then I thought
to myself like, "Oh, okay. Maybe maybe
they're just influenced, but you know,
they still could be a good person." And
that's what I was just basically like
um just just basically just giving
people the benefit of the doubt.
Do you get what I mean? Grezy.
And then they write your I said you're
saying your spelling you are.
Yeah. They're just uh uh
Yeah, that RZ is that is cringe, lad.
she says mate as well. That's another
western dude. I don't think these women
realize, Grevy, how horrible it sounds
when they say the word mate.
It sounds horrible.
But I don't even like being called mate
by a man.
And for a woman to say it, they don't
realize it's it's horrible, bro.
They don't realize how horrible it sounds,
mate. Being being called mate by a
woman. It's not good, bro. It's very masculine.
I've said it to people before, Greasy.
I'm not your [ __ ] mate.
I've said it before, bro. Like, I've
said it I've actually said it before.
I'm not your [ __ ] mate.
Being called pal is not as
is not as bad. I said it to Gre. I've
said it to Ant-Man before. I said, "I'm
not your [ __ ] mate."
cuz he doesn't he doesn't like me saying
like bless you. I always said to him,
"Oh, bless." He said, "Stop [ __ ]
saying that." And then we wind each
other up and then he calls me mate.
And yeah, we just Yeah, I said don't
call me that mate [ __ ] bro.
I can see the westernity in her eyes.
Greavesy, what do you think of that? Very westernized.
Their western eyes basically look they
look like you look you look into their
eyes and it just looks dead.
It basically there's just nothing there. This manipulation.
Do I must be a habit lad.
What did he say? These women are grievy.
Social media riddled.
Oh, I see all of them, bro. In in
London. You see all of them.
You see all of them, bro. In London. So Dusty,
I've got a question. Dusty.
So if someone's like a virgin nowadays,
people will think it's weird. But it's
not weird, is it? Because the West is finished.
Yeah. She didn't call me ugly or
anything, but she was just a [ __ ] in how
she was acting.
She says, "Oh, I like your eyebrows and
stuff. you're good-looking and stuff,
but she's a she was a [ __ ] bro. What
she was saying?
Yeah, there is.
All right. You know the thing is yeah if
I was starting how now apart from four
years ago bro I'd probably be a virgin.
I'd probably be one bro to be honest if
it was how it is now and I was starting probably.
Yeah, but that person on Reddit, Grezy,
they were saying that women are better
than men. Who the [ __ ] says that, bro?
Women are better than men.
Oh, it doesn't let me put the link up.
Who even says that? Greasy. Like, what?
Ew, a simp. It doesn't let me put the link up.
I don't like you, Mont. You're a snake, man.
Mom, I'm going to build a bear next
week. Sorry. I'm going to build a bear next week. Huh? >> Where?
>> I'm going to go to Westfield and build a bear.
>> Yep. Would you like to do it with me? Why, mom?
I'm going to win that Patrick Star toy. I'm 28. Oh, bless.
The steak was nice. [ __ ] sake.
Why don't you like you you you're you
know what you're a [ __ ] Monty. Yeah.
You say that you don't like me. I'm the
only one that's been there for you. Who
else would have went to Birmingham and
bailed you out. See, this is what these
people don't understand.
This is what these people really don't
understand, Grezy. Like they I I was
speaking to someone for a month
supporting them, then they used it against me.
I go to Birmingham to bail this [ __ ]
out. I literally went to Birmingham to
bail this bastard out and [ __ ] You
still talk [ __ ] bro. What the [ __ ]
I went to [ __ ] Birmingham and bought
you food and drinks, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
I was [ __ ] there with the whole natty
thing. I wish somebody was there for me
last week, Greavvesy. When I was sobbing,
when I was when I was sobbing last week,
no one was there, Griezy.
You don't know the half of it, lad. And
then you and then this is what I'm saying, lad.
No one was there for me.
No one was there for me, mate.
I went to Birmingham and [ __ ]
bought you stuff.
box. One second. I can't even put the
link up. I'm going to have to restart the stream.