Sorry mate. I was just on a [ __ ]
phone call with a [ __ ] friend.
Anyways, I'm going to leave you weirdos
to it anyways shortly.
Yeah, I'm going to leave you the weirdos it. See
anyways. Yeah. So, I was talking to
someone, you know,
weirdos. Like, I think these people want my ass.
Yeah, weirdos, man. No, I was talking to
someone on the [ __ ] phone. You people
are weirdos. You need to get a
life. Sorry, cut off before I wear it
cut off. You need to get off the ch and
you need to get off your life.
going desperado [ __ ] one, bro. I'm telling
you what, [ __ ] weirdo.
Yeah, weirdos. You don't know where I
live. You'll never know where I live.
You wish, mate. They haven't found me.
And even if they did found me, what are
they going to do? They're going to do
nothing. Get life, you little weirdos.
This is exactly why I come off of
YouTube last time because you all
weirdos. The police, they didn't want
nothing. The police didn't come. You all little
weirdos. This is why I'm coming off
again. You all we like you create the
same atmosphere every [ __ ] day,
lad. Yeah, [ __ ] is. That's what the
old man told
me. Was nonsense. No, the police didn't
come on my door and get a life and deal
with your obsession because I'm coming
off of YouTube again after today cuz you're all
weirdos and you need help with your
Peter belly [ __ ] obsession. You're
[ __ ] weirdos. Get a life. Get a grip.
Deal with your obsession. Deal with your
mental health, you little stalkers. You
don't know where I live and you will
never know where I live. And if you
claim so much that you do know where I
live, stop winging and come and do
something about it. You're the stalkers,
mate, not me, you know. Yeah, tool
[ __ ] is that's what the [ __ ] old
man was saying to
me. No, please. Come
on. We weren't here to knock. Get a
life, you little weirdos. You're never
going to know where I live. Get a life
and get a grip, mate. Why are you so
desperate to know where people live?
You're never going to do anything to
anyone. So, why would you even want to
know where people live? I'm leaving
YouTube anyways for a couple of weeks.
Like I said the other day, cuz your
obsession and your autism is becoming
off the scale
again. So, I'm going to be [ __ ] off
for a bit again like I was supposed to
do yesterday because it's becoming weird
again. It's becoming very very very very weird
again. This obsession and this stalking
is becoming very very weird
again, you know. Oh, did he? That's good
for him. Anyways, um yeah, it's becoming
very very very weird again. Nope, I'm
not staying live until quarter 2. I'm
leaving and I'm not coming back for a
couple of weeks. So, you can say you've
run whatever. Yeah, good for you. I'm
I'm leaving for a couple of weeks like I
was supposed to do yesterday. So, get a
grip, get a life. Um, if you people
really claim you know where I live when
you don't know where I live, you can
come to any address you think I'm at.
And yeah, you have my permission. You
won't need YouTube to do that, will you?
Get a [ __ ] life. You little weirdos. Little
stalkers. Little [ __ ] This is what I
don't want to be like, bro. Honestly,
when I'm your people's ages, you all
weirdos. Oh, he's going to my door at 2.
That's nice. He doesn't know where I
live, so that's not going to happen.
Yeah, I'll enjoy my time off. I noticed
this as well. You come on YouTube,
right, for one day and it's like, oh
man, okay, one day, yeah, we're
refreshed. Second day, it's like, and
then it's the same atmosphere. I've
noticed that. I literally noticed that
it's the same atmosphere, the same
talking, the same projection every
[ __ ] day. And it's and it's the same
on on um certain channels. It's the same
atmosphere. Like even when you see other
people typing, it's a [ __ ] community. I
actually I actually feel like them.
Yeah, you bullied me off YouTube. Good
for you, man. Keep telling yourself
that. You're not going to get me back
on. Nice try though. It's the same
atmosphere, the same mongos, the same
spastics. It's literally the same
spastics every day. I'm not even joking.
It's so weird. Oh my
god. It's a proper [ __ ] community,
isn't it? Autism. I'm telling you, it's
autism. It's the same thing as I said to
Lord Lord Jay in the live stream. I was
like, you're saying that I've got
anxiety. You're the one that don't even
leave your house. You're the one that
sits in all day talking to these weirdos
on a Saturday. It's weird, man. It's
proper weird autistic and and repeating
it. I can't explain it. No, I can't
explain it. It's hard to explain what
it's just a bunch of people in their
late 30s, late 40s that hate their life
and they just come on here and project
because they're sad with their
lives. Yeah. Yeah. You'll be on my door
at 2 p.m. You don't know where I live.
Yeah, exactly. Jealousy. Of course
they're jealous of my looks and my
money. Why do you think they come on
here every day hating every single day?
You're coming on my door. Yeah, good
luck with that one. You don't know where
I live. So you'd have to find out where
first. You don't know where I [ __ ]
live. So congratulations. Yeah, you try
that anyways, buddy. You don't know
where I live. Yeah, all of my clothes
are even at my [ __ ] moms. Does that
mean I live at my mom? You don't know
where I live. And even if you knew where
I live, you still wouldn't do
nothing. So why are you doing all of
this weirdo [ __ ] Because you're never
going to do anything. You're weirdos, man.
You know, I could understand if somebody
was actually really going to [ __ ]
pull up, but they're not. They're
weirdos. They're skint little rejects on
YouTube every day, sad with their lives.
And when I'm off of YouTube for weeks,
I'm going to come off YouTube for a
couple of weeks. And when I come back,
I'm going to show you, Barry, that it's
these people that ain't got the life.
They're on YouTube again. They're on
YouTube again. Yeah. Weirdos. Absolute
weirdos. They can't troll to save their
life. Yeah. Remember my friend told me,
"You should be a psychologist." He said
to me, "You should be a psychologist." I
said, "Yeah, I know. I'm quite smart,
aren't I?" We talking about celebrities
and stuff. He's like, "You should be a
psych." See, I don't know about these
people. And I know about these [ __ ]
people. They ain't got a [ __ ] life
stalking people, trying to find where
people live. They don't even know where
I live. And why are they even trying to
find where you live? Do they want your
ass? What is it that they want your ass
crack or something? Do they want to
stick Do they want to [ __ ] you or
something, bro? These people [ __ ]
stalking me again. I'm coming off of
YouTube, bro. For a couple of weeks.
These people stalking me. Yeah. I told
them that I ordered a fridge. I ordered
it to an address I don't even live at.
Yeah. Just like all of my [ __ ]
clothes are like my mom's. And they're
stalking me, bro. These little
stalkers, you know? I was just on the
[ __ ] phone to one of them as well.
I'm leaving. I'm gone for my own safety. They're [ __ ]
weirdos. They're absolute weirdos. Like
they take jealousy to the next level.
It's weird. [ __ ] weirdos, man. Mate,
if I live there, Yeah. they managed to
run me off of YouTube. You don't run me
off of YouTube because why do I always
come back? Yeah. Me coming on YouTube,
not arguing with you people is not
giving you little rejects what you want.
Me coming on here arguing with you is
what you little rejects want and you're
not getting it. And you're not getting
it. Yeah. A new fridge. And you're not
getting it. Because what you people are,
your lives are empty. Bro, if you knew
where I if you knew where I lived, I'd
invite you all around. I'd invite all
these haters round. I would literally be
like, "Come on. Come on. Come on. I
would invite all of these haters around
because I know they don't even leave the
house cuz they've got
anxiety. I would say yes, I live there.
Come on. That's what I would say, you
know. Yeah, he's going to my door. He
doesn't know where I live. And if he
does ever find out where I live, he's
getting a hammer through his [ __ ]
skull. Simple. He ain't going on no
one's door. Yeah. Because he will be
getting a hammer through his [ __ ]
skull, through his eye.
Yeah, get off of YouTube. Stop [ __ ]
stalking me and take the [ __ ] same
[ __ ] break as I'm [ __ ] taking. Get
off of YouTube and leave me the [ __ ]
alone. You [ __ ] little
weirdos. Absolute stalking little [ __ ]
weirdos. Yeah. You know what? Not even a
[ __ ] hammer. Yeah. If he really finds
out where I live, bro, I've got a I've
got I've got a I've got a weight
barbell, bro, that could go through his
skull right to his back. Yeah, simple.
No one's going on no one's door. Just
like when I actually did live in that
address, he never came on the door even
though he said he did. Get off of
YouTube. Change the atmosphere. Change
the vibe and get a
life. Yeah. No, no, no, no. I am. But
they're weirdos. They're weirdos.
They're [ __ ] weirdos. They're
absolute [ __ ] weirdos. Why are these
weirdos so jealous of me? They come on
here and they hate on me every single
day. Yeah, it's a
madness. Nah, I need to get off of
YouTube and stop entertaining you [ __ ]
weirdos. I need to stop entertaining
because it's a [ __ ] disabled downy
community that creates the same
atmosphere. That's what it is, bro.
2 p.m. Oh, that's that's a that's that's
going to be hard, isn't it? Because he
doesn't know where I live. So, this will be
interesting. It's the same atmosphere.
It's been going on since [ __ ]
December as well with these little
mongos. Get to [ __ ] life. Get off of [ __ ] YouTube. Simple.
Yeah. And that's [ __ ] it. You're
weirdos. Absolute weirdos. I'm sure
you're you're homosexuals. There's
nothing wrong with being a homosexual.
Yeah. Yeah. Yes. Bro, listen. Listen,
listen, listen, listen, listen, listen.
N. Well, then come and do something
about it then. They keep going for me
because they're jealous of me. I've got
more money than them. I'm better looking
than them, you know? It's always the
same thing. That's why they go for me,
bro. You know what I'm saying? Because
they're jealous of
me, you know?
That's what it is. It's jealousy. Look
at all of these people on here, bro.
There's nothing wrong with being gay.
There's I listen, there's nothing wrong
with being a gay. I was talking to an
old man today and they said that they're
trying to get him removed from his house
because he's gay, right? So, um even
though he's not gay, they're trying to
accuse him of being gay. I was like,
well, there's nothing wrong with being
gay, but what these people do on here,
it suggests that they are gay. Uh,
they've got to be jealous of me for them
to do this every single day. They You've
got something they don't have. I'm
telling you, bro. I'm telling you,
jealousy is a disease. Just like
nonslegs, he's jealous of me. Jealous of
the women that I I get. It is jealousy.
It is a [ __ ] disease. You have to
understand jealousy. Look, you just told
someone you bought a new fridge. They're
all getting jealous. They can't afford a
fridge because they're all skin. That's
a point I'm trying to make.
That's a point I'm trying to make. These
people in their 40s, they ain't got a
pot to piss in. You understand? See it
from their point. See it from their
point of view. Their lives, lad. They've
got nothing. Despite calling other
people, what bang in the background?
There was no bang in the
background. Is it a good fridge? It's a
[ __ ] It's a normal mini fridge,
bro. [ __ ] £100. And they're getting
jealous because they're all Bro, listen. these
people. You need to get a life and get a
hobby. Isn't there anything you want to
watch in the cinema or something? Have
you got nothing better to do with your
[ __ ] day than sat on YouTube stalking
people? Nothing. Literally nothing. Is
there nothing you've got better to
do? That's a serious [ __ ] question I'm asking
you. Weirdos. [ __ ] weirdos.
You're weirdos, mate. You don't remember
that time in [ __ ]
Newcastle. Get a [ __ ] life. Oh my
god. Weirdos. Absolute weirdo. I've
never known. I feel You know what?
Sometimes I feel famous, you know,
because people that only have that many
haters or people that are
famous, you know? Sometimes I feel like
[ __ ] Eminem, you know, or Michael
Jackson. I actually do.
No, it doesn't matter whether you react
to it or not because even if you don't
react to these people, they still do it.
No, no, no, no, no. Because even when
you don't react to these people, they
still do it. They will still do it. You
could be off of YouTube for a whole
year. Yeah. Not react to any of these
people and they would still do it. They
do it to Timmy for
reaction. Yeah. He's all did a takeaway.
Oh, good for him. Nobody cares. He
doesn't know where I
live. So that's a good thing, bro. Yeah,
congratulations. You don't know where I
live, but you can order whatever you
want, whenever you
want. One second.
Oh [ __ ] Sorry man. I got
disconnected. Nope. There was no knock
again. Grow up. Stop this. We've been
through all of this before. Someone's
coming on your door when they don't know
where you live. We've been through this
before. I just got disconnected. I went
in somewhere. Sorry. No, grow up. It's
It's time you people started to grow the
[ __ ] up. And that's actually coming for
me. That's me saying that. Yeah. You
need to grow up. All of this stuff. Oh,
someone's going to come on your door
does not give me one bit of anxiety. It
does not bother me. What you people do
on here every day. It does not bother
me. It's like when people come on here
and say, "Oh, they do it to
psychologically [ __ ] with you." They
don't [ __ ] with my head. They don't
psychologically [ __ ] with my head. But
what they do do is they bore me. I tell
you what these people do do. They bore
the living [ __ ] out of me. They bore me
more than watching the same film over
and over and over again. You can bear
this community three days maximum.
Literally three days maximum. you can
bear this community and that's it. And
then you stop for like a week, two week,
3 week, come on. And by the third day,
it's the same [ __ ] again. Because like
the old saying goes, you are you are um
what you um what you socialize with. So
when you socialize with [ __ ] morons,
you become a [ __ ] like them. Do you
understand? Cuz when you're off it,
you're like, "Oh, life's a bit normal.
It's a bit uh yeah, it's it's all
right." And as soon as you come back,
it's the same atmosphere. I can't
explain it. It's just like a
weird creepy stalking atmosphere. I
can't I can't I can't even explain it.
I'm not even going to attempt to explain
it. Like why don't I go out and send it?
Because I'm on a
detox and I'm done with women for a bit.
I'm not asked. I'm on a detox for like
another two weeks. And I sent it on
Tuesday. I went out Tuesday. Oh, you
didn't hear. I went out on Tuesday.
Yeah, I went out on Tuesday and [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Give me whatever
you say, buddy. Um, yeah. I went out on
Tuesday. I sent it and [ __ ] I'm not going out
until Yeah, bro. Um, like I said, I'm on
a detox, so I'm done for a bit. Done for
a little bit,
lad. Detox skin. Oh boy. And this is
exactly what I'm saying. You know, when
you come back on here, you'll see the
same comments, the same comments every
day. Same self-effected every
day. Yeah. So, I sent it on Tuesday
and and yeah, it was [ __ ] So, I'm going
to detox anyways. Got to go on holiday
soon. I've got some stuff to do. So, and
I'm going to cinema Friday as well. So,
good to have I had a beer today
actually, but I mean I'm still detoxing.
I just fancy the
beer. I can't be [ __ ] with women, bro,
at the moment. Must stay today. Yeah. [ __ ]
[ __ ] Haven't decided yet. Not decided
yet. He's getting me banned from the
Weather Spoons in Stratford. Oh, is he?
Good for him because I don't go to that
Weather Spoons and even if I did which I
don't whenever I go out I never go to
Stratford because a I never did when I
lived there and b I don't live there. So
keep clutching at straws you will listen
you re you do realize right in London if
you get somebody banned from one place
you do realize there's like a million
and one other places to go to and
there's also the street like it just
goes to show that LJ is the one that has
this anxiety. He doesn't go out. He
doesn't socialize. He's sat at home nine
albums on Saturday talking to a bunch of
people that scared to leave the house.
Come on, bro. It's boring. It's [ __ ]
boring, you know. So, yeah. It's [ __ ]
up, man. It's proper [ __ ] up. You're
going to get me banned from the Weather
Spoons in Stratford. Oh, yeah. Good for
you, man. Don't do that. Yeah. No one
cares. Yeah. Yeah. Madness, bro.
I think you people need to get a life.
That's what I think. I generally think
you people need to get off of YouTube
and get a life. Like, you need to follow
what I do in a second. In a second, you
need to follow what I do. Get off of
YouTube and [ __ ] literally wait.
Literally get up. Yeah. Yeah. He's
definitely autistic because all of this
like stalking men. And I get it. I bro,
I get if you're trying to find where
someone lives. Yeah. so you can go and
do something. But bro, even if you
actually knew where I lived, you still wouldn't do
anything. They will send they can send
letters again. They don't know where I
live. They don't know where I live, they
can send letters all they want. They
don't know where I live. And do you know
what? Even if they did know where I
live, which they wouldn't, they don't. I
don't care. They can do what they want.
They don't bother me. They can crack on
when I'm offer this YouTube, right? When
I'm off this, they can crack on. Keep
thinking they know where I live. They
can send whatever the [ __ ] they want. I
don't care. They don't know where I
live. Tell them. I I always say to
Trumodor, send a million letters. Nobody
cares. You don't know where I live. And
even if you did know where I live, I
still wouldn't care.
Simple, you know. So, yeah. And also,
you you you'd be sending it to the wrong
area because anyways, I don't even live
in Statford. Also, all of the all of the
people in Stratford, like the neighbors
and stuff, right? They they all know about
me. They literally all know about me.
The house has been broken into. People
know me on that road when I last went
there. They know about me. They know
what I'm about with this YouTube. So,
even if you did that and I was living
there, which I'm not, they wouldn't
care. Nobody gives a
[ __ ] you know?
You know what I'm saying? Like that's
it, bro. You can send what you want. I
don't give a [ __ ] You don't know where
I live. Think of it. Yeah. The reason I,
bro, with the mom thing, I had beef with
the neighbor. Yeah. It wasn't the
letters that that why I left that house.
It was because I had beef with the
neighbor and the neighbors talk. Bit
like where that old man lives. It wasn't
the posters. This was two weeks before
posters. Yeah. So, but yeah, that he is
definitely definitely definitely that lo is definitely
autistic cuz he always comes from his
live streams. The same
autism. So, let them, bro. Let them send
who they want when they want. I don't
give a flying [ __ ] [ __ ] They will
never know where I live. And that's what
it is. They want to know where people
live so they can try to control their
life. It's autism. They're not going to
ever come and do anything to anyone. You
know what I'm
saying? So, and as as and and and as
you're saying about the reaction
ghosting, no, because even if you don't
react to these people, they still do it.
So, it doesn't make sense. Even if you
don't react to these people for a
year. Yeah. They let them send whatever
they want. They don't know where I
live. Yeah. They don't know where I
live. So, it's nice. They can do
whatever they want whenever they want.
No one cares. They don't know where I
live. And even if they did know where I
live, I still wouldn't care. So done.
Simple. These people need to get a life
and get off of YouTube and sort out
their [ __ ] jealousy disorder and
[ __ ] get laid. Cuz I'm telling you,
bro, more than half these people on here
now, I'm starting to think they are [ __ ]
virgins. Barry, every day they're coming
here calling me skin. I didn't know
these people knew my personal bank
account. I didn't know they were my
personal [ __ ] bank manager. No,
they're not. So why do they come on here
calling people skin? Because they're
skin themselves. Like the these people
come on here every day calling people
disabled, calling people all of these
negative things, running this person
down, running that person down. Have
they ever took took a look at their own
lives? I was I was saying I I saw this
kind saying, "Oh, Lisa, there was Lisa,
there was [ __ ] there was me." I hold
on a minute. Right. Yeah. Have a look at
your own [ __ ] life. You can't take
one day off of YouTube. Look at your own
lives before [ __ ] judging
others. You know what I'm
saying? They are skinned little
self-projecting little munters. Yeah.
And you know what it's and and and you
know the maddest thing about it is they
call me a bun. Yeah. I've had more women
than them. I have more money than them.
I've got a better life than them. But
I'm the skin bun. Well, that's funny.
And and then when you tell these people
right to put their cameras on, none of
them can do it. They're [ __ ] absolute
[ __ ] mongos. They really really
really really are. He's 5 minutes away.
Is he? Oh, that's nice for him,
buddy. Yeah. Is he 5 minutes away? Is
that supposed to scare me? I thought it
was quart two. I thought it was quart 2.
You told me to wait until quart 2.
Anyways, I'm coming off of this
community now and I'm having a life
because I've got a life unlike you
people. So, I'll catch you in about two, three
weeks. And yeah, well, actually, we'll
wait a minute. Sorry, cuz you told me to
wait a certain time. We've been live
[ __ ] almost half an hour. Get some
help because you most definitely
definitely definitely need it. Get off
of YouTube and get a life and stop being
obsessed with people you're [ __ ]
jealous of. Right. One minute in a
bit. See? Yep. In a bit. Wait. One, two,
three, four. I'm out of here. Bye-bye.
See you in about 2 3 weeks. You repeating