And yeah, LT, if you're watching this,
this is proof that uh this [ __ ] is a
[ __ ] keyboard warrior. Another
keyboard warrior. I thought you said,
"Oh, this guy's about this. This guy's
about that, mate. He's been emailing me.
This little batty crease, little [ __ ]
little bully victim has been emailing
me, bro, for the past
[ __ ] half hour. He's a weirdo, bro.
He ain't about nothing.
He ain't about nothing. Kimmani's soft
disabled family. Look, he claims that he
knows where people live. I've told him
come about a million times. He is a
keyboard warrior just like the rest of
them. Terry de Manta is nothing but a
keyboard warrior bully victim that got
bullied out of his own area by me and
everybody saw it. Like, I don't know why
people still entertain this clown. Stop
[ __ ] emailing me, you little gay boy.
You gay little bully victim that got
bullied out of his own area. You little
[ __ ] You and your [ __ ] family. Stop
emailing me, you [ __ ] little stalker.
Yeah, I'm surprised PE the likes of LT
would actually socialize with you.
You're not about nothing. You're a
keyboard warrior. Yeah. You might be
London by name, mate, but you're not
snow [ __ ] London. Yeah. You're not
about anything. You're a keyboard
warrior. You are a keyboard warrior. Do
you think you could take anyone serious?
Yeah. When all they're doing is typing
via email, you're a keyboard warrior
bully victim. Have a word with yourself.
Go sort out your [ __ ] disabled looks
and your [ __ ] ugly
trainers. You're saying, "Oh, I know
where you are. I know where you are,
bro. Why don't you come then? Stop
emailing me. Why don't you come with
your whole family? If apparently you
know where I am, I've told you several
times, go and suck your family. And LT
has said these words you can't be saying
about people. Terry, go and suck your
family. And you're not going to do
anything. So stop emailing me, you
little batty boy. You little batty boy [ __ ] Little
[ __ ] grip and stop emailing me, you little keyboard
warrior. It's mad because LT hates these
kind of people, but he socializes with
you. You're a [ __ ] You keep saying
you know where I live. You don't know
where I live. If you so much know where
I live, why don't you come now then? Why
don't you come now then? Bad man. You
and your family, why don't you come now
then? instead of emailing me for the
past half an hour. Come now. I don't
understand what you're waiting for,
bro. You know, you're stalking me.
You're emailing me. You're trying to
tell me you know where I live, bro. You
got bullied out of your own area. Last
time you started this, you made me come
to your area and you ran away. You ran
away, you little [ __ ] with your pip
trainers, remember? and you're still
emailing me, which makes me surprised
why LT even socializes with you. He
doesn't like your kind. And you're the
same kind as these people. You might be
London by name, mate, but you're just
the same as all of these little
northerners. Stop emailing me and stop
the empty threats. You do not bother
anybody. You do not scare anybody. I
will wait up all night for you,
bro. Yeah. You don't leave me paranoid.
You don't worry me one little bit. I'm
just on here saying how much of a
keyboard warrior you are. You know, I've
I've been hearing from LT, your family's
hard, Terry. Go and suck your ugly
family and you're going to do nothing.
But guess what? I done something. I went
to your area and I made you use excuses.
I bullied you out of your [ __ ] own
area. Have you got no shame? I came to
your area and I made you not meet me.
How embarrassing is that? And this is
why I don't understand how LG can talk
to somebody like you, mate. You're a 4
foot tall [ __ ] monker. You got no
balls. Why don't you come and meet me
now? Come and meet me now with your ugly
family and I'll put a hammer through
every single one of their faces. Come
with your ugly stinking family and stop
saying how you're about this, you're
about that, you're about this. Come with
your [ __ ] family. I'll be waiting for you,
bro. [ __ ] you and [ __ ] your sides of
London and [ __ ] your family. My My words
mean nothing. Listen, you've been
emailing me for the past half an hour.
Do you want to go or not? Do you want to
come and get your head smashed in or
not? I will wait for you. Simples. Do
you want to go now? Yes or no? Come on.
Let's go. Let's go. And if you don't,
you're a keyboard warrior. So then I
would have no idea why LT wants to talk
to you. Terry, meet me now. Get your
head smashed in now. Stop typing, big
man, and come now. Yeah, you've been
emailing me with your [ __ ] [ __ ]
self with your stinking trailers, you
ugly [ __ ] Come on
now. You know, come now and stop being a
keyboard warrior. Stop being a keyboard
warrior. And that's all you are. You're
a keyboard warrior, you know. And and I
and I hope LT is watching this so he
knows exactly what you are. You're
nothing but a keyboard warrior. Trying
to tell LT, "Oh, I know this person. I
know this person." You are nothing but a
keyboard warrior. Just like Arsenal
Mark, just like Shan, you're all the
same bully victims. You would never say
boo to a goose. You're living your worst
life. Listen, you're emailing me for
[ __ ] half an hour because I'm living
in your head rentree. You're
embarrassing. Get a grip. Have a word
with yourself. Same thing as I said to Laur.
Yeah. You're trying to say how you know
this person, bro. You do not know no
one, bro. Yeah. Come and meet me now and
I'll slap 25 shades of [ __ ] out of you.
Yeah. In front of everybody on YouTube.
But you can't. You know, your life's
empty, Terry. You're probably a little
virgin, you know. You're probably the
same as everyone on L J's channel. A sad
little virgin. You ain't got nothing in
your life. Yeah. You don't laugh at me.
You laugh at yourself. Look at it. Look
at the evidence. Right. Let's look at
the evidence. You wear pip trainers.
You're 4 foot tall. You ran away from
me. You're laughing at yourself. You're
the biggest laughing stock. If somebody
ran me out of my area, mate, oh my
[ __ ] god, I would be so embarrassed,
mate. You laugh at yourselves, Terry.
You're skinn. You're single. You're 4
foot tall. You got [ __ ] shitty ass
trainers. You got no money. You can't
even come and sort me out. You're
laughing at yourself, buddy. Stop
emailing me, you little batty boy. You
little [ __ ] batty boy, bro.
[ __ ] Yeah, you're a [ __ ] You and
everybody, you know, bro, you're a [ __ ]
your area and you said that you was on
probation. Take that L, little boy. And
I'm blocking your emails as well now, buddy. Bye-bye now.
Sadd Stop emailing me, you little
[ __ ] You little bully victim. Stop
[ __ ] emailing me, you [ __ ] You
know, absolute [ __ ] bro. I swear to
God. I'm starting to think this Terryy's
jealous of me. You know, the more and
more Yeah. these people do this, the
more and more they come across as
jealous. You know that? The more and
more they do this, like the emailing,
the repeating, the more and more I'm
thinking they're jealous of me, bro. I'm
I'm not even joking. And these people
are older than me, the more I'm thinking
about it as well. Empty lives, just like
the people on LJ's channel. They're all
their lives are empty. Their lives are
[ __ ] You know what I'm
saying? It's a madness,
bro. You don't know where I am, and you
will never know where I am. And you
shouldn't want to know where I am either
because even if you knew where I was,
you ain't about to do nothing. So shut up,
man. Yeah, I'm blocking this [ __ ] weirdo
as emailing me like some sort of batty,
man. Bro, [ __ ] off, man. You
weirdo. You sad little bully victim. Get
off of YouTube and go get later. Go get
yourself some new trainers. [ __ ]
[ __ ] Absolute [ __ ]
[ __ ] of life. You're a keyboard
warrior. Why does LT even speak to you?
You're a keyboard warrior. You know what
I'm saying? You're nothing but a keyboard [ __ ]
warrior. A battery man, bro.
Yeah. Get a life.
Jealousy is a disease,
mate. Jealousy is a horrible disease. I
hope you don't I hope I hope some of you
people that are watching this don't have
it, bro. How do I block this [ __ ] Hold
on. [ __ ] [ __ ] man. Absolute
How do you do
it? Yeah. Go away, you little
stalker. [ __ ] absolute stalkers on
the You know, that's the most weirdest
thing about this community is the stalking, bro.
Weirdo, man. Absolute weirdo. Go get a
grip, you [ __ ]
sabot. You're in your 40s, mate. Coming
on here trying to bully people, but you
only bully yourself. You get bullied
every day. Imagine that, bro. The seams
on it. Get a grip. Get a [ __ ] life,
Terry. You [ __ ]
weirdo. Absolute weirdo. Go sort out
your jealousy disorder and your stalking
disorder. Bye-bye now. If I get