Oh, [ __ ]
yeah. There we go. Yeah, [Music]
man. That drunk, bro. Not going to lie. didn't even get that drunk.
Oops. What you saying, bro? needs to
man before I pop my little uh Hey,
before I pop my little head here, you
know, this is what I do occasionally.
The fridge looks sick, by the way.
Sorry, man. I had to
uh had to point that out. The fridge is looking
Hey, the fridge is [Music]
looking. It's looking sick,
bro. Got all filled up and a
zippy. Yeah, it is. [Music] Bye-bye. Bye-bye. Now,
bye-bye. Any genuine
people? No. people that get theirel
theirelves confused with
me, you know, none of that [ __ ] Thank
you. A [ __ ] alcohol detox and an
approach detox, but yeah, ended today,
man. I was in the mall sending it,
sending it. Yeah, it's
[ __ ] Yeah, it was long, man.
But we save loads of money by
drinking. Uh it's getting worse. It is
definitely definitely getting
worse. It is definitely getting worse.
This country and the the modern women,
I'm telling you,
bro, it is getting
worse. Getting worse. I mean, we got
three numbers. Like, I was early for the
film. So, cuz I was early for the film,
I thought, "Fuck it. Do these approaches in the
[ __ ] round the shopping center, bro.
I must have known that about [ __ ]
10." And this is why it's bad. And then
I done 10 approaches. I was like, "Fuck
that, bro. We don't take no L's." And I
found some alcohol that I had. I didn't
even realize I had it. It was on top of
the fridge. And I thought, "Fuck it.
We'll just go out and just send it." It was madness,
bro. It's actually [ __ ]
madness. Actually [ __ ] madness, bro.
So, I stuck the alcohol in the [ __ ]
fridge, but I need to save now. Like, proper, bro.
Like, to be fair, escort cinema all
that. It didn't cost them a lot today.
We saved drinking. So, we got three numbers
anyways. [ __ ] yeah, we played
Frankie. That was [ __ ] That's the
That's the most expensive thing was
Frankie today and then
this No, I was just drinking today, man.
I went up I had a good day to be fair.
It was actually a good
day. Done a done approaches in the mall,
went to the cinema, drunk, got free
numbers, got a [ __ ] escort, played
Frankie, and I only spent about 180,
200. So, I mean, I had a good day.
So that literally is me
now for a few
weeks. Oh [ __ ] It
was It's too hard,
lad. Well, you're you're talking to
me. You're talking to me and you're
gone. So you're not talking to me no
more. Bye-bye now.
But yeah, it's [ __ ] up, bro. It's
up. Country [ __ ] The the
the horror film I give it a six out of
10. I thought it was going to be a lot
better. Yeah, it was okay. It was
okay. Yeah. And and the thing is, bro,
like I sat here thinking
Yeah. Like cuz obviously when I was off
drinking for two weeks, I had a long
thought about things I should do and
things I shouldn't do. But I was just
like I I was saying to myself like it's
mad. Like you're 27. Like you should be
married. You should have a child by now.
Like that's what I was actually saying
to myself and where societyy's so [ __ ]
up. I was like, "Bro, like it's mad cuz
obviously I was stable and I bought this
bridge and I was like I was actually
lying there thinking to myself, this is
insane, bro. Like it's only getting
worse. It's only only getting worse, you
know? It's like I couldn't help but but
um I couldn't help but let it bother me
sort of thing.
You know what I'm
saying? And obviously I went out
approaching in the mall whilst waiting to go cinema, you
know. So yeah, it's bad. This country is bad,
lad. Yep. In a big 2025, bro, where
everyone pretends they got boyfriends. I
actually done a lot of approaches today.
Hey, I got free numbers. I actually done
so many approaches. I actually sent it.
It is so hard. I don't I don't know how
people do it. Well, most people nowadays don't do
Yeah. Yeah. It's hard, man. They're like
NPCs. They literally are like NPCs.
Like, you see the same men everywhere.
You see the same women everywhere.
They're literally the same
westernized NPCs. And obviously because
I done them approaches in the mall, I
felt like I had to go out and get a
number. So it's all it's all [ __ ] up
though. It is all [ __ ]
up. Yeah, it's
mad. Yeah, it's sad, bro. It's mad. Me
and that man on it today. Obviously not
together, but yeah, it's sad. Yeah. Yeah,
bro. Some of that's [ __ ] stable as
well. It's [ __ ] up. Bye-bye. So,
yeah. It's [ __ ] up, bro. It's [ __ ] up.
What do you do?
Eh, this country is a double negative.
Yeah, I reckon it's definitely got worse
since the past two year. since the past two years. Maybe
maybe definitely definitely. Well, I
think it has. And I've got a lamb
vindaloo as well, but now I'm hungry again. Yeah.
There. [ __ ] man.
Oh, I thought I knew this guy to be fair. One
second. Maybe he's from the same
country. I don't know. Well,
that we've got a few different ages
today. So, they're all in different categories.
But I was planning to like never drink
again. Don't really disappoint in
it. [ __ ] be depressed tomorrow.
[ __ ] a virgin, bro. You know what I mean? Yeah.
Yeah. Sean, your autism is very bad
again, you little virgin. You need to
get off of YouTube, buddy. It's no good
for your mental health. You need to get
off of YouTube and get
laid. Your autism's off the
scale again. Baddy boot. Okay, [Music] January. January.
I'm all back on YouTube, by the way. Good. Yeah. [Music]
Your autism is off the scale, buddy. Really
is. Morgan Williams. Who's that?
Put him down.
You need to go get laid.
Seriously, get off of YouTube and go get
laid. Like seriously,
man. Seriously need to lose your virginity.
See, you should get
laid. Going to watch some
Inbetweeners. Yeah. Do you know what? I
I remember mentioning it mean this to
Sean when I used to meet him. when I
used to meet that virgin and he used to
say, you know, I watched it a few times,
but it's just overexaggerated. Like that
doesn't happen in school. Yeah. No [ __ ]
Sherlock. It's a TV
show. Yeah, it's a TV show, buddy. No,
of course it's not real [ __ ] life.
It's not even
relatable. Them situations are not even
Even back in
2010, he said it's it's uh it's not at
all anything like real life. Yeah, it's a TV
show. Just like the Big Bang Theory,
it's a TV
show. Literally, it's a TV show. He was
like, "Oh, well, yeah. Um, you don't get
women come to your house. That's not the
way life works. You got Bills and stuff
again saying that a woman's fit to fit
in. See, it's all a trend with Shan.
It's like the Chevel Cole thing. He used
to say that she was good-looking, so
people didn't think he was gay cuz he
used to get picked on in college. Yeah.
It's It's not real. The inbetweeners are
not real. That's why it's far-fetched.
It's a TV show. It's a TV
show. [ __ ] virgin. It's a TV show. Of
course he's not [ __ ] real. You
[ __ ] virgin. Oh my [ __ ] god. Go
get laid, you virgin. You'd get some
[ __ ] life experience if you [ __ ]
finally did. If you finally pop that
cherry, you finally pop that V card. [ __ ]
hell. I never used to keep mentioning
Sher Cole. I mentioned Sher Co a few
times because people kept going on about
it. You literally were saying that she's
good-looking to fit
in. Literally just to fit in. Imagine
that. What a loser. You were saying that
she's good looking to fit in. I've had
more women than you and you still call
me gay, you [ __ ]
virgin. But the thing is, if her name
was not Cheryl C, he literally wouldn't
say that. He literally would not say
that. It's the name. It's literally the
name. It's not It's not even a person.
It's the [ __ ] name. He's copying.
They even They even say on the in
between, Sher Cole. He's literally
copying. You're a little
copycat. I called you that as well a few
years ago. You're a
copycat. You're literally a
copycat. You copycat.
Yeah, you are a copycat. There's no
originality that comes from you at all.
You know, the only reason you said about
uh the only reason you like Elvis
Presley is because you saw yourself in
him. You like
kids. He likes kids. He liked
kids and you like
kids. That's the only That's the only
reason you you like him. [ __ ]
virgin. That's literally that's that
that's literally the only
reason I mean it is it is a TV
show. It is a TV show, buddy.
saying Spongebob [ __ ] Squarepants isn't
real. Anyway, skin boy, how comes you've
never been abroad? You little skin
flint. How comes you've never
been? Bye-bye. How comes you've never been abroad
anyways? What's going on with that
one? You scared you got no money. Skin thing. Faster level virgin. Here
come you said to me to sleep. [Music]
You should have been to sleep. [ __ ] hell.
Nah, I lost 150 today, bro. So, my day
went like this.
Yeah, I went to the mall to watch this
woman in the yard. [ __ ] film, by the
way. I thought it was going to be better
than it was. And obviously, I was about
an hour early. So, I went and done some
approaches even though I was on alcohol
detox and and approaching detox. So, I done these
approaches. [ __ ] nothing. Literally
no nothing, bro. I was sending it and I
went to see the film and I come back. I
was like, I I need to send it today,
bro. Now I found some alcohol on top of
the old fridge. Then I put in the new
fridge, then went out, sent it, got
three numbers. Didn't spend anything
because I bought the alcohol with me. Got an
escort, which was £60. Then I went to
play Frankie, lost 150, got a vinderoo and I'm back. So
yeah, yeah, that virgin lad. So all in
all, it was a bad day and a good day. I
mean, cuz obviously I lost 150, but if
it wasn't for that, I would barely spend
nothing today. It's all about budgeting
your money, bro. I don't want to waste
money in this country. It's [ __ ] but at
the same time, I'm bored and, you know,
I need to try and meet some new women.
Even though, to be honest, they're all
the same. So, they're all
NPCs. It's like, yeah,
bye-bye. But yeah, bro, I sent it today.
You know what I was thinking, bro? Yeah,
cuz obviously I was off the booze for
like two weeks. Got this fridge sorted,
started doing shopping now. Like, I'm
more stable. I think it's kind of
[ __ ] bro. Like, and this is actually
a stable mind thinking this like 27.
Yeah. You know, you should be married.
You You should have children. You know,
you should be with someone. You know,
everything else in your life is pretty
good. You know, you get money, you got
money, you're stable. You know, there's
a lot of worries you don't have that
other people have. And that's coming
from a stable mind. So I know that when
people say that oh you need to be happy
with yourself it's [ __ ] because you
know you you know there's people you can
be happy with yourself happy more than
happy more than complete with yourself
and you know you'll still want I don't
know kids sex or marriage so it doesn't
matter what where you are in your life
and I can tell you that for nothing bro
I want like a huge detox do [ __ ]
when people say
Yeah. So fellas lie about
before. So then yeah. Well, I turned a
150 to 250 on Frankie. Then I lost it
all. Obviously was 150 of my own money,
but is what it is,
bro. Yeah, I got a bonus. It paid. I was
£100 up. Then I lost two then I lost the
250, you know.
And the maddest thing about it, Scratch,
is it's only getting worse. Like when I
was doing some approaches today in the
mall, I didn't get I got a boyfriend
once. I was like, am I am I in the right
country? Are you sure I'm in England?
Like they didn't say they had
boyfriends. They were just very
unenthusiastic, just like
MPCs, sort of glued to their phone. And
then when I finally went to central
London, then I definitely got the I got
a boyfriend. See, you should never speak
too soon. You see? Yeah. When I was in
Tottenham Court Road, I definitely
definitely got it. It was nonstop. Oh my
[ __ ] god. That happened last Friday
as well. But then when I was round where
I was earlier, I didn't get it, but they just were
unenthusiastic. Point is, it's basically
impossible in this
country. It's bad, bro. It's actually very bad.
And if I hadn't approached them all
today, I probably wouldn't have went
out. Yeah. Okay. I got three numbers.
That's not the [ __ ] point. It's the
reality of of it now, you know? It's
bad bad news, bro. Bad
news. It's not even funny. It's actually [ __ ]
up. I wish I could I can't even laugh at it anymore.
No, they don't have boyfriends. No, they
[ __ ] do not have boyfriends. Not
every single one. They don't all say
they've got boyfriends, but no, they
don't. No the [ __ ] they do [ __ ] not.
Because how do you know who the [ __ ] is
telling the truth? Most men are single.
There's a lot of women that are single.
There's a lot of good looking women that
are single. It's [ __ ] It generally
generally generally is [ __ ]
And even the ones that are genuine,
right? How would you know they're
genuine when all so many lie? You wouldn't even
know. So every single woman No, I would
say about three in 10 have a boyfriend.
I would say out of I'm not having this
conversation. It's boring. I I know
they're bullshitting and I don't care.
It It's just another excuse. I'm not
going to get into a debate whether
they're lying or they're not lying. I
know that they're bullshitting and I'm
not going to have this I'm not going to
have this conversation. It's boring.
Simple. I'm not going to have this
conversation. It bors me. You know, like
it's it's it's a boring conversation. Go
look up the statistics. I don't care.
You know, simple. It's [ __ ] hell,
bro. It's a boring
conversation. And and people cheat on
their boyfriend as well. So, how do you
explain that one? How the [ __ ] do you
one? So, I'm not I'm not having this I'm
not having this conversation. I'm not
debate. You know, it's boring as [ __ ] That's
it. I never said every single one of
them lie, but more lie than don't lie.
more lied than don't lie.
Definitely definitely definitely
definitely you know because if you go on
women's Facebooks right you never really
see that many in relationships and and
and you know it's nah no way
lad. No [ __ ] way. If you actually
think I'm not having this conversation
with you, bro. Like I'm not I'm not
going to sit here and have this
conversation with you. If you think
they've all got boyfriends, the what the
ones that say they've got boyfriends,
that's on you, bro. It I got three
numbers today. Anyways, one said I was a
type. I don't really give a [ __ ] I'm
bothered hearing it. You know, I only I
only I only done it today cuz of I was
waiting for the film to
stop. Yeah. No. Yeah.
Bye-bye. But no way. No way. They were
my boyfriends. There's no way. No
[ __ ] way. No way in
hell. What's the reason for them to lie?
Because they think they're better than
you. Um maybe they're not looking for
someone. You don't have a million
Instagram followers. There's loads of
reasons they lie. And they do it to most
people. Again, not having this
conversation. And what was I saying? You
made me [ __ ] forget what I was going to say
now. [ __ ] You made me forget what I was
going to say. So, not having this
conversation anyways. We're not getting
into this conversation about my looks. Boring. Simple. So
yeah. Yeah. They're not interested in
90% men. I don't really care, bro.
Anyways, I don't give a [ __ ] Boring
conversation. So they're just not
interested in this country. End
of I think we've been saying that for
ages. They're not interested in [ __ ]
85 90% of [ __ ] men. Don't look up the
[ __ ] statistics nowadays because this
is how you know, right? I It's not you.
Because everyone that goes around
London, Yeah. Yeah. gets the same [ __ ]
Everyone that you see go around London
get the same [ __ ] You get people
bringing back Thai women from [ __ ]
Asia. That's how you know it's them.
Because if you notice that most people
that you meet will have the same issue,
the same problem, ones that are not even
in relationships, that's how you know
it's them. There's quite a few Instagram
profiles that come up. Black guy, you
know, you know, like, you know, and they
get exact. That's how you know it's
them. That's how you know it's it's
them. Because if it was not happening to
all these other people, I'd be like,
"Hold on a minute." Right? That's
[ __ ] madness. I'd start thinking
there's something wrong with me. But it
happens to most people. I see it all the
time. I see happen in real life. I see
it happen on Instagram. And I don't
care, bro. I'm not having this
conversation anyways. Who cares? [ __ ]
them. It's no biggie, bro. It's not a
big deal. Yeah. We We didn't spend much anyways. But yeah, end
of talk about it's boring, bro.
It must [ __ ] bore you. [ __ ]
listening to it as well. It's
boring cuz I see this black guy go
around London and he gets the same [ __ ]
I see other people go around London and
they get the same
[ __ ] They don't have no walk in the
park, bro. So what? Is everyone ugly?
Think about it, bro. Is everyone just
this ugly person? Of course not. Of
[ __ ] of course not,
bro. Especially England, you know. especially what
London London Mos anyways.
So, it's my race. That's what I think it
is. I personally think it's the Cuz I
was asking a few people earlier and I
was like and they said, "Where do you
think I'm from?" And they all said that
you look Turkish even though Ant-Man
says I look white. You know what I'm
saying, bro? You
know? No. Younger people are doing it
nowadays. Nope. Younger people are doing
it nowadays, mate. I see people go to
Thailand. I see people with Thai women.
That's what I think think it is. Just like black people, you
know, just like black people, they moan
that men don't approach them and but
then when men approach them, they
pretend they got boyfriends. Is a
madness, isn't it? It's just one of them
holy things. Eh, they complain that. See
the thing is right is that these women
right the difference between these women
they complain that they can't find
people they complain that people don't
approach them and actually a woman has
said this herself and then when people
actually talk to them or try to talk
talk to them they they show no
enthusiasm. So I mean when when the
difference is is when when men
generalize women it's because they've
never been shown any different. Like me,
I've literally never been shown any
different. I have no reason to believe
that they're not all the same. I know
they're all the same. Just like these
men that you see, they're all the same
that break their [ __ ] neck to [ __ ]
look at you. If you go outside, you'll
notice that it's the same people you
see, the same women, same attitude, same
[ __ ] men with the same attitude,
cocky attitude. If you notice, every
time you go out, you meet the same people.
know. So that's
it. Anyways, end the conversation. This
is boring now. Very, very boring. You
completely ignored what I was just
explaining for the past minute. Anyways,
end of conversation.
Boring. I'm bored now. Anyways, I'm not
going over this again because the reason
is is that I'm not going to sit here and
and and argue with you. Like a lot of
you people, you don't even leave your
house. So, what would you know? What is
what? Because I I know like a lot of
you, you ain't got no life experience.
The way you talk about things, like the
way you talk about women, I've noticed
that as well. Like, you don't have
literally no life experience. You
know, like you have no life experience
at all. Like when you say, "Oh, like
women go for this, women go for that."
Like, I swear now, bro. I swear a lot of
you are housebound housebound
agrophobics. I swear now, bro. Like, why
am I going to sit here and debate with
somebody that probably don't even leave
the house? And I'm and I mean that in
the nicest ways way possible and get my age
right. You know what I'm saying? Like
you probably don't even leave your
house. What the [ __ ] would you know
about women? I probably had more women than [ __ ]
you. That's that's the madest thing
about it. Why am I going to sit here and
argue with you or or debate with you? It makes no
sense. There's too many stuck up [ __ ]
in this country. End
of going back and forth, bro. It's
pointless. I don't care, bro.
I don't give a [ __ ] Anyways, Antman's
going out tomorrow, so we'll see how he
does. Shut up, man. You're boring.
You're gone. See you later. All right.
We won't do any people on my channel. Yeah,
literally. Yeah, man. Ant man's
literally got the right
idea. I wish I was as laidback as Antam,
but I just can't not
worry. But he has actually got the right
idea. It is what it is and it will never change. That's
That's the way it is, unfortunately. You
know, Oh [ __ ] my nose hurts.
Yeah, cuz the thing is you got to
understand like before I met before I
met Morgan, right, it took years. It
literally took two years, bro. I
remember I used to go out all the time
and bro, it was [ __ ] hard.
Stephen, bro, you're right, man. I've
been I got a new fridge. I got a fridge.
Yeah, I got a new I got a fridge to save
money. Yeah, today was good
today. I went to the I went to the
cinema. I was walking around the mall. I
got an hour to kill. Done some
approaches, got nothing. Went to the
cinema, film with [ __ ] Came back drunk,
had some alcohol, went out, sent it approaching women.
and then got an escort and then lost 150
on Frankie. [ __ ] you, [ __ ] You
know, and that's it, bro. No, I was
hiding, bro. I was just busy with life,
bro. I've got busy I've got my I've been
just busy with
life and um yeah,
bro. I don't really come on here much anymore.
So well you found it
now. Yeah. No.
Yeah. But it will never change in it. This country
Yeah, it's [ __ ] up, lad. But yeah,
just been Yeah, I got a fridge, bro.
[ __ ] heavy [ __ ] It
was heavy bastard. Yeah, I already got
my bet for tomorrow. I done it when I
lost that 150 on Frankie.
Uh, I got a fourfold. Yeah, I put £7 on
it cuz I got changed from the Indian returns
£20. Yeah, 27 to1.
So, I just before coming back.
Yeah, he comes on occasionally. Yeah, man. Yeah.
What do you think Steven Howard about
getting a woman in this country? I would say
honestly I would say it is impossible
bro. Like going going obviously I got
three numbers today but going by the
whole like a summary of it. It it is
impossible. It actually is you know
unless unless you get extremely
extremely lucky. It is [ __ ] up bro. It
is actually mad [ __ ] up.
I think it
is. I think it's I think it is, bro.
These countries I generally think it is.
And I think if anyone Yeah. on here
actually went out and actually done it
themselves like me and Notorious. Yeah.
You would see it's [ __ ]
up. It's actually [ __ ] up, bro.
Yeah, it's bad, bro. It's
bad. I don't think you you you can find
anyone in this country,
bro. I don't think you
can. I don't think you can,
bro. Honestly, I don't think you can,
Yeah, you're lucky to get any numbers,
but I generally don't think you actually
can. I got a Billy Bear sandwich, by the
way, put in the fridge.
So, I don't think you can,
bro. So, I have to just live life alone,
bro, for the rest of my life.
Literally, it's [ __ ] up, isn't it?
Bad. No, he's
back. I think that might have to be you,
bro. It's [ __ ] up, though, is it? It is [ __ ]
up. There we
go. I think you got me confused with
yourself there, buddy.
Yeah, you've got me confused with
yourself there, bud. Nice paragraph,
though. That's what a lot of these
people, Stephen, Albert, they've got
theirelves confused um with me when
they're saying no money, big nose,
manta, they they've got themselves
confused with me, buddy. And when they say
skin, Yeah, bro. They're They've got themselves
um Yeah, they've got themselves um
um confused with me,
buddy. Yeah. Don't think they're
confusing themselves. That's literally
their lives on YouTube every day.
Ah, yeah. Again, bro, you've got
yourself confused with me,
buddy. Yeah, you're confusing yourself
with me again. It's not good. Anyways,
Mr. B. Yeah, I went out sent it today. I
got three numbers. It was pretty [ __ ] to
fair. Yeah, it was [ __ ] up, bro. Said it,
man. Yeah. Again, you've got yourself confused with
me. These people have got theirelves confused with me. Yeah.
definitely confusing themselves with me,
man. Yeah, I've met somebody in a smoking area, too.
Yeah. See, Grey doesn't want to go on
Tinder because Greavves knows I'm right,
so he can't go on
Tinder. Yeah. Get going, you ugly rat bastard.
[ __ ] ugly bastard virgin.
Yeah. No. Well, I got three doublers
today. We'll see if any of them reply. I
think No, I think they should. Some of
them will. Definitely. Some of them
will. We're hoping they Yeah, I think
definitely. But it was hard, bro. It was
[ __ ] hard. You don't know how many
approaches I had to do today to get them
numbers. So, it's either like you go
out, you do this, you get the same [ __ ]
or you die
boredom. Like, it's [ __ ] up, isn't it?
Like, what what is the solution to life,
bro? What is the
solution? You need a plan B, bro.
You know, you got plan A, but you need a
B. He does know about it. He does know
about this channel. [ __ ]
Did you used to watch um You got
yourself confused with me,
bud. Um Steven Howard, did you used to
watch The Inbetween Us?
I don't know, bro. [ __ ]
knows. You used to like the in between, isn't you? Yeah. Definitely.
Yeah. Don't watch a woman in the yard. It was
[ __ ] Yeah. Woman in the yard was
[ __ ] Yeah. I don't really come on here
much anymore, lad. [ __ ] boring. Same repeating people. Yeah. Exactly. Not
exactly. Yeah. I need to do some
traveling, bro. I need to do some
traveling. Do you think you would always
be the same in this country, Steven Howard?
Boyfriend. They've all got boyfriend, Steven
Howard. You are a boyfriend, do [Music]
you? Yeah, it will always be the same.
What do you think, Steven Howard? I
think it will always be the same. Do
you? No, I don't find it funny. B
It's the same old it.
Oh, do you remember Adman Steven Howard?
Boyfriend. They've all got
boyfriends. Do you remember that Steven
Howard? You got a boyfriend, do you? Man's
funny. They've all got
boyfriends. They've all got imaginary
boyfriends. Ask yourself this question, right?
You know when you go to these bars and
these clubs and whatever, why are they
never with their
boyfriends? If let's just say they
exist, right? These the these boyfriends
exist to theirs. Why are they never with
them when you want to be with your
boyfriend? Cuz they don't
exist. Notice if you see people that are
actually in relationships, yeah, they're with them.
Huh? Yeah, it's
funny. It is
funny. It's [ __ ] annoying as
well. It is funny, but it is annoying. Why place
annoying? Maybe the same reason you see
men out with male friends.
Nah. No way. No way,
lad. It's funny. It's funny to be
honest. There's no way, bro. No [ __ ] way. No
way. What is
it? I'm done anyways.
Took a while to find a
woman that was actually nice um and
actually spoke back. Well, they it got
better as I went into this place,
but yeah, it's bad,
bro. They're all stuck up. It's too many
stuck up [ __ ]
You meet the same people like even you
even you see it you even see it in
shopping centers women walking around
like their [ __ ] don't
stink you know same attitude you it's
like wherever you go people have the
same attitude you see the same people
you see the same people everywhere you
go here in
England am I the only one that's noticed
that you see the Same people, same
attitude. I've noticed that as
well. The [ __ ] NPCs, mate.
Yeah, I was born in the wrong in the
wrong uh decade, man. [ __ ] like that.
Yeah. Really, bro? Send me
it. No, I won't like it, bro. It's
annoying. It pisses me
off. I'm just sick of hearing it. I I
don't care, bro. I'm just sick of
hearing it. I don't care.
Right. At the end of the day, you
shouldn't be hearing it in clubs. You
shouldn't be hearing it in B. I don't
Well, I don't care. [ __ ] You should not
be hearing it in these
places nearly as much as you do because
it's like, well, isn't this a place to
meet new people? Isn't a club and a bar
a place to meet new people? or Steven
Howard. Do you not go to a Okay, whether
Spoons is debatable, but a bar and a
club, isn't that a place where you kind
of want to meet new people, mingle a little
bit? But how can you if they have
boyfriends, whether they do or they
don't? It's so it's it's just a place to
mingle, you know, our age. So, it
doesn't make sense whether they do or
don't. Nah, it's not funny, but it's
annoying because if it wasn't for me
doing them approaches today before the
film, I would have went out today.
No, it's not funny,
bro. It's annoying. It is actually
proper annoying. And it actually made me
go out today and I didn't want to go out
today. I meant to be [ __ ] saving, but
like I said, I found the some alcohol. So,
yeah. No, it's not funny. It's annoying,
bro. It is actually proper annoying.
Bors me. [ __ ] bors me, man.
It literally just bors
me. Yeah, you're going to laugh at this
one. I spoke to one I've actually
recorded this approach in the weather
spoons. I actually recorded some of
these approaches and she said that she's
had a boyfriend for 10 years and she's
not married. And guess where she's from?
She's from Latvia.
Whereas if you really had a boyfriend,
you'd be married by now because people
from Latapia and people from Ukraine
marry. So if you was with someone for 10
years in them countries, you would be
married. It's [ __ ] It's bollocks. I
had one today saying that she was she's
had a boyfriend for 4
weeks and she's I'll take your number.
And I was like, okay. Well, I gave her my number.
Um, obviously just the same old. It's
just it's just the same old. It's just,
bro, we don't we don't need to get into
this this this [ __ ] We all we got to
say is it's the same
old. There's there's there's nothing else.
Sadly, you got a boyfriend for 10 years.
It's [ __ ] because if you had a
boyfriend for 10 years, you would be
married. Trust me, you'd be married.
I've had all sorts. I've had a week,
four weeks, 10 years. It's just
boring. Literally, you you need a
[ __ ] plan B, lad. I'm telling you, it
is boring. It bors me. It
does. Generally bors me, you
know. Yeah. Well, it's Ant-Man's turn
tomorrow. I gave it my best today. I got
three numbers. T's turn
tomorrow. Yeah, I'll be looking forward
it. Yes. We're not saying that people,
but she's from Ukraine. She's from,
sorry, she's from Latapia. People from
Latia and people from Ukraine,
right? Marry very very early on. Trust me, they
do, you know. So, yeah.
But Stephen Howard, it's very like what
you see on YouTube and what you see on
Reddit, right, is very different to what
you experience in real life. Like you
get people that say women go for
personality, but as soon as you try to
speak to a woman, they'll pretend they
got a boyfriend. Doesn't matter who you
are. So real life actually shows a lot
different to what people say. That's why
you can never go on Reddit or YouTube
or, you know,
You know, like because what you will
experience in real life is completely
different to what they
say. Try it if you don't believe me one
day. If you're walking around a shopping
center, it's nothing like that. [Music]
Um, it's always the same people, the
same excuses, the same attitude, the
same [ __ ] men that can't keep out
their [ __ ] own business. Like I was
talking to a woman today and this guy,
he was walking and he broke his neck to
look back. It's like he broke I was
like, "Uh, what are you looking at?"
Like, why are you just
staring? Like, have you never seen
someone approach a woman
before? Yeah. I personally think there's
there there's a reason. The reason is is
it's because it's London and because you
don't look fully English. That's what it
is. That's what it is. It's, you know,
it would be like it for mo. It is like
it for most people in London. I see
people in London and they get the same
[ __ ] as me, if not
worse. So, we can't all be ugly and
wrong. You know what I'm saying? We
can't all be wrong
here. But England is the worst place for it.
You know, we can't all be ugly and
wrong. We're all different looking.
We've got different personalities with
different races, you know? So, it is
them. Like, whether people want to say
it is or not, it
is. Yeah, that's true. Some of them
could be in [ __ ] Asia. Some of them
could be in [ __ ] Thailand. They're
people on Reddit.
But I'm saying if you live anywhere like
London or Manchester, mainly London, you
will see it's not like
that. You know, you will see it's not
what people say it
is. Again, it's never going to change.
So, we need to accept
this. Yeah, I got three numbers. Okay.
Yeah, some of them are all right. But
still, it's not the point, bro. I done a
lot of approaches today before going in
the cinema and none of them said they
had a boyfriend. They were just all they all just
unenthusiastic. They just it was it was
like you get more enthusiasm from a
baby. Like you actually would get more
enthusiasm from a newborn
baby. They didn't say they had
boyfriends, but they were just stuck up.
Like I can't explain it. How How do you
explain it to someone that's not [ __ ]
done this before? You
can't. They're all the same. They're all
NPCs. It's It's like what Ant-Man
said. Blackpool will do Blackpool.
So, it's a crying shame. But
yeah, it is them. It is them.
Yeah, hopefully one of them goes
somewhere. You know, some of them are
good. I got Well, I tried. Simple. I can
safely say I tried. So whether they go
anywhere or not, I tried. End of.
So, and I didn't spend any. I didn't
even buy one drink today.
So, yeah, we'll see.
Anyways, but it is definitely getting
worse. It is definitely getting worse
from when I last remembered it, you
know. I mean, yeah, a lot of people on
Reddit live in America, but there's no
way it's any easier in
America cuz it's a westernized country.
Yeah, there's some new
ones. Well, the only the only time it
would be different in America would be
[ __ ] Alabama. I was just saying to
people on YouTube, like, you know,
before that Morgan, right, I got nothing
in London. Nothing.
Nothing. You know, my first one night
stand was in Manchester. I used to try
all the time in London. Nothing.
Nothing. You couldn't even get a date. I
remember trying for ages and you could never get
nothing. Nothing to London, bro. I swear
to God. I promise you. I swear to
God. It went on for like a year and a
half and then
it's it's sad,
bro. It's just
sad. But I don't I don't see how
Blackpool will be any different because
again, it's England.
You know, I
suck. But you can kill a
baby. See you in an hour cuz that ain't never happening,
mate. It's getting
worse. Getting worse, mate. It's getting
worse. But yeah, I got a new fridge. It
cost me £103. Steen Howard. [ __ ]
lovely it is. Maybe Baby,
Baby. Yeah, they're nice and cold now, buddy.
Yeah. Yeah. Woman in the yard. It wasn't
a good horror
film. I'm a I'm here all by myself with
the light off and I'm not
scared. Yeah, we can do. Yeah.
I'm not scared one
bit. I'm a tiny bit
scared. Anyways, I'm gone. I'll be back
tomorrow, bro. I'll be back live
tomorrow. Oh, somebody's knocking on my
door in 10 minutes. Oh, really? He's
been saying that for the past two, three
months. Anyways, I'm leaving. Bye-bye.
I'll be back live tomorrow. Anyways, um for the
football. No, I watched Woman in the
Yard. Anyways, I'm gone. It was a six
out of 10. Nothing special. I'm going.
Bye-bye. I'll be back live tomorrow.
Maybe maybe I won't be for another 3,
four days. Anyways, I'm gone cuz I'm tired.
done some so many approaches
today. Same old [ __ ] Boyfriends, free
numbers. Yeah, it will never change.
Anyways, I'm out of here, man. [ __ ] I'm tired. Bye-bye.