[Applause]
H stretch stretch stretch stretch stretchy. [Music] So
done. Yeah, man. What I just pop
on. Why the [ __ ] not there? One [Music]
second. Back up. Always have to back up my [ __ ]
now. Always got to back up my [ __ ] Always.
Christmas leaving YouTube. You'll never leave
YouTube. This is life. Just like nons
legs. Just like Virgin
Sea. I stacked up the fridge today, man.
Oh, it's looking good. I got some
expensive meat in there. I cooked some burgers
earlier. Still going back to the old
days. Yeah, I know. I've seen it. I've
seen it. I've seen it. I've seen it. I
have seen it. Well, I got a [ __ ]
yesterday. My friend come
around. No, I can't be bothered going
downstairs. I'll go downstairs in a
minute. Uh, I got a lot. I spent about
£100 today and expensive meat. But I got
pans though. I did get a lot of pans.
But obviously, you'll be saving a lot of
money. I got loads of meat,
bro. I got about 50 worth of meat.
Well, obviously it's a free [ __ ]
[ __ ] She's my [ __ ]
friend. No [ __ ]
bro. And one of the numbers replied back
as well. I got three numbers, one reply back.
So, yeah, I lost £100 yesterday on a
football bet. Yeah, join the
club. I lost £150 on a [ __ ] football
bet. Sorry, 100 pound, not 150. Yeah,
[ __ ] it£100 on a [ __ ] football bet.
Okay. Jesus. What the [ __ ] is going on,
bro? Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Skint until Monday. Rather you
than to me, mate. At least you're not as
skinn as that [ __ ] Virgin Sea. I love
how he associates Billy Bear with
nonses. That's cuz he is a
nons. That's because he is a [ __ ]
nons. Why do you think he goes on about
nons? Because he's one himself.
cuz he's a [ __ ] nons himself. That's
why he goes on about nons. It's cuz he's
a big one
himself. [ __ ] associating innocent
beats with pedophiles. That's coming from a
pedophile. Oh, you are you getting your monthly
grand? What is it? Your monthly grand,
Yeah. Yeah. She's [ __ ] really good at
it. I came in her mouth. She swallowed
it. She gave me one a few times
before. This community is just a weird
atmosphere. How are you skinned? I'm never [ __ ]
skinned. I am never ever
skin. Yeah, she is. I'm never skinned. Me [ __ ]
never. Not for like two, three years.
Maybe like three years ago. Well, I had
20 pound Christmas, but that was about
it. But then I had I got money the same
day. But I had money the same day. So
kind of got money the same day. So I didn't really Yeah.
Yeah. I never run out of money.
Never. Even when I gamble, I'm not [Music] skin.
No. Even then. Even then, bro. Even
Yeah, she come to my yard. We had some food and
that. It was
good. And I got someone else I'm going
I'm talking to as well. So, I'm chilling
for I need to make some
money to make some money,
bro. I save some money. Sorry.
Yeah, she drinks. She doesn't take
drugs. I got some alcohol as
well. I cooked some nice burgers
earlier. They were
lush. Oh, they were
lush. Yeah, they were good,
man. Friends with benefits. Fend with
Yeah. Going to have some nice meat
today. Oh, lovely. Why does Sean go on
like he's got money when he really
really is skint? Like, let's look at it.
30 in your 30s, never been abroad, never
left the country, no assets, no bed, you
shop at a charity shop. Everything
screams skin. Do you understand? When
everything screams skin, you're probably
skin. He goes on like he's got money.
He's got [ __ ]
all. I don't know why he goes on about
money when he's literally the skintest
person on this community. Like honestly,
bro, like even Monty man has got more
money. He is skint as [ __ ] Why does he
go on like he's got money? He literally
has nothing, bro. Like actually
nothing. Yeah, of course, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. I know. I know. I know. I'm just
saying. Is it? I'm just saying. I'm just
Yeah. But yeah, I've got her to come.
She gives good [ __ ] as well and she swallowed it.
So, might just stick with her. [ __ ]
it. But I still like to go out and meet other
people. I don't know. Just chilling today in
it. Two-bedroom house. How is he getting a two-bedroom
house? How is he charging his phone?
Wait, hold on a minute. How is he charging his
phone? How is he charging his phone when
he's How is he I don't understand how
he's charging his phone when he's in a
tent. That doesn't make any
sense. That does not make no sense.
Yeah, man. Stop asking these stupid
questions. Of course she gets [ __ ]
naked. For [ __ ] sake. We're adults.
What do you mean? Does she get [ __ ]
naked? No, you don't say, bro. What the
[ __ ] Really? That's mad. So why don't
he just stay with his
brother? That doesn't make any sense.
Can't he just stay with his
brother? That's madness,
bro. I have had some do. I have I have
had some that I
haven't Why is he not allowed to stay?
He's not on £800 a month
disability. No way. No one gets that. No
one gets £1,800 a month disability
without housing benefit. It's like Rice.
He's talking [ __ ]
It's like Rice when he tries to say he
gets 1,800. No, he
doesn't. No, he [ __ ]
doesn't. You are the Mong. Stop calling
me a Mong. You are You're a Mong
yourself, you [ __ ] [ __ ] Go suck my
dick. I know he does not. You are the
Mong, you [ __ ] There's not one person
that gets 1,800 disabilities. They're
not. There not one person gets that.
Stop talking [ __ ]
Stop talking utter [ __ ] shite. Right.
The most somebody can get is probably
about a grand 400. No. And you are the
mong. Stop calling you. Stop confusing
yourself with me. [ __ ]
£1,800. You are the mong. Don't confuse
yourself with me, pal.
No, you can't get 900 pound. You are a
spaz. You stop, bro. Come and say it to
my [ __ ] face. Yeah. Stop hiding
behind the [ __ ] keyboard. Come out
and say it to my face. Yeah. Come to
London today and I'll meet you and you
can come and say it to my face and I'll
tell you to suck your bum to your face.
Yeah. Now, if you're not going to do
that and you're going to be a keyboard
warrior, stop saying it behind the
keyboard, bro. You're the same as Terry.
I was telling LT about this the other
day. Stop the keyboard warrior tactics.
Yeah. If you're not prepared to call
somebody a mong or a spaz to their face,
don't do it behind a keyboard like me.
I'm telling you, go and suck your
mother. And I'll tell you to suck your
mother to your face. Just like I'll tell
nonss. Just like I tell Nlex to suck his
[ __ ] ugly mom and I'll tell Terry.
But I'll say it to their face. That's
the difference. You understand
me? That's the difference, bro?
Yeah. I get more money to order you.
Yeah. Listen, listen. Come and call me a
Mong to my face. Yeah. Get a train to
King's Cross and I will go to King's
Cross and you can call me a Mong to my
face. Yeah. And I'll tell you, go suck
your mother to your face. How about that
one? Yeah. Stop this little keyboard
warrior [ __ ] I will tell you manto man
to your face. Go suck your mother and
I'll say it to your face. So stop doing
this little keyboard warrior [ __ ] Yeah,
you would never say anything to my face.
You're a keyboard warrior. Just like
Terry. Just like Nons. Go and suck your
mother. Yeah, I'm a Mong. Okay. Well,
come and say it to my face then. Stop
saying it behind the keyboard. Get your
stupid Nottingham ass to London with
your Robin Hood, M. And then [ __ ]
come to London so I can tell you to suck your
mom. Yeah. With your Robin Hood eye.
What? What? What's the accent? Robin
Hood. What's that? That sp a up duck.
Robin Hood. Yeah. Come to London. Hey up
duck. Hey up duck. Robin Hood. Come on
Robin Hood. App duck. Come on bro.
Simple. Come on lad. Yeah. Hey up duck.
Hey up duck. That's what I'm going to
say to you when when you when you come
to London bro. That's what I'm going to
say to you. I'm going to say to you, hey
duck. Robin Hood like suck your mother
in a in a Nottingham way. How about that
one? No, bro. It's just No, no, no, no,
no, no, bro. It's just because I would
know you would never say anything to my
face. That's the
thing. Yeah, stop being all talk. No,
no, no, no, no, no, bro. No one's wound
me up. You're winding me up because you
would never say anything to our face. Hey,
updike. Do you think I could take anyone
from that city serious? Bro, I used to
go to Nottingham all the time. Yeah. You
would never say anything to my face
ever, bro. I get more money than all of
you. I already told you how much money I
get. Yeah. Well, I'm acting like the
biggest Mong now. So, come and say it to
my face. I'm acting like the biggest
Mong. Yeah. Come and say it to my face.
I'll meet you in King's Cross. I'm
acting like a Mong like your mom. Yeah.
I'm acting I'm I'm acting like a mong
just like your mongy [ __ ] mother. I'm
a mong like your [ __ ] mother. Now
come and say it to my face and stop
being a keyboard warrior. You don't want
to be labeled as a keyboard warrior, do
you? Yeah, I get £1,300 a month. I get a
I get [ __ ] three grand a month, mate. Try again. Try
again. Listen, are you going to come and
say it to my face or not? Are you just
going to keep being a keyboard warrior?
Are you going to keep being a keyboard
warrior or are you going to come and say
it to my face? Everyone wants to know
now. Okay. Are you coming or not? Simple.
Yeah. You little
[ __ ] Yeah. Okay. Monday. Yeah. Which
is tomorrow. Okay. Good. Yeah. Do a
video. Let me know when you're on your
way. You'll never I would backhand you
[ __ ] silly, son. Yeah. You're skint,
bro. You're sat there with no money and
you're trying to call me a monk. Imagine
that. You're sat
there. You're banned. Bye-bye.
Now, you're sat there trying to call me
a Mong when you're the one that sat
there with no
money. Imagine that,
bro. Imagine that for one minute. The
guy sat there with no
money. He's sat there with [ __ ] no
money, bro. And he's trying to call me a
Mong. Does that make sense to you?
Does that make sense to you, bro? It
doesn't make sense to me. Doesn't make
sense to you. It doesn't make sense to
me. Think you're trying to call me
among N man. I'm having some
uh I went to the
butchers. I went to the butchers. Got a
load of meat. Load of meat. Load of
pans. I'm back to cooking now for a little
bit. I got some nice lamb, some chicken.
So no not no not today bro not
today will be doing but not
today I had Chinese yesterday
so yeah bro I spent like 50 pound in a [ __ ]
butchers saying I need to get a [ __ ]
t-bone man definitely need to get a
t-bone uh uh [Music]
Uh, I need to save some money, bro. I
need to save some some [ __ ]
longer. Getting out of hand, man. You know?
Yeah. But there's not one benefit that
pays £1,800 a month, bro. Don't let
anyone tell you
otherwise. There is not one benefit that
pays that. I'm telling you straight, bro.
I'm telling you straight, bro. There's
not. Cuz they wouldn't Why would they
give somebody £1,800? Because no one
would work if they were if they were to
give out £1,800, bro. Yeah. People wouldn't
work. You understand me, brother? Like,
people would not work. People wouldn't
work. If they were to diss out money
like that, bro, people would not work.
You understand? Cuz why would they work
when they getting what most people are
earning? It don't make
sense. Talking absolute
[ __ ] It's just like that
rice. He talks absolute
[ __ ] You know, I know people on
benefits and they do not get paid £1,800
a month. That's foolishness because
people would not
work. Think about
it. People wouldn't work. If if people
could get their benefits, people wouldn't work. He's talking
[ __ ] He's talking [ __ ] out of his
[ __ ] anus, bro. Out of his [ __ ] absolute ass
crap. It's not real. He's talking [ __ ]
bro. Yeah, I've started cooking a bit now.
Is there a [ __ ]
lush? Takeaways are good like every four
days. Yeah, they're good like every four
days. Otherwise, they're just
too they're just too
expensive with the old Stony there. But
you get what I mean.
Go see go.
So that's a
Fake Monty Man account. Oh my god. What
is it with you people in fake accounts, bro?
Honestly, what is it with you people in fake accounts?
It's what I mean, bro. It's mad. We're madness. [Music]
Oh god. Anyways, bro, I'm tired. I'm asleep. Bye.