That's nice. was
not me. That was
Got a [ __ ] t-bone today.
Yeah. One, mate. Yummy. Coke.
be a nice bit of poke straight out of the
bottle. Slowly grab that
stuff. Good old days, eh? Man. Uhuh.
I don't really
know. Certain person says it's the same people every
day. I'll be performing fast. [ __ ] you. [ __ ] Yeah.
I don't think a lot of people know about this
channel. I actually don't think a lot of
people know about this [ __ ] channel.
I'm getting less [ __ ] channels than
the [ __ ] or less um less views than
the [ __ ] Orington version. The rat
the ugly rat face. [ __ ]
hell. People must definitely not know
about this [ __ ] channel. Oh, I'm
sorry. They must [ __ ] shut
away. cuz no one really types
it. Oh, Joe is talking about me again. He's obsessed.
That's what you know what I find so
weird about this community. You go on
someone's channel and they can't shut up
about you. [ __ ] mentally and
physically obsessed. It's just like that
Joe account that Joe account. He's
obsessed. I've just gone on to Monty and
he's talking about me. He's a weirdo. [ __ ] weirdos
l trying to say I'm on pit like I'm on
highway. Bro, you don't even know me.
This is what makes me think. Yeah, these
people get confused with
themselves again. Repeating. This is why
I don't really see the anymore. The
repeaters. Same repeaters.
Same self rejecting
repeaters probably come on anymore. You're
scared. You hear what? You're scared. You're
scared. I know. I'm so scared, man. I'm
having a 20 tbo stick for dinner
today. I'm so scared.
I know it sucks to be me in
it. It sucks to be me having a 20 pound
TV steak today, but I'm so scared it. I
wish I had loads and loads of
money. Try to get that [ __ ] round again.
Tuesday. Uh some football playing today, isn't
it? I will not be participating.
Yeah. Come anytime you want. Anytime you
want. I don't know if there was people
typing or not. Why someone
typing? We're being delivered for some
[ __ ] There's 11 people watching. No one
coming. No one's joining for some reason. Perfect. Oh, [ __ ]
me. Oh, burger. [ __ ] killed me
now. Uh, you people don't bully no one.
The only time you bully people is in your
dreams. You literally don't bully no
one. It's in your dreams that you bully
people. You bore people, but you don't
bully no one. You're just
repeaters. People that repeat themselves
can't bully anyone. You bore people.
Think about it, right? When when we're
not on YouTube, whoever how many people
you do this to, we're living our best
lives. We got more money than you. We're
better looking than you. We're living a
life that you wish you had. Like you are
on YouTube every day trying to troll
people because you are the ones that get
bullied every day in real life, not just
on YouTube. Think about it. You little
spastics have been on here doing it for
years. You don't bother no one. If you
bothered anyone so much, people wouldn't
be on YouTube. Anyways, have a good day. Goodbye.
Yeah. I think some of these people, they
generally just need to get
laid. They generally generally just need to get
laid. Like I'm I'm not even joking.
Sean, these other
people. Yeah. You I hope they force you
into work as well, buddy. I hope they
force you into
work. Yeah, man. I hope they force you into
work. You need a dose of reality as
well. Again, you're getting yourself
confused with me, buddy. You're getting
yourself confused with
me, buddy. You're getting yourself
confused with me again. And it's very,
very, very, very dangerous. Yeah. I hope
they force you into work. You
know, focus on your own life. Stop
talking about other people's life and
what they should be doing, what they
shouldn't be doing. You know, why do you
care about what other people do with
their lives? It's pathetic.
Slam. Slam delivery. [Music]
So, I can I'll do what I [ __ ] want. I
got a [ __ ] [ __ ] two days ago. I'll
do what I [ __ ] want when I [ __ ]
want. It's my
life. I will do whatever I want. Just
cuz you're housebound and you got no
confidence. Don't project your
insecurities onto me. You hater. You
undercover hater. Just cuz you're too
scared to leave your house and you can't
approach women. Don't get jealous. Now
you're going to have to get jealous.
I was going to say like how long are you
people going to keep this up for on
YouTube? But then I remember that you're
just disabled. So I mean you're just
disabled. So it's it goes in one ear and out the
other. You're autistic. Most of you use
housebound anxiety. They got a life.
Well, you do what you do. I don't
judge. Oh, here we go.
You need to get a job yourself instead
of telling other
people. You at the top of Albert Square.
Oh, good for you, buddy. I don't live
there. That's nice, bro. Good for you. I don't live.
Yeah. And we're blocking the idiots as well. Um, blocked,
blocked. There we
go. Blocking idiots
now. There we
go. Blocking the [ __ ]
But every like five, six retards, you
probably get about one decent
person. One normal [ __ ]
person. Isn't that a madness?
Eh. That's a
madness. That's a madness. Uh
I thought this person was
online. See these people in this
community, they think that they bully
people, but all they do is bully
themselves. All they do is embarrass
themselves. They make a fool of
themselves. It's ridiculous at their
age. These people need to grow up.
Germany Germany and Germany Germany need
to [ __ ] grow up. They got a life.
They're mentally [ __ ] I don't I
don't like saying that word, bro, cuz
obviously there's, you know, people that
out there, they can't help it. But they must be
retards. They've been doing the same
[ __ ] the same regurgitated [ __ ] for
years. They've got to be mentally
[ __ ] Same regurgitated [ __ ]
[ __ ] It's madness, bro.
madness needs to get laid.
Honestly, it's [ __ ] weird that
weirdos weirdos. Their lives are so
empty. Their lives are so [ __ ] that they
have to come on YouTube every day trying
to get attention from another man.
Imagine your life being that empty.
Think of an empty bucket. Yeah. Think of
like going to a well. Yeah. A well. and
see in a bucket that's completely empty.
That's what these people's lives are
like. Their lives are [ __ ] That's why
they do what they do every day. They
can't even have a civilized
conversation. Can't even have a
civilized [ __ ] session. These are
people that are older than me as well.
Imagine that. Huh?