Here we go. It feels like [ __ ] ages,
man. Yeah, man. I just don't really
[ __ ] come on here anymore cuz it's
the same old [ __ ] every [ __ ] day. But
I thought I ain't got nothing to do for
like an hour. So to come on here. So
yeah, it's just checking if it's the
same people, same repeating people,
which it probably is always and
forever. Don't ever change, bro. Yeah,
I've got one.
Yeah, I've got a GF.
Got a good old GF, mate.
Yeah. I love how you say, "Have you got
a bird yet?" Like, I've not had many
many [ __ ] women in the past. The
[ __ ] bro? Get out of here, man. I've
had plenty of [ __ ] women, but yeah, I
do in terms of that. That's why I don't
really come on here anymore. It's pointless. It's
just It's proper pointless, bro. Like,
my main got banned. You see, I didn't
even care. Uh, I got all my memories on
my other on my phone as well cuz yeah, I
don't really care. I weren't making
money from the channel. I got everything
start. Uh, I don't really care about it
to be honest. I heard about it. I don't really
care. I think it's [ __ ] mad how
Natalie G's with Monty man because the
thing is he doesn't understand that when
things goes tits up, and it will go tits
up, it's going to go all over YouTube.
Does you not understand
that? I don't know why this is not
coming on. Sorry,
bro. Oh, I don't want donations. [ __ ]
off. I don't want to show my donation
link. Move. He doesn't understand that, you
know. You know, so I don't bother with
it. I don't react to these people anymore,
bro. I haven't had one in three years.
I've had multiple women in three years.
You got yourself confused with me again,
bud. I've had multiple women in three
years. Multiple. Even women from
different country. Again, you got
yourself confused with me. This is why I
always say when I come on here, why
share your refer? I don't want to share
my [ __ ] referral link. That is
annoying. Why does that keep coming
up? And I wouldn't get with Natalie G if
you [ __ ] paid
me. If you [ __ ] paid me, bro, cuz I
know what happens when you go out with
someone from YouTube. And you know how
you know these people ain't got a life,
right? I told you about, you know, me
being in a relationship and [ __ ] Yeah.
And these people go on and on. It's like
they've never had a bird. It's madness,
bro. What is that link? Why does it keep
saying share your referral? I don't want
no Why do I move
this? What the [ __ ] is that,
bro? I don't know why it keeps doing that. One
second. That's annoying,
bro. Uh, you got yourself confused with
me. Oh, you're getting you're getting
yourself confused there, buddy. With me
again. See, a lot of these people, these little
self-reflectors. Okay, that's a bit
better. Okay. Uh, these self-reflectors
have got their lives confused with
mine. The [ __ ] is that,
man? Why does that keep doing that?
Yeah. Yeah. I see that opening virgin
still obsessed. See the thing is um Brit
Bong is like they do you know when they
come online right they come on here they
try to bully people because their lives
are empty their lives are [ __ ] bully
victims skin fat ugly no girlfriend no
life so that's why these people like
even my friend said you should be a um
you should be a psy psychologist
um because I have these people to a tea
and other things it's like the thing is
you think that these people come on here
to torment No, they torment themselves.
Think of it. Sean and all the rest of
them, they have to be obsessed with me
and jealous of me every day of their
life. From the time they wake up to the
time they go to bed, whether they get a
reaction, whether they don't get a
reaction, they will never stop because
your you existing is tormenting them.
Anything that they do online doesn't
bother no one. Repeating self-p
projection, it doesn't bother me. You
know, when I come off of YouTube, I come
off of YouTube, bro, because I'm bored
of it. you know, I wasn't making any
money from it. Obviously, I'm with this woman now. [Music]
Um, you know, so yeah, that's it. You
know, shows you it's a you problem. It's
a me problem. I've got a girlfriend, you
[ __ ] idiot. What the [ __ ] are you
talking about? It's a It's a me problem
because because Monty man pulled a
slapper who shagged everyone again.
You've got no life experience. Yeah. And
I've got a girlfriend. Try again. And
I've had women in the past 3 years as
well. Yeah. Again, get out of your
bedsit once in a while and get some life
experience. It will do you the world of
good. Get off of YouTube for a change.
And that's another thing. Yeah. So,
that's basically it. You know, every the
whole of YouTube has had Natalie
G., you know, the whole of YouTube has
had [ __ ] Natalie G, bro. Literally,
the whole of
YouTube. Um, even if I didn't have a
girlfriend. No, that shows that Natalie
G is a slapper and she would [ __ ]
anybody but Sha cuz she rejected Sha.
But you get my point. Yeah. Yeah, I
do. Yeah, I do. So, I've been busy with
that and busy with other things. I can't
sit on here all [ __ ] day, man. I got
a [ __ ] life. I haven't drunk. Do you
know my life is so mad now, Brick Tong?
I don't even have takeaways
anymore. I don't even have takeaways
anymore, bro. I've not had a takeaway. I
get a takeaway every Saturday.
Literally, I get a takeaway every
Saturday. I don't even I don't even
waste money on takeaways anymore, bro. I
stack up [ __ ] money and all [ __ ]
sorts, bro. You know what I'm saying?
It's mad. Like, I do weekly shop. Done.
Don't get a takeaway. I just don't fancy
them anymore. When you when you when you
start cooking your own food, you just
don't crave them
anymore, you know? You just stop craving
them. It's hard. Um, I'm not telling you
what she is, but I've got one, bro.
Don't worry about
that. You know, I I you know, I've
invested in like a fryer, pans, and
[ __ ] So, you save so much money. It
tastes better. You know, it's just
better. And I just don't crave the
takeaways anymore. I literally don't crave
them. Yeah. See you later, buddy. Yeah,
man. I'm sick of it as well. That's why
you don't see me on here much. just
self-reflectors that are sad with their
lives. So, most of them, you know, you
get some decent people that come on
here, but it's not a lot of people.
So, it's just weird. It is honestly
weird. Like, they can't even have a
civilized conversation. That's why I
don't bother with
it. That's why I don't bother with it, lad.
I'm about getting on a panel to [ __ ]
entertain you [ __ ] mongos. Get the
[ __ ] out of here, bro. I don't entertain
you little mongos. [ __ ] out of here,
bro. I'm only on here for an hour cuz
I'm bored and I can't [ __ ] sleep. You
know about get on a panel. [ __ ] off,
man. Go get your own [ __ ] girlfriend.
And now you can turn around and say I've
not got one. I don't care. I know what I
have. I know who I spend my time with. I
know what I do every day.
So, get on the panel. Why don't you go
get a life? Get off of YouTube, you
know. Why don't you do what I've done for one
week? Why don't you do what I've done
for one week, bro? Get off of YouTube.
Get a life, you know? L YF E. Get a
[ __ ] life. You know, that's what a
lot of you people need on here is is a
solid life, bro. You know, sat online
every day taking out your failures on
other people. It's a madness. It's
crazy. Like you you actually it's
actually mad when you actually think
about it. Like you sit on it every day,
self-p projecting every day, year in
year out, year in, year out. It's
madness. But everyone else is skin, but
everyone else is fat, but everyone else
is ugly. Well, you don't show a good
example when you're on YouTube every
[ __ ] day, do you? Man, I don't
understand you people. I really don't.
Doesn't make you know, you don't make no
sense. I've done lots of stuff. Been
spending time with my GF. Been cooking, went
swimming. Obviously, I'm on a detox, so
I've not been out drinking, but
yeah, got an electric bike as well. One
of the most expensive one. Loads of
things, man. It's what you people should
be [ __ ] doing. You
know, having a life off of [ __ ]
YouTube. You know what I'm saying? I
don't even gamble anymore.
generally don't even gamble. I don't
even gamble anymore. It's that bad.
There's lots of things I don't do
anymore cuz that's what happens, you
know, because I always wanted an electric
bike. Uh, self projecting
again. Self projectors. So many self
projectors, bro. It's a
maza. Jesus Christ. never change. What
is that as
well? Right. One second, bro. This is [ __ ]
up. Why is it doing that? [Music]
That is so
weird. How do I delete that? I don't
want What is that,
bro? Why does that keep coming up?
Sorry, I'm trying to read your uh No, it
was just to get around
places quicker, like the swimming
pool, you know. So, yeah, that's
basically what it is. So, there's a lot
of things I don't do anymore. I will go
out drinking again, but I just can't be
bothered with it. And I don't gamble
anymore either. That's how you end up
like these people on here. That's how
you end up. You end up like these people on
here. I've actually got a projector. I
need to turn it on in a bit. Pitch black
now, ain't it?
So, actually could actually turn it
on. You know, I don't need to come
online every day trying to bother people
for reaction cuz I'm not a
sado. You know what I'm saying? I'm not
a sado that ain't got a life that has to
come online trying to bully people. It's
sad, bro. It's pathetic. Actually is.
And I'm younger than you people as well.
And I seem like I'm more mature than
you. It's crazy, isn't it? know.
Uh yeah, I had charges with Natalie G,
but I like more when I was younger, but
I wouldn't get I wouldn't get with
her cuz do you know the thing that put
me off about her is like it's Money
Mike's. It's Money Mike's uh stopy
seconds. There's no point being on here
no more. No, bro. Of course there's
not. You know, but just cuz LJ is gone,
it doesn't mean everyone needs to go
over. Yeah, there is no [ __ ] on there no more.
It's sad. It's a sad
community. The only person that you're
going to still be seeing on here is the [ __ ]
um [ __ ] the Orington virgin keep
going on about me. That's literally what
it's going to become. And maybe the odd
like Timmy, but that's it. But maybe
I'll just do other videos. I might just
do cooking videos or [ __ ] just cuz I
like pulling it on my channel, bro. Like
even if it don't get
views. I might just just do videos just to do
videos. But obviously you like gambling
and I don't gamble more
so cuz it's a waste of life, bro. It's a
proper waste of
life and I can't be bothered with it
anymore. But yeah, the only one that's
going to keep going on is is that skin
Kent virgin. That's the only one that's
going to be on here is the virgin from
Kent. The skin one on the ground a month
pin exchange. No one else is going to be on here.
That don't need to send it, mate. I've got a
girlfriend, so I don't need to send anything,
buddy. But or Timmy or maybe John West
something. Yeah. They're the only people
that will be on here, lad.
So, but do you know what I think? I
Yeah. Monty man with Natalie G because
he's trying to get Kaye jealous and he
wants Kaye to get back with him. I know
these things, lad. Uh I've not seen King for ages,
man. Yeah, he's okay. Yeah. So that's
what I personally think. And don't say
I'm [ __ ] jealous because I've got a
[ __ ] girlfriend and I can go out and
[ __ ] get a woman, you know? I got
some [ __ ] other people I'm going to
meet. I'm just saying that like the history behind it.
Like I'm telling you,
lad. No one
cares. Nobody cares where that little virgin's going,
bro. Yeah. Oh, you missed it. You missed
it, LT. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. She's been
going to his [ __ ] tent and all sorts.
Yeah. Yeah. Didn't you know she went to
his tent? They're together. They're in a
relationship. Didn't you know? Yeah. I
meant to tell you this. I was going to
email you, but I don't go on this [ __ ]
anymore, bro. So, I tried to keep away from it,
buddy. Cuz it's just pathetic. They're
all pathetic on here. Yeah. Yeah. Oh,
yeah. Let me send you the link. One sec.
One sec. I knew you'd be surprised. One
sec. He's homeless. That's why he's in a
tent. Cuz he's homeless. One
second. Okay. One second, bro.
Yeah. You would have already knew. But
that's just that. Now I know you don't go on
YouTube. I definitely know you don't go
on YouTube cuz you don't know. Let me
try and send this link. What the [ __ ] is
going on with this bloody phone,
bro? It's I'm trying to send you this
link. It's [ __ ] This phone's being weird,
man. There we
go. Yes. There we go, buddy.
Yeah. But yeah, he it doesn't matter
like Yeah, he's basically doing it um to make
obviously her jealous cuz I know how these things
are. Yeah, I know, bro. I know. It's a
madness. And LJ's run off of YouTube as
well because he got caught scamming the
charity. So he's run off of YouTube.
So yeah, man. It's [ __ ] up,
lad. Yeah, it's a madness, bro. Yeah.
How we doing,
bro? I'm in a relationship now anyways,
so I don't I'm not
drunk for [ __ ] a few weeks. I've I
have takeaways every week now. Like I'm
doing different [ __ ] bro. I don't have
time to be on here, bro, arguing with
these people. You
know, yeah, it happened. They're definitely
together. What put me off her was like,
"Oh, it's money stop you seconds. [ __ ]
that." I I wouldn't
just It's mad because he spoke so much
[ __ ] about her, but then he's with her.
It doesn't make sense. Normally, yeah.
When you talk [ __ ] about a woman, you'll
say, "She's ugly. She's ugly. She's
ugly." There's no going back. You can
say all of this stuff after you've been
with them, but you can't say it prior to
being with them and then getting with
them. It doesn't make sense. But it is
funny though. It is funny. It is
funny. But I got head like [ __ ] three
times last week,
bro. Yeah. I got head like three times
last week, bro. Believe you me, I don't
need to get jealous. I had three head three times,
bro. It's not even not and it wasn't an escort
either. So, but do you know what's going
to happen is when [ __ ] this is what he
doesn't understand. Yeah. Is when you
get with somebody on YouTube, when it
goes tits up, Yeah. it's never going to
stop, bro. She's going to stop madness
like she done with Mike. Like she done
with He doesn't understand, bro. This
guy don't understand. He's like, "Oh,
I'm coming off of YouTube when I find my
new place." Nah, bro. It ain't happening
because when when [ __ ] hits the fan,
yeah, you're going to
see. Yeah. It's a
madness. Yeah. And I'm with someone now,
but I'm on a detox. I need to save
money. I'm going away soon as well. So,
uh, yeah. I haven't really been approaching
Yeah. Yeah. Obviously,
bro. Yeah. But I've got a woman. I've
got a girlfriend, bro. So, don't refer that to
me. Don't refer that to me, buddy. You
know, you know, I've I've got a woman
that comes to me, sucks my dick, cuz
obviously I don't [ __ ] I just get my
dick sucked. So yeah, props to him, bro.
But I I had head three times last last
week. It's not even a joke,
bro. I haven't even had to go out and
drink. I don't even drink anymore.
That's the maddest thing about it. I
don't do anything like that. But
uh yeah, they're still obsessed on here
anyways, bro. These people are still obsessed, still
weird. Yeah. Anyways, that Terry is a
pussyo as well. This is what I was
trying to say to you a couple of weeks
ago. Your man was emailing me, bro.
Yeah. Your man was emailing
me [ __ ] all night, bro. I think it
was about 3 weeks ago. Bro, this guy is
no different to anyone on
here. Yeah. They're not. He is a [ __ ]
Yeah. I don't know how many people that
he's told you. Yeah. That he knows, bro.
I told him, "Fuck you and [ __ ] your
family. Tell them to come for me." I
told him about a million times, bro. And
he's he's a [ __ ] He's no different
than anyone on here, bro. Emailing and
that, bro. He's the same as Kevin
Murphy. He is a [ __ ] Trust me. He was
doing it all night as well. All night.
It was like It was like a week a few
weeks ago, bro. He's a [ __ ] He's some
little ugly tap little [ __ ] skint
little [ __ ] You can't even afford any
new trainers. I don't bother with these
people anymore. It's why you don't catch
me on here no more,
bro. No, I don't have sex. I just get
[ __ ] I know it sounds weird,
eh? No, I was just talking about Terry.
But to be fair, Natalie G goes with
anyone and everyone except Sha. The only
person she's rejected is Shawn to be
honest, but she goes with anyone and
everyone. I wouldn't get with her
me. But to be fair, she went all the way
him. So, I mean, in that situation, I
mean, if someone's coming all the way to
me, then I wouldn't turn it down to be
fair. I'm not going to sit here and lie
to you and say if someone come all the
way to me I'm going to turn him down.
No. So actually Yeah. Cuz she come all
the way to him. So fair play actually.
Yeah. I don't gamble
anymore. I've not gambled for weeks. I
haven't drunk for a couple Well, I've
had like a few drinks here and there,
but not not like that. I don't gamble
anymore. Yeah, that's actually true. She
did actually come all the way to him.
So, um, I mean, if someone come all the
way to me, I mean, my girl comes all the
way to me, but but I'm saying if like if
Natalie G come all the way to me, I
wouldn't say no. So, I'm not going to
sit here and say I would say no, cuz
obviously you wouldn't, bro. Of course,
you wouldn't. Doesn't matter what you do
with him. So, yeah, man.
Yeah. It's kind of mad how he's living
in a tent, though. It's [ __ ] isn't
it? Yeah. I wonder why she got with
Monty, man. And believe you me, bro, I'm
not jealous. I've got a girlfriend and
everything I said what happened last
week happened. I promise you, bro. Do I
go to Gambling Anonymous? Nah, just
replaced it with a different
hobby. Nah, I just replaced it with a
different hobby, lad. He's living in a
tent because he's homeless.
Obviously, he broke up with Kaye. He's
homeless, so he's living in a tent. Yeah. So,
yeah, I don't even get takeaways
anymore. I' I've been cooking like for
the past week. Like I said, I get a
takeaway every Saturday and that's
it. So, I'm different now, bro. And I
don't come on here anymore.
Even though people are still obsessed
with me, you
know. I don't know. Why does it keep
saying share your referral link? [ __ ]
off. That is so
annoying. I might just turn it into like
a cooking channel or some [ __ ] I know
people like the gambling ones, but I'm
not doing that gambling [ __ ] no more.
What meals have I cooked up? I've got a
fryer. I cooked up chips, pork chops,
steak, [ __ ] everything. I've been
cooking up madnesses, bro. I've been
cooking up I just I need to do fried
chicken from scratch, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. So, I've got all
my He's a creep. He needs to go get
laid. He needs to go lose his virginity.
he'd stop being so bitter on YouTube.
You know, I've been busy cooking. I've
been busy with my [ __ ] girl, bro.
I've been busy doing [ __ ] But these
people are still on YouTube every day.
Something's not adding up here,
lad. Yeah. Pork chops, steak, [ __ ] I
got a fryer, so I do chips and [ __ ] but
we'll do some proper proper
cooking. I'll just do the cooking and
the gambling. Uh, sorry, the cooking and
the traveling videos. I won't do the
gaming ones anymore. I don't I haven't
played it, bro. Honestly, I haven't. I
bought myself a tracksuit the other day.
Yeah, it was 140 quid. I ain't bought
clothes for like 6 months. I was like,
"Oh, I've saved all this money." Yeah.
Not eating out. I might as well treat
myself to a [ __ ] tracksuit, rather
than it. It looks clean, bro. Trust me,
it's a clean one as well. But
yeah, it's been good, bro. I've been living good.
How does he power? That's what I
wondered. How he powered up his phone.
That's what I was
thinking. I'm on the rosters tonight.
Yeah, that's what I I don't understand
that either. I don't understand
that. Maybe power battery. I was
wondering exactly the same thing.
Yeah, he's with Natalie
G. Yeah, I came in this bitch's mouth
last week and she swallowed it. She swallowed baby
Peters. But I don't know how he does it.
I don't know how he does it. I've got a
projector. I need to turn it on. [ __ ]
Hell. Sorry, but I'm not even on
comments. Yeah, he's living in Heis life
actually got ruined over YouTube, guys.
If you actually look at me and Monty,
his life actually got ruined over YouTube.
Mine was just pain in the ass. Some
inconveniences. My life never actually
got ruined over
YouTube, you know. So, people thought it
did, but it actually didn't, you
know. But he's actually did got he's
actually did get ruined over
YouTube. My man's living in a tent, bro. Imagine that.
Like that is
crazy, you know, cuz if you actually
think about all the things that happened
to me, it was actually me and not
YouTube. If you actually think about it.
Yeah, I stressed the lane out, but that was
me. That wasn't people on YouTube. That
me. That's what people don't understand.
It was all me.
It wasn't people on, you know,
YouTube. Yeah. But yeah, it doesn't
matter. Anyways, he's living in a
tent. So that's crazy.
Why? I was listening to Natalie G saying like,
"Oh yeah, I thought you would have knew
about the Natalie G thing." That's what
I thought. I think you called me the
other day and I thought you was calling
me to tell me. I was like, "Bro, I
already know. I've been watching
it. I've been watching it,
bro." And obviously he can't he can't
say his mom's because the kids are there, you
know. Yeah. And he can't go to his mom's
because his kids is there.
Uh, so he's [ __ ]
basically. Imagine that. Yeah. Last
takeaway I got was I've had I've only
had two takeaways this
month and it's basically the 11th. I
done food shopping Saturday.
Well, take away Saturday, but since
Saturday, nothing. Not even a Weather
Spoons. I like shopping and stocking the
fridge up, you know. So,
yeah. And I know I just have a takeaway
every week. Maybe I'll just go for a ro
dinner this week.
Maybe. No, because maybe somebody would
have told you or something. Yeah. Yeah,
I know what you
mean. Yeah, maybe. What? Um, I don't
know, bro. Maybe you would have seen it.
I don't know. Yeah.
Yeah. That's mad. Why do you think
Natalie went with him anyways? It's not
like he's got loads of
money. I think he's with her to make Kaye jealous.
That's what I
think. Yeah, it's summer. I'm I'm still
saving for a month. It's summer. It's
not really summer. It's not summer until
like May, but I'm saving a few more
weeks and I'm going to have fun. Fun in
the sun. Fun in the sun. Fun in the sun.
That's it, bro. It's not
that It's like
[ __ ] It's like spring. It's It's not
It's not proper summer till like next
month. Trust me. It's not It's not warm
enough to wear shorts. It was hot last
week actually, but that's it. I really
fancy a drink last week. Like some beer
and that, but obviously I'm on this detox, so
my income. No, it isn't, mate. I ain't
got a lot of
income. We're not talking about my
money. That's unlimited money. I wish I
had unlimited money, man. I [ __ ]
don't. I would be
saving or like [ __ ] GTA unlimited
money in it. Imagine, bro.
Nah. What a wish,
man. Why do you think I eat in Save
money, is it?
So that's what I'm saying with these
people. Like I don't bother with them,
bro. Because you go live, oh your skin,
oh you're this, oh you're that. Ask
yourself this question, bro. Yeah. How
would these people know what is in your bank
account? How would these people know?
Like these people didn't even know that
I'm in a
relationship, you know, and like how
much money have you got? So if they
don't know who they're talking about,
then they must be confusing themselves
with confusing you with
themselves. That's the only logical
thing it can
be. They must be talking simply about their own
lives, you know. So, and they are
talking about their own
lives cuz bro, I could be I could be a
millionaire. I could have one pound in
the bank. Who would only know but me,
you know? But that's that's what I'm
saying. They talk like they know
people's lives and they're weird, man.
And they're older than me and they're immature.
So, you want £1,000? That's nice, man. I don't gamble
anymore. Can't be [ __ ] with it.
Yeah, it's nice for him. I had three [ __ ] last
week because you don't work. Because you
don't work in your world's biggest. Okay, bro.
Yeah. Ah, yeah. Yeah, bro. You keep thinking that
anyways. Yeah. Stop gambling, bro. It's
[ __ ] It's not worth it. [ __ ] gam,
bro. Go do some cooking like I do now.
Just go cook some food. It's what I do,
bro. I just
cook. Take up a hobby or something, man.
Uh, apparently he's
uh he's scammed some sort of
charity or something. He's scammed some sort of [Music] charity.
Um, and basically he got caught out
scamming the money he was supposed to
give to charity. He didn't give to
charity, a donation, something like
that. He's deleted his account and ran away.
So, he's done
for. Like I said, bro, the only person that
uh you will still you will still see on
here is the Orington virgin going on
about me and Timmy. That's the only two
people you're probably going to be
seeing on here. Now, there's no L J.
There's no me for the most part. There's
probably not going to be Monty for much
longer. Did you see Shan's thing? He
says that he's going to Amsterdam. I was
like, "Oh my god, you're so behind."
Imagine being 31 and your first trip
abroad. [ __ ] hell. I was doing that
[ __ ] when I was
23. So skinned and so behind there.
These people really, really are,
bro. I need to get my provisional sorted as
well. Take some driving lessons.
I need to do some things, bro. I can't
be on it like these
people or on it, bro. You know, it's it's [ __ ]
weird. But when the weather's nice, I'm
going to go swimming. So, actually, you
can save money in the summer. You, you
know, you just go swimming. If you, if
you want to go out and drink, just go
swimming. Go for a bike ride. You still
can do it
easy. But it is harder to save in the
summer. It definitely is. I mean, your
your but you can still do it. Your peak months
are January, February. They're the best
time to save. Anywhere after that would be
harder cuz of obviously it's been
summer, but I'm booking a trip as well.
So, I'm just saving some money to have
spare money as
well. No, bro. I don't watch I don't
watch these people,
bro. Yeah, I don't watch these people,
bro. I can't be asked with
it. I got this [ __ ] now that comes and
sucks my dick.
So, a lot of people look like him, bro.
Why do you think they do this [ __ ] every
day? Look at this,
bro. No, I lost your channel cuz you
changed the handles.
But the thing
is it's like Red Star, right? There's a
lot of people like um Money
Mike, you know, you got Red
Star, you got, you know, these people
are unhappy with their own lives. And
you know how I know because LJ was live
the other day before he left, right? And
it was one of the days where it was
scorching outside. It was a nice day
outside. I took a ride on the bike.
Yeah. I come back. Same
people. Hold on a minute. Wait. It's a
really nice day
outside, but they're on YouTube. This
isn't making sense, bro. This is not
looking right. Everyone else is skinned.
Everyone else is ugly. Everyone else is
alone. But these people are sat on
YouTube on a summer's
day. Something's not adding up, bro.
Must be talking about their own lives.
You notice you'll notice this stuff as
well. You you you'll notice like when it
gets to June, July, right? You will take
a day out to the beach or you go on
holiday, they'll be on YouTube all day
and all night.
Pathetic. You know what's going on?
Nothing. We're just chilling and talking about the
latest Natalie G and Monty.
Yeah. It doesn't add up, bro.
Yeah, I don't want any part. I mean, my
Listen, LT, my my main channel got
banned. I don't care. The only thing I
cared about was the memories, but I've
got all my memories on my phone. I'll
just start again. I'll just start from
scratch. I don't care. I weren't making
money from it. Even if I was making like
£300 a month from it, I'd be pissed off
cuz I mean, it's £300, isn't it? Like I
weren't making no money from it. So
why? Like you know what I'm saying? I'm
not making no money from this [ __ ]
channel. They're [ __ ] losers, bro.
That that that keep bothering people
every [ __ ] day. So
yeah. No, I don't know if you're a
[ __ ] bro. I tell you who is a [ __ ]
Your boy Terry, bro. Don't Don't let him
try to talk like he's about anything,
bro. We've all seen me go to his area
and he didn't show up. Please, bro. Like, it's
embarrassing. And the emailing and that.
The emailing like I can It's funny
looking back at it to be honest. But
this is what I'm saying, bro. It's not
even like they type a few things and
they start you start going mad and you
start punching things. This guy, I had
to block him on emails, bro.
I had to block him on emails, bro. This guy's
pathetic. And he claims that he knows
people about that about Bro, it just doesn't make
sense. One second.
Oh, sorry about that,
bro. Someone's calling me. It keeps going off.
Yeah, LG. I've not seen Laney for about 6
months. and you tried to tell me that I
weren't independent and then you hear
Natalie saying, "Oh, money might can't
work a washing machine." Bro, I've been
I've been washing my own clothes since I
was 14. I literally haven't seen my mom
for about 6
months. That's actually a madness when
you think about it,
bro. Yeah. So, uh I've been working a
washing machine since I was about 14,
15. I can cook, I can clean, I do
everything, bro. I done my whole
passport. done my passport myself as
well. Yeah, it's fun,
man. Misty inending
that. Am I out this weather?
Nah, no. I told you, bro. I'm on a detox
and I'm saving some
money. Well, well, technically I am out.
Well, no, no, I will be out. Probably
going swimming, actually. Yeah, you
didn't specify what you're doing when
you're going out. I probably will be
out. Yeah, maybe go for a walk. Go for
swimming. Go for a swim. I ain't been swimming in
years. So, yeah, I actually will be out
swimming actually. What am I talking
about? I'm saving for nothing. Well, I'm
saving to go away again. That's what I'm
saving for. Nah, not in the pool. I've
got a girlfriend
now and I don't really care about that
anymore. At least for a while. Nah,
bro. 6 months is a long time in it. Uh,
LT. No, I don't need to go in the pool.
I've got a girl
now. Oh, damn it. What's wrong with
this? Your link. I don't even see this
[ __ ] You didn't miss anything. I just
don't put everything on YouTube.
I've been out a few times, bro. And
yeah, I'm just with someone and I'm just
going to go
swimming. You like swimming, don't you,
LT? Good old
swim. You know, it gets boring. You
know, this whole going out. No, no, no.
When I when I sort stuff out, Yeah. I'm
going to go out every week drinking, but
that's because I want to go out every
week drinking, not just to get women. I
like going out and drinking and [ __ ]
you know, I then I just I was still
approached anyways. Even though I'm with
someone, I was still approached. But I
mean, I would only do it in the bars and
clubs when I'm drinking because I'm
going out to drink. It's something to
look forward to every week, but not at
the moment. I want to detox, but yeah,
it's fun, isn't it?
So, every Thursday, every Saturday,
we'll switch the days
up. So much to look forward to every
week in it, I guess. But I just ain't
even been doing it. Last time I went out
was two weeks ago on a Friday. I didn't
even spend any
money. No, it gets boring, bro. Going
chasing women. It's boring, man. I just
thought I'll just stick with this
person. Nah, it gets proper proper
boring. It does. No, it does get boring.
You need to switch up routines. You know that,
LT? It's like when you go to the same
gym over and over and over again. Have
you noticed after about three months you
get bored of the same gym? So what do
you do? You switch gyms. You switch up
your routine. But you don't switch up
your routine where you wake up a
different time. You switch up the
environment and stuff that you do. It's weird. But
yeah, that's what I do, bro. It's
boring, bro. It is boring. But I will go
out drinking every week again at some point.
But Ant-Man goes out every week and he's
going Thailand in like two months. You
can go out every week and
save. You just get your haircut every 3 weeks, I guess.
But yeah, I'm sure you
could. The man
be Yeah, I had some [ __ ] woman keep
asking me for money.
And I gave her money. Then I gave her
money again. I was like, "Listen, this
has got to stop." You know what I'm
saying? This is not the real world. This
not how the real world works. You want
money, go earn your own money. Stop
looking at me for money, bro. It's
annoying. Like, do I look like some sort
of [ __ ] or
something? Like, it got annoying, bro,
after a while.
Like, if it means they want to cut
contact, they can cut contact. I don't
give a [ __ ] I'd rather be by myself,
bro, than keep having some [ __ ]
vulture, you know, around me. You know
what I'm saying? I'd rather be by my
[ __ ] self. That's that's that's what
I'm in. It's someone else, bro. It's
pissing me off. It reminds me of what my
sister used to
do. No, it's not funny, bro. It is
annoying. It is. It is annoying, but I'm
not some [ __ ] mate. So, don't
[ __ ] treat me like one. You know what I'm saying?
So what, LT? You're not going to go out
raving until you come back. Why is that,
bro? Well, you don't think you can save
and go out drinking every week? Well, Ant-Man does
it. Yeah, you can. I mean, how much
would you realistically
spend on a night out just drinking? What? 100
quid? Food shopping. How much is food
shopping? Say say well I done £35 of I'd
done £35 worth of food shopping and that
lasted me like nine days. It was good
food as well. Um no he hasn't not that I know of and
and the other thing
was Yeah. So how much would you spend
when you go out just drinking? Yeah,
probably about £100
120 I'm guessing. So roughly you can
live off £200 a week
comfortably with no rent and that I'd
say about 200 a
week. I mean it's a lot to spend a week
though, ain't it? 200 a week. But that's
how much it would be drinking and
[ __ ] Maybe you get a
takeaway. I don't know, bro. It's
expensive, is it?
What could you do, LT? Could you go out
every Could you go out every week and drink? Yeah.
Yeah. But it does take like here's the
thing here. when I'm when I when I was
trying to save, right? I found it hard.
Yeah. But then you sort of get used to
it. It's hard like at first. Yeah. Like
the first four days I was like, "Oh, I'm
getting urges to like get a takeaway."
It weren't gambling. It was to get a
takeaway or to go out for a drink. But
then I just got used to it and you just
sort of get used to it where you're in a
routine where you're not doing it. So
you stop getting these urges. You know
what I'm saying? Yeah, it's uh
Yeah. Yeah. It's a madness, bro.
Yeah, it's a
madness. But yeah, if you have urges to
go out drinking when it's
sunny, you can just go
swimming. I mean, that would work. You
could there is things you can do in the
summer. But I know what you mean, LT,
cuz I was finding it hard like about
nine days ago. Yeah, I was at the start
of the saving. And I was like, "Oh, I
really want to go out drinking. I really
want a Guinness and that in it." Like I
was really fancy in a Guinness cuz the
weather was good, but now it's gone [ __ ]
again. So yeah, like I said, your best
chances are the winter, but you can
still do it in the
summer. Trust me, there were ways. Just
go swimming or something if you know
there is ways in the summer to
save, you know, for a little while. Go
swimming. What's it like 1 pound502 to
go swimming? There you go,
man. But it is hard in the summer
because you fancy drinking. You do fancy
a drink and that and you can, you know,
and I've got nice summer clothes from
what I bought last year.
So, yeah, it's [ __ ] up,
bro. I knew you'd find the Natalie G
thing funny, though.
I knew I bet you couldn't believe it
when I told you in
it. Oh, it's
mad. Oh, it's funny, bro.
[ __ ] She liked me
though, you know. She did like
me. I wouldn't. See, the thing is I
would never get with a woman on YouTube.
I would never get with a woman online
birth. You know what I'm
saying? The link. Um, that's
why. Yeah, but you only have two months
to stack realistically because November
is expensive, December's expensive,
January and February you can save and
then after that that's all you can only
save for two months. But I mean, I've
saved I've been saving for like two
weeks. I just been cooking and [ __ ] So,
you know, I've still been
saving. I might go
Disneyland. Maybe. One second. I'll show you this
thing. This is his channel and he's got
like different live streams on here.
Cuz I remember when I was
saving Cuz I remember when I was saving last
winter, it seems to go really fast. But
now, now it's summer, it's going really
slowly. Just drags on and on and on. So yeah. Yeah.
How's your How's How's your girl Morgan out
here? How's your girl Morgan? You still
chatting? You still doing
chats? You still doing chats? A L [Laughter] T bless
you. Now she's always been a pig. What
are you talking about, LC? I always
thought she was a [ __ ]
pig, you know. I thought she was a
[ __ ] pig when I first saw
her. No, she's a pig, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. She's weird,
man. Yeah. She saw Monty's kids as well.
Like, she met This is so weird, bro. She
went into Monty Monty Man's mom's house
and she's actually met the
kids. She's actually met the kids, bro.
That's [ __ ] madness, isn't it?
I thought she was a [ __ ] pig. If you
ask me, I thought she was a [ __ ] pig. [Laughter] Yeah,
man. No, she wasn't. No, she went in the
mom's house and she she was like she was
saying about kids and that and I thought
that was a bit personal, bro. Like she
was saying about, "Oh, your kids are so
nice. like I feel sorry for your kids
and that and I was trying to put myself
in Katie's shoes and if anyone was
saying that about my kids, bro, that
would piss me off. I'm not going to lie
to you. Even though I don't have kids
and I'm not Katie, but it's
like you've just met her and she's met
your kids already. That to me, I don't
know how these things work here, but to
me that seems a bit weird. How the [ __ ]
You've just met this woman once and
she's already met your kids, bro. That's [ __ ]
weird. That's what I found was a bit
weird. That's what I found was strange.
And then she was talking
like she's known them for years. It was
weird, bro. Like proper
weird. Yeah, I I thought that was quite
strange as well.
Yeah, it's a big thing in any culture,
mate. It's a big thing in any culture,
lad. It's a big thing. I thought it was
weird as well. I thought it was weird, you
know. Yeah, it's weird. It is weird. That's
weird. I thought it was strange. And I
don't even have kids. Don't talk about
my kids. No, I'm not single, but you
are. I've got a girlfriend now. But you're
single. But I know you're
single. I'm not, but you are. Yeah.
Somebody said to me, yeah, they didn't
realize I'm in a relationship now. They
were like, "Oh, uh, you're married. Of
course you are. Yeah, everyone on this
community is married. Isn't that mad?"
Yeah, you're another one that's
married. Um, anyways, somebody said,
"Uh, yeah, of course you're married."
Yeah, everyone's married on here, isn't it? Everyone's
married. But anyways, uh there's like,
"Oh, well, look, Monty Man's got a
woman, so that means the problem's not
women, and the problem is you." Well,
hold on a minute. Firstly, I'm in a
relationship. B, even if I wasn't in a
relationship, no, Natalie G's a hoe and
she [ __ ] anyone that would provide from
her. So, no, Monty just got a slag that
wants to use him, so she went to meet
him. How can they use [ __ ] How old
can they How can they [ __ ] How can
they use um She's 21. How can you use
her as an example,
bro? Oh, you're a keyboard warrior.
Yeah. And you're Oh, you're dusty, are
you? Yeah, you're bad, buddy. See you later. Sorry,
Dad. Yeah. Bye-bye, little loser.
Uh yeah, she's
21. Sorry, this is going to be [ __ ]
up, bro. But
yeah, you understand what I'm saying? Um yeah.
I mean, yeah, if you think about it, it
is [ __ ] up. Like, I've got I've gone
out trying to get women, and even though
I've had women, it weren't worth it, and
they're just [ __ ]
anyways. Like, my opinion still stays
the same on women. They're entitled.
They're [ __ ] They're [ __ ] I
still think that, but I just don't care about it
anymore. And anyone that tells you
they're not like that are absolute
simps. And that's me telling you
straight as a man now, bro. Like anyone
that tells you
otherwise, they're just simps that don't
have no life experience. And I'm telling
you, bro, because you, you know, they're just
Yeah. When you deal with enough people,
you know what they're like, lad.
Um, I don't know the story. I think they
argued and then she kicked him out and I
think she went to live with her
mom. I mean, I'm in a good position LT
and I don't even think about women to be
honest. I just told you, bro, there was
one girl that kept asking me for money
over and over and over and over again.
Yeah. And I told her basically where to
where to stuff it. I don't care, bro.
I'd rather have no one than have
somebody that thinks they can take the
piss out of me. Like even in my
position, I still don't I don't care
about them, bro.
Like, so let alone in his position.
Yeah, you're right. You can't live with
his family member because his family
member has got the kids and he's not
allowed near the
kids. These women will bring you down,
man. They'll bring you down, buddy.
You know, you think that, oh yeah, you
get a woman. No, they'll ruin your life.
They'll bring you [ __ ] down, bro.
Even the people that I used to speak to.
And I can't think of Let let me let me
let me let me go. Let me just go back a
bit. Yeah. I'm trying to think of all
the women that I've met, and it's always
been bad news. If you actually think
about it, no good has ever come from
them. They just bring you down, you
know? That's what they do. They actually
bring you down and they create problems
that you don't need in your life,
bro. And that is the truth. Like, I've
never had someone that's not like that.
Honestly, we don't need, you know, they
bring you down,
man. And that's it. It's the
truth. They're all the same. They're all
NPCs. You don't [ __ ] need that, bro. The
[ __ ] I don't bother with them anymore.
He gets highway pip and get one
bedroom. I don't know, bro. It's probably
expensive. I don't know, bro. It's probably
expensive. But that's what these women
do. They bring you down,
bro. That's what they do. They bring you
down. They're devious. They're devious.
They're cruel. And they're
entitled. They're so entitled. Like,
even ones I've met. Yeah. And I've had
stuff with, like, you can just sense the
entitledness. But I don't really deal
with them anymore. I don't bother with
them. I don't really bother with
it. I don't bother with it anymore, mate.
I met Trolls as
well. Trolls as well,
bro. You know what I'm
saying? Yeah. He's
not. Yeah, exactly. Exactly. It
does. I know he's not used to it. No. Yeah.
Yeah. That's how most people live in
London in shared
rooms. To be fair, most people live like
that because the price in London's so expensive. So
yeah, could you imagine I had a baby PT?
These people would want the baby
removed. Baby Peter straight into
care. Oh, what what a lovely site.
You know what I've noticed with women as
well, LT? See, I'm gaining with I'm
gaining life experience.
Yeah. I had a friend. Yeah. This is how
you know I've got life experience unlike
these people. And she was nice. Yeah. We
were just friends and stuff. And as soon
as she goes, as soon as women go for
these guys, Yeah. that are [ __ ] or
drug dealers, doesn't matter what color
they are, it's not a race thing. You'll
notice that they become [ __ ]
You can get a woman, right, that's like
20% entitled, normal, just like a normal
nice person, and as soon as they stop
going with these people, they start
turning into [ __ ]
themselves. I don't know if you've
noticed that, but I've definitely
definitely noticed that. I know I
noticed that with a friend. Um, and then
it they they start turning into that person.
It's weird, isn't it? It's proper
weird. They start turning into these
[ __ ] that they go
for. That's what they do. It's
weird. It's very
strange. Let me see.
Yeah. Yeah. I've noticed that about
these women as
well. I've noticed that.
They're very entitled
to you notice that they're very entitled. Yeah. bro
it. So, Virgin Legs is going to
Amsterdam. Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro. How
many times have you said you're [ __ ]
going away and you don't [ __ ] go away, bro? [ __ ] [ __ ]
Amsterdam. Could you imagine virgin legs
under the sea? You'd be like, "Well,
this is not under underground now."
Whether it's a euro store [ __ ]
plane. Could you imagine,
bro? Um, it's not underground. It's all
about going down south. [ __ ] [ __ ]
virgin skin to the
eyeballs. Probably had to [ __ ] book
it about a [ __ ] year and [ __ ]
advanced, you lad.
They left you alone,
bro. See, you're lucky, bro. At least
when you leave LT, man, they leave you
alone. These people never leave me
alone. They're obsessed with
me. Like, you don't understand, bro.
Like, I don't think you understand, LT.
I've just gone on this. Like, bro, these
people are actually obsessed with me.
Like, whether I'm on here, whether I'm
not, whether I react, whether I don't
react, they will still do it. They will
still do it. They still, even if I went
to prison. Yeah. Say I was in prison,
right, and I couldn't get a phone, they
would still do it.
This is what I was trying to explain to
you on the phone, bro. That there's a
big difference between autism and
jealousy and people doing things for a
reaction. Like these people are jealous
of me. I'm better looking than them. I
got more money than them. And they don't
like it. So what they do is they try to
get a reaction out of me. So you know, I
I stoop to their level. People doing
things for reaction are people that
um people that like bother Timmy because
they know that he's going to react to it
or they bother
[ __ ] they bother people cuz they know
that they're constantly going to get a
reaction. But these
people are mentally ill. This is what
I'm saying. Because sometimes I think
about it, bro, when I'm like
um obviously when I'm not on here and
that it's autism and jealousy, but
obviously the first the first one's
obviously definitely autism. It's
gone. They literally monitor my whole
life, bro. They're obsessed with me.
Like, I'm not even joking.
I know you don't want to go on the
channels cuz it's annoying and that, but
bro, you I think you don't actually understand. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. But they stopped after a
while though, didn't
they? I don't bring it on most of
myself. No, I don't bring it on. How do
I bring it on myself? Okay. Okay. Okay.
I'm not on YouTube, right? And they
still do it. So, how am I bringing it on
myself? I'm trying to get on with my
life. They won't shut up about me. So,
how am I bringing it on
myself? How am I bringing it on myself?
Answer me that
question. So, I'm not going to be on
YouTube for 6 months, for example. You
come back on YouTube, they're still
talking about you. How are you bringing it on
yourself? That doesn't make any sense.
You got Instagram thoughts when you on
YouTube. What are you talking about,
bro? Okay. Okay. My Okay. So, you need
to you need to specify what do you mean
by in I don't even heard that word
before, bro. These people have listen. I
don't think you understand, right? These
people have been doing this since I
first come on
YouTube. back before I met
you. Do you not understand? Oh my
god, bro. They they've been doing this
before all of
that. Yeah. Do you not understand, bro?
These people have been doing this before
all of that. They're mentally obsessed.
They've got autism. Like, and I'm not
even saying that as an insult. My friend
even said to me as well, used to be a
psych uh used to be his um psych um
psych psychologist. He
said, "No, bro. These people have been
doing this even when I first come on
YouTube. I don't What What do you think
these people are, bro? I don't think you
understand what these people are in this community.
What what do you think these people are
behind these fake accounts? Red Star,
all of these other
people. I can tell you what they are.
Fat, ugly, agriobic, no life. That's why
they're on YouTube every day. Does it
not add up and add up and add up? Do you
not understand the puzzles? Um the
pieces to the
puzzle? Have you not got the pieces to
the puzzle yet?
If these people had anything going on in
their life, they wouldn't be doing this.
Regardless whether they want a reaction
or they don't want a reaction, they get
a reaction, they don't get a reaction,
they would be living their best life.
Why are they not living their best life?
Not adding up again. See, and that's why
I should be a um
psychologist. All old as well. None of
them are young like us, lad.
See, and this is what I'm saying. These
people do this and they will never stop
because it is jealousy. And I know you
don't like that
word, but it's jealousy. Because for
these people to do this every day,
they've got to be jealous of something.
You understand? And I'm trying to make
you understand this,
lad. They're sat fat, ugly, skin loners.
So that's why they're on here every day.
See, I'll give you an example,
right? So, I come off of YouTube
sometimes a week, two
weeks, whatever, 3 weeks, whatever it
is. These people can't take one day off
of YouTube. Why is
that? Okay, you're trying to say that
I'm watching. I'm not watching. But let
me rephrase that. How comes I can take a
week or two weeks without commenting on
YouTube, but these people
can't? There you go. I just rephrased it for
you. I don't understand that they can do
it. I don't understand. And they're
older than me as well. They're older
than me. Some of them are probably even
double my age to be fair. They're older than
me. They're older than me. And it's
because they do it because they've got
nothing in their lives. That's why they
do it. That's why they do
it. Even at Donald Birmingham come off
of YouTube and he's [ __ ] agrophobic.
Well, to be fair, most of these people
are agrophobic, but he was just honest about
it. I think it's cuz they're skin,
they're fat, they're ugly.
Um, you know, and that's why they they do
it. But most of them do live on here.
Yeah. Like you get the odd one like Jay
Willow. He doesn't live on here. Like
you might get an odd person, but people
like Red Star, Harry F, they literally
have nothing but YouTube. Literally,
YouTube is literally their whole life.
Like, it's mad, isn't
it? And you know, the longer you're off
here as well, the more you see how
[ __ ] up it
is. Like, you could be off here for like
2 weeks, right? And you could just be
randomly cooking or something and you
think, "R what they do is actually mad."
Like, no. No. Again, no. What they do is
actually mad, bro. Like, every single
day. Like, cuz when you're on here every
day, you'll think, "Oh," but you really
see what normal is and what is not
normal. These people are not normal,
bro. They're not
normal, you know? They really are sad and
pathetic. And And the thing is, they
make me and and and do you know what
they do, bro? I feel sorry for them.
like they don't bother anyone. They
don't bully anyone. I actually feel sorry for
them. Like I could not imagine like
coming on YouTube every day stalking
someone, making videos of someone. I
literally that could never be
me. Like that could never ever ever ever
be me. That is weird, bro. That is so [ __ ] weird. So
yeah. Yeah, it is mental health. It
defin It's autism. What it is is it's
it's autism and jealousy. That's what it
is. I've I've narrowed it down, man.
It's it's autism and jealousy.
Deo and you forgot to mention that even
when they get a reaction, they still don't stop.
And I think that's one of the another
main thing is that even when they don't
get a reaction, they still don't stop.
So I think that's something that Yeah,
it's like you said, it's mental health. It's
autism, you know, autism,
OCD. Yeah, it
is. That LJ's definitely got autism. And
I think he's got it more than we think
does. Yeah, it is. How the [ __ ] did we
ever come across this place, bro? How
the [ __ ] did I ever ever
ever come you [ __ ] [ __ ]
community. You know, I feel like a
[ __ ] loser, bro, when I'm on it. I'm
not even joking.
Yeah, with me obviously I didn't have a
child and that but you know I had
different sources of income. I visited a
lot of places. I went to loads of
restaurants. I made loads of new
acquaintances. I mean I progressed not
in the same way as having a child but I
progressed in other ways and done things
you know. So I've also progressed you
know you know I've also progressed but
obviously not in the way you have
because we're different in it but I've also
progressed you know especially there was
a year bro there was a year obviously
you don't see it as I've gone away but
in that year when I went to Amsterdam
when I went to Belgium and that bro that
was in a period of about a year yeah
like think about it I probably done more
in a year than they had done in their
whole life. And obviously I chilled out
for a bit, but I progressed in different
ways, but I just obviously I didn't have
a kid and work, but you get what I mean.
So, and they they are in the same predicament. They
are they are right. Yeah.
Yeah, I know, bro. They used to piss me
off, these women. They don't piss me off
anymore. They don't piss me off anymore,
bro. Still think they're all the same
and they're entitled [ __ ] but you
know, I just just don't
care. Just don't care about him, bro.
is what it is. They're all devious.
They're all the same. So, what do you expect in
it? But yeah, they are in the same predicament.
Yeah. It's like Timmy. What's Timmy done
in his life, bro?
You know what has Timmy done in his life,
bro? He's [ __ ] 40 years of age. You
know, why don't any of these guys just
be up in real life and do something
social speaking every day and there. Um,
I can answer you why. Uh, I can answer
why. I put my hand up. I can answer you
Um because they've all got anxiety. Do you not
understand? They have got anxiety and
autism. Yeah. That's why they don't do
it because they're too anxious to leave their
house. There you
go. Yeah. That would be Yeah. Then then
I could actually rate it like Bomb Tra
all of them. Yeah. All meeting up. Then
I'd be like, "Okay." Yeah. Yeah, that
that would actually look good, but they
can't do that cuz they got
anxiety. They're insecure as well about
their the way that they look.
So, yeah, they've got anxiety,
lad. Yeah, they got bad anxiety, bro. Bad
anxiety. You should have known that,
bro, when I went Newcastle and [ __ ]
people didn't even meet me in a friendly way.
Yeah, they've all got anxiety, bro. All of them
have. Why do you think none of them meet
you like even in a friendly way? You understand? So,
yeah. But I know that I'm better than
all these people anyways, LT, because if
I wasn't better than these people,
they'd leave me alone.
See, that's how I know I should be a
psychologist. Because if they if they're
better than you and you're the skint one
and they've got all this money, then
they'd leave you alone and live their
life. That's what I'm saying. If they
were a normal person, they would leave
you alone and live their perfect life.
But they can't cuz their lives are [ __ ]
That's what I'm saying, bro. That that's
another way you you you also know because
Yeah, I know who you're talking about
anyways, but you get
Yeah. And they're actually batty men as
well, bro. Like, even when I've been in
love, bro, I've never done this. Never
done this level of stalking. They're
actually batty, bro. They're actually
gay. I'm a lot better than looking you,
you little virgin. I've got more money
than you. I'm better looking than you. I
get more money than you. I dress better
than you. And I've had better women than
you, [ __ ] virgin. Bye-bye now. So
listen, lad. Um, you know, even when
I've been in love with people, I'm sure
you can relate to people that you've
been in love with. LT, do you go around doing this
[ __ ] Do you go around doing this
[ __ ] No, you don't. So, are they gay or
something? Maybe they're gay. They could be gay.
gay because obviously I can't relate to these people,
but what is it? It's It's autism. I
think they're autistic. They're gay and
jealous. I think Yeah. I think autistic
gay jealous maybe. Nah. Nah.
And it's like all of the all of the
stuff right that I've I've I've like
when I've been mad at people before like
you know people I'm not going to mention
names I dropped it in the end bro cuz I can't be
bothered. I can't be [ __ ] It gets to
a point where you're like you just can't
be [ __ ] but these people never seem to
stop. I think they're [ __ ] gay or something bro. You
know, I think they're [ __ ] gay for me. Yeah.
Really? See, you you see Monty doesn't
get any of this. This is what I'm
saying. LT Monty doesn't get any of
this. Oh, do you know how hypocritical they are?
Uh Monty said that he's calling the police on
um um for making allegations allegations
and [ __ ] about
him. And then he was like, "Oh, I'm
calling the police. I'm calling the
police. I'm calling the police." This is
how you know you'll never win on this
community. And then what? Guess what?
Everyone called him. You're a grass.
You're a grass. You're a grass. But it's
okay for the people to call the police on
us. like Virgin Sea, [ __ ] Pat
Mustard, like [ __ ] you know, all
these other people like Trouble. Okay,
so it's okay for them to call the police
on us, but then and I don't even like
Monty, but then when Monty man wants to
call the police on somebody making
rumors to ruin his life, he's a grass.
From that moment, you'll know that you
will never win with these
losers. You know what I'm saying? Like
that's mental, bro. Like, what the [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] maniacs, bro. Is
it? I think they just [ __ ] target
anyone that's got a better life than me
personally. You also see the same accounts, LT, you
know, you'll never win. You got to
understand that you will never win. So,
you're best off just doing your own
videos and ignoring these little weirdos.
That's what you're best off doing.
You'll never win with these people, bro. Trust
me. Like, you really think that I
can't You really think that I I can't go around tomorrow, bro?
And, you know, put posters up of that
virgin again. But I can't be bothered,
bro. They're not even worth my time or
my money. Do you understand? They're not
even worth it. You know, you're already
living in their [ __ ] head. You don't
need to spend any more [ __ ] money, you
know. But you get my point with the
police figing it. You get my
point. They're weirdos, bro. The
weirdos. You need to do videos like
cooking videos, going to the gym,
something like that. Bro, you'll piss
these people off so badly.
You'll slap me up.
Oh, you'll slap me up. Well, you didn't
slap me up last time I went to your area
when you screaming how you're not a
fighter. You would slap anyone up, you little
virgin. Have a word with yourself. I
said the same thing to LJ.
Yeah, to be honest with you, I might
just do the videos on this channel to be
honest. [ __ ] it.
There's nothing they can do. Yeah. You
know, just turn the comments off. But
yeah, as I was saying, yeah, if you if
you want to do videos, Yeah. you need to
do videos like the gym, traveling,
cooking, you can't do gambling videos
because when you lose money, they get
off on it. Even though we can afford to
lose money, we got more money than them,
but it's still not a good thing. So, we
can't gamble because we can't just show
wins because it's not a proper gambling
channel then. So, but then obviously
it's like L's. If you don't gamble, you
will have no L's cuz obviously cooking
food, gym, traveling, whatever it is
you're doing, there's no there's no L's.
There's not another side to it. You know what I'm saying? So,
yeah, I will do a new channel to be fair.
Yeah, just send it to people on Instagram,
Reddit. Take us L's.
Yeah. Uh, and no, you didn't um take my
channel down. I actually porn bomb
myself. Try again, Virgin. You didn't
get my channel banned. Actually, I porn
bomb myself cuz I showed my dick to this
Scottish woman and it got banned. You
didn't get my channel banned. Try again,
Virgin. You see, this is what I'm
saying, LT, is that none of the stuff
that's happened, right, has ever been
through any of these
people. It's never been through any of
these people. Like my channel getting
banned, like the stuff with my neighbor,
it was all me. This is what I'm trying
to say. It was It was all
me. Yeah. Make a new channel. That's true, you know. Yeah.
I'll just go live on this channel and do
my other videos on my other
channel. I got loads of approaching
videos, man. Like unlisted ones. I've
got it to put up.
Yeah. So, how do these people not find
you? You must change the handles or something.
Anyways, I need to go in a bit, bro.
Call me in it.
Um, I need to speak to
you. Call me quickly. I need to talk to you,
buddy. my number. You don't have my
number. You should
do. Everyone's got it on YouTube, bro.
[ __ ] that [ __ ] chase docks
me. Yes. Oh, [ __ ]
sake. No. Call me one sec.
It's uh what is it? [ __ ] god. Yes. 07460 052 412.
Give us a little
bell. Give us a little
bell. See, with you, you're actually a
good troll. I like you. You're a good
troll. You're actually a good troll,
man. That's my number, by the way.
Everyone's got it.
So, give us a bell. [Laughter]
Give us a bell out [Laughter]
here. No, seriously, bro. Come on. Yeah.
I can't speak on the
phone cuz I'm coming off of YouTube,
bro. Um, for like another week or two
weeks, but I can't stay in this place
longer than a day,
lad. I physically can't stay in this
place longer than a
day. Literally, imagine that longer than
a day, bro. No.
I hardly can't, you
know. It's too weird, bro. It's too
weird. This isn't painful. I got a headache.
Do you know what? I'm going to create
another channel now,
actually. Yeah, might as well. Hey,
Virgin Boy, when are you going to
Amsterdam? You little skint flint on
£1,000 a month. Anyways, might as well
chat some [ __ ] now. I'm not going to be
on here for a little while. Oh, you
little skint virgin.
You finally going abroad after 31 years.
Screams skin to
me. No, I haven't seen it, bro. That
screams skin to me, virgin
boy. [ __ ] hell. After 31 years, you
finally saved up enough money. You
really are the definition of skin. Oh,
boy. You're so skinn. You're so skin it actually
hurts. Oh, someone's knocking on my door
at half 12. Oh, really? We've heard that
one before, buddy. Boring. And this is
exactly why you don't see me on YouTube
no more. Because it's the same
repeating. Yeah, it's the same
repeating. Same repeating. You don't
know my area and you don't know where I live. Same
repeating. You're lying. Nobody cares.
I'm coming off of YouTube in a minute.
You're not making me stay another half
an hour. We've played these games before.
Um, no. Sorry, bro. I'm not entertaining
people that will never meet me. And you
should know this, LT, bro. You don't
like keyboard warriors. You don't like
keyboard warriors as much as I do. So,
why are you telling me to let him up
when you know he's just going to talk
[ __ ] and be a keyboard
warrior? Shame on you,
buddy. Shame on you. You know that the
virgin's never ever going to meet me under any
circumstances. So why am I going to sit
there and argue with somebody that's
never going to meet me that just wants
to talk [ __ ] in these little virgin
bedsit? Does that sound logical to you?
Doesn't sound logical to me, bro. You
know why am I going to sit there and
argue with some toothless little benefit
freak on a,000 a month little virgin, right?
that's never ever going to meet me. What
a waste of time. What a waste of life.
How did he find my address? He doesn't
know my address. Nobody knows where I
live. Anyways, the only ugly one is you,
mate. Have you seen your [ __ ] face?
You look like a [ __ ] rat. Have you
seen your ugly face? You look like [ __ ]
golem, you ugly [ __ ] Have you actually
seen how ugly your face is? Like, have
you actually seen, buddy, right, how
ugly you really, really are? Like,
that's actually me saying like, "No
wonder you've had to resort to a [ __ ]
disabled girl cuz you're so
ugly. Have you actually seen how ugly
you are? I think you're getting yourself
confused with me again. A, you're skin.
B, you're ugly. C, you're on a grand a
month. How can you call anyone
skin? Doesn't make sense." But no, no,
no, no, no. Have you seen that ugly face
of yours? Have you actually seen Listen,
listen. One one second. One second. Hold
on a minute, bro. One
second. Hope you end the lead. Hold
on. Let me get a
nice Excuse me. I think this this guy's
actually uh taking a piss here. He must
be taking a
piss. Um, excuse
me, mate. There's no
way that thing is calling me ugly. LT
LT, there's no way that ugly
face is is calling me ugly. There's no
way that ugly skinned face is calling me ugly.
No one with a face like that is calling
me ugly, mate. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no. With a face like that on a,000 pound
a month is ever trying to critique me,
bro. Do you remember? Hey, do you
remember before? Yeah. When he was
trying to say when he was trying to say
a grand a month is decent. A grand a
month is nothing. That is literally
peanuts. Bro, do you know Hey, LT, bro,
do you know how much I spend in two
weeks? £1,000 a month. He thinks a,000 that is
nothing. Bro, listen. I used to get like
Bro, listen. That is literally nothing.
£1,000 a month is nothing. I don't know. Yeah, that's
nons. He's [ __ ] ugly. Look at that
ugly face. He's so
ugly. He's so [ __ ] ugly. How can you
talk about my face? I've had better
women than him. I get more money than
him. How can he talk about me?
A grand a month is decent. He's so
skinned. Okay, let's look at the facts
here. Yeah, he has no designer clothes.
He has no bed. He's never been abroad
ever. He's never been on
holiday. Screams skint to me, buddy.
That screams skint to me. that schemes.
So he's got all this
money, never been abroad, no designer
clothes, no bed, lives in a bedsit,
passport battle expire, something's not
adding up here. Remember what I was
saying, LT? When when things don't make
sense and things don't add up, they
can't be true, bro. You know, you know,
you literally have You show me more than
1K, bro. You need to show me 12 grand.
Remember, I showed you, well, sorry, no,
let me let me be more specific. I showed
you 5.7 grand. So, you need to show me,
let's just say 10 grand. Come back when
you got that 10 grand, buddy. Come back
when you got that £10,000 that I've been
waiting for somebody to show me for
[ __ ] months cuz I showed 5.7. I could
tell a lie and say, "Yeah." Yeah.
Anyways, it's the same old, bro. Yeah,
it's the same old same old. This is why
I don't come on anymore, bro.
Yeah, lad. This is why I don't come on
here, bro. Yeah, we're going round
around in circles, bro. Yeah, this is
what I'm saying. You get deep into it.
Yeah, bro. We're going round and round
in circles. Yeah, it's boring. Same old
argument. Same old people pretending to
come on your door. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I
know. I know, bro. Yeah, it is actually
the same old argument. [ __ ] hell.
These people need to grow up. You've
shown more than 10 grand. You've never
ever shown 10 grand in your virgin life.
And if you had if you have actually shown
£10,000 while you living below the
poverty line, how have you made it to 31
years of age and you've never been
abroad? Your passport's about to expire.
You've got no assets and you've got no
bed. Something's not adding up.
Something is literally not adding up.
You are sklinter than a [ __ ] skint
flint. Look at what you wear. Look at
them shitty clothes and that shitty
face. And you're trying to tell me that
you've got money. A Gucci watch, bro.
Gucci watches are worth [ __ ] all.
They're literally worth [ __ ] all. You
are sklin skintter than a [ __ ] skint
flint. Literally. I've bro I've never
had £10,000 in my life ever. I've had
about seven and I've done way more than
you have. And And I'm I'm younger than
you, Virgin boy. Virgin boy. I'm younger
than you. Something's not adding up.
You're saying that you've got all this
money, but you've never been abroad. You
have no assets. Something is not adding
up, buddy. Something is not adding up.
Literally, my wardrobe back at my mom's
is worth more than your whole house. Any
assets in your house, my garments is
worth more than anything in your
house. Virgin boy, you need to go get
laid. Literally, I can't believe you're
31 and you're still a [ __ ] virgin.
That must haunt you. Virgin boy. Virgin
boy. I love it when you when you say
something and you say, "Must be a
virgin." You know all about him cuz
you're the biggest one yourself. You
know all about the virgins because
you're one yourself, virgin
boy. Because you're one yourself. So you
know all about virgins
delayed. doesn't mate. What assets have
I got, mate? I'm not the one claiming
that I've got p£10,000, but I've never
even been abroad and I've got no assets.
That doesn't add up. If you've got
thousands and thousands and thousands,
why are you living below the poverty
line? It doesn't make any
sense. Thousands and thousands of
thousands. You see, this is how you used
to catch Bomb out with his lies. You
know, Bomb Yeah. before he got exposed.
It's It's things that don't add up.
Things that don't add up. They don't add
up, man. You know, when p when you're
trying to put the puzzle to the pieces
together, right? But it's just not
adding up, you know. So, this version
from Kent claims that he's got all this
money, no bed, no assets, never been on
holiday, no car, no driving license. He
lives in this shitty bed sitting Kent.
It's not adding up. Sorry, buddy. It's
not adding up. And you've also claimed
that you've shown £14,000.
N that doesn't make
sense. That really really really doesn't make any
sense. That really doesn't make any
sense. Uh you don't even have a TV. Uh
yes, I do have a TV. I work in TV. Try
again. Yes, I do. Uh yes, I do have a
TV. And the reason I didn't have a TV
for so long when my other one broke is because
um because I don't use a TV. So yes, I
do have a TV. Try again. Stop talking
about people that you don't know. So um
yeah, I'm not showing you nothing, mate.
Just like I'm never showing you no money
again. And it's getting that time where
it's uh it's past my bedtime. And yeah,
you [ __ ] are boring me again. So
yeah, I'll see you in about 2 weeks when
yeah, I'm have some free time again.
Have fun living your life on YouTube,
being obsessed. See you in about two
weeks. Bye-bye now.