banging up. choose the back. [Music]
Get up there
side this side. [Music]
Yeah. Have enough function. Bro, you
have to go
out. I'll risk my whole recovery for
this. Use the whole recovery for this, bro.
Again, hold me.
Back to my whole foot. [Music]
I don't know. Hey already I'm tired. [Music]
Hey, what's up, bro? Bro, I literally
risked my whole recovery for this, bro.
My [ __ ] up his old foot. I swear to God.
I [ __ ] up my whole foot, bro, for
this. I need to go Thailand, bro. 100. I
need to go Thailand. I [ __ ] up my
whole foot for this. I couldn't walk for like three
days. Oh my god,
bro. Three days. Yeah.
Imagine that for having an opinion,
bro. I love it. I got
banned. I got banned from a spoon for
giving an opinion. Imagine that. Yeah, I
can't believe it. I got fanned from an old
spoons given a [ __ ] opinion. The guy was like,
"Listen, bro. I had a mad day today. I
almost broke my foot again." I was like,
"I'm sick of the women in this country."
Yeah. He's like, "Oh, I'm 37. Not all
women are like that." I was like, "I'm
27, mate, and I've been in this country
longer than you know anyone, and I'm
telling you how it is." Yeah. He wanted
to [ __ ] try and tell me how it is.
I've been here, mate, since I was
[ __ ] born. I know what these West I
know I I know what these West Liz
countries are like. Don't try and tell
me what this is like. Yeah, I know it's
Yeah. Don't sit there, bro, and try and tell me
how how it is. Yeah. I give it back. But
when I gave it to him, do you know what
he done? He backed away. You shied away.
Yeah. You want to stay facts? I'll stay
facts to you, bro. This country is [ __ ]
It's a westernized country. It's full of
[ __ ] And I'll say it to your face,
mate. Yeah. Any security. Don't stop
shying away now, mate. Yeah. Listen,
bro. What happened, bro? Man was in a
spoon, brother. Yeah. An absolute
[ __ ] spoon, bro. Yeah. He was like,
"Bro, I was telling this guy about the
women in this country and he was like,
"Oh, don't say it to me." I said to him,
"Yeah." I said to him, "Mate, I will say
what I want when I [ __ ] want to say
it." I said to him, "Well, mate," and he
go, he goes grassing to the old
bartenders, don't he? And the bartender
comes out. Yeah. Well, that just goes to
show that you shouldn't listen to what anyone's saying,
bro. Sorry, man. Sorry, man. YouTube very good,
mate. And he he was saying about
how he was talking madness, mate. Trying
to square up here and like that.
You don't come on YouTube anymore, bro.
It's full of low lives. I don't care
about YouTube. It's full of low lives.
They ain't got a life. Listen, Slim, are
you the Scottish lad? Yeah, big up to
you, mate. These people ain't got a
life. They ain't got a life. Stand up,
brother. You know what I
mean? Mate, listen. All these people
that you name Slim, they ain't got a
life, bro. Marvelous. I don't come on
here anymore, bro. I come I'm just
coming now cuz I'm a bit pissed. I'm fed
up, bro. But these people have not got a
life. This whole sector sector that you
go on, brother, they don't like their
lives. That's why they come on YouTube
every day doing what they do cuz they
ain't got a life. They have to bounce
off their own lives to people that
they're jealous of. And I will tell you
the same thing, bro. Sober a sober same
thing. They ain't got no life. YouTube.
You see, bro, I was off for two, three
weeks. I'm gone again. I don't care
about the these people, bro. They ain't
got a life,
bro. [ __ ] them. They ain't
important. They ain't got no life but
YouTube. So, let me let me say it to
Bro, let me say to your broken words,
brother. Yeah. No life but to your
That's why they're on here every day cuz
they ain't got a life. Bro, I've been on
a date today. I've been on a date. She
turned out to be a bit of a dick, but I
went on a date. All of these people
here, they ain't got a life. They've got
no life for trying to ruin other
people's lives. Go figure, bro. Listen,
that's all I got to say to you. I ain't saying no more. I mean, you [Music] darling, bro. Yeah,
baby. You're my angel. My
darling, you say here we come again, bro.
Yeah, I know you're from Scotland, bro,
cuz I spoke to you before. Ditch this
site, bro. It's full of weirdos. It's
full of low lives. Honestly, brother,
they ain't got a life but trying to ruin
other people's. That's their life. What
does it say about them,
bro? My angel. You're my darling angel.
The guy found me from spoons. I was
like, "Mate, you're not going to sit
there and try and lecture me." Yeah. I'm
a 27 year old man. Yeah. I've got more
life experience than you will ever have.
Don't try and tell me what women are
like in my own country. And he got about
it. So, I thought, "Fuck you." Yeah. Slim.
Listen, bro. My brother, I'm coming to Scotland again
soon. Well, don't listen to anything you
say you hear on YouTube. They're all low
lives. Literally all low
lives. But listen, I don't need to get
one more than 1% [ __ ] happened to me
that he did to Monty to for me to say,
"Fuck this place. I'm out of here, bro."
Yeah. If I lost my kids over YouTube,
I'm out of here, bro. I'm done, bro.
Like, I'm done for other reasons and I
don't have kids to
lose. Yeah, I'm
done. I drinking it. [Music] I'm looking.
Okay. To say to
you, girl, I don't want to be excuse for
it. Spread to the kids no
more. But he needs to get off
YouTuber. He needs to get off
YouTuber. He needs to stop a YouTuber. Yeah.
I went on a date today, bro. Yeah, check
this. First date in the whole year and
she was an [ __ ] mate. Literally, I
voiced it to people in the spoons and
the manager banned me. He banned me for
having a different opinion. I wasn't
being violent, abusive, nothing. The guy
was being an absolute dick. Yeah. What's that? [Music] Excuse
me. You know what I'm saying? It's a [ __ ] madness,
bro. It's been a mad day, bro. And I'm
[ __ ] recovering from a [ __ ] foot
injury as well.
I'm recovering from a [ __ ] injury,
bro. Yeah, I had a foot injury. I
couldn't even move my foot,
bro. I recovered from a foot injury for
this [ __ ] [ __ ]
Look, bro. I [ __ ]
bro. I had [ __ ] foot injury, bro. For
three days. I sacrificed everything to
go on this day today. And she turned out
to be a
dick. She turned out to be a proper
[ __ ] Got two other numbers. I
didn't even plan to go out today, bro.
I'm pissed off. [ __ ] it. I don't know. But
yeah, I don't know, bro. None of them.
Listen, listen, listen. These people are not about
it. Let me tell you something, bro.
They're not about any of it. Listen.
Monty man and Tibby are not about none
of it. Because if they were about it,
they wouldn't on YouTube talking. Bro,
real roadmen, real gangsters don't come
online talking to each other. Oh, I'm
going to do this. Oh, I'm going to do
that. They don't talk. They do. Yeah.
Ask Charlie. Yeah, I've met
Charlie. Last time I went to Knots, I
met Charlie. He's a sh He's a sound guy.
People about that life don't talk. They
do, brother. Yeah. Trust me. Trust me,
bro. They don't talk. They do, bro. You
understand? I'm not scared of no one.
I'm not talking about who Timmy, bro.
The fact that Arsenal, Mark, and Timmy
are still doing calling out videos, yet
they know several people's different
addresses. They're not about that life,
bro. And that's cool, little bro. But
don't come on here talking like you're a
bad man, bro. It's ridiculous. Charlie,
I love you. I've always got respect for
you, Charles. Yeah, I met you in
Nottingham. You're a down to earth guy.
You're a cool guy, bro. I ain't got no
bad words to say about you ever. Like
you're probably like the only real one
on this community. I love you, bro. And
you know that. I told you that when I
met you in England. I love you, bro.
Like, yeah. Not Charlie's a cool
guy. Charlie's a cool dude. 100%. I
ain't got no bad words to say about you,
Charlie. Otherwise, I'll say, bro, I'm a
realist. Charlie's a legend, man. He
stays at the drama, but he advises
people. He's a cool
dude. You know what I'm saying, bro?
He's a cool
dude. Charlie, love you, Charlie, man.
We'll meet again, bro. 100%. Even if it's
outside for three or four straight, this
[ __ ] got me out, bro, on a day and I had
a foot injury. Charlie, imagine this. Yeah.
I had a foot injury, brother. Yeah. From
like I put like a lid in my foot, bro. I
I didn't recover. I didn't recover, bro.
Properly. So, I went out cuz a day, bro.
I almost died,
bro. But it's all getting better.
My foot was swollen in blood. I think I
pulled a muscle or
something. The jail room is true, but
obviously not cuz I'm not in
jail, bro. Anyway, Charlie, message me
on Facebook, bro. If you ever want to
talk ever, just message me, bro. I'm
your boy, bro. I love you, man. Charlie,
bro, I got respect for you, bro. You're
the realest. You're one of the realest
on here. I love you, bro. Understood.
Charlie, I swear I would say this, bro.
I met you in person. Yeah, Charlie's a
good guy. Big
up. Big up Charlie, man.
I spoke to I spoke to I spoke to
Australia. Are you [ __ ] [ __ ] from
Australia, mate? Yeah, I got her
number, mate. I literally recovered from
a [ __ ] injury to come out today and
I'm wasting my time. I'm going to be
[ __ ] for like three days, bro. Yeah,
boy. Might as well be out. Madness,
mate. These women go on to people,
Charlie, to waste their [ __ ]
time. Yeah, I went out last holiday.
That's last week. That was the first
time in 6 weeks, bro. I was like, "Fuck
it. Go out. It's been five, six weeks." Madness,
bro. [ __ ] England. [ __ ] the West.
Big old Charlie. That's my boy. [Music]
B of them.
I want to extend
it solo today, man.
Even it's a shame it ain't a [ __ ]
Saturday, is it? [Music]
Oh, I [ __ ] up
first. I [ __ ] my foot up.
My foot is
[ __ ] I literally sacrificed my recovery
to go on the stage today only for her to
just be like all the other women. Yeah.
I was on the weather scoo. I was talking
to this guy about the woman. He said, "I
don't want to hear it." I said, "You're
going to [ __ ] hear it cuz I will say
what I [ __ ] want to play." That's
what I said to him. He goes to the
manager. She's going to give me a
lecture. Like, mate, I've been in this
country longer than you, mate. You might
be 34, but I'm 27 and I've been here
longer than [ __ ] you, mate. Yeah.
Don't [ __ ] come to me trying to give
me a [ __ ]
lecture. Yeah. I ain't scared of no time,
mate. Yeah. Don't [ __ ] sit there and
try and give me a [ __ ] lecture. Yeah.
start and finish it, mate.
Yeah, good. No one cares. This little [ __ ] bro. Back away.
Yeah. Got two numbers. This [ __ ] [ __ ]
traveled a [ __ ] whole hour to that [ __ ] [ __ ]
She so the [ __ ] out of her I got the
[ __ ] foot injury. I tell you exactly what I
got. What's it
called? I have literally
got paranal tendonitis in my [ __ ]
foot, bro. I got Bro, I got peranal
tinitis in my [ __ ] foot, bro. I
couldn't even walk for like 3 days. I
sacrificed this whole day to go on a
date because I thought [ __ ] why not.
Don't [ __ ] try and tell me what guy
I'm telling you. Yeah. That's what I
told him. I said, "Listen, mate. I'm
[ __ ] telling you. I'm telling you,
bro." Yeah. Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
off. That's what I said to him. I said
it sober, bro. I said, "What you going
to do about it, big man?" That's what I
said to him.
I [ __ ] my whole foot up and I I had to
go doctors take painkillers. [ __ ]
man. Ain't it funny,
bro? Boss, can I get a double spice
raises with a bit of life? Bit of life.
Bit of life. Got to be.
Imagine that. Recovering from a [ __ ]
infection that almost
imagine this. Yeah. I had a foot injury.
Yeah. I was recovering. I had a foot
injury. I was recovering three days.
Three days. And I went today to go on
the states and she turned out to be a [ __ ] that
tomorrow. I'd say pain is everything
bad. I thought my leg
li What do I do for a living? I make money.
Yeah. Got ways not illegal. Not legal, but
[ __ ] What What makes you
ask? What makes you ask? What made you
Listen, it don't sound serious, but I
was dying, but like I was in pain for
three days, bro. Yeah. Yeah. I'm like
walking, bro, on a limp. I'm turning my
I'm turning my foot to the [ __ ] bathroom,
bro. Done. Done, mate.
Done. I'm surprised I'm living, mate. I
swear. Like you think people don't take it serious
here because it's a pain further to kill
me. I swear to
God I think I pulled a
mate seriously pain you wake up every
morning. There's no different than a
tooth or a headache like [ __ ] it. Watch
me. Let's go out. You see
be careful with your foot. Wear socks, bro.
You got [ __ ] limb. I'm walking like
I'm going to walk there. I'm [ __ ] mad. This
almost ain't funny. Almost.
Oh, where was Mr.
B? I got two numbers here. Two numbers.
Two number. It's good though.
But the reason the woman just off today
was two days ago injury. I had a foot
injury. I just came to come out to go
out of her and I and I done that and she
still [ __ ] around, bro. You know what
I mean? So now I've got to recover for
like another three days cuz bro, you
know, in this country, she get a woman
all day. It's hard nowadays. So when you
got it, bro, I'll go in a wheelchair. If
I have to go in a [ __ ] wheelchair number hard
again cuz you got to get them to apply
and then you got to get them to meet you.
Oh, what do you do for me then? Yeah,
that's what they ask. Yeah.
They to be picky, bro. They've got
unrealistic standards. They've got this
perfect man in their head. And if you
don't standards, they don't. But the
perfect man don't exist. And when
they're in their 30s, they understand
the perfect man don't exist. That's what
they're standing for. You know what I'm
saying? This the perfect don't exist for
anyone. But I
mean, but it's a
mand. And even if I had to go in a
wheelchair today, I'm going in a
wheelchair to go st I'm going in a wheelchair.
[ __ ] it's hard to come by for April.
April 24th. Yeah. This is my first date
this whole year. Yeah. Last I'm
not [ __ ] off. You get women here though.
They come to you
know they come to
me with your number give it to them and
they got the
choice I don't know I'm going
I don't know what I'm doing [ __ ]
off write your number on the paper give
it to them and say fiction
yes I wanted to talk to you
officer. That's what I'm saying. Why
your number out? Give them
next Saturday. Saturday. [Music] But the
day. [ __ ] this.
I'm out and about, mate, with a
fractured [ __ ] foot. I'm out and
about with a [ __ ] foot, mate. Yeah, I
know. Unbelievable, is it? No, that
ain't unbelievable, mate. Cuz I
sacrificed my recovery today, to go out
and meet this
woman. Listen, Subzero, you wouldn't do
anything, mate. You're a keyboard. Just
like most of you haters on here. You
keyboard warriors. You would never do anything to anyone. Save
yourself. I got two numbers. Two
numbers. I think I pulled a muscle, man.
I went out a few days. I pulled a muscle.
be even worse tomorrow. Yeah. [Music]
But I need to go anyways. I need to set
up some birds, mate. I got two numbers.
Don't need to get some more buff. It's
looking It's looking
dodge. It's looking a bit dodge, isn't
it? Right. Catch you in a BL.