Oh, my photo, man. [ __ ]
hell. I need to sit down
here. Where are these
pills? Here you go. Yeah,
man. [ __ ] hell. It was a long one last
night. They said I was in jail. Oh, did
they? How did How would have they known
if I'm in jail, bro? It doesn't make sense. In
jail. Same people every day. That's why
you don't see me on here, bro. Yesterday
was really, really bad.
I'll get on to it in a minute, bro. Let
some more people join. It was bad. This
is why I was going to go out today, but
I need to stop for my own mental health.
Like, I need to stop drinking. Like, I
was on I was on a straight I was on the
straight and narrow yet for ages. I started drinking
again, going out, approaching again,
eating takeaways again, and it just it
just got bad. That's why I need to stop,
bro. I need to stop cuz it it was bad,
bro. Like, yeah. bad. Why does this
always come up? Yeah, I went out. Okay,
so [ __ ] me. Hold on. I'll go on to it.
Yeah, same old I've got a boyfriend. Okay,
so I went out last week cuz I thought,
[ __ ] it. Yeah, I want to do a I want to
do a um I want to do a bank holiday,
Good Friday, all that good stuff. Yeah,
I haven't been out in like four or five
weeks. So, I was like, let me go out
Friday and Saturday. I went out Friday
on on Saturday. Now, this woman
approached me, right? And she was like,
"Oh, yeah. You're good-looking." I got
her number and was texting like
literally every 5 minutes she was
responding. I got seven numbers in them
two days. She replied, "Weren't
interested." She seemed genuine. She
seemed interested. We're on to something
here. I got a foot injury, which I
couldn't even walk straight. My [ __ ]
my whole foot was swollen, mate. I
literally had to crawl to the bathroom.
I was like, "Listen, this woman wants to
meet me on Thursday, which was
yesterday. You know, if I have to go in
a [ __ ] wheelchair, I'm going to go in
a [ __ ] wheelchair, mate. Because at
the end of the day, opportunities like
this are hard to come by. Yeah, they're
hard to come by, bro. So, I thought,
"Fuck it." Yeah, let me let me let me
go. So, I'm waiting. I'm meeting her
now. She's a bit older than me. Vibing
and stuff. Didn't even really like her.
It's not even like I liked her, but the
whole thing just pissed me off.
talking. We had a drink, went to a bar,
bought a few rounds, and then she was like,
"Um, oh, like when when do you want when
do you want to meet again?" I said to
her, she like, "I don't really feel the
vibe." And I just looked at her like,
"Are you being deadly serious? Like, you
knew what I look like. You knew what I'm
about cuz you met me in person. You
approached me. You gave me your number.
And you've come an hour away to meet me.
are you taking the [ __ ] absolute piss
about you? And I didn't even like her,
but it was the whole principle. It was
the whole principle of it all. And I was
like, "Fuck this." And then after that,
I literally just went out, sent it, sent
it, sent it, sent it, sent it. I got
three numbers. I got one reply, bro. So, yeah.
But it's madness, bro.
And that's it, bro.
Yeah. Um, so it's just been bad, bro.
It's It was bad. But to be honest with
you, I actually And you know the maddest
thing about this now? It's not even fun
going out drinking anymore. This is why
I gave up. This is why I gave up. I done
my own [ __ ] I started cooking. I'm done
with it, bro. I'm done with it. Like, I
shouldn't have went out last week. I
because, you know,
it's we're going through the same thing
again. Even though I hadn't done it for
like four or five weeks cuz I don't care
about it anymore, bro. I'm just living
life. But, you know,
um yeah, it's bad, bro. So, yeah, it
kind of like Antman went out today. I
said, "Oh, I'll meet you if you want to
go Sheffield." But I'm not really in a
mood to go out. Like, I'm I'm done with
it now for a long time again. that it
was just just the ultimate piss take.
And I didn't even like them. It weren't
even that. It's just like who? It's just
a principle. That's what you you need to
understand with things. It's just a
principle. I remember like messaging LT
at like 2:00 in the morning saying,
"Bro, this ain't right, bro. I'm telling
you, this ain't right." So, it just
seems to make it even more
hopeless. It seems that it's making it's
making it more and more and more
hopeless. Do you know what I'm saying?
And obviously you got to deal with
people's attitude. And then I went to
Weather Spoons and after that I'm pissed
off like as anyone would be pissed off.
I'm drinking. I said, "Oh, I'm sick of
these westernized women." And this guy was like,
"Oh, I don't want to hear it. I don't
want to hear it." I said to him, "Well,
you're going to [ __ ] hear it whether
you like it or not." Like, bear in mind,
I weren't in a [ __ ] mood. And then a
guy calls the manager over and he says,
"Oh, like what's this about you saying
about like all women being the same?"
came and I was like, "Yeah, I
generally," we was having a debate for
like 10 minutes and it's like, "Bro, you
might be 37. I'm 27 and guess me. Guess
what, bro? I've had a lot more life
experience than you. I've been through
hell and back through been through pains
that you wouldn't even imagine. Just
because you're 34 and I'm 27. Don't mean
nothing. I've been in the country longer
than you. I am from the West. I am made
westernized. So, I know how these women
are." And then he wanted to start a
debate and then when somebody said
something he didn't like he then walked
away. I was like bro and I'm thinking in
my head bro this is all negative. This
is this all stem from going out last
week drinking and look what it's caused.
Look at what it's all caused again. You
know what I'm saying? And this is why I
don't I don't do it anymore, bro. I
can't do it today even if I force myself
to do it today cuz I'm genuinely not in
the mood. There's no point going out if
you're if you're not in the mood.
But yeah, man. And I got a headache as well.
So it's bad, bro. It is a bad It's bad.
It is bad. It is
bad. And you know, things were uh things
were looking good as well. You know, you
know, see my mom, see my sisters. It's
all sort of getting back to normal now.
I was cooking, saving. And I'm thinking,
bro, this has got to be it now, man. You
went through all this stress. You
basically broke your [ __ ] foot. This
person wants to meet you. This might
literally be all you waiting for, bro.
All these years. And guess what? They
were just the same, just like every
other woman. And that's why I don't
bother anymore, bro. I don't bother
anymore. Clues in the title when I told
you she [ __ ] approached me. That's
why I don't care anymore, bro. I said,
"No, I'm not going to go out drinking
today. I'm going to go go get myself a
nice curry. I'm going to get myself a curry."
And obviously, I couldn't walk for a
little bit. And trust me, mate, just
because you've got pain in your foot, it
doesn't make it any more less painful
that it's not in your head or it's not
in your mouth. Bro, I could barely walk.
Thought I was dying, bro. Swear to God,
I thought I was
dying. I had to go back and then pick up
the [ __ ] prescription. So, it's
crazy. But that's life.
And now and the thing is on once you do
this again you go out drinking you know
eating takeaways you go approaching
women it's very hard to go back into
that lifestyle that you was in cooking
giving up not bothering being stable
normal you feel like I feel like that's
always a bad start to anything you don't
go to the gym for two days you go out
drinking don't go
back anything you start you can't finish
that's the thing bro and I was like I'm
not doing this [ __ ] no more fine
And people say like, "Oh, well, don't
you just go out to have fun?" Like,
"Don't you just want to go out, have
fun?" But it ain't fun. You're going out
drinking ain't fun anymore,
bro. That's the thing. It ain't fun. So, yeah. Crazy,
man. But what can you do?
E my cup of
tea. Oh, and my fridge packed up as well.
Yay. Cuz the thing is, right, in life,
right, what do they say for in life?
You're supposed to strive of positivity,
right? This whole dating thing is
negative. Do you understand? Let me let
me let me tell you something, bro. Yeah. Literally. Literally.
Right. It is a
negative. Do you understand what I'm
saying? It is literally one big fat
negative. And you're supposed to
strive for positivity in your
life. This is negative. This whole
dating thing is negative, bro. You know,
I woke up today with the whole like I
swear to God, bro, the past four weeks,
yeah, I was cooking in, saving money. I
was chilled back, got no anxiety, no
worries in the world. Yeah, it might be
slightly boring, but I have other goals
that I want to do. This seems like we
we're still going backwards now. Yeah,
we are we are literally going backwards.
And take this year from an impartial
party. I literally went out last week
and that was the first time in four or
five weeks and I'm still dealing with
this [ __ ] I'm still dealing with this
[ __ ] And I said to man, I don't know
how I am still in this
country. Yeah, it will happen. You keep
telling yourself that, buddy, mate.
Well, it won't be happening for me cuz
I'm out this country soon. So, it won't
happen for me, mate. All you're going to
get, it's like, okay, it's like even today,
right? You know that if you go out
today, exactly what will happen. I've
got a boyfriend. Okay. Number number don't
reply. Number don't
Um, you know, and then even if you get a
date, that happens. No, you don't. It's
not going to happen. You give up and you
move on with your life. That's what
you're supposed to do. That's what any
uh normal person would do. You know,
it's not normal, bro. I don't know where
I'm headed, mate, but [ __ ] out of
this [ __ ] hole.
what they call Great Britain. There's
nothing great about it. So,
yeah. Why do they waste their time and your
time when they know they're never going
to see you again? Like, we Why do they
waste their time and your time? I don't
get it. Why have I got this [ __ ] as my
picture? I don't understand why they
waste their time and your
time when they have it in their head
like they're not going to see you again anyways.
So now it's to the point that we can't
even go on dates. We can't even get
numbers because we know that if we get
any of that stuff, it's no use. And just
remember in your head as well, if
anything was going to happen, it would
have happened by now. Always remember
that in your head. And I remember in
[ __ ] mind, man. Sorry. Oh
Yeah. Bang my [ __ ] foot. I get better as
well. I was
a perile in I can't even say the
word. A paranal
uh paranal insoci
patient. That's what I was, mate, for about two
weeks. Yeah. But yeah, I know you don't
really see me on here much anymore, bro.
I'm I'm just done with the whole YouTube
thing. Bors me, mate. Bors
me. I got a new hoodie, by the way, if
you like it. Got it ages ago. Well, say
ages ago. A couple weeks
ago. So, I just just I just got out the
shower, by the way.
So, why why why why don't I try hooking
up with Kayen? Uh, can't be
asked. To be honest, I don't really come
on here much anymore. I don't want
anything to do with any of these people.
They're just low lives then.
There's there's no other way to uh to put
it. I might go and play a slot somewhere
there. At least I'll save that 150 or
something. I need to clear my head,
bro. It's no good. It's not nice when
you feel like you're going backwards,
know? But I'm I'm done for like two weeks,
bro. It's [ __ ] is
it? Yeah, I'm a bit hung over. That's
why I look [ __ ] Sorry about that, man.
don't care, bro. I'm not interested in
any of these people in this community,
bro. I don't care. It's part of the
reason I'm not on here anymore. I just
come on here to rant and just talk about
life to people that are not on here.
So, I don't care for anyone on here,
bro. I don't care about weird
drama cuz I've been, don't get it
twisted, I've been listening to some of
this and to me, let me tell you my
opinion. I've I've been listening to
some of this,
bro. I've listened to Mark Samson. I've
listened to Timmy over the past two
weeks. Bro, do you really think big hard
men that are big hard men come on
YouTube? They don't. Do you think if
this Arsenal Mark was a big man, he
would be making videos on YouTube? Do
you think if Timmy was a big hard man,
he would be making videos on YouTube? You
know, so with L J and Mark Samson, it's
repetitive. It's the same old. Like I
watched it like I don't watch it every
day. I think I was watching like two
weeks ago. They were mentioning my name.
They were mentioning my [ __ ] name,
bro. And it was pissing me off and I
just ignored it. You know, mate, I'm not
saying anything, but I know that real
gangsters don't come on YouTube making YouTube videos.
Um, and you know what made me laugh here
is Timmy was saying to Monty, "Oh, like
yeah, like you're a grass. Monty's a
grass." And I'm thinking in my head,
"Bro, Timmy, all your followers are
grasses." You know how many times I've
been arrested over this website? About
20 times. Like all of Timmy's followers
are grasses. Every single one of them.
I've never met so many grasses ever in
my life until I come on this community.
And it's like it's so repetitive and
even when you listen to it long enough,
you start actually losing brain cells.
And that's why I don't comment anymore.
So yeah. And and and and it's not even
just that. It's just weird. Like you got
a bunch of people on here jealous of
people that they don't even know. Like
I've got a bunch of people on here
jealous of me every day. Won't leave me
alone. It's proper weird. proper proper
weird like they dedicate their whole
life to stalking me because they're
jealous of me. That is batty, bro. So
that's why I just don't even bother with
this anymore. Low
lives and self projectors which seem to
um they seem to have gone away. It's
there's no point of the whole
um thing anymore. So
yeah, I think I want to play some Isle of
Horus. Yeah, got some bum chains
here. Got a tiny bit of bum chain. So I
might put it in Eye of Horus. Never
played it before, but yeah, I don't
think them fishes are going to ever pay again. So
yeah. Yeah. Then I want to get a
takeaway. So I was supposed to spend
about60 pound which ain't bad like for
over the weekend I
guess. Oh, I'm getting a nice
restaurant. There we go.
So don't have the earb anymore, do I?
Anyways, I'm gone, man. Yeah, man. Keep
uh keep living, bro. Keep
living. Basically asked her for advice
on on this
thing. Um even though I know what the
response is probably going to be
anyways, talk to her there. Anyways,
man. Anyways, I'm out of here, man. Peace.