[ __ ] Yeah. The biggest one
going. That's what I am. The biggest one
Yeah. We go backwards, bro.
Oh, we can still go a bit later. [ __ ] I
was just about to tell LT about this,
bro. And he's about to delete this
[ __ ] Reddit. Jesus Christ. What? How
two weeks have changed? [ __ ] me.
You know when people you know you know
what it is, bro? Yeah. When these people
say, "Oh, women are not the problem." I
just agree with them now. I just say,
"Yep, yep, yep. I'm the coward. I've got
no life experience. I'm a 27 year old
man that don't know nothing." Yep. Yep.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Like, bro, I just agree
with them now because I feel like, bro,
there's there's no point you sat there
having a an argument with somebody, a
debate with someone when you know your
own experiences and you know you are
right. It it's a waste of life, bro.
Like it I it it it's [ __ ] madness.
I'm not out today, oh, I'm done in this
country. I went out last week and that
was the first time in five weeks. I am
phenito. Yeah, last week was a last
draw, bro. Well, actually yesterday was
the last draw cuz it was actually
another number that I got from last
week. I am done
done. Just like I was like four or five
weeks ago, bro, when I was living my
[ __ ] best life and then I went out
again and now seem to have brought me back down
again. What the [ __ ] What does that
tell you, bro? You You know what that
you would actually think it was the most
boring like I am done, bro. I'm going to
go do some food shopping in a bit and
cook. I need to get back to how I was 3
weeks ago. Bro, this is not normal.
We're living this unnormal, frustrated
life again. And I'm nipping it in the
bud straight away. And this was all
because I went out drinking last week. I
wish I never went out last week. I
generally wish I never went out last
week. I wish I stayed
in. And my friend said to me like, "Oh,
I think you should just not drink." I
wish I [ __ ] never now. I wish I
[ __ ] never cuz I feel like I took 65
steps back than what how I was. You know
what I mean?
sat there arguing and arguing and
arguing like it's madness,
bro. I'm a coward.
Listen, I'm a coward. I'm a [ __ ] I
don't know anything. You're right about
everything. Is that what you want to
hear? Good for you, man. You got the
answer you want. Like, I just said to
him, you've got the answer you want.
There you go. Are you happy now? What
What is the point in all of this? I don't understand.
I know what I'm saying is right. So bad
that I don't even go out anymore. By
going out, I mean going out drinking.
It's that bad. Like I literally went out
last week only cuz it was a bank
holiday. Like I don't care about anymore
about this [ __ ] you
know? [ __ ] 100 [ __ ] 10 steps
forward and 65 steps back.
That's what happens when you go out
drinking. The whole dating thing, it's
all negative. It actually is. It It is
actually a negative. There's literally
no positives in it. This is what I'm saying. You
know, [ __ ] me, bro.
You can't help me. I'm wrong and you're
right. I don't know what these people
actually want to hear, bro. on this
Reddit. Yep. Gets women but me. Yep. I'm
the problem. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Okay. Like you do you want me to agree
with you or something? I don't I don't
know what these people these people actually
want. It's like what what the whole old
saying goes. Yeah. You stop going to the
gym once. You stop going to the gym once
and it's the worst thing you can do, you
know, because you have to go back to
into that lifestyle that you was in. And
it's and it takes discipline to begin
with, right? Like not eating out, but
then you get used to it. I have to
literally do it all over again now. I
wish I didn't go out last week. I
generally wish I didn't go out last
week, you know? And you [ __ ] And you
risk your [ __ ] foot injury as well.
[ __ ] this. I'm done in this country. I'm
booking a holiday next week. [ __ ] this,
mate. I am so right that I'm going to
tell you what I'm going to [ __ ] do.
I'm going to book a holiday next week
and I am gone. That's how that's how
determined I am that I am. Right. Yeah.
[ __ ] [ __ ] I'm booking a holiday next week.
Watch. I've had enough. Because do you
know what it is? Yeah. With these
people, I tell you what it is. Yeah. You
when you are eating in, when you don't
go out and drink, when you don't deal
with women, you not too bad. Like you
you don't really care. But when you
start dealing with them again, bro, I
know what they're like. Yeah. I know
what they're like. I know what I I had
to deal with last week.
Yeah. And I'm not doing this again. I'm
not I'm not doing this again,
bro. You you you you I can go back into
it again. This whole drinking, this whole dating
thing. Do you know what I'm
saying? Yeah, it's mad. Self projection.
But no, but bro, no. No. Do you know
what it is? Do you know what it is, bro?
Three weeks ago, I was the most stablest
normal person. People saying to me, "Oh,
I like how you've changed. You're more
independent. You cook now." Like no one
had a bad word. Yeah. To say about me.
Like bro, people look up to me. Yeah. I
was eating in, saving money, block
goals. Wasn't gang bucks, bro. I was so
stable. I swear to God. As soon as I got
back into this drinking and this women
[ __ ] again. I feel like I've been kicked
down the stairs by a kangaroo again. I'm
not even joking. I swear to God, bro.
It's a negative. This is what I'm I was
trying to explain to London Taylor.
Yeah. We we strive for positivity in our
life. Yeah. This is negative. Yeah. It
was so bad yesterday. Yeah. That I
didn't want to go out cuz I'm not in a
mood. Right. And I said that if I do go
out, I'm going to I'm going to go and um
I'm going to go Sheffield to see
Ant-Man. I can't drink by myself. So, I
just did end up drinking. Somebody wants
to meet me for a beer today. I can't
drink, bro. I can't drink. I'm done. I'm
done, bro. I need like a minimum of two
weeks. This is why these breaks are
important, brother. You know that that
date I went on last Thursday, I went
[ __ ] mad. Like, you don't know how
many. And I didn't even like them. It's
the whole principle. So then I went and
sent it some more. Sent it some more.
Sent it some more. And I felt like this
is it. I am done. You
know, you know, it got so bad I was
like, "Oh, I want to go out drinking
next week." I never ended up doing it.
I'll go out a week later, didn't end up
doing it. I go out a week later, I
didn't end up doing it because I didn't
miss it. You know, it's all right if you
want to go out for a drink every week
and don't expect anything. But no, this
N. I can't go out and not approach,
buddy. I can't go out and not approach.
I need to I need to see I need to sort
some things out, bro. You know how
behind I've been the past two weeks?
I've had a foot injury. My fridge broke.
I've got another [ __ ] woman that wasted
my [ __ ] time. I was speaking to one
in Birmingham yesterday. Yeah. Who I got
the number from last Thursday. I said,
"If they want to meet," and they weren't
even that good looking. I said, "If they
want to meet me," cuz they were
messaging me. If they want to meet me,
then obviously, you know, it's going to
give me more
uh more sort of um more hope. They
wasted my time. [ __ ] that. I'm done.
That was a That was a final shot. [ __ ]
them. So, I'm going to go today and get
some food and cook some I'll probably
get some pork chops to be honest. Let's
go. Let's get back forward again. We're
weeks behind now because of all this.
Yeah. So, we're weeks behind now because
of all this. So, I'm just going to I'm
just going to get some food today and
cook it. I'm done. I'm done. Done. Even
though this person wants to meet me for
a beer today, I'm
done. That's what happens. Joys are
being popular, bro.
Oh, the fridge broke, mate. And that and
yeah, I had to get a new one, but it's
Yeah, I got a refund anyways. So, I'm
not doing a football bet, mate. I don't
do football bets anymore. I don't really gamble much
anymore. What part of a new life do you
not understand, bro? And it seems like
women and and drink has
has it's kicked you down the stairs
again like a
kangaroo. It's like walking up the
stairs and getting kicked by a kangaroo.
I swear to God, it's like you're walking
upstairs. You have you ever seen them
stairs in Scooby-Doo, right? You walk
up, you walk up, walk up, and bam, you
get kicked down the stairs again. [ __ ]
this. I ain't going out in this country
again. I'm booking a holiday next week.
You're [ __ ] bad, mate. [ __ ] that. You
know, I'm done, bro.
And now even my foot is still not 100%
because I've not been able to rest it
100% because of all the [ __ ]
uh um because of like all the walking I
had to do on this date and
stuff. I had paranal
tentonitus tent I can't even pronounce
it. I was a paranal tentus patient and
it [ __ ] hurt mate trust me.
Yeah. Oh no. Yeah. I got a refund, bro. Got a
refund. But I'm done. Yeah. I just went
on this date last week from Sopix.
Proper time waster. I didn't even like
her. Like, I didn't even like her, but
it's the whole principle, bro. Like, h
[ __ ] this, bro. Anyways, we got a uh Oh,
she's on holiday. She's going to come back
soon. She's on holiday,
bro. No, I'm not talking to Timmy. He's
a [ __ ] Oh, another thing, Timmy.
Yeah, you go on about grasses. Yeah,
mate. All of the people that watch you
are grasses. Your followers are grasses.
Do you know how many times I've been
arrested over this website? 20
times. I have been arrested 20 times
over this website. And you want to talk
about other people being
grasses. If only you knew what happened
the other day, mate. We'll keep that to
ourselves. And you want to come on here
and call other people grasses. Timmy,
behave. All of the people that watch
your glasses. Behave, mate. I've been
nicked about 20 times. Yeah. All of the
people that follow you are the biggest
grasses going. Yeah. When I get when I
get a criminal record check, it will
show up like my arrest. And I will show
you every time that I've been arrested
over this website. All of the people
that you speak to are
grasses. Nah. Nah. I'm not approaching
anymore. [ __ ] that. I'm done with it.
I'm done with women. They're all the
same. I'm done. I had a bad experience
last week. Surprise,
surprise. Yeah. You don't want to know
what happened, bro. But yeah, they tried
taking my phone and everything. I was
too fast for him. I was too fast for
you. Were I piggies?
Yeah. No. No. I was too fast for you.
Were I pig? That's what I said to him.
You [ __ ] wanker. That's what I said
to him. You're nothing but a [ __ ]
pig. That's what I said to him, mate.
Yeah. And uh Yeah, he tried to get my
phone. He tried to get my phone as well. [ __ ]
[ __ ] Yeah, Pete Belly's too fast
for you, is he?
Piggy. And you know what I said, bro? I
said, "Yeah, cuz obviously I'm by
myself. I'm not with my mom anymore." Um
I said, "Why don't one of you tell me to
w my [ __ ] neck and today? Tell me to
why am I [ __ ] hecking say pig? Yeah,
because that's and and and I was
literally telling them that, bro. I
said, "Yeah, I want one of you [ __ ]
shitty [ __ ] to tell me to [ __ ] w my
neck today. Come on. Come on." They all
got scared, bro. And they all started
like licking my ass. [ __ ]
[ __ ] Yeah. They come on my door.
[ __ ] my door now. [ __ ] off, you
[ __ ] pig. That's what I said to him.
I swear, bro. I swear to God I did.
I swear to God I did, bro. So, when
you've got when when you've got
people when you've got like Yeah, it's
mad, bro. It was a madness. But yeah,
anyways, we're done with all of that
now. Anyways, so now it's Saturday. I
call it a new week cuz I do all my stuff
Saturday. So, let's try again. Eh, no
more women. No more drinking for a
while. Let's get stable
again. Women bring you down.
Women bring you down. Alpha brings you
down. All of these things are
negatives. All of these things are
negatives. You try taking my phone as
well. Too fast for you,
mate. But yeah, Timmy, man, I know like
you've done like roulette videos in the
past and deep down like we've got that
little bond, Timmy. I get it, bro. I get
it. But don't come on YouTube telling
other people how their grasses when all
of the people that follow you are the
biggest grasses going. Like please, bro.
It's embarrassing. Like, we've all seen
me get arrested in Newcastle. We've all
seen me get arrested a million times. Bro, stop
it. Like, Timmy, I I love you, bro.
Like, this is why I laugh at your
videos. I laugh at your videos. I laugh
at Arsenal Mark's videos because the the
reason I laugh at all of these videos is
because I know that none of you are
about anything. Cuz if you were really
about anything, you wouldn't be on YouTube making
videos. Do you think the Cray twins?
Yeah. Back in the day, bro, if there was
YouTube, they'd be sat there making
videos to each other. No, bro. It's a
comedy show. No one can take any anyone
on this site serious anymore because
it's it's a comedy show. It's literally
like a comedy show. It's like a comedy
sketch. No gangster would come on the
internet and and keep making videos
years later. Arsenal, Mark, Timmy, it's
embarrassing, bro. Please stop it. And I
don't I don't claim to be about
anything, but you know, and I'm not
saying I am, but I know that if I was
about something, bro, I'm not going to
be making videos on YouTube telling
people that I want to fight them. It's
embarrassing, bro. Please stop it. Stop
it to me. It's embarrassing, bro.
Everyone saw the thing in Newcastle.
Everybody saw the thing in
Newcastle. It's embarrassing, bro. It's
just like that terror. Yeah. I had to
tell London Taylor. I was like, "Bro, I
don't know who this guy is telling you
he thinks he is. He's never been on no
probation. He doesn't know people around
North London. I'm telling you who who is
he telling you that he is? He's claiming
that he's been nicked, bro. He's never
been nicked once. He would last a minute
in themselves. He's never been to court.
He's never been um probation. I don't
know who this guy is telling you he is,
but bro, this guy was emailing me at
like 3:00 in the morning, bro, like last
month. They're not about that life.
Trust me, they are not about that
life. It's embarrassing. Please. It's
really, really, really embarrassing. Now
the guy was emailing me like [ __ ]
praising that he's getting other people
n like other people's getting me nicked.
That's no bad man from North London
Road. It doesn't take Einstein to to know this
stuff. So yeah, as long as he knows
anyways I don't know what this guy is
telling you and I told him that as well
to you know directly to him bro.
So yeah, and then you go on about
Arsenal Mark, Timmy. How long has
Arsenal Mark known where people have
lived and what has he done? Nothing. So
I don't know why you bring that bunker
up. Think they're tight, but they ain't.
Bro, listen. Most people on here, they
don't leave their house. They're jealous
of anybody that's got a better life than
them. That's what it is. That's why they
try to ruin other people's life. Bobby,
whoever you are, because they ain't got
a life. Their skin, they're low lives.
They've got nothing in their lives. So
that's why they do all of this [ __ ]
every single day. It's why you don't
really see me on here um anymore, bro. Cuz
um they don't have a life. That's why
they try to ruin other people's every
single day. They they call people skin.
They call people this. They call people
that. I'm thinking, hold on a minute.
Have you not looked in the mirror and looked at
yourself? You know, and I get it. And
this is how I know people are jealous of
me because they do it to me more than
they do it to anyone. Like, you don't
see people doing this to Monty, man. You
don't see people doing this to Timmy.
You don't see them doing it to loads of
people continuously. They do it to me
because they know that I'm better than
looking at them. I got more money than
them. And they don't like it. It's
jealousy. It happens a lot in real life
as well. That's what made me think that,
hold on a minute, I get like people want
a reaction to that, but [ __ ] years
down the line, no, they're jealous of
me, bro. Their actions show it time and
time and time and time and time and time
again. And I don't bother with it no
more cuz it's a toxic community, bro.
And remember what I told you about
negatives? Of course it's jealousy, bro.
Did what these people do? Yeah, it of
course it is 100% jealousy. It's 100% jealousy,
bro. That's why they call be ugly every day,
mate. Oh, guess what? Oh, greasy. Hi. I
went on a date last
week. You want me to tell you all about
it? Because when I was walking to the
corner shop yesterday,
um I remember you you was telling me how
I'm scared to commit. You was telling me
how I'm scared to
commit. You want to hear the story? I'll
make it real quick for you because you
seem to try and tell me that I'm scared
to commit when obviously that's not the
case. Um, but bro, like I can tell you
it quickly if you want. Okay, so I went
out last week. Um, it was the first time
in about 5 weeks. I don't really drink
anymore. I'm saving money. I'm going
away soon. Like just different things.
Done with the drinking, done with the
women for the most part. If I want to go
out, you know, sometimes I'll go out,
whatever. So, I went to this nightclub.
What day was it? I think it was It was
Friday. I went out Friday, right? No, it
must have been Friday because I on day
and Saturday. Don't know how I done two
days, but I on two days. This woman, she
approached me. She was like, "Oh, yeah.
Uh, you're good-look. I like your beard
better ting a little bit." Gave me her
number and uh she went and was having a
fight outside. Got the number, texted
her the next day, which was Saturday.
She was replying literally every two
minutes. I'm thinking, "Okay, we're on
to something here." You know, I had
horal tendonitis in my feet. I couldn't
walk properly. Madness happened over the
past two weeks. Maybe it's all all of
this has happened to finally I've met um
you know, somebody worth being with.
Yeah, [ __ ] right. Anyways, so I said,
"Do you want to meet next week?" And I
was like, "Oh, well yeah, they're free
next week. Any any day from Thursday
onwards." So I basically said, "Okay,
let's meet up Thursday." So I met them,
right, with my Stony, my little
trainers. Um, they've traveled an hour
away. They traveled an hour I for what
this link is. They traveled an hour
away. I traveled 20 minutes away. Now
bear in mind, I don't really I didn't
really like them. They're like a five
out of 10. They were 31. But at the end
of the day, at my time in life, I can't
really be picky. I just went with the
flow. Obviously, it was Thursday. They
could only have a few drinks and then
they're going to go back um because they
they got work the next day, which is
fine. So, this is the first day. They've
then said, I said, "Oh, um yeah, it was
nice meeting you, whatever. When do you
want to see each other again? I'm not
shy. I'm not awkward. I know how to
speak to people." She turned around and
said to me how she um she doesn't feel
the vibe. I was like, "You [ __ ]
what?" I was thinking in my head. Yeah.
I didn't say it loud because obviously
it was the first I could send it. Even
though I didn't like her, it's like what
the [ __ ] You've approached me. You've
traveled an hour to come and see me.
Yeah, you should have saw how I looked
and you're telling me you don't feel the
vibe, bro. I'm so done. [ __ ] this. I
literally Yeah, that it pissed me off
the whole day. The whole day it pissed
me off, bro. I just went out sending it,
sending it, sending it, sending it,
sending it. And I said, "Bro, this is
going to be the last day now for many,
many, many, many, many, many, many
weeks." I just went out approaching it.
I just went out approaching. I was going
mad, bro. And then, uh, I got some
numbers. Uh, one replied, she was at a
gig. She wanted me to come and see her
at a gig. And then she was basically saying,
uh, yeah, she was, she said, "Oh, let's
meet." Um, yesterday I said, "Okay, do
you want me to come to you or do you
want to come to me?" And I said, "No,
this is the last straw cuz it's a number
I got last week. She [ __ ] me around."
Yeah. You You [ __ ] me around. I am done.
Simple. I am done. And I meant it. No, I
didn't want to get to know Nick at all.
No one spoke about sex. No one spoke
about anything, mate. I'm an adult. I'm
a 27 year old man. Yeah. I've been
dealing with people for a very long
time. So, I know exactly how to, you
know what I'm saying? This is why I
don't bother no more. This is this is
one of the main reasons why I gave up
for like four or five weeks and I
stopped the drinking and [ __ ] This is
the main part of why I stopped and now
it has sent me backwards again. Like
breaking my [ __ ] foot. This whole
dating thing, the drinking has actually
sent me backwards again. Now I'm having
to go and pull myself back up again.
Women drinking, it's negative. No matter
what any of these white knights say,
these women will never ever ever ever
change. And I've accepted it. And that's
why I gave up.
And I knew I had to give up because
that's it. So now I've got to build
myself back up again, you know, which
takes discipline. I was eating in I was
eating in. I was eating
in. I was eating in and like saving
money and I was getting a takeaway every
week. What What kind of vibe did I give
off? A normal vibe. We was talking about
our interests, where we've been,
hobbies. Um I asked her like, "What what
do you mean?" and she never she never
elaborated. And that's why I don't [ __ ]
with them no more. This is why I don't
[ __ ] with people no more because of this exact
reason. These women, what it is, they go
on these dates. There's a I think
there's a few reasons why they go on
these dates. They either do it to pass
time, use you, or they've got
unrealistic expectations. They want some
Romeo and Juliet kind of risk. That's
what it is. It's them, bro. Trust me.
This is the first date that I have been
on this whole year. Like obviously I've
got the other like woman, but I met her
a few years ago. This is the first date
that I went on this year and I and like
this is exactly why I gave up because of
this exact reason. So that's why I I'm
done with it now. I don't care about
it. You know, somebody wants to meet me
for beer today, I'm not beating them.
[ __ ] this. [ __ ] this, bro. I'm done.
Anyways, I need to go get some food in a
bit. Yeah, you get better and then you
get kicked down the stairs by a kangaroo
again, you know, but you got you got
really no one to blame but yourself cuz
you know what women are like. You know
they're all the same. You know that is
they're never going to change. And the
funny thing is greasy hair. You would
have loved this. Yeah. So I went back
into the Weather Spoons um and I said
I'm I'm sick of these westernized women
and you know how you get them like old
like people that just want to start on
people. He turned around and said,
uh, he turned around and said, "I don't
want to hear it." I said, "Well, you're
gonna [ __ ] hear it whether you
[ __ ] like it or not." And instead of
standing up for himself, you know what
he done? He went to the manager. Then
the manager come over to me. He's like,
"What the hell was going on? Why do you
keep saying about these westernized
women um being all the same and being
stuck up?" I said, "Because they [ __ ]
well are." And then he was trying to
have a debate with me, right? Saying,
"Oh, like you trying to tell me." I was
like, "Mate, I'm 27." Yeah. I don't care
if you're 34. I'm from the West. I'm
made from the West. I know what these
women are like. I'm not going to sit
here and have an argument with you in f
in the middle of a [ __ ] pub. So, you
have your experience. I I know mine,
which has made me give up. So, you you
know, you keep going on being a white
knight all your life. And that's the
word I used. I said, "You're nothing but
a white knight." And let's see where
that gets you in 10 years. Nowhere.
You're still going to be working in the
pub. You're still going to be bitchless.
You know what I'm saying? I I said I
said I'll [ __ ] say I said to you,
"Well, you're going to [ __ ] hear
about it." Yeah. That's what I said to
him. Don't [ __ ] come here in the pub
and start having a [ __ ] attitude. You
know, you maybe I didn't like the way
your your clothes look, but you don't
see me moaning about it, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. And then he goes to the manager.
What a little [ __ ] He went to the
manager all because I
said women are stuck up and entitled. He
literally went to the manager over that.
What a [ __ ] Yeah. He's He's They're
the kind of people that start stuff with
people, but then they go to the manager.
Imagine that, bro. I think I'm banned
now as well. Oh, Jesus
Christ. But anyways, the point is,
Greasy, you're trying to tell me that
I'm scared to commit. Remember what you
said? That was your words. You said that
I am scared to commit. Yeah, there you
go. I just told you the story. So, go figure,
bro. Stuck up, entitled, time
wasters. Um, and yeah, they bring you
down as well. So, but then you want to
tell me that I'm scared to commit. And I
remember exactly how I was on that date
as well. Confident, normal, myself. I
think that's more to the point myself.
You're gonna laugh at my foot injury
though. You really laugh at my foot
injury grievy was [ __ ] bad, mate. I
wish my recovery or
this Well, well, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. Unrealistic
expectations. I said unrealistic
expectations. I didn't say unrealistic
standards. I said unrealistic
expectations with there's a big
difference. Don't mishar me. There's a
big difference. It's what they expect in
a man. So like what I told you, they're
expecting some sort of Romeo
Juliet. No, there's a big difference, you know.
So it is what it is,
bro. Uh I had a in in what's it called?
Kentus. Yeah. I had some swollen foot,
bro. I couldn't even walk. I literally
had to call to the bathroom and that
bro. It was a madness. So yeah, but it
wasn't my vibe because I was myself and
I know exactly what I said. I know
exactly what I said. So yeah, it could
just be that they just they just meet
you to pass
time even use you. I mean it's the
expectations, you know, there's there's
a lot of reasons, bro. But I know I
didn't say I'll do anything wrong. I
know exactly what I look like. I risked
my recovery on that to go on that date,
mate. I wasn't even 100% healed. But I
was like, mate, if I've got to go in a
[ __ ] wheelchair, I'll go in a [ __ ]
wheelchair because like I said before,
as ridiculous as it
sounds, you know, it's hard to get an
opportunity like that to to be able to
get somebody that wants to meet you. So,
you need to grab it by the horns when
you can. You know what I'm saying? But
I'm done with it now. I am literally
done with it. That's the final shot. Yeah.
playing for one matey. That's all I can [ __ ]
say. Yeah, there's a lot of grown ass
men that get involved. Yeah, they don't
get involved with me because I'll just
tell them about himself. I'll just tell
them about himself. I don't give
a like because at the end of the day,
like these people, they're like central
London and it they don't know about like
and that you know what I'm saying. They
try to be the hero. It's like that
American guy before. Then when you just
said that, it just reminded me of that
American guy. He was like, "Oh, uh,
don't talk to her. I talk to a [ __ ]
one. You don't [ __ ] tell me who I can
[ __ ] talk to." And he was like, "All
right, big man." I said, "Yeah, I'm a
big man when I'm [ __ ] talking to you,
you know." Yeah. And he was he was in a
group like six people, bro. But all the
six people was upstairs. I didn't even
realize until he was upstairs. I didn't
even realize until he was upstairs that
he was in a group. I thought, "Oh, is
that why he acts big?" Cuz he's in a group. Typical
[ __ ] Typical [ __ ]
Yeah. Anyways, you want to know so much
more about my foot, do you,
buddy? Yeah. Here's my uh the back of
it. So, basically what it means
is this bit was swollen and it was like
it was like swollen. So, every time I
was walking, I was walking on like soon
as I had my feet. I was walking on the
lip and every time I tried to walk it,
it was twisted and broke. I was almost
crippled, bro. It's not It's not a joke.
So, I think I hit it on something when I
was sleeping. I had to go to a doctor
and everything. It's like 90% better
now, but obviously uh uh obviously
uh obviously because this woman wanted
to meet, I was on pay for this just so I
can go on a date. So, I mean that just
makes it, you know, a bit worse. And
bro, and it's not that I liked her. I
didn't really like her. She could have looked like
Dobby, you know? She could have looked
like [ __ ] Dobby, but it's the
principle. And I think that's what the
main thing is. It's the
principal, you know? It doesn't matter
what they look like. Let Let me tell you
something, bro. You want to talk about
vibes? Yeah. I'll be 100% honest with
you, Queeny. Yeah. When I met USA Dizzy
the second time when I was a bit sober,
you know what I said? I was like, I
don't really like the way she looks that
much. I was like, uh, but then I
thought, you know what? I approached her
like this one approached me. Let me just stick with
it. It takes more than one meeting, one
hour to know if you vibe with a person.
And I think that's the point I'm trying
to make because at first I thought I
didn't, but then look what happened for
two years. So that's my whole point is
that you don't know in an hour whether
you ride with someone or not. Feelings
change, things change. Obviously, I
learned that from being on on these
dates. I would never ever ever ever approach a
woman, go out with a
woman and then say go out with the woman
and then say I don't feel the vibe.
Because to me that makes no sense. To me
that literally makes no sense.
Stop. It don't make any sense. It
doesn't make any sense, but [ __ ] them.
Anyways, so anyways, let's try again.
Ah, anyways, let's try again. Eh, let's
try this healthy eating again. Hopefully
nothing bad happens next week cuz it's
always something greasy. Had to [ __ ]
fridge pack up, didn't I? Had to buy a
new fridge. So, hopefully we can get
back to normal again. No, no women, no
drinking. And you will see how your mood changes,
bro. You know what I'm saying? You will
see how your mood changes. And it's like
when I come on YouTube, Yeah. people
like, "Oh, you sound different, man. I
like that you're cooking and all of
this." And they were like, "Oh, well, so
you do realize that it wasn't women all
along." I then replied, "Uh, no, it is.
I just don't care about it anymore. I
don't want to talk about it anymore. I
don't care." People think just because I
found it positive, it changed my
mindset. No, I just don't care. I don't
need to care about them anymore. I know
I'm right and that's it. So if I know
I'm right, I'll give up and leave the
country. So and that's that's that's the
route I'm going down.
So So you know the badest thing about
this Grezy to end all of this off here
before I put a link up. You know the
maddest thing about this
greasy is that these
same women, these same women, you know
the one I told you about last week, walk
bones and wings and bone and then winge
again. Oh, we can't find a normal guy.
If only a normal guy could come into our
lives and I could stop getting with
these women beaters and these drug
dealers. Well, every time a normal guy
comes into your life, I mean, you claim
you got a boyfriend or you claim that
you can't feel a vibe, whatever the [ __ ]
that means. You know what I'm saying?
But they will moan and winge and moan
moan. Moan and winge, moan and winge,
moan and winge. That's the bit I don't understand.
Um, that's what I really really don't
understand is that they're not willing
to try yet we're the ones that scared to
commit and they can't find a normal guy.
I don't like using the term nice guy
because there like subreddits on that.
There's memes. Oh, you're a nice guy. Do
you know what I'm saying? So that's why.
And me, it's not even like I'm ugly.
Nice clothes, nice hair. So when
somebody tries to come into your life,
you do this same stuff. So and that's
why I gave up with it,
bro. If you know you're right and you
don't want to argue with me, you give
up. And that's why I know for 5 weeks.
That's why you didn't really see me.
So trust me, Grezy. Honestly,
bro, if I if I call any of these women
that I've met with different, I put my
hands up and say that I'm wrong. Because
there's been times, Grezy, where I have
been wrong in my life, I've met people
on dates and it was me, I was wrong. Cuz
I kept going on about someone else,
someone else, someone else, or I've done
something. I know, bro. I know when I've
been wrong. And trust me,
bro, 80% of the time it ain't been like
that. You know, I'm very very self-aware
what I'm saying and what I'm doing, you
know? Um, that's why I purposely drink
beer to be fair. So, like I know when
it's me and I know when it's them. Trust
me, bro. I've been wrong many
times. Many times in my life, but not
this time. Did I make any funny noise?
Do I have any
ticks? Nope. don't go on about USAD
anymore. Don't have any
ticks and don't make funny noises.
That's part of probably why the
19year-old comes around a lot now
because obviously I don't go about that.
I'm from America. So, um she probably
finally I don't want to hear about it
and obviously now I don't talk about it.
She's like, "Yay." So, we're building
that back up
again. That must have been so annoying
hearing that. [ __ ] hell. I remember
that two years ago when I used to go out
with people and it was all I would talk
about. [ __ ] hell, what are you doing,
man? Like it's crazy. I used to do it
like like two years ago and they just
thought I was
bad. You know what I'm saying? They But
now obviously I don't obviously I [ __ ] don't.
But it it was you know what was so bad
is I used to talk about it to random
people when I used to
drink. Oh, bro. It used to be
bad of me, but no, no, obviously I don't
talk about. Why would I? I don't like
them. But yeah, anyways, none of that
stuff. So, I just figured that they're
just lost causes,
mate. They're just lost causes if
they're not going to
[ __ ] you know. Yeah.
So, I know, bro. I know.
Some remember they can't find a nice guy.
They can't find a nice a normal guy apparently.
You should have saw what I was wearing
yesterday as well. I look slick, bro.
Listen, I'll show you. One second. I
actually show you what I wear if you're that interested.
Got to beat up myself. myself.
Yeah. One second, bro. I'm going to put
this video back. I'm going to put this
video up. One second, bro.
So yeah, that's why I don't
care. So I don't I don't when I don't go
on about them or when I sound positive,
it's not because I'm wrong and I've
noticed that I'm wrong. It's because I don't care
anymore. It's because I don't care
anymore, mate. Look at this sexy, bro.
Look at these arms, man. They're clean.
Look at these, bro. These arms are
actually clean, too. Look. Yeah. I'll
show you, man. Oh, what? One
sec. Oh, why is it not letting me do
it? Second. Yeah, [ __ ] I had a knock
on the door two weeks ago, Grez. It was
a load of old bill. They tried taking my [ __ ]
phone. You are getting that phone,
mate. Getting that phone, mate. You [ __ ]
mad. [ __ ] It was a load of old bill.
We've I'm not even joking. Load of old Bill,
eh? Anyways, tell me I don't look fresh
in this [ __ ] video,
bro. Load of old Bill. Yeah. He [Laughter]
eventually trying to like call the
number of that [ __ ] pigs. [ __ ]
los what? You just looked out the window
and it was just a load of our
bill. Look at that fresh
bro. And what? It was just a load of old bill. Huh? Dude,
Billy. Oh, I love how you say that, man.
[ __ ] Dan Brown is typing.
No, I'm not doing it. Go
away. There we
go. Look how snick I look.
So you can be a normal person, look a
normal person, but they still give you
grief. They still give you grief.
E, I need to my car saying that I need
to go to the supermarket. I need to go
grocery shopping, Grezy, because I don't
want to have I don't want to have
diabetes. I need to eat healthy. I don't
want to have
diabetes. Um, I don't want to have So
yeah, going to make some nice pork
there. Pork and
chips. There we are. [ __ ] Hey. Oh, man.
So I think they lost cord, man.
Honestly, and then this woman was like,
"Well, how do other people get women?
How are other people in relationships?"
Um, so that must mean the common demon
is them is you. And I said, "Well,
you're actually wrong." Yeah, there's
people in relationships. Yeah, there's
people that get women, but trust me, a
lot of people are going to Thailand now.
Loads of people dating Asian women.
Loads of people are struggling. There's
so many people struggling that it has to
be women. Because if it wasn't women,
yeah, if it wasn't
women, I would
say 10 20% of people would struggle. But
the fact that it's more than 10 20%
people struggling, it's women. Big
comment, bro. You you have all these
incel things. All these people are even
people that class themselves as incels.
If it wasn't women that this wouldn't
happen. It would be like 10%
20%. There's people that are worse than
you. So your argument don't make sense
because a lot of people get
relationships in school. They might have got lucky
um you know got lucky once, twice,
whatever. But for the most part
nowadays, people starting off, they're
going to struggle, which means it's
women. Cuz obviously the 10% could be
like maybe people
with autism or people that don't know
how to interact, then then it'll be
like, "Okay, but no, it literally is
them." Like I actually scrolled through
Reddit, it was yesterday, and I was
reading up on reasons why people gave up
on dating and a lot of it was similar to
me. I think somebody made a good point.
It was like, "Oh, um, I don't want to
humiliate myself just for a chance of
finding a partner." And I think that was
very, uh, that was very valid, I think,
cuz that is literally what you're doing.
You're you're sort of humiliating
yourself in order to try to find a
partner. And I feel like that that it
shouldn't be like
that. Um, and you're enough alone
anyways. That's another thing. You're
enough alone. I I know I'm enough alone,
mate. I've been after almost a year now.
So, you're enough alone, mate. And you
shouldn't have to humiliate yourself in
order to find someone. It's not worth
it. Yeah. So, it's not
worth sort of humiliating yourself.
Yeah, not worth
huming. might go live a little bit late
and that's me done. Yeah, I had a bad
few choices because it's [ __ ] I'm done.
I'm not arguing with people. No arguing,
none of that [ __ ] I think I I feel like
I use YouTube like therapy
lessons and I wouldn't need therapy
lessons if I just gave up with women and
gave up with the alcohol. But here we go
again. No one's
perfect. Let me try and rest me this.
Wait for this card to come and I'll be
doing some food shopping. Let's try
again. Hey. Oh, let's [ __ ] try again.
Never mind. I'll probably go out next
week, get [ __ ] run over by a [ __ ]
car. Not been the best month for Peter
Betty, mate. I'll tell you that
much. It's not been the best month for
Peter Benny, but yeah, we know uh we
know what to do
now. I don't care. I know what I'm doing
So, yeah. Don't ever try and tell me
grievy that I'm scared to commit. Cuz
I'm not scared to
commit. Not at all. Am I scared to commit,
mate? So, oh, this guy wants to meet for
beer. The joys of being popular,
eh? But I don't think I'm going to I
don't really want to go out. I'm
saying I need to go. I need to go up or
not down. So I said maybe in two weeks
we can go join if you
want but not in time for that.
Anyways, I'm done. I might be back later
for one last live stream and that's it.
Wish in the back.