Yeah, I just got back from the day.
Waste of time. That's two in one week, bro.
Which I need to be fair.
So, that was a slightly different day,
but all the more reason to give up in
these westernized countries. Oh, I just
stopped my weekly food shop. A nice
t-bone for later. I'll be having that.
Yeah, I told you, man. It's going to
take a long a little time, but we'll get
back to our normal
um we'll get back to normal routine,
man. Give it a while. We'll do it, bro.
Not a problem,
man. Yeah, I was. But she's uh she's not
in England anymore. She's in Wales for
like a month, so relationship. But, bro,
[ __ ] me. I I just literally just come
back from a date cuz this person
messaged me saying, "Oh, do you want to
meet up today?" I didn't even plan it
today. I am done in this country, mate.
Like, I was even telling Ant-Man about
this as well. And he was like, "Oh, uh,
like what you going to say out and send
it? I am done, bro. I'm fito with these
women drinking this whole [ __ ] life.
[ __ ] woke up [ __ ] constipated
today as well. I am done, mate. I was
done for a very long time. It's all bank
holiday. It's boring, mate. It generally
generally generally is boring. At 27
years of age, I've come to the
conclusion that all women are the same.
And well, to be no, to be fair, I came
to that conclusion when I was like 17.
But I was hoping to be proven wrong. And
I'm never proven wrong, which is insane,
is it? But people still defend women.
But each to their own, bro. You know,
that's up to
them. Yeah, it was kind of a slightly
different day today.
But uh she's like, "Oh, we're vibing
quite well and that because I know how
to vibe. I know how to interact with
people. I've met loads of people. Um I
know I've made loads of friends." So
just like that one last Thursday saying
she didn't feel the vibe. She's full of
[ __ ] She wasted her time and my time on
purpose, but I'm sure she'll be
complaining soon that all men are the
same and how she can't find a normal guy
like they all do. I've literally I've
had a laugh for them, babe.
generally had enough of him. I'm not
even joking. I've had enough of him,
mate, to last me a [ __ ] whole
lifetime and beyond. It's not even a joke,
man. Steve Job check.
Wait. Oh, yeah. Regulation because it's
Saturday, ain't it? Yeah. I still get
emails from them. We just
did. I wish I didn't go out last week,
bro. [ __ ] hell. If anyone ever says
to me like, "What's your biggest
regret?" It was going out last week.
Yeah. Women will never change. This
country will never change. Just a
negative. A negative, mate. And in life,
yeah, we're supposed to strive for
positivity. We're not supposed to strive
for negativity. We're supposed to stay
away from negative things now. That's
what we doing.
Yeah. It's crazy. Yeah. I met this
woman. She's from
Birmingham. I left her.
Um Oh, yeah. I just left this
one. But we're scared to commit.
Apparently, men are scared to commit. So
grieves, he says. So greaves. He
says that young man wants to get himself
some [ __ ] life experience, mate. He
[ __ ] really does. He needs to get
himself some life experience.
Like, but remember how early I said
we're going backwards? Well, now we're
forwards. We're going forwards,
mate. Yeah, we're going forwards now,
bro. Even if it's a little bit of effort, we're
done. [ __ ] hell. I didn't think I'd
be in this [ __ ] position
again. But I done a food shop and
that Oh, it's so bad. I don't even want
to talk about anymore. I don't even want
to think about anymore. It just annoys
me, mate. I don't even want to be around
women anymore. just annoys me. All of
them just annoy me,
bro. Going on a train, they're all the
[ __ ] same. I'm sick of hearing about
them. I'm sick of dealing with them. You
know what I'm saying? They will never
change. It just It just It just annoys
me. You know, when something just annoys
you, but people claim they're not all
the same. Okay, buddy. So, you say,
"Huh?" Well, at least we got something
to look forward to today. a t-bone steak
cuz I was going to go out to get a
t-bone steak. I was going to go out and
do my food shopping and this woman's
like, "Oh, do you want to meet up?" I
was like, "Okay, you know, so when I met
them, but they weren't even good, bro.
Like at the end of the
day, like they were like
30. You don't have a job, but you've
never had one of the most I've had a
job, mate, and you don't have a job.
Stop self-reflecting. This is not a
self-reflecting channel, buddy. You
don't have a job. And if you keep
self-reflect, I'm just going to ban you.
Simple. You know, I've got more life
experience than you will ever have,
mate. You know, I've seen things that
you can't even imagine. You can't even
imagine seeing. And I don't care how old
you are cuz I know you're probably older
than me. It was like this this manager
in Weather Spoon from Spain. I was like,
"You might be 34, but guess what? I'm 27
and I've got more life [ __ ]
experience than you, mate." Because with
having free time, I've gone out and done
a lot of things. I've not been stuck
working in a pub. There's nothing wrong
with working in a pub or being a manager
in a pub, but what life experience could
you really have by sat there? Uh, we're
not having this on this channel. Um,
uh, what kind of experience could you
really have in life just sat there in a
pub being a manager? You don't have deal
with people, right? I deal with people
every day. People piss me off every day.
You know what I'm saying? So, it's one
of them, man. Is it?
So, anyways, you're banned, buddy. No
self-reflecting on this channel, man.
Uh, and you're banned. And you're
banned. Sorry, I recognize a lot of
these um spatics.
So, so yeah, that's how it basically
goes really, man. I actually done a
video talking about this, but I don't
feel like there's any point uploading
it. Uh, it's very negative. Alcohol,
women, gambling, [ __ ] [ __ ] food. It's all
negative. It's all big negatives. You
don't want to do any of that all your
life, mate. [ __ ]
me. But yeah, they're never going to
change. Women will never change in this country, bro.
Birmingham, we were slightly
different. Um, she was all right. She
was a nice person. We vibe. There was
nothing wrong with her, but it's kind of
like, okay, I bought a round of drink. I
bought another round of drink, but you
want me to buy you food as well? [ __ ]
this, mate. Absolutely [ __ ] this. She
was literally like a
[ __ ] three out of 10, bro. I just got
back from the States. She was from
Birmingham, but I still didn't ditch her
because she didn't look as
good. So, anyways, you're bad, mate. Go
self-reflect on another channel. Uh, is
that the real Kayie? Let me see. Hold on.
One second. Hold
on. Right. But to answer your question,
uh, yeah, I have heard about Monty, but
guess what? I've had my own problems,
mate. Funny enough, I've had my own
problems the past two, three [ __ ]
weeks. So, but yeah, I have heard about
it. I don't know why he talks about me
and I don't know why Natalie talks about
me saying about oh like PJ wears all
these gums and he still can't get women
and I'm thinking in my head [ __ ] I've
had more women than anyone on this
community. What are you talking about? I
had a YouTube channel that literally
just got banned about like 3 weeks ago
and I'm the only one on there that has
shown women. Why do you feel the need to
bring me up? [ __ ] waste man. But
yeah, I've had my own problems anyways.
But yeah, I have seen
it. Of course I've seen it, man. Of
it. Another one ain't got no life
experience. But it is what it is,
bro. But yeah, this date was a
bit I kind of realized on Thursday that
there's no point even me going on dates
anymore. There's no point me going out
approaching. There's no point me going
out on dates. There's literally not. But
because she wanted to meet
me, I weren't going to say no, was I?
Yeah, I've got a life now, mate. I'm busy with
[ __ ] I've had a lot of [ __ ] happen the past few
weeks. [ __ ] had paranal
tentonitus in my foot. [ __ ] shitty
experiences with women, which has only
been happening since last week cuz I
stopped going out for like 5 weeks. So,
yeah, it's not been good, man. Um, I was
eating it and stuff. Now I don't
uh Yeah, since I went out last week,
it's been non-stop negative. Non-stop
negative. And that was the first time in
like five weeks. [ __ ] Princeley Road.
Nah, man. I'm not meeting no one on
YouTube, bro. I'm good, man. I'm all right, buddy.
So, but it did wind me up though. And
this is why it's imperative to take
breaks cuz you'll end up losing your
mind. I just come back from a date and
it was like, what was even the point,
bro? No point in going on these
dates. One of the reasons why I didn't
go out for five
weeks. So, yeah, the lot the date I went
on on Thursday, right? She was trying to
say she didn't feel the vibe even though
she approached me even though I'm above
average looking and she traveled an hour
to come and see me. So I was like uh
okay. So anyways, so then I had a woman
message me today saying that she wanted
to meet up. She was literally like a
three out of 10. She was [ __ ]
stinking. I don't even know why I
approached her. I must have been drunk.
But that's not what made me leave her. I
didn't leave her because she was
stinking. No, I still stayed. It was a
good conversation. The reason that made
me left her is cuz I bought a round of
drinks. Then I bought another round of
drinks and then she wanted me to buy her
food. I was like, "No, mate. I am
[ __ ] done. I am out of here, mate."
You know what I'm saying? So, like, I am
done with this [ __ ] bro. I am so done.
I am so done. This is why I don't go out
anymore, bro. This why I don't drink and
talk to women anymore. Negative.
negative after negative after negative.
They're all the same and they will
always be the same. And yes, I am
putting them all in one bracket. The
same kind of bracket that you put on the
TV. They are all the same. And I would
be [ __ ] delusional to think
otherwise. That's what happens when
you've got thermosite experience,
bro. So yeah, I went and met her in this
pub. It was [ __ ] mate. Proper
[ __ ] So you want me to buy you food,
drink, and all of that? Like I am so
done with these women, bro. None of them
you could ever imagine.
Seriously, it doesn't stop there as
well. Somebody wants to meet me for a drink
today. The joys of being so popular,
e the joys of being See, I was fine when
I gave up with women. I was fine. I was
fine, bro. When I stopped drinking and I
stopped this [ __ ] with women, I was
fine. I was feeling all right. I was
stable. I swear to God, bro. Dude, as I
went drinking again, thinking that it
was going to be different. Look where we
are, bro. Look where we
are. Stupid me. E, you got no one to blame but yourself. You
know, no more, Gary. No more,
buddy. They're all the [ __ ] same
disability. Go self-reflect on another
channel, man. Don't waste your time
self-reflecting here, man.
[ __ ] There's no point self-reflecting
on my channel, bro. No one's taking no notice of
you. Depressing, Gary, man. It's very
depressing. Imagine that having to deal
with alcohol and then dating at the same
time. God, no wonder you're so
depressed. It's enough to get any [ __ ]
down. It's enough to get any [ __ ]
down. Is it,
bro? For real, bro.
Yeah. Agitated mood swings. We stop
doing this [ __ ] to get away from it,
bro. Like I You think I can't go out
today and try today? Yeah, obviously I
could can cook some rice tea, go out
again and try. But why would I? Because
at the end of the day, lad with
confidence. Yeah. Do you know what,
right? Whoever's behind that account,
right, Mary Beth, I suspect you're Bob.
Let me tell you one thing. All of the
advice that you get on the internet,
it's not the same as real life. Like
you'll get people on the internet say
women love this, women go for this,
women go for that. And it's not just
YouTube, it's various different other
platforms. You will know what women
really are like. When you go out in real
life and you actually meet women, you
know exactly what they're like. And I
know what they're like cuz I'm 27 years
of old years of age, done a lot of
traveling. I've come across a lot of
women. I've been on a date today. They
don't care about confidence. They don't
care. And anyone with life experience
would know this. Anybody with life
experience would know how stuck up women
are in London. how much of a [ __ ] how
much [ __ ] they are in London. Like
anybody with life experience that leaves
their house would actually notice. But
the people that sit there and say it's
about this and that, they're people with
no life experience. I know that sounds
like common and that, but it's pretty
much to the tea. They've got no life
experience. They generally have no life
experience. So they just make up things
like, "Oh, they care about this or oh
they care about that or oh they care
about this or oh they care about that
because they don't actually have no life
experience which was the whole point of my approaching
videos. But anyways, I'm done with this
conversation anyways. I know what I need
to do. I need to leave this country.
That's how determined I am that I'm
right that I'm going to leave the country. Simple.
So yeah, man. It's one of
them. It will never change. They're all the same. [Music] Hello.
Yeah. Kept spamming me though, bro. I
had to. You know what I mean?
got self-reflect on another channel. Not my one,
man. There's one person that ain't even
got any [ __ ]
money. Imagine that, man.
It I'm done with this now,
bro. Cuz think about it, bro. If I
thought I was wrong in any way, shape,
or form, I'd be going out there today
sending it. I would be going out today
sending it, sending it, sending it,
sending it. You know, I'm I'm in a
perfect position to do that, but I know
they're all the same. So to prevent
further negative experiences, you give
up, you know, and that's how I think you
really know if you're telling yourself something
um or you're actually meaning it because
I've actually given up. So I know that
I'm right otherwise I wouldn't give up
because you would have that doubt in
your mind saying but they are generally
generally are all the
same. It's sad, isn't it?
One way ticket to mood rings, mate.
That's what it is. They're all the
same. Just send me a voicemail. What's
she saying? Hold on.
Yeah, man. Maybe. Maybe. I don't know,
bro. But I know that I'm done in this
country, bro. When I went out last week,
I'm telling you, that was the first time
I went out in about 6
weeks. Like, I was going on the ebike. I
was cooking in. Like I don't give a [ __ ]
about these [ __ ] As soon as I got
into I wish I never got into it again. I
wish I never ever got into it again with
these entitled [ __ ] Like I swear to
God, bro. I wish I just didn't go out.
Wish I stayed in, bro. I should
have. Oh, you're
bad. You're bad,
buddy. Want to see my little fridge?
It doesn't matter, bro. What they want.
They want visas in Brazil as well. You
get people from Brazil as
well. There we go. Stacked up the old
fridge. Nice bit of pork
chops. Nice bit of steak. Coke. Bit of
Jerry's. Yeah. I need to chuck this milk
to be fair.
She thrown out the whole fridge. Yeah,
my one packed up kind of. It's smaller, but
it's definitely better. Got some burgers
and bacon as
well. One's got a
key. Good for tensitis. Uh
patient. What is he?
was talking with my
friend. Um I was talking to my friend
um the country. I was talking to my
friend and um he was saying that, "Oh,
you can't take any of it to heart." How
can you not take it to heart, bro? It's
boring. It's boring. Like, having your
time wasted dealing with these stuck up
[ __ ] is boring, lad. Like, I don't
know how people can't take it to heart.
It's [ __ ] boring, mate. Whatever.
But yeah, she just messaged me saying
they want a drink. Well, she said they
want a coffee. I'm not going to sit down
and have coffee with someone.
Yeah. So, yeah. So, yeah. Like I said,
this one was like a slightly different
one. There you go,
man. So, yeah. [Music]
Yeah, some madness, bro.
Yeah, Gary. So, it's [ __ ] up, is it,
bro? Yeah, it is [ __ ] up, is it, mate?
It's [ __ ] up world, bro.
I don't know what it means, mate. I wish
did. Supposed to be meeting this guy today
for What else do we have? I only had
this. I didn't want anymore. I didn't
want any more beer. I'm trying to, like
I said, set up the drink.
So, yeah, bro. You can't get drunk off two beers
that Yeah. It's a depressing life here in England. One second.
Yeah, you still there.
Yeah. Bing repeating. Bye-bye.
There we go.
Well, he's down to mad you, mate. [ __ ] hell,
son. You should chill out.
Stop calling yourself disabled. It's not
nice. Stop calling yourself disabled,
man. That's not nice for a [ __ ]
Saturday evening, mate. Talking about
yourself. [ __ ] hell.
0207. There's so many
repeaters. Trust me, five. Yeah, I'm not
going to say too much, buddy. But I have
literally been spending all of my days
collecting all of what these people have
been doing to me over the years. The
harassment, the goating, the
stalking, everything. And I'm just going
to I've been reporting these people. I'm
going to keep reporting, reporting,
reporting, reporting, reporting.
And yeah, because what what the thing is
with like the police, bro, is that the
police don't understand that these
people are harassing people online.
They're ging people online every single
day. Because like when people are
reporting that, you don't understand
with these people, bro. They're
reporting people. Yeah. Saying, "Oh, I'm
a victim, mate. I've got about 100
screenshots of all of their golden, all
of their harassment." Like, bro, I
literally have everything that they've
been doing. Literally everything. I've
got 23 missed calls,
going harassing, breaking into houses.
Like, bro, literally, it's it's not a
problem. I have
everything. Um, and I've got the reports
as well, so fine by me. Literally, bro,
like, I've got a f I've got a folder on
my phone that says harassment. I've
literally got a a whole different album,
right, of of what they've done. And and
you know what's going to happen, right?
Yeah. When you go not guilty and you
have to go to trial, they're going to get [ __ ]
Yeah. Literally, like they are going to
be [ __ ] Like if they take it to
trial, they will be actually [ __ ] with
the amount of evidence that you have got
because that's what happens when stuff
goes to trial. Like
they're they'll get themselves in
trouble. All they've done is got
themselves in trouble. Not me. You know,
when people when people make allegations
against people, bro. Yeah. Yeah. And
that's and that's and that's what how
they like got the police to come to my
house because, bro, please don't please
don't just come to people's houses. Like
they will sit there saying, "Oh, I'm a
victim." No, no, no, no, mate. I've been
sending so much [ __ ] to the police and
I'm going to keep doing it and doing it
and doing it and doing it and doing it
and doing it and doing it. know what I'm
saying? And doing it and doing it. I
said, "They keep going me. They keep
harassing me. They won't leave me
alone." And when a judge looks at that,
when literally the judge looks at that,
it's done. I mean, trial is going to
take two, three years. I said, "They
won't leave me alone. They keep goating
me and bullying me." What's the judge
going to say? What? One rule for one,
one rule for another. It's not going to
work, bro. Trust me, I can show you
everything that I've got on these
people. If you add me on Snapchat, if
you add me on all of this [ __ ] I've got
literally everything. [ __ ] loads. And
you know what they're going to say?
They're going to turn around and say,
"Um, yeah, you haven't done anything to
a fight, have you?" And then they're
going to be [ __ ] And that's And trust
me, bro, I know this stuff. I know how
this stuff works. I've seek legal advice
as well. So, I'm ready to go with all of
my evidence. I've got their faces
mocking me, everything. Good luck, man.
I don't mind, bro. It's It's not a
problem to me. It's not one single
problem to me,
bro. It's not one problem. I have got so
much [ __ ] on these
people. So, it's no problem, man. I'm easy,
man. I am easy. And I'm going to keep
reporting them every single day as
well. You know what I'm saying? Like,
this is not the real world, bro. This is
YouTube. You understand? It's not the
real world. It's YouTube. Yeah, they've
done all of this stuff because they're
jealous of me. Like I at Yeah, I at
first, bro, I thought like, oh, like
they're just trying to wind people up
and they don't really do stuff. But I
know I I noticed that they're actually
jealous of me because think about it,
bro. Timmy's not had this treatment.
Monty's not had this treatment. They
want to ruin me cuz I'm I've got more
money than I'm better looking than them.
And that's what it came down to in the
end. I was sitting there thinking like,
what the [ __ ] Like, you're not some
murderer. like you're not some upright
criminal. And it came down to jealousy.
And the only thing like I could
realistically think in my life, bro, why
the [ __ ] were these people alone? Leave
you alone. It's cuz they're jealous of
you. They call you ugly. They call you
skin because they're jealous of you.
Think about it. For them to do this
every day, try to ruin people's life.
You got something they don't have. Boy,
I'm telling you, it's got to be. It has
to be. And then that's why I I' I've
just said it. So, but I've been
reporting these people anyways, bro. I
need to follow up with it again today. I
followed up with it yesterday. I said
like they still go to me. I've got all
the evidence of what they've been doing.
They won't leave me alone. Like,
literally. So, it's not a problem, bro.
Trust me, it's not a
problem. Much more lenient than the
police, you know? So, it's fine, bro.
I'm going to keep reporting and
reporting and reporting and reporting.
And listen, bro, when I get that trial
date, which is going to be in about 2
years, I will give everyone on YouTube
the date. I'm that confident that I will
give everybody on YouTube the trial
date. It's going to be like 2, three
years. If it doesn't even get dropped by
then, I will literally give you the
trial date, you know? And yeah, trust
me, I'm that confident. So, it's it's
it's not a problem, bro.
Like, that's it.
So all these people have done is got
themselves in trouble really in the end
of it if it's if it takes a year, it
takes two years, whatever, all they've
done is got themselves in big trouble.
Not me. So they in the end whether it
takes two years, three years, all
they've really done is grasp on
themselves really. So and I'll give you
the um the trial date as well. Everyone will
know. So that's it, bro. It's not a problem.
Trust me, my defense will be [ __ ]
taught. Trust me, you
know. And that's it, bro. That's It's not a
problem. It It's not a problem at all.
Cuz that's what these people like to do
on here five. They like to act the big
[ __ ] They like to act They like to act
the big man, but yet they like to run to
the police. That's literally all they
do. They like to add the And that's why
like when I was listening to Timmy to me
the other day, bro, it's like before you
come on here, I said, "Bro, you're
talking about grasses. All the people
that watch your glasses. This is the gr
the biggest grassing community I've ever
come across. They like to come on here
and act like they're some kind of bad
man, but then they run to the police,
bro. It's laughable. Like a big part of
it is absolutely laughable. They like to
And what they do is, don't get it
twisted, bro. when they go running to
the police, they they try to use their
mental health as an excuse. Like, oh,
like they're doing this, they're doing
that, they're doing this. Bro, I've got
I've got enough evidence of these people
to get them in prison. It's not even a
joke. Like, it it bro, it ain't even a
joke cuz I saved stuff over the years
and over the few months in case like,
you know, this this day ever come. So,
like, all these people have done is got
themselves in trouble. So when it goes
when it if it does if it goes to trial,
then these people have got themselves in
big trouble. Trust me, mate. And I I
promise you on everything, you know, cuz
that's how a trial works, you
see. So I've got mad stuff like, bro,
I'll send you everything. It's about 100
pages. So yeah, let's see what the
judges have got to say about now.
Okay, that's what like let's see what
the judge got. Like if if I done
criminal damage. Yeah. Five. Oh, I
actually done something. Yeah. Oh, I
actually done something. Oh, I actually
done something. Right. Oh, [ __ ] Oh, I
actually done something. I would say,
"Okay, I'm guilty." Right. And pay the
fine, do the community service. I would
do it. But why am I going to plead to
something I've not done when these
people have literally been harassing me
over the years? I'm not doing it, mate.
Like, there's no way the amount of [ __ ]
these people have done on this community
years and years and years and years and
years. [ __ ] [ __ ] that, bro. Hell no.
Like, you know, like a lot of people,
bro, like, okay, obviously, yeah, you
know, like it's your fault for staying
on this as long as you have. Like, but
unfortunately, we're in that position
now. Like, it's not going to go to trial
and even if it does, it's going to take
two years. I'm not pleading no guilty.
[ __ ] you. I'm not doing it. And that's
what I and that's what I'll say to the
solic. One law for one, one law for the
other. So, but it's not going to go
anyways. But even if it did, it's it's
it's it's [ __ ] up, bro. Trust me, it
is proper [ __ ] up. Like, they
literally come and try taking my phone
as well. Five. Yeah. I don't know. What
day? What day was it? I think it was
Friday. It was Friday. Five, bro. It was
actually on a Friday. Yeah. I hear
knocking on the door. Now, I know I
hadn't done anything. I look outside,
bro. There's a load of old bill. I was like,
"Shit." Like, I was like, "What the
[ __ ] bro? I'm looking. They're knocking
on the door. There's two of them." I
literally threw my phone, bro. I turned
my phone and I threw it. And you know
what they done? They literally Yeah.
took me in the police station, bro.
Yeah. They literally reminded me to call
as well. They reminded me to call and I
said, "Listen, I can tell you all of
these people's channels. They've got a
channel about me. They've got [ __ ] up
about me." I was telling the solicitor
as well, they will not leave me alone.
Yeah. I even told the police this t and
they said, "Oh, like gather up all the
evidence of what you've got on them." I
said, "And I've been doing it for the
past ages and ages and ages." And then
I've also got a crime reference number.
So if they try and say they ain't seen
it, but I reported that. So yeah, they
tried, bro. They tried. I said, "You're
not getting the phone, you stinking
pig." So don't even try, bro. Like
you're not getting it. And I said,
"You're a pig." I said it to his face as
well. All the stuff that I wanted to say
last time. Yeah. When like my mom was
there, I said that you're nothing but a
[ __ ] stinky little wanker pig. How's
that in English for you? And you're not
getting that phone either. And you
should have saw. And then what happened
was when they took me out when they to
when I come out the um court thing um I
went back and I got the phone. It was a
madness. It was a madness mate.
Literally, mate, you should have saw the
look that [ __ ] woman gave me, mate.
It was mad. Like as if to say like, "We
know you got a phone, but we can't find
it." Like, and I just gave it a dirtiest
look back. Yeah. [ __ ] come here
banging on my door thinking you're going
to take my property. That ain't ever
happening, mate. Nah, that ain't ever
happening, mate. You're not getting that
phone, mate. [ __ ] off. And the thing is,
they would have gave it. So, this is why
this is why five. Yeah, you understand
why people don't like police. These
people have been harassing people. These
people have been going people and then
they're coming on your door trying to
take your phone. And bear in mind, I
probably wouldn't get for a very long
time. And it's not what's on the phone
because I'm not a criminal. It's like
I've got my friends on there. I would
have literally lost everything. And
that's why people hate police. Like, you
understand? Like, and that's literally
why people hate police, you know?
So, I wouldn't mind if he was an actual
[ __ ] criminal and you got fair and
you got [ __ ] caught fair and square.
But yeah, it is crazy, bro. But it's
what these people But you got to
understand, f. what these people tell
them. It's what these people tell them
at the same time. Like, you don't know
what they're saying to the police. It's
like what Trumbol used to do. They ain't
got a life. That's why they have to get
police involved, bro. You don't know.
There's there's two sides to every
story. Yeah. And they can only be told
what they what they said, you
know. Anyways, so yeah.
So, it's not a problem. Not a problem at all.
Oh, yeah. And the solicitor said the
solicitor said as well, like it's going
to be like four, it's going to be like
three, four years if there is a trial
date. And they said that even if they
wanted to put it into a trial date, 90%
they're going to drop it. Oh man, I feel
sorry for the taxpayers. I actually feel
taxpayers. It's crazy, bro. I actually
feel I actually feel sorry for like
taxpayers, bro. I actually feel bad. I
actually feel sorry for them,
bro. Yeah, it's a mad website. That's
why I don't have anything to do with
YouTube or anything to do with these
people, bro. Cuz they're just losers.
They're just actual losers, mate.
I know I've been it for a couple days,
but the actual losers, mate. You know what I'm
saying? I actually kind of feel like
sending it today, but I'm not going to. [ __ ]
that. Got a bang in the steak. She got
Ray. Uh, just a long story, mate. But
well, I'm not going to trial, but yeah,
you get it.
These people on YouTube like to bode
people and harass people every day. Yet
they want to get the police involved
when someone says something bad to them.
Yeah, just one of them weird
things. Anyways, we're not talking about
it. Anyways, it's ridiculous. Anyways,
it's stupid. So, yeah, it's not a problem,
mate. I know what I'm doing. I know what
I have to do. So, it's not a problem. Yeah.
Not a problem,
bro. I'm [ __ ] sending it through
summer or no,
man. No, I'm done. Like I said, last
week was the last time I went out for like five
weeks. Was the last time I went out for like five
weeks. [ __ ] five weeks, bro. Five
weeks. And I wish I never went out,
mate. These women will never change.
Yeah. Who do you think grasses? They all
grass. They're all grasses on here.
Truman, the people that you don't know
the names of, they're all grasses. They
ain't got a
life. They all They all do it, man. They
all [ __ ] do it. I've been nicked
about 20 times because of this website.
They all do it, man. Loads of people do
it. I was so much happier, bro. Oh my
god. I was going out on the electric
bike. I was stable. I had no anxiety. I
don't really have much anxiety anyways,
but like I was, bro, I can't explain it.
I was It was like you was a different
person, bro. Like, electric bike,
applied for this [ __ ] job. Life was
good, man. Even though it sounds boring
to you, and as soon as I went out
drinking again, dealing with women
again, I feel like I'm back in the same boat
again. Yeah. Uh, no, not 20 times.
Probably like 10 times to be fair. I
probably been nicked about 10 times over YouTube.
So that's it, man. Yeah.
So, you know, I thought it was at first
I thought it was over that Morgan. I
thought it was over that [ __ ] Morgan.
Like, if that
Morgan called the police on me, I would
be [ __ ] Like if they came to court, I
would be [ __ ] because I I wouldn't
have no defense because, you know, she
tried to get away from you. She ignored
you. You know, you can't say, "Oh yeah,
they ghosted me." Like that's not a
defense. So like, if someone like that
lived in England, I'd be [ __ ] I'd be
[ __ ] if it continued like because I
wouldn't have no defense. But obviously
when people on YouTube have been goating
you and harassing you, it's a very very
very strong defense that you have, you
know, especially when you've reported
these people though. But with someone
like that, you'd be
[ __ ] You wouldn't go to prison, but
there's nothing you could
say. So you
then Yeah, you'd be [ __ ] You would actually be
[ __ ] you know.
But the thing is, if someone does that
from overseas, then they've got to come
to court. They've got to come all the
way to England to go to court, which
who's really going to do
that? Who's really going to do that,
man? I got I had to go to another
country to go to court. Yeah. So, Ali
and you like
that boy. Look, I got a whole fresh trim
and everything as well. What was the point of that?
[ __ ] Don't think I've been on a date
with a brother before. Oh, actually I have ages
ago. Actually, I have ages ago. Yeah.
Well, I've actually lost in Birmingham,
actually. Yeah, they're evil, mate.
Women are evil. Stay away from women.
drink. Um, stay away
from gambling as
well. Yeah, I just stick to Guinness
when I drink now cuz when I was on the
painkillers, I didn't want to drink
spirits just in case. Like I I just
wanted to drink like spirits and stuff
in it. Yeah. I wanted to drink
spirits cuz it's a bit dodgy, bro. You
know what I'm saying? Bit
Dodge. Spirits with medicine. Nah, man. That's
dodgy. Not going to lie, that's dodgy,
bro. Got these. Yeah, I actually thought
Yeah. I don't know why, but when I went
out Thursday, even though I didn't
really like them, I thought, "Okay, this
is it." Now you went through breaking
your [ __ ] foot and all of that for
like a reason, but they just all they
just are they're just all the same.
That's the thing with them. They're just
all the same. There's not even no like
adrenaline rushing anymore cuz you know. So
yeah. You know what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah. But you know what, bro? I've not
won from Gon for like six months. I've
not won from gambling for like six
months. Six months I've not won from
gambling. Imagine that. Six whole
months. [ __ ] Yeah. Gambling,
eh? Six whole
months. But I get your point. Yeah.
Obviously, like you win sometimes, but
with the women it's always the same. No
matter what this situation is. If you
didn't meet somebody years ago, man, I
don't think you really got a chance now. But um
yeah, but that one in Birmingham, she
weren't bad. She was a nice person, but
it's like what? I'm supposed to buy your
drinks and your food. [ __ ] off,
mate. Yeah, but that one from up north.
Yeah, it made me laugh when she said she
didn't feel the vibe even though she
knew what I look like. Even though I'm
confident, even though I know how to
speak to people and like I'm probably up
a her in terms of looks, but yeah,
currently don't feel a vibe. But yeah,
it's laughable in it, mate. It is
laughable. You have to laugh at
it. I don't win, mate. I can't remember
the last time I won from gambling. Nah,
you never win, mate. I lost 80 pound
when I lost 80 pound yesterday.
No, I lost 80 pound yesterday on I Horus
and um Fishing Frenzy. You never win,
mate. Never win. You can't
win. Unless you go to like a physical
casino and you play roulette, then maybe
you could. I never win. I never [ __ ] win,
mate. You're like [ __ ] impressed.
Yeah, you like feel impressed. That's
funny, man. Weird thing to say. But
yeah, it's a depressing life in it,
mate. I've not felt like this for a long
time. I could go out today and send it,
no problem. But I know I'm just going to
get the same
old. You know, you're just going to get
the same old, right? So, I got a roast
dinner to go to
tomorrow. Yeah. And it's like you can't
even be positive because it's just
negative. Like there's no you can't even
be positive about women anymore because
it's just negative. And you know what I
hate? Yeah. The thing that I hate is
when people try to change your mind.
Like, oh, they're not all like that.
That's the [ __ ] that annoys me because,
bro, if they really weren't like that, I
wouldn't be sat there telling you
they're like that at 27 years of age. I
hate it when they try to like say don't
generalize. Like I hate it when they try
to like change your mind. That pisses me
off like I'm a child. Like trying to
like I know what women are like cuz I've
been on dates with women. I've met
women. I approach women. I know what
they're like. Which is the whole reason
I stopped doing it cuz they're all the same.
So no adrenaline rush there. Hey. Yeah. So,
yeah. I won't be back on YouTube
anyways, man. This is just like a
oneoff. Probably like cook a t-bone
today, video it, and then [ __ ] off again.
Depressing, is it? It's a depressing
life here in
England. Definitely booking a holiday
next week, mate. I don't know where I'm
going, but I'm booking somewhere.
Anyway, it's got to be better than
[ __ ] [ __ ] Britain that they call gray.
E. Yeah, that's
cool. But it's no use when somebody
wants a relationship though. Ain't it 5?
Yeah. And I just basically got away from
Reddit. I got away from drinking. I got
away from women. Was the best I ever
was. I was just like binge watching in
between users to be fair. I was just
binge watching in between users to be
fair. And I was the I felt the best I ever did.
So I was just binge watching [ __ ] Inbetweeners and
[ __ ] Went to watch a horror film.
Yeah. I'm not going anywhere like Spain.
I'm going to go America to be honest.
America. I'm probably going to go
America or Thailand. Yeah, I'm going to
go Americ Thailand I reckon.
Stepping outside. Gordon. Nice. Yeah,
I'm going to I'm going to go to Thailand
or um Thailand or
um somewhere like
that. Disneyland maybe. I don't know.
But somewhere definitely somewhere.
But yeah, what do you think would happen
if I go out sending it
today? I've got boyfriend numbers that don't
reply. All of that negative stuff.
Probably all of that
negativity. They're looking up people.
Mate, do you know what? It don't even
scare me. You know, like America,
American prisons. It doesn't even scare
me. The place that scares me is like
Indonesia prisons and that
Indonesia, [ __ ] Thailand. [ __ ]
that. Them places really scare me, bro.
Them prisons. The actual prisons. [ __ ] that,
bro. No, that's scary, bro.
They're locking up people who don't get in.
Yeah. Do you know I've not heard for a
long time that your
skin used to go live and people used to
say, "Oh, your skin, your skin, your
skin." Yeah, you might be lucky. Pigs
might fly as well. Pigs might fly. When
did I go out? I went out not last week,
the week before, which was bank holiday.
Done Friday, Saturday, and I done last
Thursday as well when this state went it
up. I'm sure if you was going to Listen,
man. Listen, if you was going to meet
someone in this country, you would have
met someone by now. You're 27 years of
age. You've tried more than most people
in the world. you've traveled all over
England, you would be with someone, you
know, and the only person I have,
they're not even here anymore. They're
in Wales for a couple of weeks. Yeah. I
got back in contact with that uh with
um with that uh with that
um yeah, with that [ __ ] 19, 20 year
old. And yeah, she come around a few
times, suck my dick and that, but yeah,
I that's my only hope, man. And she
comes back. So yeah, that's my only
hope. Somebody from like a year ago. And
she's not even ugly. That's the thing
with her. She's not even ugly. She's put
on weight now. She look actually looks
better. I feel like it's that, mate. Or
and that's probably another reason. Oh,
that's it as well. Obviously, another
reason why I gave up because obviously I
had her I had her around. So, I've had
her around. I had her around. So, it's
like I didn't need to go out and drink
and try. So, I could just get her around.
But, she's actually good looking as
well. There's actually nothing wrong with her.
Yeah. Nothing wrong with her, mate. [ __ ]
hell. Tired. Going to cook my thingy
soon. No, I'm not going out. It's not
about the money. I'm not going out. I
don't need to go out. I've tried enough.
I'm not going out. When I'm in one of
these moods, mate, I won't go out now
until I feel really, really bad. You
need to take breaks, bro. You can't. I
went out yesterday. No, sorry. Um, I was
Well, I didn't go out yesterday. You
need to take
breaks. You literally It's an imperative
to take breaks cuz you'll end up losing your
mind. You end up actually losing your
mind, bro. It's not about the money.
It's about the women. It's about the
whole atmosphere. It's about the these
[ __ ] men. Like, it's not about the
money, bro. I could be be a millionaire
and I still wouldn't go out today. I'm
not doing it. I'm having a bath, cooking
my t-bone steak, and I'm going to sleep.
That's what I'm
doing. Minimum two weeks.
Minimum. You know, you tried enough as
well. You tried enough as well, man.
[ __ ] hell. This whole
uh this whole past few
weeks was trying to use me,
brother. At least you weren't a cut
though. I don't need some numbers. I've
got plenty of numbers. I don't need some
numbers. I need to leave this country,
which is what I'm
doing. Yeah, some of them replied, but
I'm done anyways. What I need to do is leave this
country. That's what I need to do. I
need to leave this country, mate. That's
what I'm going to be
doing. That's what you need to do. Leave this country.
not go out and get any more numbers.
[ __ ] that. I'm done. [ __ ] them.
No. Load of old
Bill. Load of old Bill.
I've got 93 fingers
now. I've got 93 fingers now in my harassment
album. Oh, the old bill is going to love
to see this. 93. Yeah.
93. I got like 10
videos. Lovely, mate. Lovely.
Yeah. Why don't you go out today,
Gareth? Gary, why don't you go out,
buddy? Why don't you go out? That's what
you should be doing. You should be going
out. I should have already I should
already have a holiday booked to be
fair. Um, why do they? Uh because
they've got unrealistic
expectations. They've got unrealistic
expectations and they think that they're
far better than they actually are. Yeah. That's why that's why.
Yeah. That's why, buddy. [Music]
I had one approach me, give me her
number, [ __ ] meet me, and told me she
didn't feel the vibe. [ __ ] hell, man. What's that? What's
forever? Yeah. And and the thing is, one
second, bro. I'm trying to do
something. You are
Yeah. Yeah. They think they they think
No, no. This is what they do. They think
they can do better yet throughout their
whole 20s. And they say, "Oh, we can't
find normal men. We can't find normal
guys." No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. They claim that they can't find
normal men. They can't find normal guys.
But then when normal guys come and
approach them or go on a date with them,
they claim they can't feel the vibe or
they got a boyfriend. like it, bro. It
makes sense. It just literally doesn't sense, you know?
Yeah. No, street approaching isn't
better. Street approaching isn't
better. It's [ __ ] mate. It's just all
[ __ ] I don't even want to talk about it
anymore. It just annoys me. I don't Bro,
I don't want to talk about it anymore,
bro. Sorry for bringing this up. I don't
want to talk about it anymore. It just
bores me. It's
annoying. It's hella annoying. I don't
want to talk about anymore. It just winds me
up. What's day five? [Music]
Uh, street approaching work to
Newcastle. Street approaching it work in
Newcastle. Nope. No, it didn't. What?
Somebody going on a date with me then
ghosting? Yeah, that really really
worked, didn't it? Yeah. Somebody going
on a date and then ghosting you. Yeah,
man. That worked really well. A 40 meal
and then they ghosted you after. That
really really worked, bro. Didn't it? Yeah. 100%.
Yeah, she was up for it. That street
pool in Newcastle. Bro, I think a lot of
you people actually praying there, bro.
Honestly, I love all of this. These
people are just giving me more
evidence. They're just giving me more
and more evidence.
95 things now. They're just giving me more
evidence. But it's all a waste of time.
The street, the bars, the clubs, they're
all the same. All the same entitled
women, they're all the same. And I don't
want to talk about it anymore, bro. It's
negative. We should be talking about
positive things, not women. That's a big fat
negative. We shouldn't be talking about
them. They're negative. It's all
negative, you know, even though people
don't want to say it is.
Trust me, mate. Coming for me, it's a negative, you
know. This [ __ ] Brummy woman [ __ ]
was giving me the [ __ ] runaround
yesterday as well. And then she finally
said today she wants to
meet. Yeah, it's never
positive. It's never positive. It's all
negative. Oh my god. Stupid ice cream,
man. But I love all this fight. These
people are just giving me more
evidence. They're just giving me more
evidence. Like, I love it.
Oh, you don't know how much
stuff how much stuff I've I've got these
people. You really don't know, man. It
would actually make you cry. It actually
would make you cry, bro. I'm not even
joking. They could give me more
evidence. Oh, just more and more and
more and more evidence.
Fine. Golding, harassing, stalking.
That's what I reported him for. That's
Yeah. So all these people for going,
harassing, stalking, cyber bullying,
which all comes
under keep giving me more and more and
more and more evidence. Give it to Peter
Benny. Let's get to the thousand mark.
Yeah. But um
Yeah. No. Yeah. She's up for meeting.
Yeah. But she's a
transgender. She's a
transgender. Yeah. She doesn't feel the
vibe. But then they moan in the wind
that they can't find men. That's what
makes me laugh. They moan in the wind.
They can't find a normal man.
Five. They moan in the wind that they
can't find a normal man. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't know why she approached me
first. No, no. I was in a club. I was
No, that I was in a club. Yeah. I was
about to send it. Yeah. I was about to
approach her and she's come out the
toilet. And then she approached me. She
says, "Oh, you're attractive. I like
your beard." Yeah. We're just talking
and I got her number and then we was
getting on like a house on fire over
text. met her as as my confident self
obviously is and we was just talking
about like just general chitchat and
then then I then then I said I got to go
home after this last drink cuz it was a
Thursday. I said okay. So I said let's
go out. Um so when do you want to go out
again? She said I'm not really sure I
feel the vibe and my face just dropped
thinking what like I didn't even like
her. No, I didn't like her like that.
But obviously like I I'm I'm in no
position to be picking and I was telling
London Taylor about this. Yeah. Like cuz
he's he's a cool guy that. But I still
don't agree with it. I still think that
No, bro. Like you meet someone in
person, you know what they look like.
You know what they're
about. No, I bought one round a drink
and she bought one one round. Yeah. She
was British and that's why I give up dating. Oh yeah.
And that's why I gave up on dating. So
yeah, but this wasn't about the money,
bro. Wasn't about the money at
all. It annoyed me, bro. It actually annoyed me. So yeah,
yeah, it annoyed me, bro. Actually, it
actually wow me up. Yeah, that first I
thought [ __ ] this. I done some
approaches in the Weather Spoons. I done some
approaches just everywhere, bro. And
same [ __ ] That's why I don't care
anymore, mate. I'm going to stick this
t-bone on soon. I
reckon. Yeah, this Birmingham one, I just ditched
her. I just ditched her, bro, because I
felt like she was using me. I didn't
ditch her cuz she was a three out of 10.
I ditched her cuz I felt like she was
using me. So yeah, I just [ __ ] just
left. I just left,
mate. I need to come. I don't want to
talk about this anymore, bro. And you
[ __ ] keep [ __ ] reminding me of it.
I don't want to talk about this anymore.
It's depressing. It honestly is depressing. So depressant. Yeah. Birmingham. Delete his
channel. More evidence,
lovely. Just keep the evidence coming
in. Just keep it keep it coming in, man.
To do me a favor.
got like 10 different screenshots since
being alive. [ __ ]
hell. There you
go. Going straight into my harassment
folder. Be calling the police back up on
Monday as well. It's not a working day
today. I'll keep following up this report.
So, it's not a problem. Just got new
evidence now. So, it's fine, bro. It's
fine. Anyways, moving on. So, um talking
about this, uh [ __ ] actually they
might be open now. Actually, I might
call them in a
minute. Might call a thing in a minute. So
yeah, how's the gambling anyway? Triple
H. No, no, not the coming out. The
police. I'll be calling the police again in a minute.
Yeah, cuz trust me, eventually these
people will get nicked. Trust me, mate,
cuz I'll be following it up. Following
it up, following it up, following it up,
following up. I reported them like 10
days ago. Um, the police officer still
needs to call me, but
um, they haven't yet, but they will do.
[ __ ] takes time. This [ __ ] took like 6
months, but I'll be calling
them again. So, but I don't think today
is a working day, but we'll try
anyways. It's not a problem, man.
I'm still waiting for this thing, but it's
long. Bills, bills,
bills. Yeah, I know they did. Yeah, I
know. You don't know what, bro? You
don't actually know what I got arrested
for. If I told you, you would
laugh. You would actually laugh, bro.
Like, you would think I'm actually chatting
[ __ ] Like, you would actually think I'm
chatting [ __ ] if you actually heard what
they actually arrested before. Like,
bro, you wouldn't even believe me. Like, it's
bad. Like, it's it's it's madness, bro.
Nope. It wasn't over. That wasn't over.
That all because like you're going to
laugh at it, bro. And I swear now I'm
not even joking. Like you can come if it
goes to trial. You can come in two three
years. If it comes if it goes to trial,
bro, you can come to trial and you will
see that I'm not chatting [ __ ] They literally arrested me for
allegedly calling somebody a gay
virgin. I was like, "What the fuck?" I
was like, after what all of these people
have done, that's when I started showing
them like all of what they've been
doing. About to start like my own police
reporting out. I was like, what the
[ __ ] I I literally couldn't believe it.
I said to the police officer, I was
like, you must be some bully victim
wanker. To actually come on someone's
door over that, you must be some bully
victim [ __ ] wanker. I actually said
that, bro. I was like, I couldn't
believe it, bro. I'm not even joking. I
swear to God. Yep.
Literally, it's a madness. I swear to God,
bro. Oh my god. I swear to God, bro. I
swear to God. Yep. Really, bro.
Really? But it's how these people go on
to the police, bro. You don't know what
they're telling them. Oh, I've got this.
I've got that. I've got this. These
people play the victim, but the victim
don't know, right, that what these
people are doing. the sorry the police
don't know what these people are doing.
So this is why I'm making them aware
like they've got a channel. Um they
won't leave me alone. I've had to report
it like many many many many times. I was
like yeah I know literally literally I
apparently called someone a gay virgin.
I was like prove it in court then.
That's what I said. I said prove it in
court. That's what I said. And I said to
the [ __ ] police as well listen here
you [ __ ] pig. You're going to listen
to me now piggy. Right, bro. I was
having I was having a go at them, the
police. I was and I told them all about
the channel and I was like, "Oh, [ __ ]
it. I'll start my own report and I would
have been [ __ ] as well because if they
took if they took my phone, I wouldn't
have the evidence of what they've been
doing." So, yeah. So, yeah, I've
reported them for stalking and
harassment. I've reported them for
stalking and harassment harassing
me 10 year I don't know who it who it
was 10 years ago. I don't know who it
was, but he he claims that he knew me,
but I can't recall seeing him. But I've
reported him for stalking and
harassment like, and they even said it
about like to my mom as well. Like, what
I've got is is enough. Like they these
people thought they were clever by
deleting stuff. I've got literally
everything. Literally everything.
Bullying, cyber bullying. Like, bro,
this is going to be a mad tribe. If they
even want to waste taxpayers money.
Yeah. taking this to trial. They're
going to lose. They're 100% going to
lose. You know, like it's either there's
two things that's going to happen, bro.
They're either going to drop
it or you you're either going to they're
either going to drop it. Yeah. Or you're
both going to get dumb. That's literally
like I asked my solicitor. They said
that obviously if it does go like and
they want to pursue it and and they
don't want to drop it, you're both going
to get dumb.
like like that's it. And I was like, I'd
rather that. Okay, fair enough. If if
both people get punished, you know, you
know, I'm fine. But yeah, you can't make
one rule for one, one rule for another.
You know, this has been going on for
ages. And the solicitor even knew it as
well. So I said, I'm fine with that. You
know, you know, you might get a fine,
you might get some community service,
you might get something, but he said
that like they're either going to drop it.
um you know, they're either going to
drop it or you're just going to both get
done. That's what he said. So, I was
like, either either one is is uh is that's
it. Yeah. No, Greg, I won't because I've
got evidence of what these people have
been doing. I've got all their
harassment, all their golden,
everything, bro. It's not You know what
I'm saying? I've literally got all their
golden and all their harassment. But if
you've got if you've got if you got
uh Yeah. If you listen Grezy. Yeah. If
you still got Instagram, I will show you
everything. Everything. Ready to take to
trial court if they even if they even
want to make it to trial. Even if they
want to pull it to trial. Yeah. Like,
bro, you know, it's it these people
won't win. Trust me. I've got like a
bro, I've got my own album of
harassment. Literally, I've got my own
um bro, no one's going to jail. There's
not going to be no jail [ __ ]
sentence. Yeah. Bro, the the trial is
not going to be for like two, three
years. So, anyways, we're done. Anyways,
I'm not talking about this no more. I'm
not talking about this. I'm not talking
women. Yeah, we sort it out, bro. [ __ ] hell, man.
Yeah. Anyways, we're done talking about
this anyways. [ __ ] hell. Why are we talking about
this? No one's going to jail. Literally
nobody. So, yeah. Talking about this, mate. [ __ ] this.
Yeah. At least the foot's a lot better.
which is a good thing. At least the
foot's um a lot
better. It's good anyways, bro.
It I'm on painkillers as
well. Yeah, I'm on [ __ ] painkillers,
too. Painkillers. Painkillers.
Painkillers. Like, yeah, if you went and
you plead guilty, you'd probably get
like a fine community service, but I was
like, "No, no, mate. As long as it takes
2 years, 3 years." Nah, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. I remember before
they tried to caution me for criminal
damage. I was like, "Mate, take me to
court." And then they ended up dropping
it. They tried to caution me for
breaking my own [ __ ] door. Like, nah, mate.
Yeah, I even told the police officers as
well. I said, "This will be the last
time you come on this door and try and
embarrass me." That's what I said to
them as well. So,
yeah. Yeah, I know. I had to go on a
date with a [ __ ] foot injury. Imagine
that, eh? But
yeah, but it doesn't matter. Like, it
doesn't matter what it is. community
service a fine. You shouldn't be getting
punished when these people have
literally harassed you, goed you,
they've broke into your house. You
shouldn't be having any sort of
punishment, any sort of
conviction. You know what I'm saying? So
that's that's that like obviously and
and the fact I didn't do it either. So
they can like prove that in court if
they want. That's up to them, man. Not
asked one little bit.
So, it's not a problem, mate. It's not a
problem. Sometimes these things take
time, bro. But
yeah, that's it. Anyways, I'll follow up
with this report later. Anyways, cuz you
were supposed to be calling me. He ain't
calling me. Police
officers. So, yeah. Yeah, man.
[ __ ] it now. But it doesn't matter. Like
even if it's a fine, they take like5 off your
benefits. Yeah, I know. It's a madness,
isn't it? You know what's probably going
to happen? The judge is going to take
one look at it and then just
laugh and then they probably just laugh at
it. They're probably just like,
"What?" Yeah, probably. That's probably
what's going to happen, you
know. So, but yeah, I've got all my
evidence anyways. So, [Music]
yeah. But yeah, you should be calling me
today. If you don't, I'm going to find out his name. And
um yeah, I'm call him and say these
people will not stop in harassing Peter
Belly. I've got all the evidence. They
won't stop harassing me. But I've got to
call you every [ __ ] day, mate. I'll son. You know.
Yeah. Yeah. Get your steps in when
you've got a broken
foot. But yeah, I know what they give
people. Suspended, sentence, fine. You
won't go prison. Rare people go to
prison. The only time you go prison
nowadays is if you do armed robbery,
um, armed robbery, drug dealing, and
you're definitely going to prison. But
stuff like that, mate. Even nonsense get away
nowadays. The ultimate worst they'll
give you, the ultimate worst thing
they'll give you is probably a suspended
sentence. People don't go to prison for that, mate.
So obviously it's happened but nah you
ain't going to prison you
know. Nah not for that
mate. You go to prison for like plugged
in and armed robbery and that but not for
that. Unless she was in like a tie prison
it. Yeah, I know. It's a joke of a
country. It is. It is just a It's
England is just [ __ ] though. The women, the
police. Yeah, like the like the
Um, police, women, weather. I know. I
can't believe like I was actually
laughing like when I was actually in the
cell. I I was actually laughing about
it. Obviously not laughing laughing, but
I was semi- laughing cuz I was like I
couldn't believe it. I actually thought
I was dreaming. I was like all of what
like and that's why I was like I really
need to get on to these police
now. No. Um apparently I called somebody
a gay virgin.
Grezy, a gay virgin. Apparently I called
somebody a gay virgin. Yep. Not even joking,
bro. Yep. Not even joking. Like if there
is a trial date, which I got a good
feeling there's not going to be with the
amount of evidence I've gotten these
people. Um I'm more than happy to give
you the date,
buddy. Yeah, I know. I'm not even
joking. Yep. I'm not even joking.
They've got nothing better to do with
their life. These
pigs, you know, they've been doing it
for a long time now. These [ __ ] pigs.
time and time and time and time and time
again. Yeah. Crazy, isn't
it? And then like, but it's fine, bro,
cuz I'm reporting these people now every
day. So, it's fine. Uh
yeah, all these people are going to get
themselves in trouble. Five. Trust me,
by the end of it, these people are just
going to be getting um themsel in
trouble. Trust me. Trust me on that one,
bro. You have my word. Like, doesn't
matter how long it takes. You know what I'm
saying? Doesn't matter how long it
takes. And I've got a I've got a crime
reference number as well. So, there's
actual proof that you've reported it.
See, Monty, like he's making jokes that
he's reporting. I've actually reported
these people to the police and I'm going
to keep doing it and doing it and doing
it and doing it and doing it and doing
it and doing it. But I don't think he actually has like saying.
So I've got lots of stuff, bro. Lots and
lots and lots of stuff. And that's one
of the reasons I kind of come off social
media cuz I find that with these pigs,
they will find any excuse to come on
your door. Do you know what's so mad?
You could go out right now. Yeah. For
example, and rob a bank and you'd
probably get away with it. You could
probably go out right now and rob a
bank, right? And yeah, like I said, you
you'd get away with it. You [ __ ]
swear at someone online, maybe a woman.
Don't want your door before you could
say Jack Robinson. I know. It's mad,
isn't it, bro? It's [ __ ] mad. This
country is a
joke. Oh, it's a joke, bro. It is a
I'm surprised I didn't get arrested for
the [ __ ] USA is he
thing. You know what I'm
saying? You know what I'm
saying? I'm surprised like that, you
know, the Morgan
thing. The Morgan thing. I'm surprised,
bro. USA Izzy said that she reported me,
but yeah, it's crazy, man.
USA Izzy. Do you think USA Izzy actually
reported me five? I think
so. Yeah, I was thinking about that the other day
and I was actually thinking about
it. But she started it. She started it.
She actually did start it. Obviously,
you wouldn't have a defense in court
because you wouldn't you can't say, "Oh,
yeah, she led me on." Because it's not
going to it's not a defense. Even though
what she done is [ __ ] up and what it
is is wrong. Obviously, the amount of
stuff that you've said to her, it's you
don't have a defense with these people.
I do. You know what I'm saying? I know
I've got everything that they've been
doing for years and they won't leave me
alone. So, like it's it's it's a bit of
a different situation. It's unfair the
whole USA thing, but that's just the way
it works, you
know? Well, you're going to say what?
They blocked you and so you can you said
all of these bad things. But she
actually started it. She actually did
it, you know. She did start it. But it's
not a good defense to you. You wouldn't
have a defense if that makes sense. But
yeah, he did definitely started it.
She felt like she could try to mock
people and continuously ignore people
time and time again. And you know what?
Yeah, I'm not even going to do madness
yet. I just said to her, "Yeah, can you
just please apologize?" And then that's
the end. And then she thought she could
keep ignoring and ignoring and ignoring.
Then I just messaged her dad because she
drove me to it, you know? She actually
bro. You know, and when I when I
messaged the [ __ ] on WhatsApp, she
didn't care. She She didn't care. It was
like she was kind of mocking it in a
way. She didn't give a [ __ ] And then I
was like pissed off. I was like, "Okay,
can you just please say sorry?" And and
then they just thought they could get
away with. And then when it started
affecting her, when her family started
saying, "Oh, we got this guy messaging." Yeah.
Um then obviously like messaging and
that um you know, then it then she
started saying, "Oh, you're sick and
twisted." H like what are you then? What
do you what do you class yourself as
then? If I'm sick and twisted, what do
you class yourself as?
Do you understand what I'm saying, bro?
Like it's [ __ ] up.
Yeah, she's nasty. She is. I was on her
Instagram the other day, bro. She's
nasty. Trust me. She's a nasty bastard. Nasty
[ __ ] Tr just
Yeah. Obviously like went there. She
didn't come out. It didn't need to go to
that. But you know, like don't [ __ ]
[ __ ] with me. Don't think that oh at
face at face value like you can just
[ __ ] with someone and they're not going
to say anything. I'm saying like who
does she think she is, bro? So
yeah, so I just kind of lost hope since
that really to be honest. You know, I
still gave people a chance and
whatever. Well, I didn't go out for five
weeks. Uh, no, I went out. I just didn't
go out drinking. Went out on the electric
bike. Went to KFC every week. Done food
shopping. Chilled. watched the TV
series, just that kind of stuff, bro. I
went out like but just not out drinking
and approaching women. But then when I
started again, I felt nervous cuz I do
all the time. But but I kind of lost
hope after that. Then I met these other people and then they just it's
negative. It's just negative experiences, isn't
it? Do you know what Antman said? He
said that they're just not interested in this country.
They just aren't interested in this
country. Yeah, I think he was right,
man. I think he was rightly laid. Yeah. [Music]
Yeah. Yeah. Well, no. Not even because
you remember when I went around asking
like offering money like suck dick and
that they said
no. No. No. No. No. No, I actually
thought that would have worked like
months ago. I genuinely thought that
would have worked. Maybe I'm delusional,
bro. Call me delusional, but I actually
thought that actually would have
worked. I generally thought that would have worked,
man. I'm just sick of them, bro. I'm
just sick of talking about them as well,
bro. Let's just allow it now. Yeah.
Yeah, let's just allow it in it,
bro. Yeah, I don't want to talk about
them anymore, bro. They're just like
It's just annoying talking about
him. So, yeah, I'm going to do this job
thing, get more money, and then just
[ __ ] off. That's the only thing
like and the thing I don't even the
reason I don't even have anything booked
yet, which is bad. Like if I had stuff
booked, I could just leave. Like it
would be better to go out every week
because then at least I've got something
to look forward to. I don't even have
anything to look forward to. At least if
you booked a holiday again, you have
something to look forward to whilst
you're dealing with the [ __ ] in this
country. Oh, I've only cuz with Adman,
he's like, "Oh, I've only got four weeks
to go. I've only got three weeks to go.
I've only got two months to go." Cuz he
knows eventually he's going to go back
to Thailand. Whereas me, I don't have
anything booked. So I'm kind of like [ __ ] So
So yeah, that's like if you
uh Yeah, that's basically all you can
do. You need to you need to get
something booked, bro, before like even
going out again. Like
honestly, I don't know. I don't know where, but
yeah. What's the time?
5:32. 5:32. I think it's my supper time soon.
Supper. Good old
supper. Oh, at least my foot's
better. The one the woman in Birmingham
was like, "You're walking like a spacker. Uh
uh. She was like, "Oh, you're walking
like a spack." I was like, "My foot," I
said to the other woman, "I'm walking on
a bit of a limp cuz I got a foot
injury." Yeah. I was like, "Don't mind
that in it. I've got a bit of a foot
injury, mate." So, if I'm walking like a
bit of a spacker, like you know why in
it? Yeah. Painful thing though. Painful thing.
That's one of the worst players I've had
in my life.
Might have my tea
soon. My tea.
Mushrooms, steak, onion rings. Banger
banger. It's a [Music]
banger. It's a [ __ ] banner, bro.
Yeah. I think I banned it on the wall,
man. I think I banned it on the wall.
I'm only on YouTube for today. Then I'm [ __ ]
um I'm [ __ ] gone again. So yeah, I
think I banged it on the wall when I was
sleeping. But mate, it weren't a joke,
mate. The whole foot was swollen up. I
couldn't even walk, mate. It was hurting
me, mate. And when I woke up, when I
woke up first thing in the morning, it
was like throbbing like bam, bam, bam.
Felt like someone shot me in my foot.
I had to get my friend to come over and
help me with things. I couldn't walk,
mate. And I had to like take ibuprofen
and just put ice on it cuz I went to the
doctors. That's another thing that's
[ __ ] up with this system, the NHS.
Yeah. So, I went to the doctors, right?
Okay, we're going to give you some
codonable. Yeah. For the pain. So, okay.
They'll come back in 2 hours. But they
said that you need rest and you need to
put ice on it. You need rest and you
need to put ice. So come back to the
pharmacy in two hours. No, they said a
couple of hours. I'm thinking, okay,
just give a bit of time. I went to
Morrison's. Yeah. And then [ __ ] I
went, no, where' I go? No, Tesco. I
went, sorry. Which was near a pharmacy
and oh, your prescription is not ready.
I was like, you what? So you want me to
go back home and then come back out when
you've told me to rest? That doesn't
make no sense. You literally told me to
rest. Yeah. And you're you're having me
go back out for this medication that
should be ready. You know, it should be
doesn't make sense. It doesn't make
sense. They told me I needed to
rest. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Even though they told me that I needed
to rest, I had to go back out like 3
hours later. I wasn't happy, mate.
Imagine trying to
walk. Yeah. Well, hospital weight times
are a pistake, but there's a there
there's a way around that. Go at 2:00 in the morning.
Bam. Yeah. Go at 2:00 in the morning,
man. 2 in the
morning. I was just talking about this foot injury.
have any oil for the fire? Yeah.
Yeah, it will still be busy if
you Yeah, central London
maybe. Anyways, I'm going to make myself
some food cuz I'm starving.
Oh, looking forward to cooking, but I'm going
to All right, I'm out of here. Peace.