[ __ ]
No. I'm usually uh
Question more. Question. Question Yeah. [Music]
250. It's all right there.
[ __ ] me. Yeah.
I need to show that I should
just go to today. At least we've already
got a few weeks now. H a few weeks
here. Yeah. At least if you go out
again, you can I got five weeks to go. I
feel Antman had the right idea by doing
that booking before going out, you know.
At least, you know, you've only got a
couple of weeks
here dealing with this [ __ ] And at
least I'm only 27. I'm thinking to my
30s to realize this, so that's good. All
right. This is the only week where I'm
actually like back to normal. Yeah. And
then three, four weeks. I swear to
God. Jesus [ __ ]
Christ. When it rains it [ __ ] paws, don't
it? Yeah. I'm out of here soon
anyways. Probably deal with the [ __ ] you
get when you go out. year in year out.
Year in year out, year in, [ __ ] year
out. You know what I'm saying?
Uh, year in, you out, year in, year out.
This guy from the This guy from New
Zealand was like, "Better luck next
time." I was like, "Mate, there's not
going to be no next time. I'm
leaving." That week was the final straw,
bro. This country, that was the final
straw. That was me done, bro. That was
literally me done. That was me done. Done.
That's the that was the only thing left
to do. I think
yeah, the only thing was that was left
to do was to book a
holiday. That was the only positive
thing left to do. I think when it comes
to this [ __ ] country with these [ __ ]
women in it.
[ __ ] helped as well to be
honest. Arguing, arguing, arguing and
arguing and arguing is [ __ ]
pointless, bro. It's a waste of life.
What are you arguing over, bro? If these
people were right, you would have had
different experiences. It's that it's
that simple. Or there's no need to keep
arguing. They're all the same and it
will always be all the same. That's it. No biggie, man.
Yeah. What it is, mate. It's what it
is. But it literally sent me backwards
for like a week, bro. I'm not even
joking. Like literally a whole week.
Like I'm finally back to normalish kind of. [ __ ]
hell. Don't go out drinking. Hey. [Music]
Hey. I learned my [ __ ]
lesson. Yeah, I learned my lesson.
Yeah, cuz we hear about these things all
the time like gambling,
alcohol, like but we never hear about
women being a negative. No one ever has
a bad word to say about them when it
literally is cuz if we did not go out of
that bank holiday, we would have been
fine. You know, we would have been fine.
know, [ __ ] annoying, bro. They are.
They piss me off. That's what they do as
well. Annoying time
wasters, hypocrites. They're
everything. And I put them all in one
bracket, every single one of
them. So, yeah.
I forgot just how bad dates were until I
went on them
again. I was like, "Oh [ __ ] is this how
bad they actually are? [ __ ]
hell." But they'll moan and winge and
they can't find a normal person. They'll
moan and winge and we'll have to listen
to their winging. Yeah. [ __ ]
me. [ __ ] me,
man. Just chill now. Watch YouTube
videos. I'm just going to chill today.
Just a nice chill. Nice chill
out. Minds me.
Uh, none of you people on here own
anyone. You're just keyboard warrior
cowards. Bye-bye now.
Anyways, stop repeating yourself. Stop
self stop self
projecting. Getting old now, man. The
community is dead. Like, there's not
even no point doing that on here
anymore. Trust me, you little keyboard
warriors don't own no
one. You just don't own
You probably don't even own a [ __ ]
normal pair of trainers, mate. Let alone
own someone like me. You don't know no
one. You're just
cowards. Like the definition of this the
definition of this community is just
cowards. Like there's there's there's
nothing else to really say about these
people that they're just coward self
projectors. Like that's
literally all they are. Like they're not
even worth arguing with. to this people
that ain't got alive. [Music]
a good m talking about yourself
again. I've actually got uh cash right
on the side of me. Actually, not going
to show you though. I don't need to show
you anything because you're self
projecting. Stop talking about yourself.
There's a good fellow.
Yeah, I'm very very skint. Yeah, I'm
very skint. Yeah, let me listen. Hear this.
Yeah, that's the sound of money and I'm
not showing you nothing. You're just talking about
yourself. Show you 20. I'm not showing
you nothing. Go self-reflect on another
channel. How's it going? Um, it's going
um it's going good, man. Better than the
past couple of days. Um, finally back to
my routine again. Cooking in, give up
drinking. I booked a holiday, so I'm
looking forward to that. Something had
to give, man. Like, we can't keep doing
this all our [ __ ] life. You know, the
the these time wasting women in this
country, the bad experience, the bad experiences, the
drinking. Yeah, it's gone better than it
was the past couple of
days. Show you 20 pound and you'll show
20 grand, mate. You got shown thousands
multiple times and you couldn't show nothing.
Behave. Behave yourself. Behave,
mate. Yeah, I booked to go to Thailand,
bro. Um, so like now if I do go out in
the future here, I know that I've only
got a short amount of time before I
leave. I should have done this ages ago,
mate. But to be fair, I'm still only 27.
Some people would take to their 30s, you
know. So yeah, I'm not doing this with
these these women in this country
anymore, mate. It just pissed me off.
All last week just pissed me off, bro.
Like, it just pissed me off. It's not
even a joke. I woke up like with mad
mood swings yesterday as well. Um, I
went to my mom's to have a roast dinner,
but I weren't even like going to, but I
calmed down. But today, I feel better
than I did.
You know, I'm sick of the women in this
country. I wish I never went out that
bank holiday. I wish I never went out.
I'm not even joking. I wish I stayed. I
I wish I never, lad. [ __ ] this. [ __ ] this,
mate. About how you don't feel the vibe.
Get out of here, mate. [ __ ] off. I'm out
of here. I'm done with this
[ __ ] Yeah, the flights are long, but they're quite
cheap. No, I'm just going on holiday,
mate. I just need a
holiday. That's what I need. I just need
a holiday, mate.
Just need a good old holiday by myself.
That's what I
need. So, no, I'm not. But obviously,
I'll get some people when I'm out there,
obviously. Just need a good old holiday,
break. I've had a lot of stress the past two, three
weeks. And then the [ __ ] [ __ ] drags
you down again. The alcohol and the
women drag you down again. They're all
the same, man.
bit for just for holiday. Uh, no. That's
the point of a holiday is going
somewhere for that's the whole point of
holiday. But um, why choose Thailand? I
mean, it's cheap, easy to get women,
nice food, good weather, nice people.
What more could you
want? No point going to Spain. It's full
of [ __ ] English people.
Spain is [ __ ] full of English people.
Why the [ __ ] would you want to go Spain?
Might as well stay in
England. You might as well [ __ ] stay
in [ __ ] England if you're going
somewhere like [ __ ] Spain. But they're
[ __ ] Cuz that's what England's full of [ __ ] Absolute
[ __ ] Yeah, you got a lot of here. So yeah,
man. These women will never change in
this country. Oh, you'd be a damn fool
to think any of them are different.
You'd be a damn fool to think any of
them were different, mate. None of them are.
So yeah, it will never change. It's boring. It's
aggravating. So had to do something
about it in the end. So I
am like I said, bro, them five, six
weeks were the best five, six weeks of
my life. No drinking, no talking to
women, none of that stuff. My life was
ace. Soon as you talk to women again,
same problem happens. So what suggests
the problem is is obviously [ __ ]
them, isn't it? These entitled westernized [ __ ]
[ __ ] you know? And it's not even
just that. It's just the whole country
is full of [ __ ] It's not even just
them. You say one thing in the pub, the
guy gets a hissy fit out of it and he
calls the manager of like, you know what
I'm saying? Cuz I I just said to I just
said to London Taylor, I just messaged
him. I don't know why I messaged him,
but I just said to him like, "Bro, it's
the actual principle." Like, imagine a
32y old thinking that they're better
than you. A 32 year old that's hit the
[ __ ] wall cuz you hit the wall when
you're 29 as a woman. 32. You've hit the
[ __ ] wall, mate. You've hit the wall.
Literally, who the [ __ ] do they think
that they're better than? That's even
worse. Even though you didn't like them,
that's even [ __ ] worse. So, you got
people that are in their 30s now
thinking they're better than above
average looking men. I'm so [ __ ]
done, bro. And then, and I met that one from [ __ ]
Birmingham. She's like [ __ ] trying to
She's like a gold digger.
So, I'm just sick of them. I hate them.
I literally do. That's why I've decided
to do something about it. But that's
why should have been done a long time ago, but
yeah, it is what it is. Eh, I have to
click to see the comments. [ __ ] I don't
know why it say share your referral
link. What? What is that? Why does that
keep popping up, man? It's
annoying. So, that's where we're at.
Anyways, the wall
[ __ ] They go on dates to waste your
time and their
time. That's what I don't get. They go
on dates to waste your time and their
time, but they claim that there's
nothing wrong with them. People claim
that there's nothing wrong with these
people, yet you would go on a date to
waste your time and the other person's
time. It's so It's so weird. They're
such weirdos. Like where I didn't deal
with them for such a long time, bro. I
kind of forgot five, six weeks. But
they're proper proper weirdos, aren't
they? And then you get people on like
Grievy that says that we're scared to
commit. Apparently we're scared to
commit. Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro. He says
that we're the ones that are scared to
commit. Yeah, I've met people before
where they looked completely different.
I just stayed with them
cuz, you know, it is what it is, man.
You approach them, you [ __ ] stay with them.
Yeah. And I'm way better than a lot of
these women that I've actually met. I'm
way better than them. Like not to blow
smoke up my own ass, like I'm not better
than everyone, but I know that I'm
better than some of these women that
I've met and they've cuz for the for the
simple fact is they've hit the wall and
I haven't. How about that one? They've
hit the wall and I
haven't. You know, when a woman is 32,
33, most of the time they look like a
man when they're 50. It would take us to
get into our mid4s, 50s to start looking
like them, but yet they still think that
they're better than people. It's crazy. [ __ ]
hell. Then they will winge and moan and
they can't find anyone. Oh, Jesus
Christ. And we have to listen to it.
It's It's [ __ ] up, is
it? Madness, it charges downstairs. Props.
Yeah. You're the only one that needs
your hairline done, mate. This [ __ ]
community. You're not the only one that
needs your hairline done in this
community, bro. There's loads of people
that need their their [ __ ] hair done.
People like Red Star, other people.
That's why they come on here and call
you bald and skint because they're
talking about themselves every day. Um,
but like there's a lot of people, bro.
You ain't the only
one. You're not the only one, buddy. The
only one that admits
it. I'm going to binge watch Soprano
pictures in a bit. I need a chill day
today, man. I need a chill day. Probably
going to cook some burgers in a bit.
Maybe some Yeah, I make some pork chops. Red shell. Yeah. [Music] Start.
Let's keep an eye on that.
What's there as
well? But yeah, why do you comment here
every day saying that skin thing as well
still, man? It's getting proper boring,
bro. Like, we get it, man. Like, [ __ ]
you people skin. Got to do something
about it, man. Stop coming on here
projecting every single
day calling people skin. You don't know
what people have. What people don't
have. You don't know what people have.
You don't know what people don't have.
Mate, look. You just call me Skint,
right? I've got a bit of bum change here.
Yeah. Let me show you. I shouldn't even
be doing this to be fair. But I've got
literally a little bit of pocket change
to take to the corner shop right
here. Stop talking about people that you
don't know. Yeah. Because then it's sort
of like you're kind of talking about
yourself again. You
understand? Stop talking about people
that you don't know. Stop repeating
yourself. Yeah. You
understand? Stop coming online. Keep
talking about people that you don't
know. You're talking about yourselves
cuz you're on here. You're on here every
day, bro. I shouldn't even be on here.
There. There you go. You got a few 50
notes. That's corner shop pocket chain.
Stop talking about people that you don't
know. Talking about yourself. Well, you
talking about You're talking about
yourself. But stop coming online every
day talking about
yourself. You know, coming online every
day talking about your own
life because if you weren't skin, you
would be on here every day hating. You
know what I'm
saying? They're all glasses as well.
They're proper grasses as well. five.
You know, I've I've never come across in
my whole life so many grasses in one
place at once as well. That's why I
don't get into it with them. That's why
I don't get into it with like L J and
all of them because I know they're just
grasses. So, there's no point. It's like
that. Did you see that L J when he's
going on Timmy's door and that, bro? I
was going to start on him. I was going
to tell him to come to London. What's
the point? They're glasses. There's no
point. They're all glasses on here.
Think of it, bro. So why am I going to
I'm not even going to get into it with
these people, bro. If you know people
are grasses, you don't [ __ ] with them.
Simple. Him, the people that follow him.
[ __ ] all that, bro. They're all grasses,
man. Why I don't get into it with them.
I don't get into it with any of these
people. Because how many people have
been on my door versus how many times
have police been on my door? Think about
it, right? Who's been on the door more?
Police or people from this website?
People, you know, police. So, at the end
of the day, I Why would you get into it
with grasses? It doesn't make
sense. I wish you come on my door, mate.
Oh, I wish you come on my
door. I wish he come on my door, bro. I
would have whipped his ass. Why do you
think he went to Birmingham?
Why do you think he went to Birmingham,
bro? Because of
uh cuz he knows, in it, bro. He
knows. He got his ass whooped coming
here, boy. Telling you, he would have
got his ass [ __ ]
whooped. Trust me, he would
have. Why go to Birmingham? Birmingham
of all places is a [ __ ] [ __ ]
man. Yeah, they come on here every day
and call you skinty. You got more money
than them. I know. It's a madness, isn't
it? Just self
projectors. This little
self-reflectors, 5o, whoever you are.
These people on like £300 a month and
then they gamble their money and then
come on the internet and call other people skin.
They literally talk about theirelves.
They talk about their own lives. It's a
nice day outside today. These people are
going to be sat on YouTube. They're
going to be sat on the
internet. To be fair, I'm going to be
chilling today. Not on here, but I'll
just be chilling because I'm tired. Had
a long few
weeks. So, had to buy a new washing
machine and [ __ ] So, I had like a
long a long week. I went out of bank
holiday. I went out and enough. Yeah.
Yeah. It's a shame women are all the
same. Is it
Fiverr? What do you think it is? I think
they're looking for Mr. Perfect. I was
trying to figure this out yesterday. Is
it that they want to pass time or is it
because they they're looking for Mr.
Perfect. Mr. Perfect don't exist. I'd
love to know really what it
is because they moan about being single.
They moan they can't find normal
men, but they approach people then
apparently can't feel the vibe. So, I
mean, I'm kind of lost to be honest with
you, you know? And you'll get these
little simps, right, or these little
white knights that say it's not women,
but mate, trust me, it [ __ ] well is.
It [ __ ] well is, mate. And I would
know because I've done this [ __ ] enough
time. A [ __ ] 32y old thinking that
they're better than you. What is life,
bro? Come on. What is actual
life? Yeah, they think that they're
better than they actually are.
It's crazy, bro. It actually
is. And they say the common demeanor
demonito is the men that struggle.
Actually, it's the women because more
men struggle than don't struggle. And
then they'll go on about people that are
in relationships. Bro, people are only
in relationships because they might have
got lucky. They might have met in
school. They might have met on a dating
app. That doesn't go for the whole of
the the whole population. It's not even
a valid argument. Like it's literally
not even a valid argument because why
are so many people going to Thailand?
Why are so many people struggling? Why
is it that whenever you're in these
clubs and conversation comes about you
hardly get anyone disagree with you? Cuz
obviously it is literally
them because if it wasn't you wouldn't
hear about anyone struggling ever. Of
course it's them. is 100% them, you
know, but people don't like to admit it
is them for some reason. I don't know,
bro. Five, six weeks, no drinking, no
talking to them. Life was good, man.
perfect. And look, we're back into this
again, you know, back into it. Madness.
It's got to be their standards are not
really because I'm thinking, bro. Yeah,
I'm not ugly. Obviously, I'm not ugly.
Like, and a lot of other people are not
ugly. I get Oh, [ __ ] And a lot of other
people are not ugly. I get it. Yeah. But
they can't be wasting my time and their
time on purpose because why would
someone do that? It's either that
they're they want to pass time or
they've got unrealistic expectations. It
has to be that. It has to be that
because if we go on a date with somebody
that's six, seven out of 10 and they're
somewhat they've got somewhat of a
personality, bro, we're not ditching
them. So, it has to be they've got unre
they're expecting some sort of Romeo and
Juliet. I'm telling you, it's got to be
that. It has to be because nothing else
would make make sense. Think about it,
bro. If you're average to above average
looking, you dress good, you smell good,
you're confident. If you say you met a
woman that was exactly the same, what
you're telling me that you're not going
to vibe with her? See, so it's actually
them that's got unrealistic
expectations. I'd rather use the words
expectations than standards to be
fair. They're expecting some Romeo and
Juliet, mate. I'm telling you, [ __ ]
Miss Piggy and [ __ ] Kermit the Frog.
I'm telling you, bro, it's got to be cuz
there's nothing wrong with me. There's
nothing wrong with a lot of other
people. Sorry if you're 32 or or older
and you take offense to that, but when
you're a 32 year old woman, you've
approached the war
already. And I can speak I can speak on
this one, bro. Because when I met USA, I
didn't even really like her to begin
with. I was like, "Okay, well, they've
got an accent. Let me just roll with
it." But then they tell us that we've
got unrealistic standards. This is what
doesn't make any sense. Right?
Anytime that you you know you say, "Oh,
they've got unrealistic standards." They
say that it's men. That's not true,
though. Because men are the only ones
that lower their
standards. And women are the only ones
that date above. So, how does that make any
sense? There has been times, bro, where
where I've just stuck with it. I have,
bro. Trust me, with people that are
absolutely stinking. So then if you are
not stinking, why are they not sticking
with you? Don't make sense. So there you
go. Definitely them,
bro. It's not just London, mate. It's
the whole of
England. It's not just London, mate.
It's the whole of England. It's the
whole of It's the whole of the
West. It's everywhere, mate. It's not
one city is easier than the other. I
mean, this woman was from up
north. Um, but it's still like, you're
in London, you're a
[ __ ] The one in Birmingham was nice,
but she was like a three out of 10. And
she was trying to be a gold digger,
which is why I ditched her, cuz she was
trying to be a gold digger. Not cuz she
was a three out of 10, because she was
trying to be a gold digger. So, that's
why I just left her. Wasn't even this how she
looked. Even with that 20 year old now
she's 20. She's got this entitled vibe.
Like I I know cuz I deal with them. I
know what they're like. They've got this entitled vibe.
So So yeah, it's not just London. It's
everywhere in the West. America, Canada,
Australia. They're all
[ __ ] They're all [ __ ]
here. You should go places like Brazil.
Go places like Brazil,
uh, Brazil and [ __ ] Philippines,
[ __ ] Thailand. Even Brazil, bro. You
can go to Brazil as well. Brazil is
good. You can go to
Brazil. Yeah, go Brazil as
well. It's not just Philippines, South
America, but anywhere in the West. Ah, [ __ ] Absolute
Yeah, they go quiet as well. There was
just one that I
met [ __ ] near my area. They've gone
silent. Bors me, mate. [ __ ] bors
me. [ __ ] bors
Yeah, one second. I'm just going to get
a drink. Hold on. I need to get my drink
and a charger. Charger. What's up? Nice
color. Um, how much in
London? Well, I only get
[ __ ] It's like
60. I got this 20 year old, but she's
Oh, [ __ ] Don't die. Don't die. Don't
die. But she's um she's in Wales at the
minute. She's a bit weird. Bit bipolar and that. But
yeah. Oh, [ __ ] hell. It's funny how
you said it wasn't like this 50 years
ago, bro. It wasn't like this about
[ __ ] 20 years ago, man. Not 50 years
ago, 20 years ago. It's all this Tik Tok
and Instagram and
[ __ ] It's [ __ ] isn't
it? These women will never change.
bro. Yo, how we doing, Greasy? Yeah.
Yeah. So, yeah, I booked to go to Thailand. Greasy,
lad. I know. There's so many simps on
Instagram, bro. Instagram. There I don't
know how many times. Yeah, they're going
to simp until they realize that sing is
never going to get them
laid. I It's just
crazy. Like I don't think Greavves is a
simp. I wouldn't even call um you
know, like I I wouldn't even call Grezy
um a simp or a white knight. He's just a
little lamb with a lot to learn. That's
all I'd say greasy is. Cuz don't forget,
yeah, like like I keep saying, I gave up
for like five, six weeks, the drinking,
the women I was eating in, I was h
they're not too bad women, but then when
you start dealing with them again, you
know exactly what every single one of
them's like. And I generalize every
single one of them. And when I'm proven
wrong is the day that I'll say I'm
wrong. Like, imagine that, bro. Having a
32 year old that think that thinks
they're better than you. Hey, [ __ ]
hell. And I'm still in my 20s. [ __ ]
this. These women are [ __ ] man. I'm telling
you. And then I apparently I'm the I'm
the one that's scared to commit, says
Grievy. I'm the one that's scared to
commit. Yeah, I'm the one that went on
this [ __ ] date and the [ __ ] was
making up [ __ ] excuses even though
she approached me. Even though she
approached me and she traveled an hour
away to come and see me. Yeah, I'm like
decent looking and apparently she can't
feel the vibe. Okay, whatever.
So, yeah. I mean, yeah, technically
people get drunk and then the next day
they don't really feel it
anymore. But, I mean, to travel an hour
away still when you're sober,
uh, that's a bit strange to be honest. But,
hey, any wonder why they can't find
anyone, Little Lamb? Is it any wonder
they can't find
anyone? They generalize men based on the
men that they choose. We gen Well, I
generalize women because it's all I've ever been
shown. You know what I'm saying? It's
all I've ever been shown. So, that's all
I have to go off by. I can't go off by
other people's experiences because that
wouldn't make sense.
Well, I tried sticking to the same one
on [ __ ] last
Thursday. You know, I risked my foot injury for
it. You know what I'm saying? I was
going to stick with her even though I
didn't really like her. She's a five out
of 10. I was like, "Fuck it." You know,
I'm getting old now. I can't be bothered
doing this [ __ ] But look, they still
make excuses even though they approached
me. So, it's like, "What the fuck?" And
yeah, that Birmingham one, I could have
stayed with her, but she's a three out
of 10. And she wanted me, she expected
me to pay for
everything. I was like, "Fuck this. I'm
I ditched her and then just went to the
butchers and cook myself a t-bone steak.
I'm not [ __ ] doing
this." Oh, do you want to know what
Laney um made me? Do you want to know
what Laney made me um yesterday?
Grezy, this is what Laney made me. Yeah.
So, this is picture number one.
She cooked me a lovely roast dinner. So
this is the dinner.
Yeah, that's the dinner. That was
before. And then when Peter Belly put
his mouth around
it, it turned into this.
Whoopsie. Oopsy daisy. Where did that go?
Grezy, I had to um I had to buy a new
washing machine, Grezy. It packed up. I
literally had to buy a new washing
machine, Grezy. It packed
up. You know what that means, Grezy? It literally packed
up. Maybe you're a bit too young to understand that
word. Yeah, it's packed up.
[ __ ] packed up, mate. I tried to put
a [ __ ] towel wash on Grezy. We packed up. [ __ ]
hell. It's not
funny. Not funny,
Grezy. It's not funny,
matey. You know what that means? Grezy packed
up. Yeah, that Sunday dinner sent me to
sleep. Ah. Ah,
lovely. No, washing machine's coming tomorrow.
So, yeah, I was going to get it from
Argosh. Yeah, but it took [ __ ] like
it was taking like 5 days. So, I had to
get from somewhere else. So, I can't
wait 2 three days. I had like some
clothes and that. So,
yeah. I had to buy a new washing
machine. [ __ ] sake,
man. Yeah, bro. But yeah, I did try to I
went on these dates. Greasy. I was trying to
commit. They've just got unrealistic expectations. I
think I mean, yeah, you get like you get
people that go out with women. You get
people that are in
relationships, but I'm I think starting
from now for the most part is going to
be very difficult, you know, cuz they
just have Mr. Perfect in their head.
They go on these dates expecting, "Oh,
he's gonna woo me like Romeo and
Juliet." I mean, which which is crazy
because it's like I feel like when you
go on these dates, yeah, you can only do
all you can. You can only look the best
that you can, which you're already
decent looking anyways. So, there's what
more is it that they actually want? See,
that's the bit that doesn't make sense.
Whereas, when we see a woman that's
decent looking or good-looking, they're
doing their best is enough for us. But
then you can look your best and do your
best and they will still make an excuse.
So that's what makes me think they've
got like I said unrealistic expectations cuz
Yeah. Cuz we don't care. Like if if a
woman's 6, seven out of 10, one could be
shy, one could be outgoing, one could be
vegetarian, one could eat meat, but
we're never going to turn these people
down. A man is never going to turn any
of these people down. You you
understand? They will the slightest
little thing, they they they won't want
to see you again. That's the [ __ ] up
thing about it,
bro. That's if that makes sense. I'm
trying to make it make sense. But yeah,
like let me put myself in my shoes. What
am I like a 6 out of 10, 7 out of 10? If
I had a woman that's a six, seven out of
[ __ ] 10 in her [ __ ] 20s, as
outgoing as I am, mate, I'd marry a
[ __ ] So that's them having unrealistic
standards. That's what I'm saying. And I
have lowered my standards. I have
lowered my standards. I have lowered my
standards before. USA Izzy, that's lowering my
standards. I didn't even like the [ __ ] to begin
with until she started coming on to me,
grievy, and giving me a little
snog and putting her arms around me,
Greavvesy, and telling me the slower the
better. No, but in all seriousness, like
you get my point, like being 100%
serious, you know? So, it is [ __ ] up.
Yeah, I had so much food yesterday, bro.
I didn't eat again after
that. But you get my point. Anyways, I'm
sure you do.
So, nice Coca-Cola had some nice Ben & Jerry's yesterday,
Grezy. Um, and why do you think I tried
making it work with this 1920 year old, bro? Cuz
[ __ ] cuz when I used to like [ __ ]
with these people and that like not [ __ ]
with them but like just didn't take it
serious. It was more the fact cuz of
that [ __ ] It wasn't the fact that I didn't like
them. Yeah. I just said to her I'm going
toilet and then [ __ ] off. And she was
stinking. She was stinking, bro. She was
stinking. But I didn't leave her cuz she
was stinking. I left her because she was
trying to use me. That's the difference.
So, I'm not stinking. I'm decent
looking. I smell good. So, what's what's
your problem? And I'm not trying to use
anyone. So, that's how you got to see it. You
know, that's how you really really
really got to see
it. They exclude themsel to a type. That's the
difference. Yeah. I done it before to
someone um two years
ago. It was It was April. It was It was
around Yeah, I think I think it might
have been the same year. Was it the same
year as she was saying? It must have
been the same year. It was April. Yeah.
I just ditched her. Not cuz I didn't
like her. Oh, there's no vibe cuz people
didn't People used to say, "Oh, I don't
think you like me." No, no, no, no. But
I was just so pissed off in that
[ __ ] that I didn't want to really
[ __ ] around with anyone else. That's
what it was. It wasn't because I thought
I was, you know, I had someone in
America. I think it was two months
ago. We We met on a Thursday. We were
supposed to meet on a Saturday. Guess
what? Oh, I'm going to try again with my
ex. [ __ ] this. I think that's I think
that's literally why I stopped for like
five, six weeks. I think after that I
stopped for about five, six weeks, then
I done it again.
But yeah, I left her cuz she was a gold
digger and the fact that yeah, she's
meeting her friend in an hour and she's
going to go back to Birmingham, so
what's the point? You
know, been there, done that, won the
t-shirt, but then they tried to [ __ ]
say that, oh yeah, you don't even pay
for women, but what happens when you do, bro?
So yeah, it can stay hot all week, mate.
I'm done. I booked a holiday. It can
stay hot as long as it wants to. I am not
interested. So yeah, when I say
something, bro, listen to it cuz I
didn't give up. I didn't give up for
five, six weeks for no reason. I am the
Neo done. When I say something, bro,
believe it. I didn't give up for five,
six weeks for no reason. I don't want to
deal with [ __ ]
again. Yeah, I don't want to deal with [ __ ]
again. I mean, like, there's no point
even me going out greasy. They clearly
have all got
boyfriends. Yeah, they'll be out on the
streets and skirts and Cleveland, but
they don't want me talking to them.
They've all got
boyfriends. Yeah, but I don't want to go
and speak to them, man. They've all got
boyfriends. I don't want to speak to
people that's all got boyfriends.
They've all got boyfriends apparently.
So, you know, I don't want to be like I
don't want to get on the wrong end of
that. They've all got boyfriends,
lad. Like, that's not even going to
tempt me, bro. I'm going to Thailand.
I've already booked my holiday. They can
be out all they want. I don't care. They
can be out. They could be out naked and
I still wouldn't care. They could be out
lit. They could be walking the street
naked, Grezy, and I still wouldn't care.
I'm done. It gets to a certain point
where you're like, "No, [ __ ] this. [ __ ]
this." You know what I'm saying, bro? I
think you get to that
point. Definitely. They could be out
naked. I still don't give a [ __ ] I'm
getting that plane out of here.
So, you're not going to tempt me,
Dad. But, but no, but technically, I
could I could still go out cuz it's like
what Antman done. He had the right idea.
He knew every time he went out, every
week he went out, he'd be closer to
leaving this country. So be like, "Oh,
[ __ ] this. Oh, but I got something to
look forward to, so it's not too bad."
That's where I went wrong. I never had
anything to look forward to when I'd go
out. I didn't just be dealing with the
same [ __ ] week in week out, week in,
week out, week in, week out, you know? [ __ ] that. Uh [Music]
Yeah. Yep. You are repeated. Bye-bye
now. It's so good watching it. Yeah.
Yeah. So that's
it. Anyways, Greavves. I'm enough alone,
mate. I've done it for 27 years of my
life. I realized that I was stronger
than I actually thought I was. I'm enough
alone. You ever feel like that,
Greasy? That you're just enough
alone? I feel like I'm enough alone.
Definitely enough alone. I've been doing
it for so long now. So, yeah. What's the
point of welcoming anyone to the life of Peter B
now? There's none, is there? But
yeah, what do you reckon the most
annoying part of the dating is? I think it's the
ghosting. Ghosting. I think them going
on dates, wasting your time, maybe. I
think that's the most annoying
thing. See, I like I said last week, if
I just got the numbers that didn't
reply, it would have pissed me off. It
would just be like, "Oh, same old." I
think it's the fact that they met you
and actually wasted your time and ped
you on. That's what pissed me off. Cuz
when you go out and you drink, you know
that they're going to say they got
boyfriends. You know what you're
actually going to get. So, you can't
really moan about it. You should be
going out to just drink anyways. But
then when you have somebody lead you on
like this person done, and they're
literally they're leading you on and
wasting your time intentionally, that's
what pisses me off.
You know, that's what pisses me
off, you know, and they do it on purpose
as well cuz they know that nobody wants
them. So, they have to feel better by
leading people on because you'll notice
that the people that do this have got
[ __ ] lives. Look at USA and America.
Nothing fat, hit the wall, [ __ ] has to
use filters. It's the people that do
this. They have because no one wants
them. They want to feel validated, you know,
special and stuff. And that's why they
they do this. Just like this 32y old,
she's hit the wall,
bro. But yeah, so gets to a point where
you're like, nah, [ __ ]
this. [ __ ] this, mate. So
yeah, they do give false hope that they definitely definitely do.
But stop talking about yourself. It's
not good for your mental
health. Stop talking about yourself like that,
buddy. Not good, man. Go self-reflect on
another channel. You repeat
her. I know. Isn't it mad? I've got no
friends. I've got none of this. I've got
nothing. Yet you are the same people
that are on YouTube every day. You can't
get off it. I know. It's mad. It I'm
friendless. I'm skin. I'm everything.
Yeah, I know. But I can take one day off
of YouTube and you can't. Speaks volume
in it. Speaks volume.
that. Yeah, it's just all self
projection. So many self projectors. You
might as well just be in the [ __ ]
cinema. Might as well just be in the
really. And you know, you notice they do
this around Christmas time as well. You
get a lot of these people around
Christmas saying, "Oh, you're going to
you got no family. You're going to be
alone Christmas." It's all because
they're the ones that have got no family.
and they have no one. It's just
self-reflection. Yeah, this community is
going to be the same forever dead as
well. Is it a good horror
film? No, I don't really care about the
boy finishing me. That that don't bother
me. It's the whole leading on and
wasting my time. That's what bothers me.
That's what bothers me,
mate. Is it a good one?
Yeah. I didn't even know. See, you don't
even know when there's things on in this
anymore anymore because it don't come up
adverts. Let me see.
Yeah, it's it's a sad life a G, but it
is what it is. Never going to change. [Music]
Oh, doesn't look that
good. Doesn't look that good, bro. [Music]
Yeah, I just kind of watch like things
on YouTube where people just go around
to like deprived areas meeting new
people. It's quite a good watch to be fair. Yeah. Yeah, it's mad.
Yeah. Yeah. She can gag for all she
wants. I'm done with women, mate. I hate all of
them. So, she can gag all she wants.
That's good for her, man. Don't
care. Done. I'm done. Done.
That [ __ ] from Birmingham was a gold
digger. Accent was mad as
well. But it was good banter. It was
Uh, it's not even worth going out in this
country, Greasy. It's not even worth
going out in this country,
lad. We've all got boyfriends. Delayed.
Yeah. Yeah. Then it' be different. Then
different. USA was stinking as well, but
not as bad as
that. It was stinking as
well, but not quite as
bad. They make up stuff as well, bro. [ __ ] hell.
Yep. Understand as
well. You give her a ride, bro. Go
message her then. You got her
Instagram. Goes message her. Everyone
knows what what everyone has her
Instagram. Go and message
her. Go get a ride from her,
bro. Too far away.
Yeah, you can't even be positive about
it anymore, bro. I think when you've had
too many bad experiences, I don't think
you can even you can even change your
mind anymore about it,
bro. Cuz you're
delusional. If you start trying to think
positive, you are actually delusional. I
would actually be delusional, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. I think a lot of people give up on
the dating though. I think a lot of
people give up on dating.
Yeah. No, I'm not going to end it, bro.
I'm not depressed. [ __ ] hell. I've
just give up with dating. I've had too
many bad experiences to last me a whole
entire lifetime. And as much as people
say they're different, well, I believe
it when I see it. People say pigs fly,
but I've never seen
it. People say pigs fly, but I've never
seen a pig
fly. People say the elephant man exists.
I've never seen the elephant man. The
talk is cheap. You see, we can sit there
all day and have debates, opinions,
arguments, but talk is cheap. I believe
it when I see
it. And I think that's that's the best
way to go about things. like believe
something when you see
it. And I've never seen it, so I have no
reason to believe it. You know, from
what I've experienced, they're
all they're all the same. From all the
experiences I go I I can think of, they
are literally all the
same. Yeah. In the dating game, there's
no light at the end of the tunnel. Yeah.
In terms of dating. Yeah, that's that is the
reality. You just have to give up and leave this
country. Well, the only thing you can do
is is book a holiday like I've done and
go out every week here until you
leave. That's all you can do. Yeah.
Yeah, that's it, bro.
Yeah, give USA is he a ride. Why don't
you go message the [ __ ] on
Instagram? Change the
photo. There you go, man.
You should message her,
man. You should talk [ __ ] about me, bro.
You got more chance than replying. Oh
yeah, Antman's moving there. You don't
have to move there. You just go there
for like two You just go there for like
months. No, she won't. So, yeah, she'll probably ignore
you. That's what she done to my friend.
She tried playing the victim and then
tried talking [ __ ] about me. But then
when my friend, obviously my friend
knows what I'm about. Then she blocked
him. Like at the very first before all
this thing come about, anyone that would
slag me like, you know, they'd message
me, but then they knew like basically um Yeah.
You're a [ __ ] liar, mate.
But yeah, that's probably what she says
to people that approach her. She has a
boyfriend. Oh my god. She's a tip. She's
just a typical [ __ ] as well. Like, you
could just tell that she would say that.
She could literally just You could
literally tell that she would just say
that to somebody that goes and
approaches her. Oh, I've got a boyfriend.
like trying to tell me that it was my
lucky day for getting your skanky [ __ ]
Yeah, I spent like what £110 that day,
but it's my lucky day. That just goes to
show how entitled they are. How would it
be my lucky day? Doesn't make any
sense. That's how entitled they are. They're
[ __ ] All the same,
mate. This is Coco's nice and cold.
They're all the same. Every single one of them. So,
yeah. How the [ __ ] would it have been my
lucky day, mate? Getting your skunky [ __ ] E.
Yeah. You spent 250 quid.
You plonker. You don't mate. You don't
spend £250 on a first
date. Oh, mate. Please tell me you at least got
laid. I've never I think I spent £700
once. When I went over that 19year-old
once, I think I spent about 700 quid.
Hotels, drinking, food. I spent about
700 pound. I
did. But I had a lot of money.
So, and I don't I gambled as well, but
no, but I think I won money
gambling. I think I won money though.
So, yeah, I won money though. I think I
won about 600
pound. It doesn't Yeah. So what? And so what,
bro? But I have spent £700 before.
gambling, drinking, hotel and that. I have,
bro. Yeah. Well, at least you got
something. I won't be dating anymore,
mate. My dating days are
done. At least you got something. Still
a bit much though. 250
quid. It's a bit
dear. Yeah, it was decent. Yeah, it was in
London. At least you [ __ ] got something in
this. I'm done with the whole dating [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I booked Thailand.
Yeah. Yeah. I booked Thailand, bro.
Yesterday I booked the flights and I'm
just going to change accommodation when
I'm over there. It's cheap
enough. Yeah. I thought, "Fuck this,
mate." After [ __ ] last week, I
thought, "Fuck this [ __ ]
brother." You know what I mean?
Yeah. Do you know what Ant-Man said? He
said that they're just not interested in this country. Uh so
yeah, I booked it, bro. The flights. And
obviously once you're over there, you
just should you just stay at different
accommodation and that. No, I'm going by
myself, but I'm going to meet him when
I'm over there.
So, cuz I like this is enough, mate. This is
enough. Hopefully, I'm going to be
making money to go out every
Saturday. I probably will just go out
every weekend cuz I know
um cuz I know like
uh cuz I know that
like I know
um that I'll be leaving soon, so it's
not a biggie,
bro. Don't care if it's hell of a
flight, bro. You got to do what you need
to do, mate. I've had a head of the p
I've had a hell of a past 3 weeks, mate.
Fridge broke, washing machine broke,
[ __ ] my foot up, couldn't walk for two
weeks. Like, literally nothing's
bothering me now, bro. That's it. Done. [ __ ] this
country. I've applied for this thingy
job thingy. I'm not going to tell you
what it is, but I've still not heard
back from them. That's just going to be
money to make for Saturday's
outings. And then yeah, that's perfect
routine, mate. I think that's at this
point that's that's all you got. He's
leaving this country,
mate. Yeah, 100%, bro.
100%. I can't get off a plane. [Music]
Are you sure you're not bomb, man? Hey,
I've got loads of videos, you know, from
my other channel that got terminated. I
backed them all
up, but yeah, I've actually got a new YouTube
channel. I need to post some stuff on
it. I'm not going to tell anyone the
name, but I've actually got a new
YouTube channel that I actually post videos
on, but I don't really come on here much
anymore, so I don't bother.
Yeah. Yeah. Tim said that he's going on
holiday. That was a load of [ __ ] Do
you know what? I just laugh at like when
Timmy's arguing with these people. It's
funny, bro, cuz it's like you got to
laugh at them in it. They're not
serious, man. They're not serious. It's
just like when this Arsenal Mark like
does videos of me like, "Bro, you're not
serious. Stop it. Stop forcing it. Cuz
if you was if you were serious, you
wouldn't be on YouTube doing videos."
Like, you know what I'm saying, bro?
Like, he goes on like he's just cocky
bad man yet, but he's on YouTube making
videos. Like, bro, you're a
laughingtock. Like, we know that you're
just trying to get attention. Stop it.
Please, just stop it, man. Stop it.
Like, it's it's embarrassing. Please. You
know. Yeah. He was going to see, bro.
But the thing is, but that's the whole
point I'm I'm trying to make here. I I
don't know why this guy always does
videos. Like, think of it. Yeah. The guy
has my address. Yeah. And he's still on YouTube making
videos. So, what does that tell you,
bro? that the guy's a clown. Not one
single person on this community is about
anything. Not LJ, not Timmy, not Arsenal
Mark, not anyone. None of them are about
it because they wouldn't they're not
about it, bro. It's it's it's that it's
that simple. He just wants
attention. He just wants attention and love.
Yeah. So, yeah, that's it,
man. Yeah, I got a good YouTube channel.
Yeah, the the name is actually class,
but obviously I'm not going to give you
it. What other YouTube channel, is it?
Yeah. So, I didn't care about the main
channel. It was just like all the videos
on there. But I've got all the videos on
there on my thing.
So, everyone knows my address, bro.
Everybody knows my address.
Oh, anyways, I'm going to go, man, in a
bit. I need to chill
out. No, but he knows my
address. No, but he knows my address cuz everyone
does some reason.
Do you fancy some eye of Horus today?
Nah. You sure you don't fancy some eye
of Horus? Nah, I'm done with that
gambling [ __ ] I need to get this
washing machine in tomorrow. I need to
wash some clothes. See, at first, yeah,
it's very hard to stop all these bad
things like eating out, drinking for a
little bit. It's very hard at first, but
once you get used to it, you know, you
get, you know, once you you're
disciplined to start it. Yeah. You get
used to it. And that's what I was
saying. The whole drinking and the whole
women thing set me back again. So, nah,
man. I'm not gambling, bro. I was only
joking. No gambling for me,
Dad. No gambling for me. Not for
Yeah, never mind.
Yeah, I'm going to post some videos on
my other channel, I think.
Yeah. Yeah, I think
so. Good old approaching videos, eh?
But to be fair, they kind of were
boring. I didn't know. Bless
you. Okay. Bless you. Oh, that Scottish
transgender is is she's got a funny
personality. Oh, bless you. You know
what? Yeah, I actually said I'm going to
come to Glasggo and see you.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to come to Glasggo
and see you,
matey. I'm going to come to Glasgow and
see you, matey. Yeah.
I'm going to come to Glasgow and
see they all float
down. They all float
down. Oh [ __ ] What's the day today?
That cord still ain't come, has it?
It's Monday. Ain't about is it probably should have been
[ __ ] I don't think there is a bigger
creepy loser with online than than you
PJ. Not even joking.
Really? Have you looked in the mirror
lately? I take it you've not looked in
the mirror lately. Eh, try looking at
yourself. You might find one. If you
look in the mirror, you might you might
find a bigger one than me. No, you'll
definitely find a bigger one than me, which is
yourself. Stop talking about yourself.
It's not good for your mental health,
man. I don't know how many times I have
to tell you little
self-reflectors cuz think about it, man.
Like use people you come online every day your
[ __ ] weirdo lives hating hating
hating hating on people that you don't
even know about. Like you sit there all
day every day. You can't get off of
YouTube hating. It says your life in a
nutshell. It literally says everything
about your life, mate. If I had to come
online Yeah. and hate on people that I
don't know every day. Brother, I'm
looking in that mirror. I'm not going to
lie to you. I tell you right now, I'm
looking in that
mirror. You come on here, you you call
people that you don't even know. Like
you call them names like skin or this,
that, and the other. And like in a in a
real, you're just getting yourself
confused with other people. That's
literally all you're doing. You're just
getting yourself confused with other people.
You know, you ain't got a life. You
people in your 40s, you ain't made it.
So, you come on here every day to feel
special. Pathetic, man. It is really
pathetic what you people do on here.
Really, really, really, really pathetic. You
know, you take it out on other people
because your lives are [ __ ] That's what
it is. Cuz you ain't got a life. It's
over. You're a lot older than me and
that's why you do what you do. [ __ ] up,
man. Sad, man. Sad. Sad.
Sad. Nope. Don't gamble anymore.
Really? Don't gamble anyone more, mate.
No. No. Not me, matey. Not me.
Not me. Not me. Not
No, I did. But now I don't gamble. I
lost 80 pound last week. Yeah. 40 on
fishing frenzy, 40 on Eye of
Horus. Yeah. But not
anymore. Forgive me, man. I had a
stressful couple of weeks. I had a I had
a stressful couple of weeks, man. We're
finally back to
normalish. Forgive me. Yeah, stressful
couple of weeks. I'm not even
joking. Yeah, it was stressful, but
we're kind of back to normal
now. Kind of. Yeah.
So, is that what is that what a lot of
you people do? gamble all day every
day. And that's why you come on YouTube
and you start
hating. And that's why you come on
YouTube, start hating and
[ __ ] And then you give it and then you
can't take it.
Yeah. Yeah. Sounds about right, mate.
Sounds about right.
Yeah. Could have stop a bit, man. All
right, I'm gone. past.