You got to laugh at these little
sers. [ __ ] hell, man. They are proper
silk, man. [ __ ] I told you
that. I was just telling
her about this. Literally, they ain't
got a life, man. How they [ __ ] found
me, I don't know. They ain't got no
life, but talking people. It just
confirms it. It It goes It goes into
more than a wind up, bro, with these
people here. They're proper sados, man.
I swear to God, they're proper sadistic
[ __ ] monkers. They ain't got a life,
mate. [ __ ] hell, man. Look at what
half of these people look like on here.
[ __ ] hell. They're such
stalkers. I swear to God, they they live
to stalk men with a better life than
them. They're weirdos. [ __ ] hell. I
was just telling LT the same thing. I
said, "Yeah, I got that fat [ __ ]
stalking me as well. That [ __ ] Jamie
Thompson. You just know he's just some
fat agrophobic loser that ain't got
nothing in his life. That he has to
stalk two different men right on the
same platform." What a weirdo. [ __ ]
hell. They ain't got a life. They really
really really ain't got like at at first
[ __ ] I thought, okay, yeah, it's just
like it's just bad. They're just trying
to piss people off. But no, I feel sorry
for them. I was actually laughing the
whole way through cooking this. I
actually Bro, I feel sorry for them,
bro. I actually do. They live very sad
lives on YouTube every day
stalking. But you know, if you actually
look up what these people look like, you
would obviously know why they do this, you
know. [ __ ] sad, man. Sad sad
stalkers. It's a shame, isn't it? Sad sad
stalkers. We changed the handles. I was
telling LT, I've done the same thing.
I've changed the handles, changed the
titles, but these people still stalled
me. [ __ ] weirdos. They ain't got no
wife. They ain't got no kids. It
confirms it. I thought at first, okay,
yeah, maybe. But these people ain't got
nothing to sit online every day doing
what they do, bro. There's something
seriously something seriously up with
their life. Oh, he said he's going to
Stratford. Oh, good for him. No one
cares. We've been through this before.
Anyways, uh back to the stalkers. Yeah.
So, you make a new YouTube channel to
get away from these absolute weirdos.
Yeah. I'm cooking some food, by the way.
Yeah. To get away from these absolute [ __ ]
weirdos. And then when you uh try to get
away from these weirdos, they literally
like hunt you down and stalk you. Bro, I
literally made a new YouTube channel
about an hour ago. Different handle,
different name. Nobody knew about it.
Like literally not one person knew about
this channel. I was just building it up.
Yeah. Bam. You get these little spastics
coming. How the [ __ ] do they find it,
bro? They're weirdos, man. They got a
life. That Thompson ain't got a life,
mate. He has not got
any sat online stalking men. He's done
to two different people now. LT he's
done it to. He's done it to me as well.
Weirdos, no life. They envy anyone
that's got a better life than them. I
figured these people out. Even my friend
J said that, "Oh, like you should be a
psych you should be a psych
psychologist." They envy anyone with a
better life than them. I I swear to God,
bro, not any of these people knew about
that YouTube channel. Yeah. No one on
this community. Yeah. You downloaded all
the videos. That's That's fine, bro.
That's cool. That's fine, bro. Like,
it's all right, man.
That's fine, bro. Good for you, man. No one
cares. You've Yeah, that's nice, bro. No
problem. I just deleted all the videos
cuz I don't want new people following
me. And Nope. No, I didn't. No, I
didn't, bro. These people are weirdos,
man. They're stalkers.
Sorry, I'm cooking, mate.
Yeah. Oh, really? That's nice for you,
man. No one cares anyways. Weirdo. These
people have got no life. Yeah, truth
talker. No, I didn't sub to it. Sorry,
bro. I'm cooking. I'm trying to
multitask. I didn't sub to it. I didn't.
No, like nothing, bro. They're weirdos.
They're absolute weirdos. They ain't got
a life. These people ain't got a life,
man. I'm telling you, bro. These people
really ain't got a life. Fat, ugly [ __ ]
that can't leave the house, stuck on
YouTube every day. Literally, it's the truth, man.
Like listen, bro. No one cares if you
put videos up laughing. I don't care.
It's calm, bro. Because you will never
say anything to anyone's face. No one
cares about keyboard warriors, bro. We
outgrew that, bro. We outgrew that [ __ ]
Yeah. Was about 12, 13. No one cares
what a bunch of keyboard warriors have
got to say, bro. It's boring. It's weird
what you do online, bro. No one
cares. No. I'm cooking some pork
chops. No one cares, bro. We're over all of that.
Right. Yo, keyboard
warriors. So, I'm crisping up some
uh lovely pork chops.
Yay. They ain't got a
life. Crying, crying, crying. They ain't
got a life. These people, you got to
feel bad for them, bro. Bro, they're
stalkers. They're absolute [ __ ] stalkers,
mate. There you go. doing some nice
chips. They're stalkers, man. No one
knew the channel. I'm telling you, bro.
Nobody knew the chat and no, bro. But
somehow they found it. How does that make
sense? Nobody knew the channel,
bro. Go off a little bit. I
reckon they got a life, bro. I think
they want to be me, bro. I swear down
this Jamie Thompson. I think they want
to be in me,
bro. Yeah, I don't care. Yeah, I don't
care, bro. Good for him. I don't care. A
real gangster don't make YouTube videos.
Good for him, man. No one cares. We've
been through this before. No repeating
on my channel. You mention it again, I'm
going to block you, bro. Yes, I know
he's he has probably done that. He's
done it about a million times, but
remember a real
gangster don't make YouTube videos. They
come and do something anymore and I'm blocking you.
Simple. Simple. Yeah. Come to Peek and
you'll feel me, right?
Bye-bye. Told you, bro. I told you. Um,
bye-bye. Told you that was warning.
Second warning. You've been weird drama
on my channel. You're done, mate, bro. I
literally Yeah, bro. Oh my
goodness. Yeah, I literally made a new
channel to get away from these little
sulkers. Literally within an hour they
found me, bro. They're [ __ ] They're
freaks. They're still They found my
channel, bro. I can see all the stuff on there.
Crazy. Honestly, these are They're
weirdos. They're jealous of me. They're
so jealous of me. They follow me around
everywhere, bro. I swear down. I made a
new channel to get away from these
people. Literally to get away from these
people. Yeah, I was going to go live on
this channel, do some gambling videos.
Um, some gambling videos, some gambling
videos, and then I would have just went
live like and just come here. But my
other channel was something else. I'm
going to make a new channel
again and I'm just not going to put the
approaches on public cuz maybe they
found me through the approaches. But I
mean, I changed the handles and all
that, but they somehow still found me.
But yeah, it's not a problem, bro.
Because I'm just going to make a new
channel. I literally made a channel to
get away from these
weirdos, but yet look what they do. They
follow you everywhere and find you.
They're [ __ ] weirdos, mate. Absolute
weirdos. And it goes to show, yeah, that
Jamie has got nothing in his life. no
wife, no kids, he's sad with his life.
He's got no money. He can't even leave
his house. Every time they do stuff like
this, bro, it it says so much about
their life that it like honestly, bro,
like to me, it's funny, but it's weird
at the same time. Like, it hasn't
triggered me. It's It's funny, but it's
weird, but it says everything about
their life. Every time they do stuff
like this, it it it goes to show the
jealousy. the jealousy towards you. It
that's all it shows. Like literally
every time they do stuff like this, it
shows how much jealousy they have toward
you. And it does honestly it does. And I
hate that word,
bro. I hate that word, bro. Trust me, it
is otherwise I wouldn't say it. Yeah.
You know what I'm
saying? And then you got people on here
bringing up weird drama like this
keyboard Arsenal Mark. I made a new
channel to literally get away from these
[ __ ] To get away from these stalk
kids. That's the whole point of not
uploading on here. To get away from
these people. You understand? And then
they still following you. They're [ __ ] weirdos,
man. Weird little
sus. Weird little
sulkers. What I'm
saying? He ain't got a wife, man. He
ain't got a wife. Oh, he about his wife
that he's got. Yeah, he's got a wife.
That's why he's sat on YouTube stalking
two different men. He's done with London
Taylor as well. Yeah, he does with
London Taylor as well. Trust me, bro.
They ain't going to find this next one.
Believe that. They're not going to find
this next one. They ain't got a life.
lie. That's it, bro. Two different men
seemed on it, bro.
Yeah, I I made a new channel to get away
from them. Literally to get away from
Come on, chips. Wait for you now. To
literally get away from them, bro. You
know what I'm
saying? One second.
chips. They got
mate. [ __ ] me,
bro. He's not in my phone,
bro. But anyways, I'm going to make a
new channel anyways. No, no problem,
bro. And I'll know if they've seen me
again. He ain't got a life, man. But to
be honest, man, if you was born with a
face like these, think about it, bro. to
say no one to be fair to him though like
what else would he really have to do but
stalking on the
internet think about it he's stalking on
the internet look the way he looks
wonder is there any [ __ ] wonder think about it
Huh? Dishing this food
off. I know, bro. They're losers.
They're losers. They're jealous of me.
That's what it is, bro. They're jealous
of me because they wouldn't do this
otherwise, bro. Look, they've actually
took time out of their whole It's like
they want to be you, bro. This is why I
made another channel to get away from
them. Somehow these [ __ ] found me.
What the [ __ ] There's a few different
reasons why I wanted to get away from
this place, bro. The grassing, the
repeating. Yeah, that ain't me, bro. So,
why would I stick on a community that's
full of all
that? It don't make
sense. One second.
Waiting on the chips now.
There's some negative hat. But
yeah, it's all right, bro. Love is
blind. I've seen fat men with hot birds.
Yeah, mate. If he had a hot bird, he
wouldn't be on YouTube stalking me every
day, mate. That would be blind to see.
If he had a [ __ ] hot bird, he would
be sat on [ __ ] YouTube on his fat ass
stalking people, would he?
Yeah. That ain't
[ __ ] Take a bite. glad.
You know what I'm saying? But if he had
a hot bird and he had anything going on
in his life, he wouldn't be stalking men
on a hot summer's day. Doesn't matter
what country he's in. You know what I'm
saying? Come on.
sound the [ __ ] wind. That's what I
only think about
it. Look at all the people that's been on this [ __ ]
Jimmy man. And yeah, okay. They had
grief. Yeah. Okay.
I might have a grief or whatever, but
not my level, bro. Not my [ __ ] level.
You know what I'm saying? Madness. Yeah. One [Music]
second. He is a
stalker. But to be honest with you, if
you was born in a place like
that, so much jealousy and
narcissisticness in this community.
Jill, does this community just like give
off like creepy
vibes? [ __ ] weirdo,
man. These people are [ __ ] weirdos,
man. You know, it is him, mate, because
he's coming to live stream. It is him,
mate. That's what most of these people
on here look like, though. They're
[ __ ] ugly. It's why they're on
YouTube every day calling people they
don't know cuz they're [ __ ] ugly
bastards. Excuse my French. It's truth
though. People don't like that. It is
what it is,
man. There we go. Pork chips veg.
Done. Done it,
bro. It's death, man. It's
death. It's definitely definitely
definitely definitely definitely and I
think it's autism as well. I think a lot
of people on here as well they've got autism
cuz I don't
know he sounded like a
[ __ ] Yeah, he sounded like a
[ __ ] That's what he sounded like. I'm going to go
But think of it all
down. I've already got enough evidence
of these people anyways, mate. So,
they're [ __ ] either way. I've
literally got an album of all of them
harassing me. This is more evidence for
me. Keep it coming, mate. I'm spoiled. You
know, there's a few reasons why I I come
off this [ __ ] right?
cuz it's full of repeaters. It's full of
self projectors and it's full of people
that want to start [ __ ] online like
they're some kind of big man and then
get the police involved. It's weird
drama. People talk about meeting all the
time yet no one ever does [ __ ] But they
come on here every day and it's like
[ __ ] with that bro. I'd rather just join
a new community. Then you try to join a
new community and you try to join the
new community and they find you. But
they won't find you this time.
me. It's probably cuz they searched
approaches or something, but this time they won't. I
got I'm sat here having a pork
dinner, Mr. Be. A nice pork dinner. I
played friends in Horus last week, but
I'm booked to go Thailand.
So, these people are [ __ ] stupid,
mate. I'm telling you.
I made a new channel to get away from
these people. Like the only videos I was
going to put on here was the gambling
ones cuz it's gambling. Cuz I knew
though I knew that if
I if I done any gambling videos on that
channel, they would find
me cuz they're all gambling addicts on
here. So, but there's a good chance of
them finding me. But they still found me anyways.
Weirdos [ __ ] weirdos,
man. Oh, nice
pork. Nice bit of pork.
How much is pork shop?
1.70. No, I'm not drinking for two
weeks, man. I need a
break. No, I'm good, man. probably better.
Nah, probably the way I found me,
bro. I'm not getting involved with
anyone of this community, bro. new glasses.
So when you have
people like when you got people like Mark
here pretending to call people out and
[ __ ] I'm like, "Yep, yep. Okay, okay,
yep, yep. I'm not getting a role no
more, bro. Any drama, any weirdness, right?
And that's why I made a new channel. But
somehow you just found just found
me. These people actually found me when
I made a new channel. Imagine
that. So you
Murphy, you want to call me a [ __ ]
Yep. I'm the biggest [ __ ] going.
Everything you say now, I agree with you. Yep.
Yep. When it comes to this grass
community, I am the biggest [ __ ] going.
the biggest [ __ ] the biggest bottle
job. I'm everything when it comes to this community.
Yeah. But I'm just a minute, bro. When
it comes to you grasses, Yeah. I'm the
biggest I'm the biggest [ __ ] Biggest
bottle job. Biggest
everything. It's easy that
way. It's not a problem,
bro. Always okay, man. Always okay. always.
Okay. I'd be better if these people
stopped stalking me. Now I've got to
make another channel. Do you know what
the channel's name was? Found my
Mama. And I never told anyone the name
of it, even though I wanted to,
cuz obviously it's it's a memory in it.
So, Found My
Mama. [ __ ] found me.
It was called Found My Mama. He
Murphy. Found my mama. Oh my.
Um, I'm going to try again to find
another um name.
Now I eat vegetables now to make sure I
get enough vitamins in case that the
fruit thing was linked to the vitamins
just to be on the safe side, you know.
So you everyone will find you. I know
for a fact there's so people follow me.
But how do they follow everything I do,
bro? And I'm changing the name, bro. I'm
changing the names though. How can they follow
me? Unless they're following you on
Instagram. I'm going to try and not do
that and see if see if they still find
me. But I'm making a new channel,
brother. That's the whole point.
Amazing. I need a cup of tea after this
food, bro. Oh, detox is going to be good,
eh? I'm coming to Liverpool soon. Kevin
Murphy, I'm going to see Billy Moore.
Don't know if you know who that
is. I won't be meeting you for a fight,
mate. I'm a [ __ ]
Why do you think I don't get involved
when this Arsenal Mark is pretending to
call people out again, bro? I'm not
about that [ __ ] on here
anymore. Too many glasses,
mate. Too many glasses, mate.
Why? I had a
problem. I want to another channel.