There we go. That's a perfect
example why you shouldn't do
it. Perfect [ __ ]
example. Have to get another to be fair. Oh, gaming
gaming. Oh, dear me.
Oh dear, dear me. A leopard never
changes it. Now I remember how them mood
swings. Now I remember them smooth them mood
swings. But hey, you win some, you lose
some. Win some lose some. So they say.
I've been hearing that for about se
seven months now. Right. Let's check
this. January, February, March, April,
four, five, six, almost about seven
months. I think it was about in October.
You hear I heard the same thing. You can
win, it's gambling. You can win, it's
gambling. Try a different game. Oh my
god, bro. Why do we always forget this
stuff before we gamble? I don't
understand why we we we forget this
stuff when when you know when you gamble
and that. I don't know why we forget
this stuff, man. It drives us mad. Even
if it's just a little amount of money,
it's not an option for us. This is what
I was I was I I was trying to say to
Ant-Man, like it's not an option. I
can't gamble. This is exactly the reason
why. This is exactly the reason why. And
it's not to do with how much money you
lose. You can lose 20 pound. It would
still get you that way. It's not about
[ __ ] losing [ __ ] how much money
you lose cuz that's [ __ ] silly, man.
You can have loads and loads and loads
of money. Losing 50 100 pound is enough
to get you depressed. It it it it turns
somebody into into crippling depression.
I swear to God it does, bro. I play that
[ __ ] eye of [ __ ] Horus.
Oh, I Horus. People seem to think, oh
yeah, you only lose £50, you only lose
£100, you still got money. It's not the
[ __ ] point. We spent £300 on a
[ __ ] washing machine the other day.
Guess what? It didn't bother us. You
lose £100, you feel like killing
yourself. Like, you literally have a
have a tantrum for about 20, 30 [ __ ]
minutes, even though you still got
money. People don't understand. They
think, oh, it's got to be a little
amount of money that you lose. It It's
only a little bit of amount of money
that you got to lose. Like, no, bro. No,
no. You can lose 100 pound. You can lose
5 10% of your money. It still has the
same effect. It's losing on it that is
annoying. You know what I'm saying, bro?
It's losing on it that is annoying.
Yeah, I just went for a walk and I
thought, let me just try £100 on a Horus
bonus. Paid £16. It's boring now. We
ain't won for seven months. Only
£100. [ __ ] hell. Look, which is
nothing to me. But it's not the point.
It doesn't matter that it's not nothing.
this just losing or it has this whole
effect on your body, your mind. It's
like a demon. Yeah. Climbing into your
body, mocking you, mocking you, mocking
you. That's what it is. It doesn't
matter how much it is. £50,
£100, whatever. 20 it does not matter.
It is not an option. You losing is not
option. End of. And it made me want to
kill myself. It started getting me like
that again. generally getting me like
that again. And it does. It [ __ ] does, you
know, it's not an option. This is why I
say to people like secular slots, it's
not a form of entertainment. It's not.
Even if you have all your bills paid,
even if you got food in the fridge, even
if you've got loads of money, it is not
an option. Losing is not an option.
Continuously. When you continuously
lose, you know, you can't, you know what
I'm saying? Look at me. I just lost
£100. What the [ __ ] You
know, same old [ __ ] Same old [ __ ] Same
old [ __ ] Same old [ __ ] Same old [ __ ]
Same old [ __ ] Boring. Boring. Boring.
You see what I'm
saying? And you have to scream and shout
like for like 30 minutes until you calm
down. It's crazy, man. It's crazy.
People like me shouldn't do it. I don't
know why the [ __ ] you don't forget about
the last time when you think about doing it again.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. And
people like tried to say to me before,
"Oh, well, maybe you're born with a weak
personality and your personality is not
made for gambling, mate. I'm a strong
person." You know, it's mad, bro. It
Yeah,£100's nothing to me, bro. I've got
more money than you would ever have. But
guess what? I have more money than you
would ever have. So, yeah, you can call
me what you want. I have more money than
you would ever have. So, good luck with
that, buddy. I'm a loser. I am a loser
with more money than
you. And you see, this is what I'm
saying, bro. When you come on this
community, Yeah. and you're trying to
show the real side of gambling, people
take the piss out of it. Yeah. People
take the piss out of it. Yeah. And then
you get people like Secular Slots that
says, "Oh, uh, as long as you got your
bills paid and everything's fine, bro.
What does that even mean? You could lose
£50 and it would still affect you. You
could still lose. You could lose 100.
It's the gambling and losing that is
affecting you. That is what it is. It's
not an option. Whether it's £10, 20,30,
£50, it is not an
option. You know, especially nowadays
where you, you know, you can't even
win. Like it's like you win and the next
day you lose. It is literally not an
option. If it makes you suicidal like it
makes me, you shouldn't do it. Any amount of
money, it is not an option. It's not an option,
lad. You know what I'm saying, bro? It
is not an option. You don't understand.
Like, we used to get that job account
that say, "Oh, well, maybe if you only
lost £10, it's losing on their machines
is not an option." You know, that's it.
That's all it is. You can't lose. That's
it. I've not won in about seven months. Imagine that,
bro. Yeah. I don't do I don't do much
content anymore. I was just saying I
just lost 100 pound, which is nothing to
me really. Obviously, it's not, but it's made
me Yeah. just think about suicide. And
it was money I could afford to lose as
well. That's why I'm trying to say it's
not a form of entertainment. This is
what I'm trying to say, you
know. No, I don't need to go back. I
need to quit gambling. That's what I'm
doing, mate. But don't come on my
channel and try and troll me, please.
I'm not Timmy. I'm not Monty. I'm not
[ __ ] If you're blatantly trying to
take the piss, okay, fair enough. But
don't come on here trying to take the
piss like I don't know what you're
[ __ ] doing. God, I shouldn't even
gamble today. Why did I even do that?
You know how it gets you? Like [ __ ]
hell. It's the same thing every time.
Like it's not about the money. We got
money. That's That doesn't mean
anything. It's We shouldn't have done it
because we know all what it causes every
time. Yeah. Secular slot says it's a
form of entertainment. So he says, but
secular slots don't use his own money.
So you know what I'm saying? Like
secular slots, he doesn't use real money.
ain't an option. The amount of money is
irrelevant. You can't do it. Clearly,
you can't do
it. You know, I said, I'm not going to
do 150. I'll only do 100. And look what
happens. It's the same old story every
single time with them machines.
every single time they
mach what the amount of money is. It's
irrelevant. Same old story with them.
But people seem to think that you need
to lose loads and loads of money. Where
did that come from? That you need to
lose loads and loads of
money. You need to lose loads and loads
of money. So what? You need to lose
loads and loads of money for it to
affect you. How do you work that one
out? Why do you need to lose loads and
loads of money for it to affect you? For
what reason? You don't need to.
Obviously, yeah, it's not an option,
bro, for people like me. Sadly, people
like me shouldn't do it. People like me
shouldn't do it. And it's not because
you're weak. It's not because anything
like that, because we're actually very
strong if you actually think about all
the stuff that's happened to us, you
know, all of the stuff that's happened
to us. We're not weak. It's we can't
lose. Losing's not an option, bro. You
know what I mean? So yeah. So
yeah, but they say once you've got your
bills paid, which we do, if it's any
disposable money, it's okay. But it's
not okay. It's not okay because you
wouldn't be here telling everyone in
[ __ ] YouTube that it's not [ __ ]
okay. You know what I'm
saying? It's literally not an option. It
literally is not an option. It gives you
hours and hours and hours and hours and
hours of mood swings, you know, and you
used to get the secular slots that used
to make excuses. Oh, uh, yeah, well,
maybe you've got underlying problems.
Nope. Not the press completely. Getting
back to myself, put them right. Oh,
maybe you ain't got your bills paid.
Paid all my bills. Maybe you've got no
money. Got money. So, they want to
continuously make excuses time and time
and time and time and time and time and
time and time again, you know, and even
if it's only one person that it makes it
feel like that's enough for me, bro.
That's enough for
me. Because if it wouldn't make anyone
feel like that, you know, even if you
had ADHD, AD ADHD, was it
ADHD? And you went bowling, would you
come out with mood swings? No. Would you
go come out the cinema with mood swings?
No. So, it proves my
point. It [ __ ] proves my [ __ ]
point. It's gambling. I know you like to
try to think it gambling.
No, no, no, no, no,
no. [ __ ] off.
Yeah. See, look at all of this stuff
that he causes time and time and time
again and time and time and time again.
Seven months losing streak wars. Seven
months and they able to win. Yeah. Ad
man wants to try to say, "Oh, you can
win. You can win. You can win." So he
says, "So a lot of people say, but mate,
we're being proven wrong time and time
and time and time and time
again. It also happened in
um also happened in the Weather Spoons
as well with a smaller amount of money.
Obviously smaller amount of money. It
happened the other
day, but they claim you can win. They
claim you can win. You can win some of
the time because you've won. Cuz you've
cuz you've got garments and you've won
before. I've literally not won in seven
months. Like actions speak louder than [ __ ]
words. Lost my benefit money, mate. I've
got more money than you would ever
have. I've got more money than you will
ever ever ever ever have. Believe that.
And that's exactly what I'm saying. I
feel like I'm the adult on this
community. You don't need to lose all
your money. You don't even need to lose
half of your money for it to affect your
whole body and your whole mind. This is
exactly what I'm
saying. You know what I'm saying? You
don't need to lose even 5% of your
money. Just losing on them is annoying.
Just losing on the rig [ __ ] is
annoying. How I've not come one of them
machines, bro. I shall never know for
the past few years. I shall never know
how how I've held my temper. Probably
because I know that they can just fix
them. They were insured and I'm going to
get a fine probably.
Yeah. But you can win. You can win. You
can win. That's what they say. You can
win. You can win. You can win. That's
all they ever
say. Ever say, you know what I'm saying? It's annoying.
I'm off for bit. Anyways, I need to call someone.