I'm sorry, lad. I had to [ __ ] restart
that. I had to restart it, bro, cuz it
wasn't letting me put the link up.
>> Yeah, man. It wasn't letting me put the
link up for some reason.
[ __ ] this bit cray.
This [ __ ] cray.
Starting to think just most of these
women are just very unstable, bro.
Let me put the link up.
One second, bro.
This time for sure.
Why is it not letting me put the link up, lad?
Second, bro. I want the link.
Nothing's happened to my hair, bro. Stop
self-reflecting otherwise you get kicked.
Okay, one minute.
I look bald. Yeah, that's
self-reflecting lad. See you later.
Anyways, get kicked.
The link should work now.
No, I want it to bother, bro. It should
work now. No.
No. Is it working, bro? Yeah,
it should be working now, brother.
No, it's still not working. Why
it doesn't work? I don't know why that
work. Want to try again, bro?