Okay, so I'm going to make a delicious
homemade burger. Right, this is
dedicated to Greasy. So, it's early
hours in the morning. I'm a bit peckish.
So, what we done
yesterday, we marinated this is actually
called burger maxing. Same as looks
maxing looking the best. This is going
to be the best tasting burger. So,
marinated some mints um with onion,
black pepper, and here's what you do. I
got it from the butchers, by the way. It was expensive.
And what you do, Bezy, is
so you know sometimes you go to like
these burger shops and they taste
plasticky or rubbery. Not Not with this
one, mate. This is all fresh beef. So
what you do first beef tasting beef.
So what you do is
I'll show you how it's done.
Right. You need to get this
but then you need to get rid of the
ends. I'll show you how it's done.
One second. I can't record it at the
same time as doing it.
Put it all back. Get rid of all the
ends. All the ends. And you put it back
in the mints for other burgers you want.
This has got to be a lush burger. Okay.
All right. One second.
You have to press down really hard on it
to get it right.
Like I said, you have to get your
fingers and whilst you're squeezing it,
you you have to get rid of the ends.
As much as you can.
This is worth doing it. Yeah. So
here we go.
So got done it. And then what you do is
now you don't have to add
what the [ __ ]
Okay. So there's no butter. I don't know
why there's no butter, but
it comes with it own oil.
should be butter. It tastes better with
butter, but it's it's not a uh big
problem. So, what you do is put it on
that. This is going to be a massive one.
Close it down.
Normally, I add butter. You don't have
to add butter, but normally I do it.
Rub it up. That mince was expensive, by
the way. It was 12 [ __ ] quid. Trust me. Bacon, cheese. [Applause] [Music]
Hopefully it doesn't stick. Sometimes it
Oh, look at that greasy. Sometimes it
can stick if you put a mud towards the
center of it. Yeah,
look at that. It's already cooking nicely.
I already have bacon with lime. [Music]
It's literally called Burger Maxim, bro. Burger maxim.
No, no, no.
If you've ever wondered how they
You can probably smell it all the way
from where you're watching it. It's so lush.
Then going to put two slices of bacon.
Oh, in the grill. Oh, man.
Yeah, I'm going to put two sides of the
bacon on it, I reckon. So, no, I think
one's enough actually. Quite big.
N two, actually. Might as well. [ __ ] it.
Put one on. Yeah. [Music] Yep. What?
I have to pause and then resume when
it's ready or something.
Oh, look at that.
Look at that greasy
cooking up nicely, isn't it?
This video is, like I said, dedicated to greasy.
Then put the cheese on the bun.
Yeah. And then obviously you melt it,
put in the microwave.
So nice to uh Burger Max. It just tastes
like pure beef, you know?
Like pure beef. It's yummy.
So nice. It is.
And the bacon's cooking.
Obviously, it's already been marinated
in onions, so
I'm looking forward to this.
One more time before we turn it. [Music]
Look at that.
The only bad things with these is that
when you've had them for a while, they
start sticking on the top.
So, if I put it there and try to close it,
you'll see what I mean. Look at them squares.
There we go. See that onion? Oh, mate.
This is going to be delish.
Right. So, I'm going to pause and then I'll resume
when uh when it's done.
There we go. Piggies are crooked.