Yo. Okay, so this is going to be my
response to Ricky Millington. Um, thank
you for replying, man. Um, highly
appreciate it. Um, I was I was waiting
all day yesterday for your reply. Um,
and I hadn't heard from you. I didn't
get a reply. And to be honest with you,
I was getting a bit worried. Uh, I was
about to call the ambulance because
let's face it, right? you're fast enough
to talk [ __ ] behind people's back um on
other people's channel, but when it's to
do with saying something to that person
on their channel, you've got nothing to
say at all, you know. Let's let's face
it, you know, but anyways, um you
replied um and yeah, welcome back um
nonetheless. And yeah, thank you for
your reply. It's good seeing your name
um on my channel um again in so long
because you was an old school viewer
before I caught you talking [ __ ] behind
my back. But anyways, nonetheless, thank
you for your reply and that's what this
video is going to be about. So, you
replied to um my video uh where I was
showing where women was leading me on
and playing games and saying how they
were going to meet me and then all of a
sudden they come out with an excuse as
to why they can't meet me. So, I went on
your reply and your reply is a
paragraph. So, I'm going to go over some
of the things that you've said. The
first one being is you were saying about
how Ire of desperation and how I'm
desperate and I'm coming across as
desperate and whatever. Okay. So, if
that is the case, why are these women
talking to me, loving my messages, and
agreeing to meet me? I mean, please do,
sir, answer that one because I'm very
intrigued to what the reply would be
because I'm pretty sure if he was coming
across in any kind of bad way, they
wouldn't be replying loving your
messages and agreeing to meet you. I'm
pretty sure of that. Now, did I say
loving messages? Oh, I did. Which gets
me onto my second point. Now, the first
thing I'm going to ask you before
getting on to the second point is Ricky,
I'm not trying to offend you or belittle
you or make fun out of you or anything
like that, but have you been to Specs
Savers uh recently? And if you haven't
been to Spec Savers, I highly recommend
you um doing so even though you might
have to go to Leeds or Sheffield to go
to one um because it wouldn't surprise
me that there's that there's not one in
Hull because Hull being Hull deprived
and all of that. You might have to
travel to Sheffield or But anyways, just
just go to um your you know local
local uh spec savers. Now, the reason
I'm saying this is because your second
point was you were saying about how I
was loving women's messages and putting
love hearts on their messages and you
was basically trying to make a point of
that's contributing to the reason why
women lead me on and waste my time and
say they're going to meet me and then
they don't meet me. Now, if you haven't
got anything wrong with your eyesight,
which gets onto the specs saves point,
you would have surely to god seen that
they were loving my messages before I
was loving their messages. And there was
a lot of them where they've loved my
first message. And there was a lot of
them where I never loved their messages
and they loved my messages. And they
loved more of my messages than I love
their messages. So, I find it very very
strange um how you seem to dismiss all
of the things that they loved of my
messages, but you seem to cling on to
the ones that I did, which makes me
think that you've clearly got something
wrong with your eyesight. Here's a bit
of friendly advice, Ricky. Um if you are
going to try to critique what somebody
has done in the future, you might want
to make sure um that the women haven't
done exactly the same thing in their
messages. that you're accusing me of
[ __ ] doing. Um, and that is actually
um a bit of friendly advice and it will
help you go far in life because let's go
let's go by [ __ ] Ricky Millington's
logic, right? So, a woman can love your
messages on WhatsApp. Put a love heart.
That's completely fine. That's cute.
That's a-ok. Okay, that's all right. But
you, as soon as you love one of their
messages, mate, you're you're a weirdo.
You're desperate. There's something
wrong with you. It gives them every
excuse in the book to lead you on. And
they will lead you on, my son. So, as
soon as you love any one of their
messages, even though they've loved a
lot of yours, mate, they're going to
lead you on. And rightfully so, son.
Don't you ever, ever, ever love any
woman's message on WhatsApp? Because
that is a crime. Do you understand how
stupid that sounds? It sounds ridiculous
because it is ridiculous. Because if
you're trying to contribute that to
being a problem, then surely to god
these women that were loving my messages
were also the same problem as me. So it
just just make it make sense. It doesn't
make any sense what you're saying. Now
let's get on to the second bit because I
don't want to drag on to that. Um so you
were saying about how um what I'm saying
is too much and what I'm doing is too
much. Starting with the voice notes.
Now, I don't know Ricky, but I don't
think there is meeting requirements that
you need to pass to be able to send
somebody a [ __ ] voice note. I mean,
Jesus Christ, you know, I send voice
notes to people all the time and they
send voice notes to me all the time.
Instagram, Facebook, um, you know,
whatever. People that I haven't even
met. Why can't you send somebody a voice
note that you've only met [ __ ] once?
I mean, people do it all the time,
Ricky. There's no requirement that you
need to meet somebody, for example, 26
times before you can send them a voice
note. You've met someone once, can't
send them a voice note, mate. That's a
criminal That's a criminal offense. Ah,
I mean, I I've received voice notes from
people that I've met once, and I've also
sent voice notes. Isn't that just a
thing that people choose to do? I didn't
know you had to meet somebody 26 times
before being able to send them a [ __ ]
voice note. Another thing you might want
to make make sense, you know, before
saying these kind of things, Ricky. Um,
you know, there's people that don't meet
people that send voice notes. I I don't
get your point. There there's no
connection between the two. There's no
you need to meet somebody several times
to be able to send them a voice note. It
doesn't make sense, you know. And then
you were saying about how I was asking
women um do they like me? What do they
like about me? And reticky,
I was just asking a question because it
opens chat to be able to flirt with
them. If they say I like this about you,
I can say I like that about you. And to
be honest with you, it's not as bad as
you're making out. It's just a question.
Okay. But what about all of the ones
where I didn't ask that, Ricky? What
about the ones where they didn't reply
to the first message? What about the one
that, you know, replied back and and
didn't reply back again? What about the
one that agreed to meet me then said on
the day she was supposed to meet me that
she was apparently getting back with her
ex? There was no voice notes there.
There was no love hearts there. There
was no [ __ ] asking questions there,
Rickster. So, it seems very much that
you've picked out conversations that
suit yourself, that you think you can
critique, and that you're going to win
the argument. It's not going to work.
It's not going to work, you know, and
and and that's it. What about all of
them messages? Tell us. What about all
of them ones that had none of these
things that you're saying? Huh? And
that's that. And the other thing was is
you were saying about how um I said to a
woman that I was going to go to a city.
Um make it right, Ricky. I said I was
going to go to her country. And I'll
explain it if you want me to. Yeah. So
that woman I was speaking to for about a
month. Met her. She was from Finland.
Met her on a Sunday. She seemed down to
earth. She seemed nice. She seemed okay
to be honest. And to be honest with you,
um I said to her prior like, "Would you
meet me if I come there?" And she said,
"Yeah." And because I was dealing with
[ __ ] um with women in this country, the
mind game is the [ __ ] I thought,
you know what, at this point,
something's got to give. I'm getting a
bit older. Um you know, if I need to go
to Finland to spend time with a woman,
why not? You only live once. And to me,
that's that's fine. You know, she's
agreed to me. We was talking. We've met
in person. You know, you only live once.
Why not try and meet a woman in Finland?
Why not try to Why not try to expand
your [ __ ] horizons? something that
you might not know anything about. So I
don't think I was wrong in in in doing
that. Then the thing that makes me laugh
the last one is you were saying stop
trying to meet women because you don't know them.
Ah I mean isn't isn't that how you get
to know somebody by meeting them talking
to them and trying to meet them for a
date to try to get to know more about
them? I mean isn't that isn't that
normal? Because I hate to break it to
you, Ricky, but everybody starts off as
strangers. So, if you go on a dating
app, right, don't meet anyone because,
oh, I don't know you. I don't know you.
I don't know you. Or if you speak to
somebody on Instagram, oh, I can't meet
you because I don't know you. I don't
know you. I mean, that doesn't make any
sense. I mean, if anything, you
approaching a woman in person should
make her want to trust you more because
a there's various different reasons. She
sees what you look like. She's more
probably inclined to trust you because
she's met you face to face. She's gave
you your number. She's typing. You go on
a date to try to get to know someone.
Isn't that the whole point of meeting
new people? Like, correct me if I'm
[ __ ] wrong. I mean, let me give you a
fun fact. Um, uh, Rick, um, you know,
USA Izzy, uh, when I first met her, her
very first message was, "Do you want to
meet on Tuesday?" Uh-huh. There's women
on dating apps that have come to my
house within the same day, but they
didn't know me, Rickster. Did they? They
didn't [ __ ] know me. So, me getting a
woman's number from a [ __ ] nightclub
and trying to meet her within a [ __ ]
week. You can't do that because you
don't know her. But women, oh yeah, they
can they can say they want to meet you
within the first message. Yeah, they
could meet somebody the same day on a
dating app. They can do all of these
things. But you you try to meet a woman
within a week, I'm calling the [ __ ]
police on you because you don't know
her. So stop it. Make it make sense. I
don't think any thing that you have
wrote in that paragraph made any sense.
I mean it it's mad because you do hear
all of these excuses like you will meet
a woman right um from a nightclub or on
a street or what whatever whatever it is
and you will try to meet her within a
week and then you'll get all of these
people that say oh you're trying to meet
her too fast you're trying to meet her
too fast I mean and you're thinking to
yourself what are you what are you
supposed to do talk talk to a woman for
10 years I mean why why can't you meet
somebody within a week if you've
approached somebody you've got to know
them in person you're texting why do you
need to long it out. I I don't
understand. I really really don't
understand. But yet a woman, she can
meet you the same day, she can meet you
the next day, but you you try to meet a
woman you approached, you don't know
her. Do not even bother. The double
standards and the hypocrisy in
everything that you have wrote is is
beyond me. It really really is. You
know, you know, it's it is strange. It's
very strange. So, what a woman can meet
somebody in the same day or try to meet
somebody within the first message and
that's fine. But yet, a man that's
trying to find a relationship, trying to
meet women and get to know them on
dates, you can't do that because you
don't know her.
What What the [ __ ] am I am I am I am I
missing something here, Ricky? Cuz I I I
I don't understand your point. I really
really don't. You know, you're saying
that I can't try to meet a woman who
I've approached to go on a date with to
get to know her because I don't know
her, but then it's okay for a woman to
try to meet somebody the same day or
within the first message or there and
then. But I can't try to find a
girlfriend. I can't try and find a date
because I don't know someone.
Jesus Christ. [ __ ] me. I'll be I'll be
very very curious to see what your your
response will be.