Yo. Okay, so this is going to be my
reply to um Virgin Boy, the ratfaced
narcissist. Um yeah, before I get into
this, yeah, I just wanted to say, you
know, the more you call me big nose, it
just goes to show how insecure you
really are of your own looks. Because,
mate, there's literally nothing wrong
with my nose. You are the one that looks
like a [ __ ] rat. Your face looks like
it's melting. And the funniest part is
you've literally got no teeth in your
mouth and then you say it over and over
and over again. It's all signs of
somebody that's insecure about
themselves. Um, so which will uh tie
into what I'm about to say. So let's get
on to your video. Right. So you were
saying about how I'm the narcissist
because I say that I'm better looking
than everybody and I've got more money
and ret. Um, and hold on a minute. Since
when did the truth become somebody being
a narcissist? Now, the reason I've said
I'm better looking than everybody on
here is because whenever somebody comes
on here and they say, "Oh, you're a M
and oh, you're this and oh, you're that,
you know," and I say, "Okay, we'll show
your face." And then they don't do it.
And the fact that these people are very,
very old and we've seen what a lot of
them look like. Yeah, I kind of gathered
a little bit that I'm probably better
looking than them. And you know, when
people have come on here and projected
their skittness to me and I've shown
£6,000 and had you all running away, you
know, when you've started on me, I mean,
yeah, that kind of actually happened.
That was facts. There's nothing um
narcissistic about the truth. And what
put the icing on the cake is the fact
that hold on a minute. If these people
weren't jealous of you, do you think
they would spend all of their life all
day every day stalking you, harassing
you, will not leave you alone? You
because bear in mind, most of these
people have never met me. They don't
know me and they never will. So, if
they're doing this every single day,
they've got to be jealous of something.
So that's what made me think like, oh,
it's got to be my looks or the fact that
I've got a better life than them and you
know, I've got more money than them
because they they're clearly jealous of
something. You know, the the the con
coming to that conclusion is now
inevitable. You know what I'm saying? So
I mean that's that's you have to be
jealous of something if you're doing
that all day every day. If they wasn't,
then I'd be like, "Oh, I'm a normal
person." But for people, and there's
more than about three people to do this
every day, they've got to be jealous of
something. Like, it's it has to be.
There's there's there's nothing else it
can be. And then um I love the little
bit in the end that you was you added
about how um
how uh what was it? Um you was like,
"Oh, I I raped women on a scale of 1 to
10." That's not a narcissistic trait,
you absolute [ __ ] [ __ ] You know,
people rate each other, you know, out of
10 all the [ __ ] time. It's just stuff
people's been doing for years. There's
literally nothing narcissistic about
that because that would mean that most
women are narcissistic because women
also rape men, you [ __ ] idiot. So,
you might actually want to think um
before you um actually um uh talk. And
then you were saying about how um I'm
the one that's got a traumatic
childhood. Bro, my dad died at a young
age. My dad was not in my life. I mean,
yeah, it's sad, but you know, people die
in people's lives. Uh your mom starved
you to the point where you literally
ended up in hospital. My dad has never
beat my mom up. My dad has never beat
any of my sisters up. That's completely
made up. And if that actually did
happen, I wouldn't have told you that. I
mean, that's news to me. My dad was
never in my life. And you want to talk
about my brother? That was my half
brother who I met once. So, I mean, I
speak to my mom. I speak to my sisters.
You don't speak to your mom. And you
don't speak to your sisters. You are the
one that's got the traumatic childhood.
And then you was making up stories about
how my sister's boyfriend pinned me up
against the wall. Uh, bro, that was
literally what your stepdad done to you.
Um um then that's the story of when you
pretended that you uh got arrested 22
times. No one's ever pinned me up
against nothing. Um and then yeah, like
that's literally complete and utter um
[ __ ] And then the other thing you
were saying was uh about what was it?
Oh, you said so much [ __ ] Um you was
about you was saying about um
what was it about how um yeah if anyone
would would do this now I would tell
them I would tell them I would tell them
tell them what you're never going to
meet anybody you've already proven what
you're about you know being a excuse me
hiccups being a keyboard warrior all
you've done for the years of you being
on [ __ ] YouTube is been a keyboard
board warrior. That's all you will be
and all you'll ever be. Just like your
boyfriend, Red Star, you know, you're
never going to meet anyone. You're never
going to say anything to anyone's face.
Um, you know, so why do you still act
like you're some kind of big man, you
know? It's like, [ __ ] me. Like, even
when I was in Birmingham last month,
right, you know, I called out that prime
because not that I had to, it's, you
know, he kept starting on me and ta,
you know, I've backed up a lot of the
[ __ ] I've said. you have had the worst
mouth than anyone on it and you will
never ever meet anyone. You are
literally the biggest cow would ever,
you know, and anybody that's not biased
would would tell you that. And then you
was basically trying to say about how,
you know, oh, I post what I want. I post
what I want. I post what I want. Yeah.
You'll post what you want. That's why
you literally deleted 95% of stuff from
your channel when you call the police.
Yeah. Because you will post whatever you
want. Yeah. I'm pretty sure if you could
post whatever you want, you wouldn't
have deleted 95% of your [ __ ] of your
content, you absolute [ __ ] [ __ ]
Um, you know, that that doesn't even
make any [ __ ] sense. Um, and then um
yeah, you was trying to say about how um
you know um I've had and here's another
thing, right? You keep going on about
how you've cut contact with me, you've
stopped meeting me because of my
behavior. Think about it. If that was
the actual case, you wouldn't be on
YouTube stalking me all day, every day.
You are the obsessed one. Yeah, because
I saw that bit that you was mentioning
about Timmy. You have got a channel
dedicated to me. You are obsessed every
single day. You've been doing this for
years. You are not somebody that cut
contact with me. Because think about it,
if anyone met a woman, right, and the
woman [ __ ] you off or you met a friend
and he and and and they [ __ ] you off.
They [ __ ] you off for good. They don't
come on YouTube for years and years and
years stalking you every single day.
That's exactly what you have been doing.
You are obsessed, you know, and you, you
know, you proved what you're about, you
know, over the [ __ ] years, right? And
then you was trying to say about how
I've said stuff about your dad and meta t.
No, you know, I've met you a few times,
right? And then we stopped meeting
because I didn't want to meet you
anymore because you was just a weirdo.
And you know, a lot of people on um
PlayStation warned me about you. But you
know, I thought, you know, this kid's
getting bullied cuz you used to get
bullied on PlayStation. You know, people
did not like you. But I thought, you
know, you're just getting bullied,
whatever. Let me let me give you the
beneficiary of the doubt, as Timmy would
say. And then I cut contact with you,
right? And then every single time
we have got into arguments, I said,
"Okay, come and say it to my face." And
because I was 19, 20 years of age at
that time and I wasn't no longer 17 or
[ __ ] 16, you weren't you didn't want
it anymore because I wasn't was an
adult. And well, it's typical with you
narcissists. You can start on a kid or
somebody a few years, you know, younger
than you, but then when it comes to a
grown man like my [ __ ] self, you you
play victim. you go running to the
[ __ ] police. You know what I'm
saying? We all know that if I wasn't aif
if I was a 15, 16 year old kid, you
wouldn't run to the police. You know,
it's because you can't stand up to a
man. You know, look, you've been on
YouTube starting [ __ ] for god knows how
many years. And as soon as somebody
retaliates, oh, you go running to the
police. That is literally narcissism.
That is what you are. So you coming on
here saying about how, oh yeah, you're a
narcissist because you rate women out of
10. You have literally been on this
YouTube [ __ ] stalking me for as long as
I can [ __ ] remember. And as soon as I
retaliate, you literally make it your
goal to be a victim. That is the number
one trait of narcissism, you know? And
that's exactly why you deleted 95% of
that [ __ ] on your channel that I've got
on my [ __ ] phone. And if and when
this court day ever [ __ ] happens,
which it will never happen, that's why
they've prolonged it for so long. I
would I am sure the judge would love to
see all this [ __ ] that you've been doing
for [ __ ] years. You know, oh, I I
haven't done it. I can post what I want.
If that was the case, you wouldn't have
deleted 95% of the [ __ ] from your
channel, would you, big man? You know,
at the end of the [ __ ] day, you know,
all of the things that you've you've
listed about me being a narcissist,
what? Because I beat you at the money
game that you started or because you
people are too ugly to show your face,
yet you start on people every single
day. That somehow makes me the
narcissist. No, you are the narcissist.
Yeah. you're big enough and ugly enough
in your case literally ugly enough to
come starting on people that you think
you can walk all over and then as soon
as someone you know stands up for
themselves you literally go one running
crying to the police that is literally
what a narcissist would do you know it's
like these women right we all know that
I'd say realistically a good 80% of
these women are narcissists yeah and
that's what similar [ __ ] what they do
you know they'll victimize themselves
and play games. That's exactly what you
done when you couldn't walk all over a
grown man, you know, or meet anyone or
say anything to anyone's face and you
literally got what you've been given
back over the years on YouTube. You went
crying to the police trying to make it
seem like I'm the one that started it.
That is a narcissist, which is probably
why it it it got your [ __ ] you know,
it got you so rattled on that video
because that is that is literally what a
narcissist would literally do. Come on
YouTube starting [ __ ] every day with
somebody will not leave someone alone,
which is why I had to explain. This [ __ ]
has been harassing me for years. And
then as soon as they do something back
to you, you go running and crying to the
police. And if really what you're saying
is the truth, oh, I can post what I want
and I never done anything wrong or no,
no, no, no, no. You wouldn't have
deleted 95% [ __ ] from your channel
because boy, I better believe when I was
doing stuff, nothing was deleted on my
channel. You know it. You've deleted 95%
of the stuff um you know on on your
channel. You you're not going to like
this, but I'm going to tell you some
home truths. You are jealous of me.
That's why you won't leave me alone
every single day. That's why you keep
coming on YouTube every day calling me a
big nose for somebody that's apparently
cut contact with someone I quote because
of their behavior. You're jealous. It's
clear you're jealous. You know, somebody
coming on here coming to conclusions
that things has to be doesn't make them
a narcissist. There's literally nothing
narcissistic about me. You know, there's
everything narcissistic about you. And
every single person that's not [ __ ]
biased knows it. They know it anyways,
but anyone that's not biased will admit
it. You do all of this [ __ ] every single
day cuz you are jealous. Yeah. Because
if I wasn't better looking and I wasn't
all of these things that I'm apparently
bigger myself up to be, you would just
leave someone alone. You would literally
leave somebody alone. But the more and
more and more you do it, it pushes and
pushes to that conclusion even more. And
and trust me, I I will be the first one
to say that I hate the word jealousy.
It's very lazy, you know. But when
it the conclusion is pushing everything
in the corner and there's nothing else
it can be, [ __ ] you're jealous. You
and Red Star are jealous. You live to do
this. You've been doing it for years.
You know, you've not it's not like
you've you've done this for like a month
or two months or during COVID just to
get a bit of a reaction. You have been
doing this for [ __ ] years and you're
never ever going to stop. This is the
thing is you you I think that's the main
part with this. It's not what they're
doing. It's the fact that they're never
ever ever ever ever going to stop. But
apparently I'm not this and I'm not that
and I'm all of these things that I'm I'm
bigger myself up to be. Bro, if that was
the case, you would just leave people
alone. You know, how can I think that I
am not better looking than all of these
people when you constantly have a bunch
of [ __ ] middle-aged men every single
day that won't leave you alone?
What? How could you possibly think not
highly of yourself? Because where semi
little ego if you like come from is
because if you have got people giving
you attention every day will not leave
you alone stalk you for as long as they
have and like I was saying don't don't
even know you then you're clearly got to
be better looking than them you clearly
you know you
it has to be that because if I knew
somebody was ugly and I knew somebody
was, I don't know, skin or whatever, I
would literally just not even waste my
time on them. It would be the opposite.
So, the reason I where this little
semi-ego come from is the conclusion
that you made me come to. The conclusion
that you made me come to, which is
reality. You know what I'm saying?
Because if that's not the case, [ __ ] off
and leave people alone.
It's it's you know what I'm saying? You
you are the narcissist. You generally
generally have been on YouTube for years [ __ ] stirring,
harassing people cuz you don't bully
anyone, but you harass people, you stalk
people, and as soon as somebody gives it
back to you, you go running to the
police. That is the number one trait of
[ __ ] uh a narcissist, you know? And
then you're trying to come on here
saying I'm a narcissist because I
[ __ ] called what? a woman something
out of 10. Get real with your [ __ ]
self, you silly little [ __ ] Before
[ __ ] making videos on people, [ __ ] idiot.