Okay. So, I'm going to pull up the video
um where basically um I've had
conversations with um women that I've
approached. So, all of these messages
that are about to go up or different
women that I've approached, whether it's
bars, clubs, the street, and as you can
see, um all they do is just play games,
lead you on, or they're just not
interested before they even get to know
you. um or your personality. Um I can't
talk over um you know the the video
because for some reason the m my
microphone is not working on Instagram
or WhatsApp or the screen recorder for
some I've been trying to resolve it and
I've used every method and the
microphone is still not working. So
yeah, um the messages are going to go
up. Um I'm going to um enable the
comments. So, if anyone wants to try and
tell me what I've said wrong in these
messages, what I've done wrong in these
messages, feel free because, like I
said, I've got nothing to hide. Um, and
yeah, it's just basically um showing
some of the [ __ ] that I've been putting
up with um for years with these women.
Um, and it's it's depressing. So, yeah,
I'm going to put the messages up now.
Um, and yeah.
feel free to tell me what I'm doing
wrong and what I've said wrong in any of them conversations.
Um, so yeah, let's see how it goes. Like
I said, I'd love to be able to
do an audio over it, but for some reason
I I can't find a way to get the mic
working on apps. Um, God knows why. But
yeah, anyways, um,
I'll put it up in a minute. All these conversations [Music]