Yo. Okay, so I was thinking, yeah, it's
been way too long. Yeah, that I have
been depriving Greavvesy of content.
Poor [ __ ] Um, so I just put £50 on a
roulette. I lost it. I'm going to try
with another £100. This time I'm going
to try the global draw one. Um, and this
is what gambling videos are supposed to
be like. Joseph Fro, if you're watching,
not you just showing every time you win,
actually showing whether you win or
whether you lose. um as it's a gambling
channel, you know, you are only showing
wins and also another thing I think
you're also putting money in the machine
and acting like you've win. You've won a
lot of the time as well. So, yeah, I'll
take £100 out and
yeah, and I'll show you that I use real
money and whether I win or lose, it's
just going to go up.
just in case anyone's thinking of
playing these machines. Um,
well, just you you can be the judge from
this video. So, anyways, I'll pause and resume
drawing the money.
There we go. Got the money. Didn't
Joseph Far say that if he live streams
in the betting shop, he's going to get
banned? Well, this video is also proven,
but not to be a load of [ __ ] Um,
>> welcome to Global Rolex.
>> Single Z. Yeah,
there we go.
I don't know why I always do double on
this for some reason.
The green is harder to get on this one. Okay,
there we go.
No more bets. Thank you. >> 17 21.
That's a good start.
>> Red far to one. That is a good start. That's
>> place your bets, please.
>> One second. Move this. Get comfortable.
>> Now, what this normally does,
>> no more bets. Thank you.
>> Come on. 100 to one. 10 to Oh, 40. Oh,
that's not bad to be fair.
What these normally do is >> please
>> they like to
they like to give um you a win and then
take the money back off you
try to get an extra if that makes sense. >> Lost.
>> Yeah, that one was definitely a loss.
>> Seven red odd.
>> Place your bets. >> Yeah.
>> No more bets. Thank you.
No. Yeah, it takes the next
>> money back trying to get the next spin.
>> That makes sense.
>> Place your bets, please.
>> No more bets. Thank you.
>> [ __ ] eight. You dirty. At least we're
getting spins to be fair, though. It's
not bad when you're getting spin.
>> Place more bets, please.
>> Come on.
pushing my lucky it
think I am man. No
>> one more.
>> No, we're going to have to lower that. I reckon >> 29 out. >> Maybe
>> place your bet.
>> Come on.
This is hard, man. No. Nope.
This is what it does. Trying to get the next spin. [ __ ] man. [ __ ] But
>> no more bets. Thank you. >> Missed.
It's always the way. You can't win
anything for them. >> Red.
>> I mean, you win £40 and then it takes
the place, please.
>> I mean, yeah. >> Nope.
>> No more bets. Thank you.
>> Nah, just attacks the same area. It's
been the same story ever since I um
started playing these to be fair.
>> Can't get anything from him. >> Yeah.
No more bets. Thank you.
>> 22 black.
>> Bit [ __ ]
>> Place your bets, please.
>> No more bets. Thank you.
>> Oh, you dirty bastard.
>> Red odd.
>> Place your bets. Come on. 17. No. No,
>> I don't think so today. No. [snorts] >> Nope.
>> No more bats. Thank you.
>> You just can't win to save your life on
even when you do get a spin. God.
>> So, it makes you wonder how people are
continuously winning on these machines. Um,
>> hold back. Thank you.
>> Look at this.
>> 50. That's not that bad, is it?
>> Place your bets.
>> Come on. Give us a nice little 17
with 100 to one.
>> Any more bets? Thank you.
>> Nope. Just misses everything. It's the
same thing. It gives you a win and then
it takes the win back
>> uh trying to get the next spin. It's the
same story if you can even get a spin to
be fair. It just takes it back trying to
get the next one. It's the same story with them.
>> No more bets. Thank you.
>> Come on. Move 10 to one. [ __ ] off.
>> Oh Jesus Christ.
>> Come on, man. No, no, >> nope. Nothing
at all. [snorts] Nope.
>> No more bets. Thank you.
>> 23 10 to one. Of course it was. [laughter] Do
>> you know what? They're so rigged. You
just have to laugh at them. You can't
even get mad at these things.
>> But obviously, you know,
>> I wanted to give Greg some content. You
can you just laugh at them.
>> They're something to laugh at.
>> Thank you.
>> See, missed again. Same area, left side
of zero. They actually are just
something to laugh at. Not even get
annoyed at. They're just literally
something to laugh at. >> Yep.
No more bets. Thank you.
>> Missed it again. It's the same area.
>> Sevenies would love this. Watch, please.
>> No more. Thank you. Come on.
[ __ ] 100 to one, man. >> Even
anyways, it now >> nothing. >> Nope.
>> Nope. I'm just like a robot.
So, I guess we've disproved Joseph
Harra. Thank you.
>> When it come We have dismissed uh we
have proven Joseph Farrar wrong on two
things on this video is a we don't get
uh banned for
you know, recording gambling videos or
going live with gambling and you don't
win on the [ __ ] So yeah, no,
someone just saw me as well.
>> No more. No. 15
10 to one. Of course it was.
>> Yeah, of course it was.
>> Would have been anything else.
>> No more bets. Thank you.
>> Missed it again. That left side of zero.
It's loving it. Loving it. Loving it. [clears throat]
>> Nothing's changed with the gambling
then. Uh nothing's also changed with the Oh,
>> yeah. cuz it's a >> Yeah.
>> Nothing's changed with the gambling.
Nothing's changed with the waiting
around for things.
Nothing ever changes.
You can't even get a bloody whim.
>> No more bucks. Thank you.
>> Black off.
>> What's that?
>> How about 17?
No. Too much to ask for?
That would be nice, wouldn't it? No.
>> Nah, of course not.
>> Be too easy, wouldn't it?
>> No more bets. Thank you.
>> See, it just misses absolutely everything
>> even when there's 30 numbers that are
covered. So thick.
>> Place your bets, please. So so fixed. So fixed.
>> No more bets. Thank you.
>> Nah, it's not having none of it. Have
you noticed that 20 and 17 has not come
out once throughout this whole entire
session? And you can see how much money
was also in the credit as well, which
also shows you um that how are you
losing all that money on the two pound spin?
Never happens in a million years unless
it was rigged, which it is. So yeah. >> Nope.
>> No more bets. Thank you.
>> Missed it again.
You sure about that? 20 22 on a 10 to
one. You sure?
>> Come on. Finish me off.
Get on my last nerves. Come on.
There we go.
And there you go. So, you're not
winning. You're not pulling out um
hundreds from the machines, thousands
from the machines, and you're not
getting banned um from recording or
going live. So, yeah. So, we've we've
also [ __ ] your f with them with that
uh logic. Same old story. Nothing ever
changes. But there you go, Grezy. Uh
that's the uh that's the video for you.
Hope you enjoyed it, you poor [ __ ]
Was dedicated to you, you poor [ __ ] Yeah.