Hey, I'm back. Video's uploading.
The short went on first before the
video, but it was all right to be fair.
Uh, I finished the curry. Indigo
never defeated me, mate. The video's coming up.
That's what happens when you're a big,
strong Turkish man. It sure was.
Still got my can of Coke. Got half a can
of Coke left. I'm like a certain virgin
that we both know.
I've ate it. I finished it. M
I've already finished the curry and I
finished the chicken.
It actually tastes better than the vindaloo.
You can't even have a masta [ __ ] version.
I'll be all right. Mom, you sure?
They are to be fair. Can you blame me
though? When you're not skin like a
certain person, Indigo, you do tend to
get takeaways a bit more.
You know, when you're not skin like a
certain boy, virgin boy, you know, like
I can do with a nice milkshake now. Um, banana milkshake. Yeah.
I like the milk.
That's nice. That was really nice. Venito.
That is Venito.
I just had a I just had a lamb foul.
Didn't defeat me. Videos to come. I'm
still a big strong Turkish man that can
pull American women and not have to
resort to disabled mate.
That's all all the vindaloo over the
years. I built up my um tolerance, you
know. I built up my uh uh my um I built
up my um spy tournament, you see. And
also cuz I'm not [ __ ] skate like a certain virgin.
No, no, mate. Sorry, mate. Has to be
said. Has to be said. Cuz
you already found
Because you already found your mama.
You should be uploading, huh?
Mate, you got to be so proud of me.
You'll be so proud of me, lads. Was yummy.
See, the chicken tickers, I don't even
cut them. I just shove them in my mouth. You know, [ __ ] delicious. [ __ ] delish. Oh gosh.
Oh my brother, dear.
Oh, Timmy is deleting comments.
Oh, that was lovely, bro.
Oh, that was [ __ ] nice.
Why isn't the video uploading?
Why is it not uploading my little video?
What's going on?
I've uploaded a little video.
Oh, that coming was lost. Right.
I'm going to brush my teeth now cuz I
always do that after I eat. Drink cola.
Keep my lashes in shape shape. All right. What's up? Daddy. Nice. school. My mama. Oh, [ __ ]
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Oh, that was nice.
Cross my lashes. Yep. Videos to come.
Grevy. It didn't defeat me. I'm trying
to upload it, but for some reason it's
not doing it.
Oh god d Oh gosh.
Where is he?
Yeah, it was lovely, bro. I'm going to
start having that one now instead of the vindaloo grievy.
I just bust my little nashes. My little
I always bust my teeth after I eat and
drink Coke. Do you, Grezy?
Let's try and upload it again. It's not working.
Uh well, you're not you're not going to
be able to watch the uh video yet,
Grezy, because it's not been made. So,
you're not going to be able to watch it. Grievy,
how about this? I'll let you I'll let
you know the very second it comes out.
The very very second. We've the very
second it comes out, I'll let you know.
Well, you're not going to be able to
watch it until it comes out. So, what
are you going to do, Grezy?
So, what are you what are you going to do?
That's you in life. Then
you you you wait. You wait.
It's been made.
[ __ ] up there, Grezy.
Until it's been made.
It's got It's It's been made. Yeah.
You think anyone's going to anyone's
going to go near someone?
might be pin for Greavves.
What do I use my little VPN for?
Oh, it's been made. It's been made. It's
been made. Rezy, it's been made. It's been released,
I think. There we go.
I'm re I'm re-watching the video,
Greavvesy. I'm re-watching it.
This is some lovely ownage right here.
Oh, I got my first thumbs up. I got my
first thumbs up. I got my first thumbs
I've done a video, Stephen Hard. I done
a I done a foodie video on my main channel, mate.
Maybe I could watch it and do a reaction
video to it. Grievesy,
I could do it right now. Just say the
word and I'll do it. Just like a little reaction
to the video, to the ownage.
I could do that greasy if you want
and you'll be able to see it live.
Did I do
believe I could take spice, mate? I'm
not like that little virgin.
Ken Virgin that will ever be a part of London.
Then leaving a club once, mate. I'm a
big strong Turkish man. It's all of the
It's all It's all um It's all I built up
a tolerance over the years, haven't I? Music.
I built up uh tolerance over the years for this.
Looks like someone shattered the plate.
[ __ ] off, you silly goose. No, it was a
nice story, man.
More than what that [ __ ] virgin could
ever have. So, is that how I get my
vitamins now, Grezy?
Let me get my little vitamins. Greasy.
Bless me, Dad.
I like the problem with that mint sauce,
bro. Can't say I do.
That's how I get my vitamins in it since
I got abandoned. Yep.
Well, well, that tomorrow means that tomorrow.
Watch the play up. Really?
Well, can I use
Can I use USA for the top up? Huh?
Or is that not Is that out the question?
They're going to crucify my bank account, please. Grim
crucify my bank accounts.
Maybe she'll give me some lovely vitamins.
Oh, lady got a chili concarni.
I think she was going to make a bit of conci today.
Oh, but was sleeping. What if I go there, Greavvesy?
Then would it still be out the question?
Remember I said I was going to go go all
the way there to touch her?
That account thought it was funny when I
said that. Going all that way to touch her.
To touch her.
Is that cute?
You silly goose.
Yeah, she said she is all right.
I asked her. She said, "Yeah."
H That was really delicious.
Yeah, she said she is all right, lad.
I got three thumbs up on my dating video, Grezy.
Is that good? Three thumbs up.
Is that good? Three thumbs up, Grezy.
Don't know what's wrong with Laney today.
Just been sleeping. I think she's in
pain with her hips or something.
Lane is a miserable old sod. Remember
that come in and said that Grevy
Lane is a miserable old sod.
So, what's what what food is Timmy going
to have tomorrow? Is he going to be a copycat?
Are you going to be a little copycat?
Nah, no one can c No one can copy my
courage because they can't take spice
squeezy. That's why it can't be copied.
You get it?
One sec. I'm going to go on Reddit now.
Let's see what Reddit has.
They tell her to be my mama.
So then what if Laney what if Laney dies
or whatever? Gregy, who's going to be my mommy then?
Who's going to be my mama? Grezy,
I'll have to find a new mama in it.
Find a name, mama. Oh, bless.
Not even one hiccup, Grezy. Not even one hiccup.
Day tomorrow, Thursday.
arguing with people on YouTube. Imagine
Yeah, I'm banned from texting on
Instagram for seven days, we so just so you know.
What do you reckon I got banned for?
Finding a woman to be my mama. Greavvesy.
Is that typical at 28?
Christian Izzy would be a lovely mama.
You go to work, feed me, make my bed and
stuff. Greavvesy, what do you think of
that? Cook me some lovely food.
[ __ ] you. Is that
your name? Mama
Peter Betty can't get attached anymore.
because he's already found he taken a
No, Greavvesy. Greavves know there's
another saying as well. Taking a baby
away from its mama.
I also come up with that one. Greasy.
Taking a baby away from its mama.
Do you remember when I come on here and
said that's what it felt like?
Taking a baby away from its mama. Yeah,
that's what it felt like.
taking a baby away from its mama. Did
you like that little saying, Grezy? I'd
been on the train. Yeah. And it pop in
my head with somebody commenting it and
it made me it made me laugh. Grieves.
Do I have attachment issues? Greavves.
I was right there though, wasn't I? Uh, Greavvesy.
Was I right or was I right?
I was right, isn't it? We don't have to
say, but I was right, wasn't I?
I was right, wasn't I, lad?
Someone blocked me on Reddit.
I said to them, "Hey, hey, I have a
question." They said, "Go ahead."
I said that I'm my age that I am, and
I'm trying to find a woman that would
also be my mommy at the same time. Is
this weird? And they blocked me.
They blocked me on Reddit.
We Why they block me
block that saying that I want to find a
mama. What's the point of [ __ ]
What's the point of [ __ ] like opening
a message? You're just going to block
someone? That's a bit silly.
But this have really bad attachment issues.
I'm being serious on Reddit when I'm
when I'm texting these people. All I see
I'm being serious, aren't I, Grezy? When
I'm texting these people in it on
Reddit, what do you think, Grezy? I'm
being serious, aren't I? Grezy.
I want to be loved. Grezy. Loved and fed.
Loved and fed. Greavvesy.
Is that cute? Unfed, easy.
Oh gosh, why is it not working?
This bloody Reddit app. It's not working.
Oh, here we go. I'm back on Reddit now, Grezy.
I'm looking for a new mama. One second.
So why couldn't that 19year-old be my
mama then Greavvesy Greasy.
Could have that 19year-old be my mama. Grevy.
to the cinema tomorrow.
Someone on Reddit, Grezy said, "Do you
have a mom?" I said, "Yeah, I want a new
mom that can feed me."
That's being serious, isn't it, Grezy?
He blocked you for so trouble. God bless you, Greavvesy.
I've heard Grievy's voice, everyone.
Greavves is a lovely character.
He's a lovely character.
How long am I going to be on Reddit for today? Grievy,
imagine someone takes my phone and they
say, "That's enough Reddit for today."
I'll go mad, won't I, Grezy?
That's enough Reddit for today.
I'm going mad in it. Oh gosh.
They're asking me questions.
They're saying how old am I on Reddit
cuz I said I want a new mama. They're
asking me how old I am. I said I'm 28.
What do you reckon they're going to say
to that? Crazy.
You're never too old for a mama.
Yeah. I don't want to grow up.
I want to I want to stay this way forever.
Why should we grow up for liking
boobies? Greavesy. We shouldn't have to
grow up for liking boobies, should we?
Is that a thing to grow up about? I don't know.
Why should we grow up?
We're allowed to find a new mama and
stuff greasy, aren't we? Simple.
Oh, fruit mad was old.
Yeah, man. I don't know. You might have
to cut down on the pool.
I don't watch Paul
and every porn that I watch is is when I
when the rare time I do watch porn is
vintage porn. None of this fake [ __ ] you know?
Yeah. What content would you like to see?
I don't drink anymore.
Leave me alone. I'm a poor fellow. One second.
What content would you like to see?
I don't watch porn
unless it's vintage.
No, I don't watch anymore.
I only watched it when you told me about
it. Oh, I'm feeling sleepy now, Greg. I
think it was that
My phone's [ __ ] up. Why?
Everyone on Reddit says that I've got a kink. Rezy.
I'm speaking to someone on Reddit. Green
I'm on Reddit. Greasy.
Oh, do you know what someone said to
this woman? Jeez, reading some Jeez,
reading some of your responses,
you are hostile and very defensive as
you did say very dramatic seems you tend
to get offended easy even when someone
isn't actually insulting you. But even
just asking questions about something
you came to a public form to speak, seek
advice about, you got to work to do that
in your personality. People, let alone
men don't want to be surrounded by that
kind of childish attitude and drama. Oh,
that's lovely. Someone's sticking up for
men for once. Lovely. Yeah. Uh,
where I'm gone.
Oh, do you know what someone said to
this woman? Jeez, reading some Jeez,
reading some of your responses,
you are hostile and very defensive as
you did say very dramatic. Seems you
tend to get offended easy even when
someone isn't actually insulting you.
But even just asking questions about
something you came to a public forum to
speak seek advice about. You got to work
to do that in your personality. People
let alone men don't want to be
surrounded by that kind of childish
attitude and drama. Oh, that's lovely.
Someone's sticking up for men for once. Lovely.