Right. So, I ordered the um trainers um
when I woke up. I was going to get them
yesterday. It's not cuz I couldn't
afford them. It's because Grevy would
let me. Um but I am running lower money
now. I mean, what screams more running
lower money than having a nice breakfast
at the pub. Got a nice t-bone for later.
Got some piggies. Yeah. The moral of the
story is don't talk about people that
you don't know. You don't know how much
money people have. You don't know how
much money people don't have.
Not everyone has the same life as you
people that the people that self- project.
>> Yeah. Not everyone, but the people that self project.
Got a lovely chebone for later.
I'll be enjoying that. Lush.
Can't wait for these trainers to come tomorrow
with the jeans. I'm going to send it, mate.
M got a nice football for tomorrow as well. Lovely.