Yo. Okay, so I just wanted to do a video
to um Smokey being the ratfaced
ugly virgin. Um and yeah, the reason I
wanted to um put the virgin into this as
well is because um I've noticed he's so,
you know, quick to, you know, try to
host fights and go people into fighting
and [ __ ] stirring, but then when you go
to his shitty virgin area, um he doesn't
even come out. Um, but then he tries to
talk about other people's L's. Yeah,
literally all he does is run to police
every single time he gets owned on
YouTube. What a [ __ ] loser. Um, but
anyways, we'll get on to that bit um a
bit later. So, I'm going to start off
with this smoky bee. Yeah. But um before
I do, I just wanted to say that I had
absolutely no intentions of coming on uh
YouTube yesterday cuz I had a hard long
think and I woke up and I was like,
"Bro, these people are not even worth
it." Like all these fat, ugly, depressed
people do um day in day out is just
self-reflect. You know, their ugliness,
their loneliness, their skintess, like
that's literally what they live to do.
They have got no life. Um, and one of
the maddest things about this is that
they've been doing this now for years.
Um, you know, it's not like they've done
it, you know, during COVID or for, you
know, 3 months or they were bored for a
month. Like, they have been doing this
for years. Um, and to think of it right,
they've been doing it for like 10 years.
And to think that if they didn't do this
10 years ago, they wouldn't be where
they are now 10 years later. lives
ruined, old, fat, ugly, um, and feel the
need to self-project their lives onto
strangers every single day. Because,
believe it or not, I know this might be
a surprise, but these people ain't got
no life. They ain't got no life. They
ain't got nobody. They ain't got no
family. Um, which we will get on to, um,
you know, in a bit. And that's why they
do this. They're just lonely people that
just been bullied all their life. Um,
and that's and that's why they come on
here. Um, and they've got absolutely no
life outside of projecting their life to
strangers on here, which is another mad
thing is that the people that they hate
on and they self-reflect their life onto
is people that they don't know. So, you
tell me one person in the world that's
made it, that's got a good life that
would come on the internet every single day
hating for 10 years. I don't think
you'll find I don't think you'll find
one, you know? So, um, then I thought,
you know, yeah, okay, these people are
just not worth the time anymore. Um,
something's got to give. So, I'm just
going to change the content up on this
channel. I'm going to do videos where
like I'm traveling, disable the likes,
disable the dislikes, and that's it. And
maybe go live once a month and speak to
the genuine people. And then I'll just
go on my other channel because, yeah,
these people are just not worth it. Um,
we're getting into 2026 now. It's still
the same people doing the same [ __ ]
It's boring now then. So, I weren't
going to go live yesterday at least.
Then I see the Smoky Beast saying about
how he's going to come on my mom's door.
I was like, "Bro, listen. Mark my
words." Yeah. In a big with a big black
felt tip, you're not coming on my mom's
door, bro. Yeah. Just just get that out
the way. Um, what I will say before
getting into this part is that have you
not noticed every year around Christmas
time these self-p projectors get worse?
Self-p projecting their ugliness. Um,
you know, doing anything to try to ruin
your Christmas, you know, harassing you.
They do this every year. Um, last year
obviously I fed out with my family, so I
was live on YouTube. So these people
also live on YouTube, so it wasn't as
bad. But the year before that, the year
before that, the year before that, this
year, I've noticed every year around
December, these people go for you. It's
like a pack of wolves surrounding you.
And it's because they ain't got no
family. They're going to be lonely
Christmas. Um, you know how they
constantly come on here and tell people
that they're lonely and they ain't got
this all the things they are themselves.
They realize that like it sucks to be
alone on Christmas. Um, I'm sure people
have been alone on Christmas once. These
people are always lonely Christmas. Um,
and that's why they do this. They
self-reflect. They hate. They will do
anything to try to ruin people's
Christmas. I, you know, I've had many
accounts going for me recently. Um, I've
had to block 30 accounts. Um, all
because you've got family and you're not
lonely like them. They hate the fact
that I've got a mother. Um, you know,
I've noticed this now. I noticed, you
know, they do this every time. Um, you
around this time of year, the
self-projecting and the bitterness. But,
yeah, it's got worse and worse and worse
and worse. And they don't stop. These
people ain't got no family. They ain't
got no nothing. I'm telling you, bro,
they don't. Um, and every year, like I
said, around December, it gets worse and
worse and worse. They will, it's sick
that they actually want to ruin people's
Christmas because they're fat, ugly
people that have got nothing. Um, I'm
going to be, you know, with family
eating food Christmas. They're going to
be sat there with no one. And that's
what they hate. That's what they hate.
Just like they hate that you're younger
than them and that you're better looking
than them. Um, they hate that they're
not they hate that you're not them. Um,
like I've said many many times before,
like they hate anyone that's not fat and
ugly like them and that's why they pick
problems. Um, they they turn their nose
up. Um, you're not, you know, you're not
you're not one of them. So, you know,
you're not ugly, fat, and going to be
lonely Christmas and that's why they go
for you. They're very very sad, lonely
people on this community. And by people,
I mean the haters. I don't mean
obviously there's some genuine people
there, but I mean the haters. So,
Smokeoky Be. Yeah. Listen, um if you do
come on Saturday, right? Um don't play
the victim when you get your ass
whooped. Don't try and sit there and
say, "Oh, yeah. I told you to come. I
told you to come." Because at the end of
the day, you have been harassing me.
You've done it to Timmy as well for the
past 10 days non-stop saying about how
you bully me, you bully. And I'm
thinking, bro, I'm willing to test your
theory. So, you either go live in London
or you come on the door. So, don't make
it seem like I was harassing you to come
on my door. Don't Don't try and play the
victim if that happens. And it really
really also shows that you've got no
life because this whole conversation is
all because I've got family and you
don't, just like nonslegs don't, which
we'll get on to in a minute. Um, this is
where all of this is coming from. Like,
you're actually willing to travel to
someone's door in December, right? And
you're going to lose. You're not going
to win. All cuz I've got more family
than you and I'm not going to be alone
Christmas. Because believe it or not,
mate, I don't buy you [ __ ] If you had a
life, if you had a family, you would not
be on it in December contemplating
whether you're going to go on someone's
door over YouTube that you don't know
and you're going to lose. So, I mean,
that shows even more. You're trying to
do anything to try to ruin people's
Christmas because you're going to be
with nobody Christmas Day just like
every year with these haters on here.
So, we phrase the word haters, but yeah,
you you're more mod you're more than
welcome to come if you want. You're not
going to win. Like, I will fold you up.
Like, it's it's it's and and and bring
your boyfriend nonslegs as well if you
are going to come, please. Um, so it's
like they're doing anything in their
power to try to ruin people's Christmas
because they're lonely, lonely, sad,
skint people that ain't got nothing. Um,
it is quite sad to be fair. Um, but like
I said, they do it every year. So yeah,
if you are going to do that then yeah.
But yeah, it's weird how you would be
willing to travel to someone's door in
December just cuz they got more family
than you. It's really really sad these
people. You really see their the
greeneyed monster in these people,
especially this time of year. Yeah,
that's that's going to be the title of
this video. The greeneyed monster really
comes out this time of year with these
jealous They're jealous either way. Um
but it really shows more. Um, but it's
like what Ronald Pump said, you're
better looking than them. You got more
money than them. You got a better life
than them. And it kills them. They're
jealous and they'll never leave you
alone. It's true. Um, so yeah, that's
that. So, if you are going to come, then
you're going to get your ass whooped.
So, I'm just I'm just letting you know.
Um, but put your money where your mouth
is. Simple as that. Um, but yeah, don't
make it seem like I harassed you. you've
been harassing me and Timmy, so I I want
to call your bluff basically. Um madness
this is even a thing and conversation
just because someone's got more family
than you. But anyways, then nonslegs
tried coming on my um hangouts earlier,
so I thought, oh, let let the [ __ ] in
because it's funny. Some of the stuff's
funny, like him saying Cheryl Cole was
attractive because he wanted to fit in
in college because he was getting
bullied. Um how he has to copy my
holiday because he's got absolutely no
mind of his own. So I'm thinking, "Oh,
this shit's funny." And he really
started to go in at my about my dead
dad, my dead brother, which was my half
brother, and I didn't even live with my
dad. Like really being spiteful. And
then you think, ah, self-p projection
again. This guy got starved by his mom.
His mom hates him. He doesn't see his
sister. Like they he's got no family.
Um, just like these people in here. And
he's really trying to self-project
another greeneyed monster. And I'm
thinking, bro, okay. Yeah, my dad died.
I mean, people die. You've actually got
a [ __ ] childhood that you was abused in.
Um, your mom starved you. Your mom hates
you. Um, you know, your mom, your
stepdad used to bully you. I mean, look
closer to home. It's a bit like when
you're trying to call people an incel.
Bro, I've been with more women than you.
I've never had to resort to a disabled.
So, you said that you was um, you know,
using uh, you know, saying about incelss
uh, on your channel, mate. Show yourself
you're the biggest incel. Um, you had to
start going with disabled girls because
no normal woman wanted you cuz you're
ugly. Um, another thing you tried to
call people ugly again. You're talking
about yourself. Incel. You're talking
about yourself. Broken family. You're
talking about yourself. I mean, if I you
was talking about family members of mine
that died. Yeah. But guess what? I've
still got more family than you will ever
have. So that's saying something about
your broken family. And then more and
more and more self-p projection [ __ ]
from this loser. Um, you know, and the
funniest thing is is that he will never
ever say anything to anyone's face. Um,
he will talk about dead relatives. He
will be a little [ __ ] over the
internet. He will do all of this weird
stuff. But we all know the real virgin
when you're in his area and he's running
to the police. We all know the real
virgin when you're saying stuff to him
on YouTube and he's running to the
police crying because he's a loser. We
all know the real him when people have
put posters in his area and he shhat his
pants um running to the police. We all
know the real him. Um you know it
doesn't matter how many years ago it
was. It's absolutely pathetic how the
biggest coward in the world that I've
ever come across can can can try to go
and [ __ ] stir people into fighting and
like if this if you want to [ __ ] stir
that much mate you're more than welcome
to come on Saturday you know you like to
talk about dead relatives and and stuff
and whatever and self-p project your
life but you would never ever say
anything to anyone's face and you try to
talk about these L's that I've took
where someone's told me
But mate, you've got short eyesight
because in all of these videos, I was
giving it to them back. I was not
running to the police screaming I wasn't
a fighter. You was. So, somebody didn't
come to my area making me run to the
police. I mean, I'm pretty sure the
train video, all the other videos, I
mouthd off back. Doesn't matter if it
was louder, quieter. I did not go
running to the police when somebody
argued with me on the train. I did not
go running to the police like a loser
when I was outside a [ __ ] club with a
[ __ ] bouncer. That is you. So, you
seem to be getting a lot of things um
confused with yourself. You being the
ugly one, you being the incel one, you
being the one with no family, and you
being the one that's took multiple
multiple multiple multiple multiple L's.
I have never run to the police crying um
because someone's come to my area.
That's that's you. That is definitely
definitely definitely you. Um so yeah.
So anyways, I'm no longer giving you
this is the last I'm saying about these
two now. I'm not giving them any kind of
platform. The only thing you're going to
see me now doing is videos or whatever
videos. Um that is and that's it. So
yeah. Anyways, nonsleg same thing to
you. Uh if you've got anything to say,
join your boyfriend on uh Saturday um
when he apparently comes to my house,
which is not happening. Uh because
again, you like to go fights, you like
to [ __ ] stir, but we've all seen the
real you. Um even though people will
pretend they don't. So yeah. Anyways, um
I'll see you on Saturday um with uh your
boyfriend since you've got so much
energy to go and [ __ ] stir fights, but
yet when people go to your area, you
don't show up. It's funny, isn't it? And
the madness, the thing is, right, is
that these people on here say that they
don't like nons. And they say that they
go for people that mate. These people on
here on this community, they love
nonsense. They constantly stick up for
nons legs cuz he's a nons. like they
they they're nons like him. Um that's
why they stick up for him. But anyways,
yeah, man. If you've truly got anything
to say, you're more than welcome to come
on Saturday. Um you [ __ ] virgin. Um
and until then, that's it. I will not be
mentioning you again. I will not be
laughing again because at the end of the
day, mate, it's almost 2026.
Your virgin ass has been doing this for
seven years. Being a virgin on the
internet, being a keyboard warrior, not
meeting anyone. I mean, if you're more
than happy to be a virgin all your life
on YouTube, that's you, mate. But some
of us have actually got lives. So,
that's the end. I'm got nothing left to
say. You will not be mentioned on my
channel anymore. Um, if anyone brings
you up, they'll be getting banned. And
that's it. So, you'll be talking to
yourself from now on. If you do not come
on Saturday, um, I'm going to be
ignoring you until then anyways, you
little virgin. Um, you're not getting a
platform. Um, and it's the same thing to
that smoky bee as well. Like I would
love for you to both come, you know. Yeah.