Okay, so now it is Friday and I am going
to do um some sober approaches.
Um I'm literally going to do this one right here.
>> Don't be like looking for her face.
Right, we'll do another one because it's
going to sound like I'm a good spec.
>> Excuse me. I had to go to say that.
>> Thank you.
>> What's your name?
>> Name is >> Peter.
>> Peter. My name is Peter.
>> Nice to meet you, sir.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> What country are you from?
>> I'm from Albania.
>> Albania. Albania.
>> Yeah. Yeah. A lot of people say to me
that I look Albanian, but I'm not I look
>> Albanian. Yeah. Yeah. When you So
>> I know he's Albanian, but he's trying to speak.
>> Maybe you could teach me the Albanian
language. I don't know because people
always say that.
>> So what made you come to London places?
>> I come to study.
>> You come to study. Oh, nice. What do you study? Never heard.
>> Sounds very I've heard accounting. I've
never heard someone studying business.
>> Yeah, business accounting is in business
as well. So,
>> that sounds very that sounds very interesting.
>> Check it out.
>> What are you up to today?
>> Well, I have a trip to go with my
student for my class.
>> Okay. So, you're in a bit of a rush? >> Yeah.
>> Have a great Cuz if you if you wasn't in
a rush, I would have said, "I'm very
very hungry from yesterday." So if you
wanted to get Nandos, we could go to
Nandos. But since you're in a rush, another time, >> huh?
>> We didn't know that.
>> I I as you on WhatsApp and another time
since you're in a rush today.
>> Have a great day. But I really
appreciate even the comments on
everything and even that you even try to
to talk to me, but I even I really
appreciate. Have a great day. Have a great life.
>> Great. Bye. Bye.
>> See you later.
>> There we go.
Told you. I didn't want to tell her I
was drinking from all last night. I
absolutely smashed it. Literally. I
actually thought she was actually going
to give her a number there, but nope.
Completely sober as well, mate.
Oh, I like her. Um,
[ __ ] it. I'm going to be right.