Yo, so this is going to be a video to
Smokey B and Joseph Fra. So, we'll start
with Smokey B. How does it feel that
you're a little [ __ ] house that didn't
come on my door? Um, you said you was
going to come on the door and you
didn't. You You literally said that you
was going to come on the door and you
never. And this is what I mean with
these biased people in this community,
right? No one's called him out for being
a [ __ ] house. No one's called him out
for saying that, you know, he was going
to come on the door and he never. And
this is what I mean. This is why these
people on here are just a complete and
utter waste of time. Um, you know, we'll
get on with to Joseph in a bit, but
yeah, that's how you know they're all
biased because even when they say
they're going to do something or they
take L's or they get beat at the money
game, they still come back for more.
Even when they've been embarrassed, like
they're just a waste of time um people
in this community. But that just shows
that they are they are biased because no
one's called him out for um [ __ ] it
um when he was supposed to come on uh
come on the door. Um, and yeah, I just
wanted to say um that I saw your
community post where you were saying
read the last one properly. I only said
I was going to go on your door if you
showed me two grand. No, Smokey B. All
you done was edited that today when you
took that L to make it seem like it was
something different and you didn't take
the L. I know what you done. You know,
everyone saw it. Three days ago when
that community post was put up by you,
there was no mention of £2,000. Yeah.
There was no mention of me showing you
£2,000 before coming on the door. All
you've done today was change that
because you knew you're not about it and
you know you didn't want people to to to
give you stick. But either way, people
know what you've done. They knew what
you like and no one called you out
because they're all biased um on here
and that's that. And at the end of the
day, it doesn't make any sense. Why
would you need somebody to show you two
grand before going on their door? How
does that make any sense? That's
literally like somebody harassing me on
YouTube, right, for six, seven years and
they finally got doxed, right, by a
private investigator and me saying, "I
really want to go on their door, but
they've got to show me £2,000.
Oh, I'm not going on their door." You
know, it doesn't make any sense. Did
Mark Samson show me £2,000 when I went
to his area two times or when I went to
Trevor Dawson's area or went to the
Skint Virgin's area um you know, three
times? Did any of them show me money?
No. No, because that's not how that
works. Smokey bee, if you was really
about anything, you wouldn't need anyone
to show you any money for the 100th
millionth time, right? You've been shown
money. You've been shown thousands. Why
are you still on here asking people to
show you money? I mean, you get shown
money, you run away, and then a week
later you come back and you ask them to
show money again. We know what you
people do on it. Same self-reflecting
skin money game, you know? It's it's the
same old [ __ ] You're not about it. If
you was about anything, you would have
come in a door and you wouldn't be
asking people to show you anything. You
know, you've been shown money. You've
been shown money time and time and time
and time again. Just like you've been
shown women time and time and time
again. Just like you've been shown a
better life time and time and time
again. [ __ ] me. I went on Timmy's live
stream a couple of days ago and they
were calling me v. They were calling me
a virgin and I've literally proved I've
had sex. Again, I don't care that
they've called me a virgin, but it's
proves that they're biased. That no
matter what they're shown, they're still
going to come on here and talk [ __ ] cuz
they're biased. You show them money,
they still call you skin. You stick your
[ __ ] dick up a woman, they will still
say you're a virgin. That's what they do
on here. They're just self-reflectors.
Show money, show money, they run away,
ask you to show money again next week.
Smokey B, if you was about anything, you
don't need anyone to show you £2,000.
You can look at your own £2,000. If you
really had as much money as you say you
do, wouldn't you just look at your own
money? Why can't you just look at your
own money? Why do you want to see
someone else's money and be proven wrong
again for the millionth time? You've
been proven wrong multiple times, you
know, in various different, you know,
circumstances, situations, you've been
proven wrong. Why if you have got all of
this money would you need somebody to
show you two grand before going on their
dot? It doesn't make sense. You're a
[ __ ] So before [ __ ] coming on here,
you know, try to call other people a
mong, just remember that you're asking
people to show you money for the
millionth time before you go on their
door and they've already shown you money
before. Okay? So if that was the case,
then how comes all of the times I've
shown you money before, you ain't come
on the door? You're a [ __ ] house. End
of. All you done with that community
post was edited it. You don't need
people to show you money in order for
you to come on their [ __ ] door. It
doesn't make sense, right? So, you're a
[ __ ] house. Take the L. Um, and that's
it. So, yeah. Now, on to Joseph Ferrar,
right? So, I went um so you know how you
were saying about how uh you know, you
saying about if I said I was going to
come off of YouTube for two weeks and I
can't and no wonder take no wonder no
one takes my word um you know, serious.
Um, listen, you might want to get your
facts right. I literally said that I was
stopping going live um as much and I was
going to do videos disabling the likes
and the comments. I didn't say I was
leaving YouTube. So, you might want to
listen to what I actually said before,
you know, sticking your nose in. And
then you said, "No wonder no one can
take my words serious."
Really, bro? Your boyfriend today didn't
even turn up when he was supposed to.
Your smoky bee boyfriend. Your [ __ ]
N's boyfriend in Orington doesn't come
out when someone goes to his area three
times. You can't even talk on a [ __ ]
panel and you're trying to tell me how
you and anyone else can't take my word
serious. Really, bro? I can assure you I
have met for the most fights um than
anyone on here. I've shown the most
money than anyone on here. I've met I've
been with more, you know, I've shown
more women than anyone on. using
different, you know, analogies, you
know, in case you want to think it's
this, that I have basically to put it, I
have shown more than anyone on here. And
the only reason that I've took L's is
because I put myself out there to put to
take them L's. I'm not like you, Joseph,
a coward that can't even talk. So yeah,
of course I'm going to take L's if I'm
meeting people for fights. It is going
to go horribly wrong one day. You know,
it's like I have met more like listen,
when you go on your boyfriend's chat,
Lord Jay, Trevor Dawson is on there.
I've tried to meet him. Bomb. Try to
meet him. You know, there's there's so
many people that I have tried to meet
and and you're trying to tell me you
can't take my word serious and how you
laugh at me when I'm not being funny.
You can't even talk on a panel. You're
you're scared of your own voice. [ __ ]
showing your face. I don't give a [ __ ]
what you look like. You can't even
[ __ ] join a panel and talk and you're
trying to tell me about people taking
people's words serious when I've proved
the most um on here. And again, they're
never going to admit it because you're
not fat and ugly like them. So, they
don't like it. You know, that's that's
how they are. If you're not fat and ugly
like these people, they will always be
against you. They will never admit their
L's. Just like Smokey Be [ __ ] House did
show up today. No one's going to say
anything about it. Maybe one or two
people will, but they won't. And here's
another thing, Joseph Fra, right? If I
didn't know about you people on here
being biased and not showing up and no
one calls you out for it and whatever, I
would have been to Newcastle today going
live, mate, and calling you out. Yes, I
would have. Now, before you sit there
and tried to tell me about how I would
do nothing, right? Listen, mate. I've
been to Middlesbrough trying to meet
Trevor Dawson. I've been to Mark
Samson's area. I've tried to meet Bomb.
I've tried to meet so many different
people on here. So before you want to
try and tell me how I will do nothing,
right? You and your boyfriends have
never done nothing, right? Everyone has
seen all of the people on here that I've
tried to meet. Yeah. And you know, and
that's the end of that. So I won't go
because we all know exactly what's going
to happen. I'm going to go to Newcastle.
I'm going to call you out just to laugh
in your face. That's all I was going to
do. Um I'm going to come back to London.
You're going to start your [ __ ] again,
right? And no one's going to call you
out. Like, and that's not fair because
at the end of the day, if you do madness
like that, like you want to sit back and
relax for 3 days and watch the other
person get humiliated by the other
people. You know what I mean? Like, you
know, you've gone, you've tried to meet
them, they haven't met, you can sit,
watch these people get roasted for being
a [ __ ] bag that they are, but that
doesn't happen. They're all biased on
it. That's that's that's my main point.
um you know it's like it'd be lovely you
know sit back with a cup of tea biscuits
and these people get called out for the
[ __ ] bags that they are um it's quite
entertaining and you've caused that to
happen you know it was your your
welloing so at the end of the day but
that doesn't happen because they're all
biased so that's trust me Joseph listen
before you try and say that that is not
what I was going to do if I didn't know
you was all biased remember I've already
done it remember I've already done
multiple things like that in past, you
know. Bomb was winding me up before I
knew that they were all biased. Oh yeah.
Um, he was winding me up, winding me up,
winding me up, winding me up. This
[ __ ] [ __ ] was winding me up, bro. On
a Good Friday. I just went to
Manchester, called him out, and I've
done it a couple of times as well. I've
done it a couple of times cuz him like
you make excuses. Yeah. So then I
realized they're all biased. So [ __ ]
him. Now I want to get on to right these
gambling things that you keep putting
up. Now, here's the thing, right? I, as
well as everyone else knows, you do not
keep winning money from gambling. Now,
before you try and say that I'm jealous,
I've got more disposable money than you.
I can do whatever I want. I can go out
right now if I want to. I've got
designer clothes. I have probably done
more in my life at 28 than you have done
at 38. So, before you try to say that
it's jealousy, I assure you, nobody
could even pay me money to go back into
gambling. But, let's be real, Joseph.
You're not constantly winning on them
machines. Give it up now. Right. The
only way somebody could probably come
close to constantly winning money
gambling is probably like something like
poker or doing singles on the football
and even then they're not always going
to win. Something where the house don't
have the edge. You are not keep winning
on them machines. Bro, give it up now.
How many times now have you, you know,
put videos up and shown you've winning
and what you've not had a five, six, 700
pound loss in all of these months that
you've been gambling and showing these
wins. Come on. It's not realistic,
Joseph. And you're playing on like the
worst machines ever. Um, you know, that
will [ __ ] you over eventually or I'm not
saying you would go broke, but you would
have some loss, four, five, 600 pound.
But the fact that you claim that you
keep winning, it's a load of old
bllocks. And at the end of the day, if
you do keep winning, you know, show the
videos. Um, you know, I would love for
you to win loads and loads of loads and
loads of loads of loads of loads of
money and bankrupt the [ __ ] bookies
and never have to work again. I would
love that. So, I assure you it's not
jealousy, but we all know that's
[ __ ] Um, and anybody that has an
opinion like this on any gambling
channel has an opinion. It's not about
being jealous, right? These people could
generally be millionaires and say,
"Well, hold on a minute. That doesn't
logically make any sense. How does this
person keep winning money on slots and
never seem to lose?" Somebody could have
that opinion and generally not be
jealous and have more money than that
person. You know, if if someone's you
people have said it to stop and step,
how is this guy never losing? They're
not jealous. They're they're generally
curious. How does that not happen?
Because you know, you you are a bit
similar. You know, you're only showing
wins. And trust me, mate, you them machines, right,
are not going to are not going to keep
paying and paying and paying and paying
and paying and you never lose. Give it
up, kid. Right? At the end of the day, I
when I used to put gambling videos out
there, um I used to lose uh loads and
loads. And even in landbased casinos
when it was more fairer, there was times
where I lost 600700 pound. Yes, there
is. You apparently don't seem to be
losing. It's not happening, mate.
Especially on them machines. They're the
worst payout percentage machines. So, at
the end of the day, Joe, if I'm younger
than you, I'm better looking than you.
I've got more disposable money than you.
I can assure you somebody can have an
opinion without being jealous. Um
because it's [ __ ] Someone's allowed
to call and shout [ __ ] when they see
it and generally just not be jealous. Um
you know and and that's what it is. I
would love you to bankrupt these bookies
and get a lot out of him, but that's not
realistic, is it? That really really
really really isn't. If you literally
done a video, right, and you went to
like couple of bookies and you clean
them out, I'd be like, "Well done." So
it's not jealousy, mate. People can call
[ __ ] when they see [ __ ] and I
can see through your [ __ ] you know.
And at the end of the day, it's like
when you're trying to say that
someone's, you know, got a, you know,
someone's living under poverty, brother,
you've got a 200lb phone, right? You
[ __ ] you got 30 jeans. I can assure
you at 28 years of age, I've traveled
more than you have. Yeah. So, it's like
you need to stop because some poor
[ __ ] is going to go on your channel
and think, "Oh, this guy's always
winning. This guy's always winning. this
guy is always winning and you're really
really not always winning. Come on.
There there's something more to it
because if you was winning if you was
winning that much money, Joseph Fra, you
wouldn't be working. You wouldn't feel
the need to work cuz you're winning all
this money. And I would love for that to
be the case. I'd congratulate you. But
we all know that it's [ __ ] So,
we'll call it out on [ __ ] at the end
of the day. That's people are allowed to
have an opinion. Just like me, if I was
gambling, right, back in the gambling
days, and I was only showing wins and
people said, "Nah, they're not jealous
of me." These people could generally
have more money than me. These gen they
they could generally be thinking, "How
do you always win?" And that's what it
is. It's not that you've won 20, 30, 40
grand. It's that you don't seem to ever
lose, which is not realistic. It's not
happening, Joseph. So, at the end of the
day, you need to start if you really
really are winning on these machines and
never ever ever ever ever ever ever
losing, right? Do some full videos. Do
some full videos with the amount of
money you put on. And when you keep
winning, I'll be like, "Fair play. You
keep winning." Cuz I'm not jealous. I
don't need to be jealous of anyone,
especially on anyone of this community.
And I will congratulate you. And like
I've said, if you go to these bookies
and you know, you clean them out and you
made them all go bust on video, I'd be
like, "Fair play. [ __ ] that's
lovely." But it's not. You're full of
[ __ ] and you're a bullshitter. That's
why people are calling you out. They're
calling you out on your [ __ ]
Nothing to do with jealousy. There's a f
there's a fine line between calling
someone out on what they see as [ __ ]
and someone being jealous. I I love it
when people with money, you know? I know
people with more money than you can
[ __ ] imagine and I don't care, you
know, and that's that. So yeah, that's
my video to both of you [ __ ]
absolute [ __ ] clowns.