Okay, so I just wanted to uh respond to
Joseph Fra. I can't wait until I get
into this last bit. These people really
are biased. Um, it is unbelievable. But
before I get into what you wrote, I just
wanted to ask you, why didn't you bring
up the whole thing where when I call
nonslegs a virgin, you're straight to
his rescue like Superman teleporting,
saying, "Oh, he can't be a he can't be a
virgin. He's got a girlfriend." And
you've done it about six times on my
live stream. You've done it over and
over and over again. Um, but yet when he
calls me a virgin, you don't bring up
when I put a porno out there that got
his channel banned. How I've been in bed
with several different women that
weren't escorts, how women have admitted
to sleeping with me, and how everyone
has seen me with women numerous times.
You weren't there then, was you? [sighs]
No, of course you weren't, you biased
[ __ ] Um, and that's why I called you
a non lover. Uh, because you're biased
and I just made up a name for you as the
non lover. didn't call you a non. I
called you a non lover. So don't ever
say that I called you a n. I called you
a n lover because that's the way it was
coming across. You're so far to be up
his backside out of his mouth when I'm
talking about him. But then when he's
talking about me or anyone else is
calling me a virgin for that matter.
Well, you're nowhere to be seen, are
you, Joseph? Are you? No. [ __ ] biased
[ __ ] Um and that's why I blocked you
for a little bit. Now we're going to get
on to what you've wrote now. um because
it's only fair. Now, okay, I will give
you a little bit attention seeing as you
clear. Now, I just wanted to say you
clearly can't spell properly for
somebody that calls out other people for
using I quote incorrect punctuation. So,
I'm going to autocorrect it for you. Uh,
okay. I will give you a little bit of
attention seeing as you clearly don't
get it from anywhere else, especially
women. So, listen up. See, I was nice
enough to to auto correct. Um, not sure
why you are again bringing Lord Jay into
it, but he did get slated for not
meeting Jaden. I go in his chat like I
go in others. Doesn't mean I agree with
everything. Well, the reason I brought
up Lord Jay is an example of how you are
biased. You went on my chat saying about
how you're never commenting on him again
because I lie and I've lied about this
and I'm pathetic and I'm a joke. Yet the
next thing you're on L's channel biging
him up. So, and he's lied about
everything. So it was it was it was a
clear example of how you are biased.
That's why I brought it up. Now another
thing is I don't know why you're talking
about two or three people that might
have slated L J um for not meeting Jaden
because that's all it would have been. I
I know about this because when I've
tried to meet Bomb before, you might get
two or three people that are unbiased,
but the vast majority of the people in
this community, I'd say probably about
98% of them, they are all biased. um
anyone that's younger and better looking
than them, they will find and pick
problems with them. Um and that is
generally generally what I believe and
I'll back it up on on the next bit.
Right? So the thing is is that we're not
we're talking about you not calling him
out for it. We're talking about you not
slating him. We're not talking about two
or three people. I'm calling you out for
you being biased. I don't care about two
or three other people that might have
disagreed with him and saw sense because
it would have only been two or three
people. I'm very much calling you biased
for you keep going on his chat despite
him lying about most things and him, you
know, and and not calling him out on it.
I'm calling out you for not slating him.
And like I said, the only people that
would have slated him was one or two
people, three people at the very
maximum. So, I [snorts] don't know why
you're talking about 3% of people in
this community when I'm clearly it's
clearly dedicated to you being biased.
So, I don't know why you're talking
about two or three people if there was
them at all. So, I don't know how that
went to that, but anyways, um the fact
is you are on his channel. You've never
called him out on any of the lies that
he's lied about. You are biased. End of
that's that. So, anyways, jealousy.
Trust me, not one person on here is
jealous of you in your life. I could
understand if you had a great life, but
you don't. You are clinging on to looks
and youth that are fading by the day.
You just don't get life. you want to
battle life rather than accept and work
with what you've got. Now you've got
that opinion on me and that's that's
that's fair. You know, you you can have
that opinion. You can write. What I will
ask you is what about you people then
middle-aged in your 40s, 50s, ugly as
[ __ ] fat people, ain't got a life,
continuously come on here year in year
out bothering people, stalking people,
trying to [ __ ] up people's lives. look
at yourselves before trying to talk
about me. And believe it or not, right,
I didn't think I didn't come across
someone's channel and thought, "Oh, he's
older than me. He's jealous of me. Oh,
this guy's jealous of me. Oh, that guy's
jealous of me. Him, he's jealous of me."
I didn't guess these things. I made I
come to the conclusion that, bro, if
you've got all of these people that are
obsessed with you every day, will not
leave you alone. They stalk me on
Reddit. They stalk me on different
platforms. They will not leave me alone
for love nor money. It has to be an act
of a jealous person because people that
are not jealous and people that have got
a better life than you don't come on
here from the time they wake up to the
time they go bed having channels
dedicated to you, stalking you, making
community posts about you. It's acts of
a jealous person. Um, so that's the
conclusion that I come to after seeing
these people's actions. I didn't think,
oh well, he's 45, he's jealous of me. We
didn't guess people was randomly jealous
of us. We go by like the bias list, how
biased you people are, which we're going
to get into more of that in a minute.
And how you've got all of this group of
people that are obsessed with you and
more than likely these people are older
and uglier than you. It has to be
jealousy. And again, I've asked numerous
times for these people to show
themselves on camera, show your face,
and they always use the same excuse that
we're not low IQ. We're too smart. But
if you was really not low IQ and you
were smart, you wouldn't be coming on
here every day repeating yourself using
the same comebacks. So that excuse is is
not even going to wash. So [snorts]
that's that. I mean, I'm going by these
people's actions. If these people didn't
do what they did, I would just think
that they're just people in the
community just doing what they're doing.
But it's what you're doing is why I'm
thinking that you're jealous. Um, which
I'm in my right to have make an
assumption after what I'm witnessing.
You know, it is clearly jealousy. Think
about it. Mo most of the people in this
community go for you. You're younger
than them and you're better looking than
them. That is not arguable. No matter
what you try and say, my looks are fade
and I'm older. It's not arguable that
you are younger and better looking than
these people. That that's the end of
that. So it's you know what I mean? And
the people that you're not don't do
this. So they don't they just leave you
alone. You know what I'm saying? So then
you wrote you seem to completely ignore
what you said and never done in the
past. Oh, the irony. That's why we
laughing acid stuff. I I completely ignore.
Bro, you people come on here every day
calling me a virgin when I've literally
proved I've had sex. You call me skin
even though I've shown thousands and
thousands of pounds. You call me ugly
even though I've proved I'm the one of
the best looking people on this
community, if not the best looking
person on this community. What do you
mean that I ignore things? I I I I think
you're actually projecting with that
one. I ignore things. If you mate, if
people didn't ignore the things I've
shown them, they wouldn't be coming out
saying the things that they're [ __ ]
saying. Come on now. Um and then uh you
was like the makebelieve holidays, the
prime incident after giving hard. You
are all talking no action. You also pick
your targets like the bouncer where he
was at work. All right. Bouncers beat
people up all the time. bounces fight
people all the time. The only reason
that you are using him being at work as
an excuse is because he backed down. Not
cuz he was at work. It's because he
backed down. Now, at the end of the day,
mate, if you go on YouTube and you and
you type bouncer fights, you will see
that if anybody can get away with
slapping someone at work, it will either
be a police officer or it will be a
bouncer. Another one of your little
biased excuses. Furthermore, okay, what
about when I went to Mark Samson's area
two times? What about when I went to
Trev Trevor Dawson's area in Middlesbrough?
What about when I stuck it on them two
lads month before last and they didn't
even stand up? So, you're always going
to be full of excuses where whether
someone's working or they're not
working. But, I'll have you know that
bounces beat people up and smash people
up all the time. And I even offered to
meet him after work and for me to give
him give him my number. So you are
always constantly going to be full of
[ __ ] and full of excuses even when
you're [ __ ] proven wrong. This was my
whole issue with with you know with the
people on this community. And another
thing is is that you're trying to say
that I I couldn't hit him because he was
at work. Okay, let's go down memory lane
with Goldilocks and the free bears here.
Now does anybody remember? I'm sure you
do. even though you're not going to
you're going to pretend that you don't
where I used to go to the Admiral's
casino and I used to go go on a bus to
go to the Admiral's casino. And this one
time there was this black bus driver and
he was running up his mouth, running up
his mouth, running up his mouth. And he
was at work, but no one had a problem
with him shouting up his mouth, running
up his mouth. They didn't call him a
coward knowing that I wouldn't be able
to hit him because he's I quote at work.
They called me a [ __ ] for not saying
anything back to him. But now we see it
on the other foot is when you actually
do give it back to someone who can very
much defend himself with that job line.
Oh, is that work? Another way to prove
that these jealous people have always
been biased. Everybody remembers that
bus thing where that man was running up
his mouth, running up his mouth, running
up his mouth. And because I didn't say
anything back, you're a [ __ ] But then
when you do give it back, you know he's
at work and he can't hit you. the oldest
excuse in the book with these biased
people. It's been going on for [ __ ]
years and years and years and everyone
that knows who's been on nights out.
I've been all over the country and I've
seen a lot of [ __ ] up things that
bounces have done. Like we've all seen
in Wales where a bouncer's gone around
the corner and started fighting someone
and it had to be broke up. You using him
being at work is not an excuse. And
there's several several several several
videos of bouncers beating people up.
And the guy in the bus, he was at work
and you still wanted me to go at him.
You called me a [ __ ] for not going at
the bus driver. But then when somebody
does go at the bus driver, well, you
know he's at work. It's the same thing
with you people all the time. Biasness.
[ __ ] off. You know, and then you wrote,
"If you really wanted someone, you could
do it clever. go to their door or when
they least expect it. Now again, you
must be self- projecting. I don't know
where any of you people live. You know
where I live. I don't know where you
live. You people know where I live. So
you might want to tell people on L J's
channel or other people's channel that
you come on here hating every day, but
you actually know where I live. I don't
know where any of you's live. But that
bouncer thing is so biased because
everyone saw that bus incident where
people was calling me a [ __ ] calling
me a [ __ ] house, but then when you go at
people, they can't hit you cuz they're
at work. Oh, you are a [ __ ] biased
[ __ ] Um, that's why I blocked you um,
you know, for that's why I blocked you
uh for a little bit on my channel.
[ __ ] biased. Biased. Biased. chosen for art.