Yo. Okay, so time for a new video. Um,
I've got a few things to, um, get off my chest. So,
yeah. Um, in this video, um, I want to
talk about how why do people keep
dismissing my struggles. Um, I've
mentioned this a few times in the past
on my live stream, but I've never really
gone in detail about it or done a video
about it, so I am going to in this
video. And how insane and unrealistic
are women's standards nowadays? Like
they're so picky. Like it's um it's not
even a joke. Um but yeah. So yeah, I've
not been on YouTube for a little bit. Um
before I get into that, I just wanted to
um say this. I've not been on YouTube
for a little while. Just been chilling
and yeah, just wanted to break from it.
Um, to be honest, um, I've not drunk or
approached any women since the last
time. Um, I generally feel like that was
the final straw for me because, you
know, the fact that you can go out and,
you know, look your best, do your best,
and get 10 numbers and not even get a single date,
I don't think you're going to meet
anyone in this country. Um, and then
that was just like, yeah, I need to move
on now. Give up. And to be honest with
you, the first week after it was
depressing to be fair. Um because you
know, you see it as like you tried your
best, you looked your best. There's no
real excuse why you don't have a date or
you don't have anybody. Um you've done
you put the effort in, you've tried your
best, you've looked your best, and it's
like ever since then, I've not been able
to find the desire or the motivation to
even entertain the idea of even trying
again. um because it's just it's
disgusting. Like, excuse my friends. Um
and that is enough to discourage anyone.
And it's so discouraging. And I feel
like even if I got like the urge ever
again to want to try, I feel like okay,
well, but you could potentially get 10
numbers and not even get a date whilst
looking your best. What's going to be
different this time? And you know that
and obviously the fact that I've I've
been dealing with this with women for
years now. you know, it's not even just
a one-off, but I think that was the
final cherry on the cake to be honest
with you. That was the final straw. Um,
yeah, it was bad. Um, so anyways,
um, the week two weeks after that, which
was last week, one of the numbers
actually did reply and she said, "Oh
yeah, I've been busy with um, uni. Sorry
I couldn't reply back sooner." And I was
like, "It took you" I was thinking in my
head, "So, it took you two weeks to
reply back to my message.
I don't think you was busy for 2 weeks.
Come on. That's that's ridiculous." But
anyways, at this point, um, I was just
trying to cling on to any kind of
positivity that I could, any, you know,
I was very, very optimistic because, you
know, I wanted to really think that I
was going to get something out of the
effort that I put in. So, um I just
thought, okay, yeah, you might have
spent £500, 600 and got 10 numbers, but
you've got somebody that's replied back
now. We won the money back. Um this
woman's agreed to meet and I was just
trying to, you know, I've got some nice
clothes to wear cuz I got him dry
cleananed. And I thought, yeah, like
this is everything happens for a reason.
Deep down I knew she was going to [ __ ]
me over just like every woman does. But
I was trying to like think that it
wasn't going to happen, even though deep
down I knew she was going to [ __ ] me
over, which she did. Um, so she said to
me, um, you know, uh, when you're around
my area again, um, let me know, um, and
we'll meet we'll meet up. So, um, so I
said, "Yeah, I'm coming Saturday." And
she said, "Oh, yeah, okay. Should be
fine. Uh, where would you want to meet?"
And I told her, um, you know, where I
want to, um, meet and, you know, the
place and around the area, Liverpool
Street, and she said, "Yeah, it should
be fine." So, we arranged to meet and on the Saturday
and on the Friday, well,
she said she was sick and she's been
sick for the past few days, which would
have been the Wednesday, but we agreed
to meet on the Thursday. So, another
woman that's led me on and gave me false
hope. Isn't it so mad how you seem to
find all of these women that lead people
on play games, play mind games,
but nah, they're not the same. I mean,
they just have the same mannerisms. They
just do the same stuff. They just act
the same way, but they're not the
[ __ ] same. So, it says these white
knights. I mean, it really does at this
point make you [ __ ] wonder how people
that are not apparently all the same
do exactly the same thing. Like, I'm not
even going to have an opinion on any of
that now because I'm just going to make
you realize how silly that sounds. Um,
for anyone that thinks women aren't all
the same, you do realize how silly that
sounds. how people that are apparently
all different do exactly the same stuff.
They have exactly the same excuses, the
same mannerisms, and they play the same
games, but they're not all the same.
Okay, anyways, moving on. Um, so yeah,
so she led me on and yeah, she didn't
meet me, which was the last Saturday we
were supposed to meet. So, another one
bites the dust. Same old, same old. So,
I went on Reddit today and I found this
woman um who said that she was um
struggling with dating. Now, this is
even though this is a very uh
hypothetical uh example, it still
nonetheless triggered me because it's
it's still what they're doing. Um even
though she lived in another country, I
didn't know what she looked like, the
point still stands. So, she was saying
how she struggled with dating and she
can't find anyone and reta tet. And she
was a decent age, by the way. She was
23. Obviously, I'm 28 in 2 weeks, so I
just told her I was 28. Um, and I said
to her, "Would you go on a date with me
hypothetically?" She turned around and
said, "Oh, no. Uh, cuz you're not
Muslim." Um, and you're too old for me.
Now, both excuses I have heard a million
times before. Again, that's so weird to
hear the same thing from different women
that are apparently not all the same.
Again, I'll leave you with that one so
you can see how ridiculous it sounds
when you're claiming that all women
aren't the same. So, um this is another
thing that they use um when they don't
want to get with somebody. They'll say
that you're Muslim um so we can't get
with you or you're too old or ret. Now,
I was scrolling through her Reddit page
and you know, just as you do, cuz it was
very it was so very publicly uh it was
so very public. So, we'll get on to
this. And it turned out that she had
been with a 28-year-old before. Now, I
turned around and said, "Oh, well, you
said that I'm too old for you. So, why
wouldn't you why why have you been on a
date with another 28-year-old, but you
wouldn't go on a date with me?" Um, and
what I showed her the video of me
looking I looked good. Groomed beard,
nice hair. There was nothing wrong with
me. There was nothing wrong with my
looks. And even though I looked my best,
and I'm I'm by no way by no means
perfect, and no one's perfect, but I
feel like I'm pretty good enough to be
given a chance like you would have
thought, but nope. Um because I'm not her unrealistic
standard. Um oh, I can't get with you
cuz you're too old for me. Um or you
know, you're Muslim. So, they'll use all
of these excuses in the book not to get
with you. They'll even lie to you um
because you're not their type. And by
their type, I mean you might have a
beard and they don't want somebody with
a beard or they um they want somebody
with no beard or they want somebody with
a beard or the the very the reasons that
they will reject you are very very
shallow and very very materialistic. Um
it's not like you're fat and ugly and
you stink or something like that. Like
they would literally reject somebody for
having green eyes and not blue eyes.
They're that shallow. Yeah. Literally.
So, and I don't know why they seem to
think by lying it. Lying makes it worse.
Like, let's just use this as an a as a
exception. If you found a a goth woman
and she was only into goth men or there
was there were circumstances where
people just want to date exactly the
same as them, as long as they are honest
and they are not lying, then I feel like
yeah, it's [ __ ] up. They're shallow,
but at the same time, they're honest.
So, I feel like in some cases, there's
an exception. But the video that I
showed her of me, there was nothing
wrong with the way that I looked.
Groomed, looked good, not fat. Like,
there's literally nothing wrong with me.
And she made a load of excuses why she
wouldn't even give me a chance to go on
a date with me because probably I had a
beard or something so materialistic and
shallow. Um, it's it's mad. So, she come
out with all these excuses. Oh, well,
you got um well, you're not Muslim or
you're too old for me. I don't know why
they don't just be honest and say, you
know, I don't like you because you have
a beard or you don't have a beard. Um as
ridiculous as it sounds, the lies, it's
it's ridiculous. And and what is the
most weirdest thing about it is there's
nothing wrong with the way that you
look. This is the this is the thing. If
you was generally fat and ugly and
broke, I could understand it. Like I
fully fully am, you know, for working on
yourself, you know, you need to go to
the gym, work on yourself, whatever. I I
I get it. I fully fully fully get it.
But when you're a [ __ ] conventionally
above average [ __ ] man and you've got
people making [ __ ] excuses why they
wouldn't even give you a chance because
you're not a [ __ ] Muslim or you're
not [ __ ] or you're 5 years older than
them. What the [ __ ] has this society
[ __ ] come to? And that to me just I I
couldn't believe what I was seeing with
my own eyes to be honest with you. It's
it's it's insane. And that's what the
[ __ ] problem is. They're unrealistic
standards, right? At the end of the day,
right? You go on um
uh Reddit and they'll be all for women
go for personality. Women don't go for
looks, bro. They go for more than looks.
If you are not their exact type, they
wouldn't they won't even entertain you.
Like that's how bad it is. Whether
that's 6'4, white, blue eyes, or maybe
it's just like a very very very exact
type. If you're not any of them things,
they're not even going to give you the
chance to get to know your personality because
for order for them to give you a chance,
you need to get you need to get past
their standard threshold. They're very
unre unrealistic one at that, you know,
and and that's what it is. They have got unrealistic
standards. Like like I said, it could be
as simple as somebody having a beard,
not having a beard. It's very very and
to be honest with you, it's weird
because it's like what they would
rather, you know, um not go with
somebody because they've got a beard or
they don't have a beard and risk losing
out on a nice person with a nice
personality just for the sake of
something so ridiculous as a beard, no
beard, blue eyes, green eyes. It's so
[ __ ] up and materialistic.
Like, it's it really really really is.
And it's it's mad. But like I said, if
you was fat and ugly and whatever and
you or you didn't shave, then I could
understand. But the thing is, when you
are conventionally above average looking
and they're making excuses why they
wouldn't even give you a chance, it's
kind of [ __ ] up. No. Um, and obviously
it's hypothetically. I mean, I would
have never met them. They don't live
here. But the point still stands. It's
still them doing the same [ __ ] [ __ ]
It doesn't matter where they um where
they live. So, I mean that that in
itself is insane. Now, if you're not
their exact type, they won't even give
you a chance. So,
but then people say it's not about
looks. Well, it clearly is more than
looks because even if you are decent
looking, if you are not their type,
they're not even going to give you a
chance. They're too picky. Like, we
that's been proven multiple times, you
know. So, that's as far as them being
too picky goes. And the last thing I
wanted to talk about is about um the
dismissing my struggles.
Now um whether this be in person,
whether this be online such as Reddit,
Instagram, whenever I go on the internet
or I say women are all the same or I've
had bad experiences with women or I will
never find anyone or whatever it is I'm
saying at that precise moment. I will
back up a lot of the stuff that I'll say
like I'll show like where women have led
me on um you know used me led me on gave
me false hope agreed to meet me then
didn't like I will very much back up
what I am saying and I have no problem
doing that now the problem with that is
every single time I do it sort of gets
dismissed it doesn't really suit anyone
like it goes in one ear and out the
other like it is generally insane and it
got to a point where I was thinking
yesterday like, bro, there's no point
even talking about this anymore. There's
no point getting into a debate, any
conflict because they're just going to
dismiss your struggles and make excuses
for women. So, I mean, no one's really
winning here. You know, we're going
round and round in circles like they'll
use excuses like, "Oh, you've tried to
meet a woman too fast or ret when like I
know I haven't and I know my texts were
fine." And then I turn around and say,
"Okay, what? Okay, then what about the
ones where they didn't reply back to the
first message? Or what about the ones
where um they agreed to meet me and then
they never? Um what about the ones that
said one message and all of a sudden
disappeared? What was the excuse with
these ones and then they say nothing? So
when they can't take the blame off you,
they're not interested. So they will
very very much dismiss your struggles.
And it's mad because if you was to speak
and and I always say to them, okay, I've
approached a woman and I've tried to
meet her within a week. Okay, what do
you want me to do? Speak to a woman for
10 years before meeting her. Like I
don't understand their point. But then I
move on to show them the ones that have
led me on and played games and I'll show
them multiple multiple screenshots and
it just won't suit them. They're not
interested. They don't care. It goes in
one ear and out the other. It's like you
are not even a candidate in this debate
because they're not interested in what
they're shown. So I mean that's just
insane to me to be honest. Um I was
saying I had this um debate with my mom
the other day and I was saying like oh
yeah like I kind of think women are all
the same talking about like 3 weeks ago
and she was like no no no. I said well I
can prove it. You can go down my phone
you can see all the bad experiences I've
had. And then I I simply said to her,
"When I'm proven when I'm shown
different by these women, I will believe
different." And no woman has proved to
me that she's decent. She's not a time
waster, and she's not a game player. I
am yet to be proven any of these women
exist despite what people try and say.
So, I mean, actions speak louder than
words. So, I feel like I was very much
in my rights by saying, "I will believe
it when I see it." and then everyone's a
winner because we're agreeing to
disagree and if a woman proves you wrong
then obviously you will agree with them
but I don't think a woman can ever prove
me wrong. So um clearly so I mean that's
it and I just said you can go on my
phone you can see all of my messages.
I've had bad experiences
um and it never ever changes. So um that's that.
that's that's that to be honest with
you. like they dismiss your struggles.
Like whatever you show them, they they
they they make excuses for women as
well. Like, oh, they changed their mind
that quickly or they can never ever be
at fault for just like wasting your time
or, you know, leading you on. Like,
there's always an excuse for it. Like,
it's never like they say, "Oh, you're
wrong." And they're wrong sometimes.
Like, they they will justify every bad
thing that they do, leading you on,
wasting your time. They literally will just justify
everything. Um, and some things they
will say, "Oh, they they just changed
their mind." What? So, all of these
women that have agreed to meet me and
suddenly backed out has just change
changed their mind so quickly. I mean, I
have never ever in my life went to go on
a date with a woman and change my mind.
So yeah, they they they generally just
dismiss where the women are in the wrong
and where they lead you on and they try
to nitpick things where you could
potentially be wrong. It's it's a
[ __ ] madness. But I'm glad that I um
got this off my chest to be honest
because it's absolutely disgusting. You
know, the you know, the [ __ ] I've been
putting up with with these women for
[ __ ] years. You know, I generally
can't wait to leave now. Um even more
so. Um I mean, like I said, that that
thing on Reddit pissed me off, you know?
It's like it's mad. They're liars and I
don't know why they think by lying to
someone it's any better. It's honesty is
the best policy. You know, the old
saying goes. And that's all I wanted to
say. So, if you made it to the end, thanks.