Yo. Okay, so time for a new video.
Greedy, I know you've been waiting, but
you know, I've just been busy and uh
yeah, so I'm in the arcade. I did say I
was going to do an arcade video for you.
So, I've already got this toy. I've
already got that one there for my mom,
Stitch. And I've also got
uh Tiger, his name is Tigger, who I gave
to uh um a child basically. I'm trying
to get this [ __ ] Um I tried this uh
day before yesterday and I couldn't get
them. So, and I've got 549 tickets um
obviously to be added on to how many
more tickets I get today. So, let's try
to win that bear and then I'll show you
like the other ones and stuff and we'll
see. And then obviously the prizes as well. So, we go.
>> Yeah. I bought a new track, by the way,
the other day. Greasy. So comfy. So Yeah.
start with this.
>> Don't know how I'm going to record
whilst um trying to play it, but
>> thank you. [music]
>> Oh, okay. Thank you. Yeah, [music]
[ __ ] He's going to tell me if I'm
recording there, but
this is a nice position. So, with these
machines, you always want to go for
the the one closest. [music]
[music] That's a good grip though, is it? This 549 tickets.
>> Thank you. >> [music]
>> in my um pocket.
He's not at all. [music]
So yeah, this is for you, Green. This is
only the start of [music]
I told you new year. We're going to be
doing we're going to be doing different [ __ ]
Maybe I should really go [music] for that one.
>> Thank you.
>> I reckon this one [music] get
Game, game, game. RIP. [music] Maybe. Oh, [ __ ]
>> Keep on going. >> [music]
>> Try him. Let's see if we can move closer. [music]
Come on. That's a perfect grip as well.
Come on. Come on. No, you bastard. [music] More closer.
Come on. Come on. That
[music] now he's in the exact same spot
as that one. That one.
>> Thank you. [music]
>> I'm going to play some poor after this.
Come on. No. No. No. [music]
No. I'm going to try to eat off. [music] Thank you. Come on.
Nah, no chance. [music]
No chance at all. [music]
Come on. Oh, you [ __ ] >> [music]
>> When they lie on their back, that's a
good time to start getting trying to get [music]
you [ __ ] [ __ ] [music] man.
My mom loves even though I got her the
stint, but still. >> [music]
>> Oh, she won't have it, will it?
>> Thank you. [music]
Come [music] on. Nah,
[ __ ] Just [music] slips on it.
No chance. Just slips. [music] Come you.
It's nowhere near. See, even things like
this losing on this. Um, so I've been
playing roulette um a bit recently and
I've had to quit it uh cuz yeah, reasons
that you probably already know. The mood
swings started coming back at that.
[ __ ] god. [music]
It's getting closer.
>> Thank you. [music]
Come on this time. Sean, come on. [music]
I'm going to have to try another 10
pound with that. Can't lie.
One second. Pause and resume.
By the way, you're capped to £50, by the
way. So, after £50, um,
you uh they you can't do anymore for some reason.
But enough of that, we're going to get
on to trying to win more tickets.
But I reckon
you got this ER in the bag, man. [music]
Oh, I already I had one try left. Come on.
Come on. Lift the [music] [ __ ] asses up.
I have one free already.
N. Oh, come on. Come on. Stop slipping, man. [music] No. No.
I shouldn't really be in these places. I
hate music. I'm one of them people.
That's why I don't play roulette
anymore. But I mean, this is just for
me. It's a bit funny.
It doesn't even move. Look, [music]
I'm going to pause on the zoom.
>> Thank you.
>> Slipping as usual. >> Nope.
>> Yeah, I knew it. You can tell by the grid. >> [music]
>> Yeah, if you don't like losing like me,
these are the worst places to come to. Um, yeah, basically [music]
I've won bandic tiger and stitch.
Would have been this [ __ ] though,
would you? Yeah. >> [music]
>> I'm going to try one more on this and
then we're going to go back to this
>> [ __ ] [ __ ] [music]
Come on, man. Perfect grid.
Oh, just go back.
[ __ ] hell, man.
These toys mean a lot to me, by the way.
Come on. I don't think that's bigger
than that. You can tell by so it just
it's just back to where it was already. Pointless. [music]
See, look. It just goes back to exactly
how it was.
>> So fixed. It's unbelievable. [music]
>> It just goes straight back to how it was. [music] >> [music] >> [ __ ]
What the [ __ ] bro?
Can't even win a toy. [music]
>> Yeah, I won. Yeah, free already.
Pause. Now slipped again.
Oh, so annoying these machines because
of you. Do not go on. If you do not like
playing duo or roulette or any type of
form of gambling, which is why I gave
up, you shouldn't be playing stuff like this.
It's done the same thing again. It's
like a perfect grip and it just misses everything.
>> Yeah, you can tell by [music] the mood
swing. I don't like losing. Yeah,
[music] but it's going to be We're going
to be losing. So, there you go. It's
done the same thing again. >> [music]
>> Thank you.
>> It's done the same thing again. [music] No,
we might have a bit more of a chance out
to the back and then we're going to go
to the barrels and see how many [music]
Oh, that's a good grip.
Oh, you [ __ ] bastard, man. You can't
win. They're so fixed. And then it just
goes back to [music] how it was before. Come on.
[ __ ] off, man. [music] >> [music]
>> It just [ __ ] misses every time. It's
[ __ ] bro. Like I said, if you do
not like losing, do not come to these
places. I shouldn't even be going to
these places, bro, cuz of how I am. And
I used to lose lose on roulette. Even
when it's money, I can afford to lose.
It just drives me mad. Um, so yeah.
Anyways, we're going to try the the bables now.
>> But I'm not going to lie to you, bro. I
shouldn't even tell you what thoughts I
was having the other day when I was
playing with it. Bad bad thoughts. Um
and that's why people like me shouldn't
uh shouldn't gamble. Um and obviously
this is a form of gambling.
Yeah. So, but anything to uh you know to
keep grieving content. Eh,
I hate losing like me. I get demons in
my head like a demon. I hate losing anything.
>> Um yeah, I should even tell you, bro.
Like when I lost um I think it was about
£100 like last week on roulette, I was
thinking to go to the casino waiting for
the manager to finish and give him a
couple of black eyes. People like me
shouldn't gamble. That's why I don't.
Why do you think for a year I stopped?
>> I'm so scared. I wish I had a ham
sandwich because my
>> I think if I got it one more time that
would have been me like I would have
done something I seriously
would have later regretted. I hate losing.
But like I said this is how dedicated I
am to greasy. You know
there you go. Look now. >> Oh
25 tickets. 25 tickets.
>> You just won 25 tickets.
>> Boy, play again.
>> There you are. [music] 500 kill.
500 would be good, isn't it? That ain't happening. 10.
>> I think we found ourselves a clue. You
>> imagine someone that hates losing at
anything is going to somewhere like this.
Doesn't make sense, does it?
500 maybe. No. Oh, 25 is all right. So,
>> 25 tickets. Nice job.
>> You want to play again? Oh.
Oh, you won 10 tickets.
>> We'll see if I can get any prizes as well. >> 500.
Oh, it has to go here as well, by the
way. It can't just go anywhere. It has
to go there. So, >> transport.
>> Yeah, 25.
>> I think we found ourselves a clue. You won 25.
>> I might have to cut this off and do part
two because we'll get too long. about to play again.
>> Where's 500? 25. 25's
>> 25 tickets. Nice job. I'll
>> show you the better one after this.
The free time.
>> That deserves a Scooby snack. You won 25 tickets.
Yeah, that's all right.
>> J, you just won 25 tickets,
>> right? So, I'm going to top up. Oh, yeah.
>> Anything to keep you in content, baby.
Anything to keep you in content, mate.
>> Pull the handle before the
So, I got these. I've got 500 in my pocket. >> [ __ ]
>> Oh, what?
I had another go. I can't keep up. [ __ ] 500.
>> Oh, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> I think we found ourselves a clue. You
won 25 tickets.
>> Should I got 549 here again?
>> Yeah. I don't know if there's someone here.
>> Oh, look at that, mate. Lovely. tickets. [music]
>> Yeah. Why someone like me would go to a
place like this? I shall never know.
Knowing I hate losing
How many tickets? I want to try to get 500 tickets.
Five. Of course it was.
These are also rigged as well, like
roulette. But like I said, anything to
keep Reezy content. 25. >> Okay.
I'm just going to put them away. I'm >> [music] >> 50.
>> Yeah, 50 is good.
There you go. 50.
There's no good prizes on the penny
pusher, so there's no point. >> [music]
>> I need to cut this off soon, man.
Come on. 600 will be. I haven't had 600 yet.
>> Keep going. Keep going. Keep going. Keep
Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop.
How was that five? That was [ __ ] 200.
[ __ ] weak bastard. It would What the
[ __ ] That was 200.
[ __ ] dirty bastard, man. That's why I
don't go in these places. I hate losing.
But I did say to Greens I was going to
do it. I don't like losing on anything.
On anything. I get a demon into my head.
You don't know what I'm like, bro. I'm
bad. I'm really really bad.
as you should be. Nah,
I'm going to have to cut this off. Um,
do part two cuz this is almost going to
cut off. One sec.