Yo. Okay, so I'm going to do a new video
because yeah, I wanted to get some um
things off of my chest. And the title of
this video is going to be a country
designed to annoy you. Like I generally
feel like, yeah, England or pretty much
anywhere in the UK is just like a
country just to just to be designed to
actually piss you off. Like, and I'm not
just talking about like dating or women.
And I'm talking about like various
different things. So I went to the
cinema today um and to be honest with
you, it doesn't normally um bother me,
you know, like you see couples and
whatever, but you know, even before the
cinema, like you'll see these like women
out and you'd want to like go and speak
to them, but obviously you know that if
you do go and speak to them, it's just
going to be the same response. I have a
boyfriend, you know, I'm not interested
or they play games and that's all it's
ever going to be. And obviously, you
know, like, so then obviously you can't
do it. So, and obviously your mind is
telling you, "Oh, you should do it. You
should try." And then when you try,
you're back in the same rut again. So
that's what I mean by it's like designed
to piss you off. Like it's designed to
annoy you. Um, and obviously, yeah, if
you don't do it, then you're you're
good. But if you do do it, then you're
back to square one again. And who knows,
you might go out and end up wasting £300
again and, you know, getting the same
old thing. numbers that play games or
people saying that they've got
boyfriends. And then I went to the
cinema. Yeah, I was in the cinema. I
swear to God, bro, I saw this. He
couldn't have been older than 16, right,
holding hands with like probably a 23
year old woman. Like, I'm not even
joking. I was like a bit weird. And then
I saw this guy, right, with um a woman
and he was [ __ ] stinking. And do you
know what? Yeah, I've got no problems
with like people being ugly because at
the end of the day like people can't
choose how they look because people are
what they are. You know, people can
self-improve. That's all you can is is
that's all you can do is try your best.
You know, you can't ever knock anyone
for trying, which is what I'm going to
get on to in a minute. And like he was
with literally about, bro, an eight out
of 10. And if they were actually good
people, then I could understand it. But
they're they're ugly in the inside and
out. And it seems like, you know, some
of these people can just [ __ ] you
know, get women no problems. And
obviously, I'm not jealous. Like, it's
not a a jealousy thing. I've never been
jealous of anyone, you know, with money
or anything, but it it's sort of like
it's mocking you. It's laughing you at
laughing at you and saying, you know,
you know, you've tried all of these
times. You're good-looking. you've tried
more than anybody in the world and you
can't get anyone, you know, and and
obviously because of my history. If you
was like, if I was a dwarf, right, then
I could understand, you know, you got something,
you know, you got something wrong with
you or, you know, you was disabled or
you was ugly or or even if you didn't
try, then I'd be like, "Okay, yeah, you
can blame yourself. You know, the
world's not against you." No, no, no.
But bro, when you're not ugly and you
legitimately have tried so hard and then
you have to see that [ __ ] right, it's
like it is generally like trying to
annoy you. Um, and then you'll see a guy
that's actually decent looking. Bear
with me. Like you'll actually see decent
looking guys with the most ugliest
women. Like fat and ugly. I swear to
God. Like it's it's so bad. So, you
know, you get all of these people that
sit there and say, "Oh, uh, yeah. Well,
um, you know what about other guys in
relationships? And they don't tell you
that a lot of these guys in
relationships had to [ __ ] lower their
standards to almost [ __ ] zero to even
get in a relationship. Um, it's strange.
And then you'll see like the average
guys were just like an average woman,
which is which is normal. Like if they
were average looking or bit below and
you know they were really good people
and they actually worked on themsel then
then I could understand it. you know,
like credit women's credit shoe. But
when you have to see [ __ ] like that and
then you've got to see like stuck up
women like everywhere. Like I saw it all
today as well, you know, like just stuck
up women same look in their eye. It's
just it's just horrible. And then, you
know, some people might think, "Oh,
okay. Well, let me gamble." And then you
gamble and then, you know, if you gamble
and you lose, then it's even worse.
That's what I mean. It's it's it's very
much a country designed to annoy you and
get you rattled. um you know, if you let
it or you know, even when you go to like
a bar and you try to speak to women and
you get kicked out for trying to speak
to women, you know, it seems very much a
country designed to piss you off. Um and
you know, stuff like the weather, you
know, one day you might decide to go out
and you might want to drink and then it
starts pissing down with rain, you know,
like it does seem a country designed to
get under your skin. Um, you know, I
thought I felt like that a few times to
be honest with you, you know, and and at
the end of the day, you know, if he was
ugly or you just didn't try one or the
other or both, then yeah, okay, we get
it. Like you you can only be mad at
yourself. But in in a situation like
mine, there's no being mad at yourself
cuz you've tried and you're decent
looking, so there's there's there's
nothing wrong with you. Um, put it this
way, if I didn't try in all of them
years, I would have been set for life as
far as money goes.
So read into that what you will. Um you
know and it yeah it does seem very much
like um a country designed to annoy you.
You know even with things like the
police and the government and the
waiting around for things and not to
mention even like when you try to go
like when you try to go to work and
you've got to deal with stupid entitled
[ __ ] that you know want to start
[ __ ] but can't finish it and they don't
even know you. like it seems like a it
generally does seem like a country
designed to annoy you. Um, you know, you
try your hardest, you know, you have to
deal with [ __ ] with women, then you see
people that are, you know, having had to
try and ugly and got no personality and
somehow they're with someone or, you
know, people being [ __ ] at work or
you you know what I'm saying? Or the
weather being [ __ ] It generally seems
like it's like one thing will tempt you
to do something that will then make you
want to do other things that are bad.
Like if that makes sense. It's hard to
try and explain. That's what I mean by
like it is generally a country just
designed to annoy you. And not to
mention the fact that like you see the
same people with the same attitude every
everywhere you go. You see the same
[ __ ] people with the same attitude.
It's it's insane, man. like it generally
generally is. It's a country designed to
annoy you. I'm telling you 100% it is
with the women, with the weather, with
you know even I guess gambling. You know
it's like I said it's like you will be
tempted for example say to like approach
a woman and you're not going to get
anything but the same old [ __ ] that
you've been getting for years and you
think oh well I can't get a buzz this
way so let me gamble and then the
gambling will [ __ ] you over or something
similar to that. Like it's it's just a
country designed to annoy you.
you know, and also like with the prices
of things as well, you know, even if you
want to go for a night out, it's really
really expensive and then in the end you
don't get anything. It does seem like it
is a country designed to to piss you
off, you know. Um, that's my opinion on
it. Anyways, you know, it's it's a
madness. It's it's crazy. But I just
thought I'd just do a video about this
cuz I wanted to get some things off my
chest. So, yeah. England sucks.