Yo, Timmy. So, this is going to be a
video to you. Um, so before I start, I
don't know why you've got these
50year-old old ugly virgin men on your
um channel trying to say that I've got
no job. I've got no money. I've got no
never had a girlfriend or I've literally
proved that I've already had all of
these things a million times. I'm
telling you, these people in this
community, they're old, fat, ugly, angry
gamblers. And every single time they do
their balls in and they get a reality of
what they are themselves, you know,
skint, jobless, they're actually
virgins. Um, that's why they s on
YouTube every day cuz they ain't got a
life. Um, they try to call you it to try
to make themselves feel better. Like
they're trying to say, "Oh, like you're
almost 30." Bro, these people are not
almost. They're in their 50s and they're
probably most of them are still virgins.
Ain't got a life, ain't got a job cuz
they're sat on YouTube every day. They
really know how to self project their
life onto others. I give them that.
They're very good at self-projecting.
Um, you know, they hate the fact that
you're younger than them and you're
better looking than them, so they try to
make you feel as hopeless as they are.
It's [ __ ] pathetic. And this is
exactly what I was saying about um uh
you know I was saying earlier you know
it's uh you know when when you when
they're jealous of you you know these
people um you know they they'll just
self-reflect and say that you're this
and you're that when all of these things
apply to themselves they're literally
old fat ugly still virgins and got a pot
to piss in and because that's their life
they tried to tell you that's your life.
Yeah. Self-jection. Um, anyways, so
Timmy, let me tell you something, mate.
Yeah. Firstly, Yeah. Okay. I done an I
done an 11 minute video in response to a
17minute video. Nobody owns me on this
community. You Virgin Boy and [ __ ]
Red Star has been stalking me and doing
videos on me for years. I literally live
in their head, rentree. No one owns me.
They have to sit online all day, every
day being jealous of me when 90% of the
time I don't even react to them. They
don't [ __ ] own me. They own their
[ __ ] selves. They embarrass
themselves every day on YouTube. Just
like your self-reflecting ugly fat old
fart followers that try to tell you you
don't have the things that they don't
have and never had. Um, you know what
I'm saying? Just like when they try to
call people skin and then you show them
money and they all run away. Yeah. Self-
projected. It's what you all do on it.
You know, you've been doing it for
years. And um, yeah, Timmy, why are you
doing a video trying to say, "Oh, yeah,
you're more than welcome to come to
Birmingham. Am I not going to come to
London?" Timmy, I was in Birmingham last
month calling you out and you was in the
chat and you never come out, you know.
So, stop acting like you're [ __ ]
hard, you know? I was in your city last
month and you did not come out. Yes. And
you got called out. You was on the chat.
So, you can't even say you didn't see
it. So, at the end of the day, why the
[ __ ] to me do you think I did not go to
[ __ ] Birmingham on Friday to knock
the [ __ ] out of Money Mike? Because do
you remember the saying, bro? A wise man
learns from his mistakes. We all know
what you do on here. You know, people
come up there and, you know, call you
out and then when people call you out,
you don't show up and then you pretend
like it never happened. Yeah. There was
literally that example last month when I
called you out in uh Birmingham and I
didn't even go there prime to prime call
you out. Um but then I thought cuz I'm
there I'll do it anyways. And what did
you do? You shacked your pants. So why
the [ __ ] am I going to waste my time and
my money again, you know, calling you on
money Mike out when you've already shown
that you you don't show up? You can't
use any excuses that, oh, it's a public
place. No, no, no. You got called out
last month and you did not show up. So,
I don't know why you're coming on
YouTube still acting like you're a big
man. But this is exactly what I was
saying. You know, when you're not liked
on here, right? because you're better
looking than these people and you got
more more in them more than them in life
and you're young, you know, just simple
as that, they'll find reasons to dislike
you. So, no matter what you do, um
they'll just completely deny it
happened. Like, but how many times that
[ __ ] Arsenal Mark come on YouTube
acting like he was some kind of big
[ __ ] you know, [ __ ] god knows how
many times after I went to his area two
times. This is what I'm saying. They're
all the same on here. This is why I
don't waste my time. But listen, Timmy,
I am never coming to Birmingham again.
Ever. You know, the only reason I went
is because [ __ ] Monty was [ __ ]
crying and I felt bad and I thought, let
me take up that opportunity to call you
out. And guess what? You didn't come
out. Just like all of the other timeless
people, you know, when I've gone to
these people's cities and they don't
come out, you know, it's pointless. So,
at the end of the day, mate, if you've
really got a problem, you and Mike, you
can easily come to London and I will um
I will, you know, pay for your train
fair. Stop telling people to come to
Birmingham for [ __ ] sake. You and
Monty have been [ __ ] going back and
forth now for [ __ ] what, four or five
months yet? None of you's met each
other. You've not gone on his door,
which I don't know how you've not gone
on his door when you knew where he
lived. I've come to Birmingham myself
and called you out and you haven't come
out and you're still coming on YouTube
trying to call people out. Timmy, you're
not about that life. You know, I've come
to Birmingham last month. I called you
out. You was nowhere to be seen. Stop
with the big man [ __ ] talk cuz you're
not about it. You know, simple. You
you prime [ __ ] Mike and all of them.
You was nowhere to be [ __ ] seen when
I was in Birmingham last [ __ ] month.
You're all the [ __ ] same. [ __ ]
pathetic. Pathetic, man. Stop doing
videos of me, you [ __ ] idiot.