Yo. Okay, so time for a new video. And
boy, do I have some things to get off my
chest. So, I thought what better way to
than lump all of my thoughts into one
video, make a good video, and basically
think out loud as I talk.
Um, so yeah, I'm going to start with the
whole dating thing and then I'm going to
move on to a few other different things
because it's not all going to be about
dating and women. But so I went out
yesterday um drinking um trying to meet
a woman um approaching women. I had a
good night to be fair. Um and to be fair
um it was my first time out in about a
month. The last time I went out before
that was um the Sunday before my mom's
birthday. Um I was in a couple of weeks
and I thought, you know what, let me go
out and get a roast dinner, have a few
Guinnesses and you know, try and meet um
a woman, approach some women as a single
person should do if if they want to try
and meet somebody. And yeah, I had
nothing better to do. So I thought why
not go out and have some fun. So, I done
a couple of approaches and I met this
woman from Finland and she seemed all
right, responding nicely, no ignoring,
she seemed down to earth, she didn't
seem stuck up, she seemed just all
right, you know, and she said to me that
if I went to Finland that she would meet
me. Um, she agreed to it. And then out
of the blue, she hit me with, "Oh, um,
yeah, I've just I'm seeing I'm meeting
somebody I like and I want to see um how
it goes." Um,
so yeah, wishing you all the best. I was
like, "Oh no, here we go again. Why
can't you just meet somebody that
doesn't play games or doesn't lead you
on?" I mean it's this is part of the
reason why I stopped um for that month
is because it was always the same old
you know you would go and try and
approach a woman and you know she would
say she has a boyfriend when nine times
out of 10 she doesn't or they give you
attitude when you approach or they just
walk away or they give you their number
and lead you on for their own
entertainment. And to be honest with you
it was getting depressing. Um, and I was
like, you know, I'm going to take a
break, go on a detox, um, save a bit of
money and just take a break from it all
because everybody needs a break once in
a while. And breaks do you good. Um,
that's the whole point of them. And then
yesterday, I decided to go out and try
again. Um, because it had been a month
and I thought, yeah, I had some money on
the side. I won a football bet. That's
how I had cash. I never carry cash on
me. So, I had cash on the side. So, I
thought, do you know what? I want to go
out today. I want to have fun. I want to
try and meet a woman. Um, but I want to
look my absolute best. Like, there's no
point putting 50% into something when
you can put 100% into something. So, I
went to the barbers, got a full service, eyebrows,
you know, hair, beard, got my face
waxed, uh, got a face mask, um, you
know, just got the full service and the
barber done a good job and, you know, I
paid good money. So, ready to go out,
looking good, smelling good, all that
good stuff. So, went into central London
and I approached
10 women. Um, the first one um said that
she was married. She gave me a bit of
attitude. The others just didn't really
say much. The other said that she had a
boyfriend. And to be fair, the first one
I done, I was a bit apprehensive because
I hadn't done it for, you know, a month.
So, I was trying to get back into the um
get back into it basically because where
I hadn't done it for so long. But yeah,
I done the 10 approaches and just no one
was interested. Um and like I've said
many times before, you know, if you can
barely get a conversation out of a
woman, I don't know where this so called
hope people are telling you you have
actually is unless I'm missing
something. But then I thought, okay,
whatever. It's just approaching on the
street. Maybe they don't want to talk
because they're in a rush or, you know,
whatever. Maybe they think you're trying
to sell something or whatever the case
may be. The night, well, the day is
still very young. We got all day. We're
going to go to some pubs. We're going to
go to some clubs. We're going to go to
some bars. And hopefully our luck
changes um you know, as as as the day or
night rather progresses. And you know,
you you you would think that somebody
looking their best and being confident
and trying and putting effort into this
as well as money, you would have thought
that you would get you would find a
woman that at least gives you a chance.
Um that's what you would think, but
reality the reality is it isn't like
that. So in the end um I made some new
friends. I met my friend and I got 10
women's numbers. Like they're real
numbers. Um and I didn't think I was
going to get 10 numbers to be fair. I
was thinking I was going to get maybe
three. Um I broke my record by getting
10 numbers. Um I was like, "Wow, Jesus
Christ." Um maybe where I hadn't been
out for so long, I enjoyed it more when
I actually did. Um cuz the less you do
something, the more you enjoy it when
you actually do do it. So maybe it was
that. But I got 10 numbers and yeah, my
record was eight before that. But it
it's not like I'd go out every week and
get eight numbers. It's normally about
three or four. But the fact I got 10
numbers, I was proud of myself. So, you
know, you have to give yourself credit
where credit is due. You went out, you
looked your best, you done your best,
you smelt your best. What more can one
possibly do? Um, and I feel like deep
down that's one of the reasons why I'm
not too annoyed because I know I tried
and there's nothing else I could have
done. I gave it my all and that's all I
could do. So, to be honest with you, I
didn't think anything was going to come
out of them numbers because the way I
see it is I've been dealing with this
for years. You know, a woman giving me
her number, playing mind games, leading
me on. Um, and I don't expect all of a
sudden it's going to be any different
now. And I'd be a fool, too, you know.
But having said that, I did think some
of them would reply to be fair. I did
actually think some of them would have
replied. Not one woman replied. Yeah,
I'm not not even joking. Like I
generally don't think people um believed
me when I said that. So I don't know
where this said hope is people are
trying to feed me. I mean think about
yesterday. Even if you wanted to erase
all of the past things that I've done,
you know, going to this city, that city,
approaching thousands and thousands of
women, even if you wanted to erase that
and forget about that and just use
yesterday. Take yesterday for example. I
went out looking my best, doing my best,
smelling my bre best. I got 10 numbers
and not even one woman had the decency
to reply back. But yet somehow people
think that one day I'm going to
magically meet a woman and be with a
woman and fall in love. To me, it's just
not realistic. I mean, at the end of the
day, I wasn't expecting I was going to
get married to any of these numbers or
have kids with any of these numbers as
soon as I met them. I did think one of
them would have at least gave me a
chance. They would have at least like
accepted a date, you know, next week. I
would have been happy with that. you
know, wherever the date went. I would
have been like, "Okay, you put effort
into it. You got a date. Whatever
happens happens." The fact that I didn't
even get a date with is how much. And I
done a lot of approaches. A lot of
approaches. Like, it's not even a joke.
Um, my feet are still hurting to be
honest. My ankle, my shin from all that
walking. Um, and I don't even have a
single date lined up. That tells you all
you need to know. Um, at the end of the
day, right, you get these women that
say, "We can't find someone. We can't
find someone. We can't find someone."
Um, yet they will go on multiple dates a
month. Whereas, I used this example to a
woman before that I could go out every
week and I wouldn't even get one date a
month. Whereas yesterday is probably
about a month's worth. Uh, probably
about a month's worth. Like, you know,
if I went out every week, I probably
would get about 10 12 numbers at the end
of the month. So, yesterday I got 10
numbers. I don't even have a date and my
feet are hurting, my shin's hurting.
Whereas these women, they can just get a
date whenever um they want and it's
crazy. And I know they're picky and I
know they're looking for Mr. Perfect.
But the the fact of the matter is if you
can't even get a date lined up and don't
forget a date doesn't mean anything.
That's the first step to establishing
whether two people are on the same level
and connect. If you can't even get a
date with the amount that you're trying
and the effort you're putting in, I
don't think they're interested in this
country. Um, that's just the way I see
it. I mean, it's not like, you know, you
went out yesterday and you got two
numbers or three numbers or you didn't
look your best because then I'd be like,
okay, that's just normal, you know, if
you get three numbers and they don't go
anywhere. At the same time, I did enjoy
yesterday. It was a good night out. I
don't regret it. I respect myself for
trying, but that is [ __ ] up, bro. I
can't lie to you. Like, to get 10
numbers and not even get a single date,
that is disgusting. Like, there's
there's no other word to describe it.
But then a woman doesn't even need to
try to even get a date. Whereas me, I
had to look my best, pay the barber good
money, I've almost got broken feet with
all of the trying I've done, and I don't
have a single date lined up.
Crazy, isn't it? very very very crazy.
So I mean I would love to know where
this socalled hope um where this
so-called hope rather is um it might be
in a in a in a chess chest and I don't
have the key to it because I can't see
any hope trying to find somebody in this
country and that's my god's honest um
truth. It is disgusting how not one of
them women even had the decency to
apply. That is bad. That is really
really really bad. and I looked my best,
done my best, wasn't fat, don't look
ugly. Um, and that still wasn't good
enough. So, I mean, but like I said, I
respect myself for trying, for actually
going out there and trying. Now, here's
another thing, right?
Another thing that annoys me about this
country is not just the dating game.
It's does anyone else feel like you can't
go and do anything normal without
hiccups in this country? And what I mean
by that is after I went out approaching
um last night, I went to um the escort
house. Let's just call it an escort
house. And we made a deal, right? Cuz
obviously I like [ __ ] So I'll give
you £100, you give me a [ __ ] I get
to finish. Um not going to get into
details, but basically she agreed to it.
You give money, you get a service.
That's business, right? Like that's
normally how business is. So midway
while she was giving me a [ __ ] she's
like, "Oh, you can't finish. Um, like
you have to finish yourself off." I'm
not going to get into details, but I was
like, "No, I gave you £100. We made a
deal." The same the things she's saying
would have cost about
£70, £80. Um, whereas obviously if you
want to finish it cost a bit more, you
know, some of them don't like people
finishing in their mouth, whatever.
Okay. And I was like, "No, I want half
my money back." Cuz obviously I'd
already done stuff. And she was like,
"No." I was like, "No, I want half my
money back." we agreed and you um you
agreed to it and now you're saying that
I can't do this and it it literally
became a big thing. Like in the end I
got half the money back what I wanted
but somebody could have seriously got
hurt um yesterday and it's like what the
[ __ ] Why does it have to be like that?
Listen, you should have just been able
to have gone out yesterday, do some
approaches, right? Go and get an escort.
No bumpy rides along the road, no
hiccups, no problems. Get the service
that you paid for. Message one of the
numbers yesterday, um, the next day,
which is today, and schedule a date with
a woman. Why is there always got to be
hiccups in this country? And that's not
the only thing as well. Like there's I'm
I'm going to I'm going to um give you
another few examples. It's like
yesterday should have been you get a few
women's numbers, you schedule a date
with one of these women, you use an
escort, you pay the money, you get the
service. Why has there always got to be
problems? To be fair, there wasn't a
problem that big before. There's never
really problems, but there's always a
problem. You go on the bus, you get some
entitled [ __ ] can't mind their own
business. You go to work, you get
entitled [ __ ] that can't mind their
own business. Um, have to get involved
with [ __ ] Um, you know, you go to the
cinema, right? Um, here's another thing.
Um, I went to the cinema um earlier um
whilst I was waiting for the numbers to
apply because I thought that at least
one of them was going to have the
decency to reply. Went to the cinema as
I do. I love horror films.
The machine wasn't working.
Like it's the machine was not working. I
had to wait 15 minutes for them to put
the Pepsi in the cup, right? And then I
and then they downsize the picker mix to
something so small for the price that
you've paid. Why has there always got to
be hiccups? Why can't you just go out
one day and have a normal day without
any problems, any, you know, you can't
even go to work without there being
hiccups? You know, it's it's it's like I
I I really don't understand it. Why
can't think It just feels like there's
nothing normal in this country and it
generally feels like everything is
designed to irritate you. like um you
know the dating game, the waiting around
for things, the government, the you know
the it's crazy like it honestly is you
know the waiting around for things like
I could have missed my film yesterday if
they weren't if they took any longer you
know at the end of the day because it
was coming out water instead of Pepsi.
It's like there's always got to be
hiccups in this country. Like I I can't
explain it. It's just like I don't know
man. I don't know if anyone else is also
in a bad mood living in this country,
but I mean, the dating game's [ __ ] in
it. You got to wait around for
everything. There's always got to be
problems. The escort, for example, how
about you just pay for a service, get
the service, you get the service, they
get the money, done. It's like there's
always got to be hiccups with with with
a lot of the things that you do. You
can't just go out and have a normal day
at the cinema or use an escort and get
the service that you pay for or go out
and meet a woman and get a date and see
where it goes. It can never ever be a a
stressfree day or thing without hiccups.
Um, and that's another thing that annoys
me about this country. It really,
really, really does. Um, it feels like
it generally is designed to irritate
you. Um, it it really does. Like it's
it's crazy. So, that's what I wanted to
share. Um, dating game still messed up.
I still can't believe that, um, not one
of them women replied. Um, that's
insane. You would have thought one of
them would have at least had a decency.
Um, and that's it. I'm going to go to
bed now because I'm still tired from
last night's effort. Um, which got me no
in the end. But like I said, I can sleep
well tonight knowing that I tried and I
put effort into it. Um, but yeah, that's
my video anyways. So, hope you enjoyed
it and yeah, there we go.