Yo, just before I rip into these little
um weirdos like, yeah, this is one of
the reasons why I don't come on YouTube
anymore because it's just the same
repeating low lives that have just been
doing this for years. And to be honest
with you, it's kind of embarrassing to
watch these people embarrass themselves
every single day and just keep bullying
themselves year in year out, year in
year out. Cuz come on, bro. Let's be
realistic about this. These people are
proper proper life bully victims. Like
they do not come on YouTube every single
day repeating themselves and hating
because their lives are so good and
they've got more than this person. Like
their lives are in the shambles. And
anyone that they hate on deep down it it
is literally jealousy. Like it it
literally is. And everyone knows that
you know I hate using that word but what
else could it really really point to?
And you know, I'm not even a
psychologist, but anyways. Um, so you
put up an advert when I'm selling a
fridge and I'm selling a a washing
machine. Yeah, that's kind of what
people do when they move house, you
[ __ ] [ __ ] Um, if you actually left
your mom's bedsit, you [ __ ] virgin.
Um, you'd actually know. But here's the
thing. Am I selling my TV? No. Am I
selling my Xbox that you don't have? No.
Am I selling my designer clothes that's
worth more than your whole life? No.
Like, bro, come on. You put the word
skint with multiple T's. That's cute.
Was I the one that showed £6,000 and
made you and Lord J's followers run away
continuously because your 300 above
benefits does not stretch to that. Yeah,
it happened on more than one occasion.
Bro, when you write skin and this and
that and the other, you're only talking
about yourself. You're only hurting
yourself. Like we come to the conclusion
that when you were shown money numerous
times and you failed to show any money
back that the fact that you can't take a
day off of YouTube, bro, you're only
talking about yourself. Like ugly, fat,
bald, skinn, it's all yourselves. That's
exactly why you're on YouTube every day
doing what you do. There's no other
explanation, you know? I mean, [ __ ]
You've been doing this all summer as
well. If you have all this money and all
this life, why are you on this community
doing what you do every day, it's not
looking right, as a young man would say,
see, and you know, they come on here
every day, these sad little 40year-olds
hating. And deep down, it's jealousy.
Like, I I personally think if I was to
put money on it, I'd say it's probably
cuz you're better looking than them. Um,
you still got more money than them,
believe it or not. Um, and obviously
you're young. They're old virgins, no
friends, no family. So this application
is literally all these people have in
their life. Um and um the other thing is
is like I can show these people money
again and again and again and again and
again, but bro, we've done it again and
again and again and again. And how many
times you going to keep showing money to
these skint people who don't have any
money themselves, which is why they
continuously call people skint because
they're talking about their own lives.
You know, they've been they've been
doing it for years. I mean, you don't
need to show people money a million
times. They ain't got none. Get the
point, bro? They ain't got nothing to
show. And then they will do this for
years and years and years. I feel bad
for them. I mean, think of it, bro. Look
at this little [ __ ] He's been doing
this for [ __ ] years. Like, bro, we
all know deep down that you put a
picture up of me because I'm a million
times better looking than you. I've had
more women than you. And bro, if you're
sat here trying to make fun out of my
looks, that's cute. That's okay. Why
don't you show your face? Because here's
the difference. If I was on a community
flaming somebody about their looks every
day, and someone said, "Well, why don't
you show your face?" Bro, I would show
my face and prove that I'm better
looking. But that's the difference. You
can't do that because you're a um you're
a fat ugly bastard.
That's why you can't show your face.
Like all of this stalking is cute. It's
just jealousy. It just goes to show that
you really want to be me. Like you're so
tormented every single day you have to
sit on the internet being obsessed with
me cuz deep down you know I'm better
looking than you and I've got a better
life than you. Because think about it,
bro. Read go back to what you said. You
said that I'm skinned. Okay, I'm skint,
but you're the one sat on YouTube every
day stalking me on a hot summer's day.
So, think about it, bro. Who is the real
skint fat Goldilocks virgin? It's your
[ __ ] self. And guess what? Any reply
that you write back? You're going to
look stupid cuz you can't show your
face. So, bro, it's cute. It really,
really is embarrassing.
And then you got this little Milton Kees
keyboard warrior that literally runs up
his mouth on the internet and then when
he gets called out, he shits his pants.
Again, another reason not to entertain
them. And another thing is they seek
attention from men online because their
lives are [ __ ] Their lives are empty.
So that's why they need attention. They
need people making videos on them. It's
because they have nothing without
YouTube. Like anyone who's watching
this, go monitor this prick's channel.
You will see it's the same people every
day. They have nothing in life but
YouTube and their mom's bedsit and their
300 pound benefits. Believe you me, bro,
the truth always comes out from Peter
Belly. Did I weren't I the first one
that said bomb was projecting and guess
what [ __ ] was right again. Yeah,
these people are low lives. Like you
wouldn't even find these kind of people
on the street. Well, of course you
would. They've all got anxiety. They
don't leave the house. You wouldn't find
these kind of [ __ ] low lives on the
street. And then right, you got this
[ __ ] [ __ ] He's talking about, "Oh
yeah, Uber money girlfriend Thailand."
Talking about themselves again. These
people have been proven to be in their
40s. These people have proven to be
skin. These people have proven to be
ugly numerous times. They only talk
about theirelves. So they've again their
disability the disability that they
suffer with which what they get their
benefits for it confuses them with other
people. So when they're saying that
you're they're sure that they're just
talking about themselves and they prove
you right every day cuz they can't get
off YouTube. It's something that they
can't do. But anyways, back onto this
[ __ ] Um this guy's coming on here
calling me skin again. It's cute. Wasn't
this the same guy that was begging for
drinks in Weather Spoons wearing a plain
black t-shirt? Wait, wait, hold on.
Wasn't this the same guy, bro, that went
live in Weather Spoons getting people to
pay for his drinks? Huh? Yeah. I think
the Skint one is you, matey. I think the
Skint one is is definitely definitely
you. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, like I said,
when I was showing £6,000,
no one was anywhere to be seen. Didn't
it take you 10 years to save up to go to
Vegas? Brother, it's not looking right.
You're coming online like calling people
skin, yet you're in Weather Spoons,
begging for drinks, wearing a black
t-shirt. Bro, I'm not going to lie, it
ain't looking right. As a young man once
said, like, bro, you really, really need
to get a life. Get off of YouTube. Stop
bullying yourself. I'm going to I'm
literally going to title this. Yeah,
these people need to stop bullying
themselves because I'm starting to feel
bad for them. Like, at first there was
something to laugh at, but now I'm
really starting to feel bad. It's bad
enough that they get bullied every
single day in real life that they have
to come on here um and self-reflect to
make themselves feel less bullied. You
see, then they don't win an argument
against me when they're not talking over
people. I have these people to a t-bone
steak. They're so predictable. They're
spastics. But they really, really need
to stop bullying people. I'm going to
set up a GoFundMe for these people in
desperate need of a life. You know how
you never get to see the children in
need? These people are in desperate need
for a [ __ ] life, mate. The next
advert that comes on the TV, I'm going
to put it as these people are in
desperate need for a life. I'm starting
to feel bad. I really am, bro.