Yo. Okay, so I finally got a response
back. Fair play, man. I generally didn't
think I was going to um you know, see
today, you know, with it being a week
and a half. Still haven't heard from
this guy. I was starting to get very,
very, very worried. Um I was, you know,
almost half an inch away from leaving
the Little Britain shop because I was
sick of waiting. I was just standing
there waiting for for a response back um
because I'd sent him two emails over a
week ago and I wasn't hearing anything
back and I I was generally generally um
generally getting worried because you
know I don't really like mysteries and
things that remain mysteries and never
knowing the answers. But saying that um
I still haven't got the answers because
the email that he has just sent me has
got no relation or no involvement to any
of the two previous emails I had sent
him and what I had asked him. Um, quick
uh little friendly tip here, LT. If you
are going to project your ugliness and
your disabledness and your runess onto
me in the future, which is what you're
doing on here, you might want to answer
the questions that I had asked you
before doing so. Um, bit bit of a bit of
a friendly tip because that way you
don't look like a complete dumpy. Just
just a bit of advice there um for you.
So, um, yeah. So, quick disclaimer.
Yeah. Before I get into this, um, now I
sent this guy two emails. Didn't mention
his race. Didn't mention his looks.
Didn't mention his mom. Didn't mention
his dad. Didn't mention his cousin.
Didn't mention Didn't mention his mom.
Didn't sorry, didn't mention his
brother. Didn't mention his sister. I
didn't mention any of that stuff. I
didn't mention his child, which he don't
have. I'll say it. If no one else is
going to say it, I'll say it. I don't
believe this guy has got children.
Whether he does, whether he doesn't, I
don't personally believe he does. He
hasn't proved not even 10% of the stuff
that he claims he's got. And it doesn't
really matter. Kids was not u mentioned.
I simply asked him, "Why is it that
every single time that I call non legs a
virgin, you're straight to his rescue?
He's got a girlfriend, man. He's got a
girlfriend." And you start having like a
panic attack. Meanwhile, when he's
calling me a virgin, you don't bring up
the video of me getting a [ __ ] The
19-year-old who I had a friend with
benefits with when I was in bed with
this one. when I was in bed naked with
that one when I had this one and that
one admitted to sleeping with me. It
just seemed a bit it just seemed a bit
biased. Obviously LT is not the only
one. A lot of people do it on here. Um
you know because me and Nons used to
have this back and forth. Yo, obviously
I don't waste my time on these jealous
people anymore because I had a long
think to myself which I'll I would
explain in this video as well. Um you
know a bit later, but we always used to
call each other virgins. And every
single time I'd call him a virgin,
people jumped to his rescue saying he's
got a girlfriend. and he's got a
girlfriend. When they should really be
wondering is not how somebody that's got
a fat, ugly girlfriend can be a virgin,
but how somebody like me who's actually
prove they've had sex could be a virgin.
But you never heard anything about that,
did you? No, there was loads of
different excuses and load of different
agendas as to why. Now, I had asked this
uh question previously um before, but
obviously I felt like I was going back
and forth with these people because they
didn't have the brain power to um answer
it and they didn't answer it and I was
just going back and forth. So, I
thought, okay, now is my my perfect
opportunity to ask LT um because
obviously he's being biased and well,
he's got a degree. Oh, sorry, let me
rephrase that. He claims he's got a
degree because he this guy does not have
any degree of any kind. I'm more
intelligent than him. Um, and um, you
know, don't let him don't let him don't
let him try and fool you into thinking
he's got a degree. I don't class myself
as intelligent, but I'm much more
intelligent than he is. Um, and yeah, so
I I just asked him, "Why are you being a
why you being a biased [ __ ] if you're I
said to him as well like, "Your
boyfriend is calling me a virgin. Why
are you not talking about the women that
I've been with? Why you not talking
about the porno? Why are you not
bringing about the bringing up the
million and two times that I have proven
I've had sex, but yet you're you're
you're talking about a fat ugly
girlfriend. Then he come up with these
excuses saying, "Bro, you showed a
[ __ ] You showed a [ __ ] I mean,
yeah, I showed a [ __ ] on video. A
[ __ ] 99 times out of 100 leads to
sex." Yeah, bro. I did. A [ __ ] is is
more proof than showing a fat, ugly
girlfriend. um a couple of times. So, I
thought, "Yeah, that's that's that's
more than showing the fat ugly
girlfriend." Then it was an excuse of,
"Oh, no, it don't count." Uh because you
you paid you paid you you paid them. I
was like, "Pay them?" Well, I paid every
single woman that I've been with. So, I
paid Sig. I paid a woman in Manchester.
I paid a 19year-old. I paid uh I paid
all of these people. And then there's
been many, many more people as well, but
they're they're just the ones that come
to mind. So, I paid every single one of
these women women and somehow that does
not count. Well, I'm going to pretend
that you're right and I'm going to agree
with you. Yes, bro. I'm a millionaire
and I paid every single one of these women
a million pounds to sleep with me and
that's still more proof than showing a
fat ugly girlfriend. So, you're very,
very low IQ and some of the things that
you say don't even make sense. I was
being uh I was being sarcastic there.
Obviously, I didn't pay these women, but
I mean, bro, okay, I paid I paid every
single woman a million pound to get with
me. Yeah, that's more than a fat, ugly
girlfriend that you ain't even seen give
a [ __ ] And that's [snorts] the whole
biasness. Um, they're fast enough to
jump down my throat when I'm going for
uh non-slegs and calling him a virgin,
even though they've got no proof that
he's done anything technically. Um, and
I was just thinking, yeah, like if a
[ __ ] is no proof, um, then a
girlfriend is no proof. Um, it sounds
immature, but this is the only way to
prove that these people are biased. Um,
and what I found was very strange is
that this guy claims he doesn't like
cowards. He's had his own problems with
non legs. Um, and he would still
continuously um, defend and stick up for
him. Um, which is very very strange cuz
he has actually had his own problems
with him. He says that he doesn't like
cowards. He says that I'm a coward even
though nons is more of a coward than I
could ever be. Um, but then he's
sticking up for him. And before you sit
there and say you're not, cuz I already
know what he's going to try and say
back. Before you sit there and try and
say, "Oh, you're not sticking up for
him." You're only saying what's right.
But you're not though, are you? Because
I'm pretty sure this guy calls me a
virgin every single day. And you never
talk about the women that I've proven
I've had sex with and not just a fat
ugly girlfriend. And obviously because
he knows that I'm right, he's come
trying to insult me and all of this
[ __ ] So, um, yeah, this guy does not
have no degree of any kind. Um he's he's
he he really really doesn't. So let's
get on to the [ __ ] that you're writing.
Yeah. I have had enough of your
[ __ ] Of my [ __ ] What [ __ ]
What have I done other than ask you why
you're a biased [ __ ] and why you keep
defending your boyfriend? I've had I've
had enough of your bias [ __ ] Um but
you don't see me crying about it. You
know, I had to wait over a week for your
response, right? And he was like, "Stop
emailing me, ma. I will do what I want."
Um, firstly, you don't tell me what to
do, right? You email me about Jane. You
email me about Mark. I've never told you
to stop emailing me. So, don't [ __ ]
try and tell me what I can and can't
[ __ ] do. That's one thing you're not
going to do, right? Don't even try to
tell me what to do, cuz that is just not
happening, bro. That is just not
happening. Right, ma? Yeah. Okay. I'm a
ma. Yeah, but I mean, we know I'm better
looking than you. We know you got a big
forehead. We know you got big bobbly
eyes. We know that you beg old women on
YouTube. So, am I really the m bro or is
or is it you? Let's think about it
logically. Am I really the m or is it LT
the one that has to beg women on the
internet? I mean, think about it. Yeah,
you came on the scene about 2 and 1/2
weeks ago when I was going at Autumn
Rose because she was going at me. There
is no coincidence that you've just
appeared on that very video of all the
ones that I've done and then you've
chose to get involved. Bro, you're if
you're this good-looking guy and I'm the
M, then why has a M never had to beg old
women on YouTube, bro? Like you answer.
Everyone wants to know it cuz no one
else is going to say it, so I'll say it. Go on.
You are a [ __ ] and you will continue to
be a [ __ ] forever. You sick loner. I'm
I'm a sick loner, bro. You're the guy
that has to pretend that you got kids.
You're the one that's got got to pretend
that you've got a family. You're the one
that's got to beg women on the internet.
Does Does anything you say to me not
apply about yourself, bro? And this is a
funny this this was a funny one as well.
28 years old and you still live under
your granny's mother's armpits. Um bear
mind I haven't said anything about he's
fab you or anything. I will be doing now
because he is he he's talking about me.
Right. You have no children. [laughter]
[ __ ] me. That is he really using that as
an insult? This is a guy that claims
he's got a degree by the way. He claims
he's saying that you've got no children.
Bro, that's a blessing in disguise if
someone's got no children in this
[ __ ] age. I generally feel sorry for
people that's got children in this day
and age. Imagine a rap battle. Yeah.
Imagine two people rapping and one
saying you got no children. Did you even
think before he wrote that the [ __ ]
dumpty? No relationship, bro. You ain't
got a relationship yourself. That's why
you beg old women on all the women that
you beg on the internet. They ain't even
nice. Yeah, that's the funny thing about
it. You've been caught wanking in public
and get tormented by everyone. Now, you
know when you said, "I get tormented by
everyone." Let me just let me just let
me just explain this to you, bro. Yeah,
you are very very lucky that I'm
responding to you today. You know, I'm
done with all of these people, you know,
nonslegs, all of these self-p projectors
and all of these people. I'm completely
done with them. I was live yesterday. I
ignored them all. Yeah. You are very
very lucky that you're getting a
response. And you know why I don't reply
to these people the same as you is
because I started to notice a pattern
with people like Terry Nons legs LJ all
of the rest of them that do this [ __ ]
every day is that they're all ugly.
They're all scruffy. None of them look
good. None of them got anything but
YouTube. They're on YouTube 24/7. That's
why I don't care. Like you can sit there
and say that you bully people, that you
torment people, but we see the real you.
We see what you do and what use look
like. And when a when a pattern starts
going straight and hold on, this one's
ugly, that one's ugly, that one's a
faroot [ __ ] that one's missing teeth,
it explains why you people do what you
do every day. So stuff like that does
not bother me. I've only replied to you
because I've been waiting for ages for
you to reply to me. And after this, I'm
going to be off YouTube for 2 weeks. Me
replying to you today is equivalent to
about £10,000 because my time you you're
very lucky I'm responding to you. Very
lucky cuz I don't respond to self
projectors anymore. So consider yourself
lucky. You have not got the balls to see
anyone in person. Again, bro, I've met
more people than you. I've traveled
England more than you. I've been to more
places than you. How does that even make
any sense? How are you telling someone
that's tried to meet more people than
you that they're never going to meet
anyone? And then he comes out with this
[ __ ] Tiger pounded your big nose
into a sold mattress. I mean, A, bro,
this was about 5 years ago. You're
boring now. And and B, that's not what
happened. And I'm not explaining the
story over and over again. You can keep
thinking that happened cuz you got your
own little gender. Just like how legs
can't be a virgin because he's got a fat
ugly girlfriend, but someone like me
can. Someone that's produced a po. You
keep telling yourself that and living
four or five years ago, bro, in the past
cuz no one cares. You bloody crippled
disabled melt. The only one that's
crippled and disabled is yourself, bro.
Yeah. Your head is too big for your dad
bod and your father and brother off
themselves having up. Why don't you show
everybody what you look like instead of
saying and typing words about what other
people look like? Because the thing is
with you people, yeah, you've got a lot
to say about people and the way that
they look. But isn't it just so funny
how the people that show themselves and
the people that get caught out in the
end all seem to be ugly. All the same
people like you that's got a lot to say.
Why do you think it doesn't bother us,
bro? We know what you people are. We
know what you people are like.
Disclaimer. That's another disclaimer
for you. Right. And then you said your
dad bod and your father and brother off
themselves. Bro, you're very touchy. I
hit a nerve. I think it's because you
know that I'm right. You know that I'm
more intelligent than you. And you know
what I'm saying is is is right about you
defending your boyfriend. You know,
you're very very touchy about your
boyfriend talking about dead relatives
now and [ __ ] All because I told you
that you suck your boyfriend's dick
every time I call him a virgin. Cuz it's
the truth. I wasn't trying to be nasty
or get a reaction. I'm telling the
truth. You know, you bloody [ __ ]
disabled mess your head. Okay, we read
that. Uh, so for your dad, B and your
father and brother off themselves. No,
they didn't because having your fight
family in their DNA meant they are weak
specimens of deproable semen. Now, you
can say what you want about my family
and whatever, but guess what? My
family's never needed backup like yours.
My mom never needed backup back in the
day. My dad never needed backup when the
[ __ ] was still alive. I've never ever
needed backup. So, guess what, bro? The
Taylor family needs backup, but the
Fight family just never did. They just
never did, bro. The Taylor Swift family
did, but the Fight family, that's one
thing. We never ever ever ever ever
needed backup. I mean, [ __ ] Laney was
more [ __ ] harder than you back in the
day. Would you think that the Taylor
family has always needed backup? Now,
you can tell everybody all you want
about how you've tried meeting people
solo before, but you failed to tell
everyone how many times you had four or
five people standing outside that front
[ __ ] door because you could not fight
your own battles. Yeah. You failed to
mention these times. You like to mention
the times where you turned up by
yourself. You never fail to mention it,
but you failed to mention the times that
you needed backup with your Greek
friend, with your cousin. That's what
the Taylor family induces, backup.
something the fight family never needed.
Yeah, I will take you serious when you
have the guts to let me put those paws
all over your bog eyes, brother. Again,
the only one that's got you your eyes
are like a you know them black fishes
with the the the poppy eyes. That's what
your eyes are like. You got a big
forehead. You got a dirty for [ __ ]
hairline. Don't even try to talk about
someone that's better looking than you,
bro. Yeah. And again, if you really are
really good-looking and I'm ugly, why
are you begging ass women online, bro?
Why are you begging old hags? I've never
known in my life. And another thing is,
bro, yeah, since you want to talk about
family members. You are not known in any
hood. You're not known in Tottenham.
You're not known anywhere in London.
You're just a pretender. No one knows
about you. All you've done is stumbled
across a community with a bunch of
weaklings, not myself included. And
you've took that in. You've took
advantage of that. You've used that to
your advantage. You're not about that
life. You'll never be about that life.
Why do you think you're online in 2026
still doing the hard man act, bro? Why?
Come on, tell us. It's the truth. What
I'm saying is the truth. And you could
never put your paws all over my bog
eyes. It wouldn't You wouldn't even be
able to put your hands on me, bro.
You're talking. All you do is live four
or five years in the past. That's all
you do. You could never ever put your
hands on a guy like me, bro. Keep
dreaming. You're not worth it. You know,
you're lucky that you even got got my
response. But I will not count on it
because M was born a top tier fan.
Again, you're calling me a M when I'm
better looking. You know, every single
Do you know the funny thing is? Yeah.
Every single person on here that tries
to call me a mon, I'm better looking
than do you not find that strange? Terry
Nonss, all of the people that do you not
find the pattern very straight and
weird? All of these people that seem to
do this are [ __ ] stinking ugly. I I
found that weird. [snorts] So, top tier,
have fun spouting crap online as usual,
you stinking bedroom hunchback disabled
mun. No one's spilling crap, you [ __ ]
bogey gorilla looking [ __ ] We're just
stating how you're biased. Yeah, just
because you don't like the truth, don't
start crying to me, bro. Don't start
crying to me. Simple as that. And that's
the last response you're getting off me.
You're very, very lucky I got a
response. Uh, and you got a response.
Sorry, you biased bastard. See you later. Done.