What are you going to do to me? What are
you going to do, bro? I'll give you a
punch right in my face. Go on. Go on.
Punch me. Punch me in my face. Right
here, bro. Come on. Come on. Come on.
>> Punch me in my face. Come on. You don't
scare me, bro. You don't scare me, bro.
>> You don't scare me, bro. Huh? You're a
[ __ ] [ __ ] Punch me in my face. Go
on. Go on. I'll turn you upside down.
You little [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] off, you
[ __ ] You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
asking a 28-y old for ID and I'm
probably older than you, you stupid little [ __ ]
>> I've just thought you just done what
you've done there.
>> Go on. What are you going to do? What
are you gonna do, bro? What are you
gonna do to me, bro? Go on.
>> You never do that to me.
>> Exactly. It's a suck your mom, bro. [ __ ]
>> What are you going to do? Are you going
to do something?
>> Don't. What are you going to do?
What are you going to do, bro? You're
going to do nothing cuz you're a little
[ __ ] You're a little [ __ ] Listen,
bro. Let me Let me understand this, bro.
Yeah. I understand you're doing your job.
I'll take your number.
>> Huh? I'll take your number and we can do
this after work.
>> You're not going to do nothing to me, bro. >> Yeah.
>> Listen. What are you going to do?
>> Exactly. Cuz you're a [ __ ] [ __ ]
So, [ __ ] you, bro.
>> He's not going to spot me out, bro. He
can try, but he ain't going to spot me out, bro.
>> I'll get I'll get his number and I'll
meet him after work.
>> You do now?
>> Yeah. He's not going to do nothing. I
just called him a dick and I told him to
suck his mother.
>> What are you doing?
>> Yeah, bro. I'm I'm going to see. I'm
showing what a [ __ ] is.
>> And guess what? I told him to suck his
barb and he's not doing that, mate. So,
there you go. >> Huh?
>> You shake your tits off.
>> I'm shaking my tits off. I'm standing
right here, bro.
>> No, you're not. You're
>> No, I'm standing right here, bro. And
he's not going to do nothing.
>> Leave him alone. Look, I'm standing
right in. He's not going to do nothing.
Get yourself drink somewhere else. Have
a good night.
>> No, I'll do what I want. Thank you.
Don't tell me what to do. Thank you. I'll
>> tell you what to do, man.
>> Yeah, I'll do what I want. Don't tell me
what to do.
>> I'll do what I want. Shut the [ __ ] up.
Simple. Oh, you I will do what I want to
do. You're not going to tell me what to
do, man. How about you stop being a
[ __ ] and mind your own business?
>> I'm not I'm talking to him and he's getting involved.
>> And he's getting involved. And he's >> Yeah.
>> Watch this video the next day.
>> And I will know what I'm doing.
That's all you need to do.
>> And you need to stop mind. You need to
mind your own business. Stop getting
involved. Anyway, your
>> I'm talking to him. Yes. And I'll do
what I want. I'm not going to [ __ ] off.
You don't tell me what to do, bro.
>> Yeah. And I'm not taking your advice. I
don't want Yeah. [ __ ] off. Look at you,
bro. Yeah. S
>> I'm shaking. Am I twitching? I'm
standing right here.
>> Yeah. Do yourself a favor, mate. Have a nice night.
>> [ __ ] Go back to New where you come
from, you little son.
>> Okay. Whatever.
>> Yeah. Well, I man. Well, I man [ __ ] off
at where you come from. You silly [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> Where you from?
>> Huh? From London, bro.
>> You [ __ ] off, you silly little [ __ ]
What are you going to do? You're going
to do nothing. So, shut the [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Look at you. You [ __ ] ugly
[ __ ] Look at them traders, mate. My
traders cost more than your outfit.
Don't keep it. Don't keep it. Don't keep my
>> Yeah. Sort your outfit out, you silly
little tra. You silly little them
traders worth more bother than your own
outfit. You silly little tram.
>> [ __ ] silly [ __ ]