Okay, so I'm just about to go live and
I'm going to go live. I'm going to mute
it. Going to go downstairs, make a tea,
and I've unblocked a couple of people by
the way, those people. And I want to see
if it's really these people that have
got no life that are skin hate them. And
let's see if it's these people that's
been projecting all along. Right. Okay.
Maybe I might not mute myself. I just
want to talk.
I'll be on here for 10 minutes maximum
cuz we're going to my sisters today. I'm
busy. Just a little uh little tester.
Okay. Got to go downstairs and make a
tea now. [snorts] Right. Close.
Oh my god,
they're on YouTube. Christmas. I knew
it. Oh my god. I knew it. I've just
walked up the stairs. They got no life.
Oh [ __ ] [ __ ] hell. One second.
They fell into my trap. They're on YouTube.
Oh, they're on YouTube. They're on
YouTube. They're on YouTube. Jesus.
Oh my god. There we go. YouTube
Christmas [ __ ] date. Fill into my
trap. There you go. You got 11 people on
here watching. Look, they're on [ __ ]
YouTube. They got no life. They got no
[ __ ] life. They fell into my [ __ ]
trap. I knew it. I knew these people had
no family. I [ __ ] knew it, boys. I
told my mom I was going to do this as
well. 17 people [ __ ] watching.
They're on [ __ ] YouTube Christmas
Day, yet they talk about other [ __ ]
people. I've planned this since I've
woke up. Yeah, I w to come back until
New Year's. And look, they're on YouTube
typing away. It's so clear. It's them
that they're talking about. I told my
mom I was doing this, by the way. I'd
literally told my mom that before I was
with my sister today, I'm going to go
live. See, look, 17 people and they're
on YouTube. They've got no family. I
[ __ ] knew it, boys. I knew it. I
[ __ ] knew it. You know, they can't
help themselves even on Christmas
[ __ ] day. [ __ ] coming. Yeah.
Telling other people that they got no
[ __ ] family and they don't have this.
And look, look at this idiot. Look at
this idiot. You got 17 people. 18 people
watching. Yeah. Yeah. These people are
supposed to have families. They're
supposed to have money. They're supposed
to have a [ __ ] life. Yeah, mate. It's
bollocks. It's absolutely [ __ ]
bollocks. 18 [ __ ] people lurking.
What the [ __ ] bro? You don't even get
that on a [ __ ] weekend.
Mad, bro. These people are going to be
lonely Christmas. I [ __ ] knew it. I
knew it. I [ __ ] knew it.
Self projection. Self projection. Look,
I told you they fell right into my trap.
They fell right into Peter Belly's trap.
That's all I basically come on here to
say. See if it was the same people on
YouTube. And it is. Same people Christmas Day.
Oh, thank you, man. Thank you so much.
>> Christmas day.
>> Oh, thank you, man.
>> Thank you, man. Thank you. It just shows
that you people ain't got a life and you
ain't got no family. That's all I
basically come on here to [ __ ] prove
to be honest with you. Um, yeah. You
ain't got no life. You ain't got no
family. You ain't got no money. Bunch of
[ __ ] fat, ugly people that ain't got
no life. That's all all I basically come
on here to say really. And look look at
all them lurkers now.