Okay, so this is going to be my response
to the ugly ratfaced toothless virgin
living in a bed sit with no bed in it
with the fat ugly girlfriend. Yeah, you
have to wait for that bit. Um, so yeah,
I saw your uh comment um and you were
saying about um yeah, I've never had a
girlfriend and I'm almost uh 30 and you
know that's saying something. What is it
saying? No, no. Like, what is it
actually saying? You don't actually say
what it's saying. Um, I have had a
girlfriend and I've also had multiple
chances to be in relationships with
multiple different women. All of whom is
not disabled and a the wolf and a
[ __ ] like your girlfriend that can't
even string a [ __ ] sentence together.
Isn't it mad how you really really
really need to uh take a uh you need to
you need to take a closer look to your
bedsit. Now obviously the the saying is
a closer look to home but obviously you
don't have a home. You live in a bedsit.
Um it's funny how you come on here and
you try to call me the incel yet you're
the one that has to resort to disabled
women and I've literally been with the
women that you wish you could be with.
Um, you know what I'm saying? Like all
of the women that I've [ __ ] and I've
shown and I've done [ __ ] with and I've
gone on dates with, but I'm the incel.
Yet you're the one that has to resort to
a [ __ ] disabled girl that can't even
talk. What the [ __ ] Are you [ __ ] for
real right now? If anyone's the incel,
it's [ __ ] you, you weirdo. And then
when you're coming on here trying to You
really really need need to look in the
mirror. You come on here trying to call
me ugly when to be honest with you mate
that ship has already sailed a long time
ago. I think at this point even the
people that don't like me will admit
that I'm a million times better looking
than you. Like even when you're on here
trying to call me ugly. It's like your
face says it all that you you're just
lying to yourself.
It's just to the point where you're
lying to yourself. And in that paragraph
you wrote that I'm going to reply to,
you use the word skin four times, mate.
The only one that is skin is your
[ __ ] self. I've beat you at the money
game every single [ __ ] time. I've got
better clothes than you. I've had a
better life than you. I've got a better
life than you. I'm sat on a bed
something that you can't even afford,
mate. Everything that you try to say
about me is is about yourself. You
[ __ ] skint [ __ ] incel [ __ ]
virgin. Everything you try and say about
me is about your own life. And the
funniest one is when you um say about how
oh you live in your mom's spare room and
ret mate you don't even know who I live
with and you don't even know where I
actually live. You live in a cancelled
shitty bedsit with no bed in it. How you
think that you've got the room to talk
about where anybody else lives and
anybody else's living circumstances is
beyond me. And let me give you a fun
fact right here, right? Most of the
people in London live with their
parents. And I mean both their parents,
their mom and their dad, you know, and I
guess some just live with their mom or
some live with their dad, right? And it
is nowhere near as bad as you're making
it out to be, mate. I've lived by
myself. I've lived with [ __ ] tenants.
I've lived with my mom and the only
reason you think living with your mom is
so bad is because your mom hates you.
And when you lived with your mom, she
starved you and she [ __ ] disowned you
and [ __ ] put you into [ __ ] care at
a young age, mate. It's nowhere near as
bad as you're making it out to be. Um,
you know, maybe your [ __ ] up childhood
makes you think that, but uh, you know,
it's not ideal. It's not exactly ideal,
but there's it's nowhere near as bad as
as you're making out to me. You know, a
lot of people do it for various
different reasons because they need to
they want to save money or whatever.
Like, there's there's nothing wrong with
with living with your mom. Nowhere near
as bad as you're making out to be, you
[ __ ] virgin. You live in a [ __ ]
bed sit with no [ __ ] bed in it.
Living with your mom in a natural house,
mate. You'd actually be winning compared
to your circumstances now. You know what
I'm saying? You you live in a [ __ ]
bedset and you ain't even got a bed and
you're talking about somebody that lives
with a parent who they don't even live
with. Get a [ __ ] grip. Um so onto your paragraph
virgin boy. Um now another thing
actually know before I I start this I I
really wanted to say right that this is
actually being serious now. Um
what is the end goal here? You're never
going to meet anyone, you know? You're
never going to stop this [ __ ] on
YouTube. Are you going to stop this [ __ ]
on YouTube or are you just going to keep
doing it and doing it? Because the thing
is, the more you do this, the more it
just goes to show that you're just a low
life, that you're skin, that you ain't
got anything, the more you do this on
YouTube, what you do every day, it just
shows that you got nothing. Like, that's
all it does. Honestly, it does. Same as
like these 40-year-old self-p projecting
skint weirdos that tried to call other
people half their age what their reality
actually is. Skin, no life, no job, all
the things they tried to put onto you.
Honest to God, yeah, you doing all of
this stuff, it just it just shows you
haven't got anything. And and that is
actually me being serious because
somebody with a life and all this money,
they wouldn't be on there doing this.
It's it's just it's just common sense,
you know, sat on YouTube getting into
cycle or pointless arguments that don't
go anywhere. If you had money and you
weren't skin, you wouldn't be on here
doing this every single day. And you've
already proven to be skimp by myself
many times, just like a lot of people
have. Anyways, [ __ ] it. Onto this [ __ ]
So, um, you was basically saying about
how, uh, yeah, I keep going on about
the, uh, six grand that I've shown once,
um, and 14 grand that you've shown once.
You've never shown 14 grand, not even
once. Because if you did show 14 grand,
you would have shown it when I showed
that six grand. You know, it's just
we're having the same argument over and
over and over and over again. And
there's there's there's no argument for
it. You've been shown money, you
couldn't double it. End off. You lost.
There's no there's no two ways about it.
And then what made me laugh is all of
these excuses that you're coming out
with, right, about why you couldn't show
the 12 grand. Like, oh, well, yeah, the
bank's not going to allow you to show 12
grand. Yes, they would. If you went to
the bank and you wanted your 12 grand
cash, it would take about 3 days for you
to get your 12 grand. It's your money.
They would have to give you your money.
you you are full of excuses. It's like
what Joe was doing um uh yesterday and
the day before. Oh, I didn't have I
didn't have 12 grand um lying about,
mate. The the bank would have gave you
12 grand. You could have easily got it
from the bank in 3 days. So, you using
that as an excuse. It it's it's
ridiculous. It's because you never had
12 grand. It's not because the bank
wouldn't give you it or ret. it's
because you don't have it. So, stop
using excuses like, "Oh, the [ __ ]
bank is not going to give us 12 grand."
And at the end of the day, mate, even if
that was the truth, which it isn't the
truth, you could have easily got a bank
statement out of the hole in the wall.
So, at the end of the day, mate, just
give it up. You know, at the end of the
day, right, it's not the fact that
someone has shown you six grand. It's
the It's the fact that every single time
you have been shown money, you run away.
That's the point. It's not about what
we've [ __ ] shown and the amount of
money that we've shown. It's every
single time you've been shown money. Why
is it that all you people run off?
It's because you have no money because
you are skinned. It's the same argument
over and over and over again. You know,
like [ __ ] take the L in the end, bro.
You know, it's not a big deal. Don't
[ __ ] keep going on like banks
wouldn't give you 12 grand if you wanted
12 grand. Of course they would. 12 grand
is not a big big big big amount. You
know, people, you know, when people buy
cars, you know, a lot of people, you
know, pay thousands in cash. So, all of
this, oh, the bank, you know, it's
[ __ ] mate, because you could have
easily got a hole in you, you could have
easily got a bank statement [ __ ] from
the hole in the wall, mate. So, at the
end of the day, stop making excuses why
you, Joe, and all of these other people
don't have 12 grand because it's it's
making you look silly now about how the
bank wouldn't give you 12 grand and no,
no, no, no, no, no, mate, you didn't
have the 12 grand. Simple as that.
Because if you did, you would have
showed it. Stop using [ __ ] oh, well,
the bank's not going to, oh, give you
the money or no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. The bank would have gave you the
money in about three days. They would
have probably put it in like an envelope
and gave you it. So that old chestnut is
not going to wash. And at the end of the
day, you could have easily shown a bank
statement that you can get from the hole
in the wall. So what's the excuse for
that then? Okay. Okay. So the bank
doesn't give you money, right? Okay.
Let's go by your logic. The bank doesn't
give you a proxy 12 grand, which is your
own money, virgin boy, in the in the bed
sit with a fat ugly girlfriend. So, why
didn't you get a hole in the Why did you
get a bank statement from the hole in
the wall? Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Why didn't you get a
bank statement from the hole in the
wall? Do you want me to answer you that?
It's because if you got a bank statement
from the hole in the wall, it would have
shown you a balance which is nowhere
near 12 grand because you're skimp in
other words. So, I mean that's that. So
get a grip.
Stop making excuses cuz you don't have
12 grand. [ __ ] using the bank [ __ ]
not giving you the money as an excuse.
You [ __ ] virgin. [ __ ] 12 grand is
not a [ __ ] big amount. Jesus Christ.
Anyone would think it's a billion.
[ __ ] virgin. Skint virgin full of excuses.