Right. So, I just wanted to um put some
of these people in their place here. So,
I don't know what [ __ ] photo this is
or where it's from, but it's definitely
definitely definitely definitely not a
recent one. Uh cuz I can assure
everybody that I am not overweight. Then
I've gone on the comments and as you saw
this yesterday and it's actually made me
like piss myself laughing because at the
end of the day, yeah, all of these
people that are writing this are older,
fatter, and uglier than you. Um, like I
said, there's a reason why these people
do not put their cameras on um because
they're fat and ugly. Um, all of the
people that have come on here in the
past tried to talk about um people's
looks and whatever it is, whenever these
people have been doxed, they've always
been older, fatter, and ugly. Um, it's
never been someone that's like your age
or younger and better looking than you.
So, when you actually think of it like
that, um, it's just self-reflecting with
these fat, ugly [ __ ] I can't be
convinced that somehow these people are
younger, better looking, but yet they
continuously come on the internet for 10
years harassing people. I mean, I just I
just don't buy it. I mean, even if you
click on some of these accounts, right?
Um, you know, uh, they've been made like
10, 18 years ago. I mean, all of these
people are older, fatter, and uglier
than you. So that's what makes the whole
thing not make no sense. There's a
reason why people like this will not put
their cameras on. They will never ever
show their faces. They will never ever
show what they look like. They know deep
down that you're younger and better
looking than them. And that's where all
the hate comes from. And like I said, if
they if if that was not the case, they
would happily show you what they looked
like. They'd happily come on camera. Um
what makes me laugh with this is don't
forget he's better looking than everyone
though. Uh, Autumn, yes, I am probably
the best looking on this community. Most
of these people on here do not show
their faces. Um, and when their faces do
get out there, they're always fat and
ugly. Um, secondly, uh, are you trying
to be sarcastic? Uh, you're using
filters, right? You are literally using filters.
These are filters. There's no filters on
my [ __ ] Everyone sees me when I'm live.
Everyone sees what I look like when I'm
live. You are using filters and you are
still fatter and uglier than me. Yeah.
And and you want to talk about me.
You're coming from the person that has
to use filters. You don't see me using
filters. So you're the one that's using
filters. And then the absolute nerve he
has to call anyone fat. Yes. I've got a
big nerve. You are all fat and ugly.
Yeah. That's why you won't put your
cameras on. Yes. Yes. All the haters on
this channel. I can put all of my money
on this. Okay. Let me let me put it this
way, Alton. I can put my money on this right now
that you are all uglier and fatter than
me. That's how that's how confident I
am. I'm not even fat anyways, but if if
you want to put it that way, um I
guarantee you if these people put their
cameras on, they are fatter and they're
ugly. Now, here's the thing. There's no
point in saying right the absolute nerve
he has to call anyone fat. Um, whilst
most of you are hiding your faces, you
people should all show what you look
like and then come back to me and see
what happens. Like literally just change
all your profile pictures to what you
look like and then come back and talk
about me and see how far you get.
Exactly. All of these people on here,
they are older, they are fatter, they
are uglier, and even if it takes like 5
10 years for one of these people to get
docked and their faces to get out there,
there will be another Pat Mustard.
There'll be another bomb and there will
be another um
another bomb and another Pat Mustard.
What's the other [ __ ] Uh gray cat. So
that's why you really have to think when
these people are saying all of these
things, they are much older. They are
much uglier. Probably half of them are
virgins to be honest with you. So that's
why it has no effect because we all know
that time tells and we will know that
these people are much older and they're
much uglier. Um, otherwise they would
show their face. They don't show their
faces for a reason. Um, and when their
faces do get out there, they [ __ ] off of
YouTube for about six months. That's why
whatever these people say, it's just
about themselves. All they really do is
put themselves down. Look at this.
Unemployed, disabled, out of shape,
broke, ugly, and ambitious. That's just
his life. That's just complete self-p
projection. Um, everything that they say
is just about themselves. Um, and if
they put their cameras on, I'd be proven
right and I wouldn't be proven wrong.
Um, and if I was to be proven wrong, do
it. Um, but yeah, I don't know how
awesome someone that uses filters who is
much much fatter than me is is trying to
be sarcastic. Take the filters off and
then come back to me and try and tell me
what I look like. You [ __ ] idiot.
Bunch of retards on this community. Where to