Yo, so I'm going to be live on this um
new channel of mine because it doesn't
let me go live on my main channel
because it says that there's too many
destinations connected to the Streamyard
and I don't know the accounts um to log
into the Streamyards to remove the
destinations. So, I've had to make a
whole new channel um to go live on. So,
yeah, I'm going to go live. I'm going to
have to long this video out a bit
because it has to be a video, not a
short, in order for me to put the link
in the description. Um, so yeah, I've
just tried a couple of times and it's
just been a short, so I've had to have
to drag it on. But yeah, I'm going to be
live on that channel. Uh, no self-projecting
um people cuz you're just going to get
blocked. Um, I don't entertain people
like that. Um, I meant it when I said,
"Yeah, we're done with these people um
in the new year." And it's the new year,
so anyone that comes on hating, you're
just literally going to get blocked. So
don't even waste your time. Um, telling
you that right now. Don't even waste
your time cuz you're just going to get
banned and blocked. Um, so yeah,
that's that basically for the genuine
people like Greavesy,
Steven Howard, you know, people that can
actually have a
have a civilized conversation
and not self uh reflect their failures
onto people that they don't know every
day, etc. So, yeah, they're the kind of
people that we want on um
on our channel. Well, my channel. So
yeah, like I said, I'm going to have to
long this out a bit cuz when I when it
was a short, I tried to put the link in
the comments and they didn't let me. So
it has to be the link in the description
and you can't put a description on a short. So
yeah, just going to have to wait a
little bit. So yeah,
we are back.
[ __ ] it up. Yeah,
hopefully now should be enough time for
it to turn into a video, not short.
There is a time
that you have to go over for it to be a
video, not short, but I forget.
I thought it was 2 minutes and 30
seconds, but um clearly clearly not. So
clearly clearly clearly not. I'm going
to leave it to four minutes just to be
just in case cuz I don't want to do the
whole thing all over again. Just like my
third fourth attempt doing this.
This is boring.
Right, should be enough time now.