Right. Just going to do this approach
here in Liverpool Street. Yeah. Hope
you're ready for the uh I've got a boyfriend. Oh, well,
>> excuse me. Sorry. I just walked past
you. I wanted to come back and say that
you look cute.
>> Thank you. I have a boyfriend.
>> You have a boyfriend? I have a boyfriend, too.
>> Called it.
>> I [ __ ] called it, lad. 100% called it, mate.
Oh god, no one's got balls like me. I
had to say about walking past
because I had I literally did walk past
her and whilst I was talking to my
whilst I was talking on my phone, I
actually went and I come back. So I had
to say like I walked past and said I'll
come back cuz she saw me walk. I was
talking to my phone.
Yes, baby. I've got a boyfriend.
Ah, yep. Called it.