Right. So, um this is going to be a
video to um the biased Joseph Ferrar.
Um you concentrate on going to Thailand
or America. Then again, you have never
flown across water, but good luck.
You've canceled twice before. No wonder
no one respects your word. Joseph L has
literally lied about countless different
things and we see you on his channel all
the time. Do you know what? Yeah. The
conclusion I come to today with these
people is that it's deeprooted hate and
jealousy with these people. I'm telling
you, it is 100 million 1% the case that,
you know, I'm younger than them. I'm
better looking at than them. And that's
why they constantly go for you. They go
at you. They're biased. And at the end
of the day, that is literally what it
is. Um, and I'm going to do another
video um on this, but you're saying that
no one respects your word, bro. You're
on L J's channel that lies about
everything. um you know, owning
property, um saying that he's going to
go on Jaden's door, saying that he's
been with certain women. Um he lies
about everything. You know, I've I've
listed things he's lied about, but you
got no problem going on his channel.
Make it make sense. You know, you're
supposed to be intelligent and you know,
you've done it also um before with um
you know, Nlegs. Um you know, there's me
calling him a virgin and you're straight
to his rescue like Superman. Oh, how can
he be a virgin? He's got a girlfriend,
but yet when he's calling me a virgin,
even though I've proved I've stuck my
dick up a woman, you're nowhere to be
seen. That's why I called you a biased
nons lover. Um I never called you um a
nons. I called you a biased nonslover
cuz you are a nons lover because you're
straight away to his rescue. Um when I'm
calling him what he is, which is a
virgin, I know him better than himself.
But yeah, that that in itself should
tell you that you're never going to win
with these jealous people. I mean, that
in itself, without getting in getting
any further, you know, I've literally
put a porno out there. I proved I had
sex multiple times and they still call
you a virgin. It is jealousy with these
people, trust me. Even though they won't
admit it and they'll lie to themselves.
Um, it is jealousy with these people.
Um, I have asked them numerous times to
put their cameras on and show what they
look like. They won't do it. Um, for the
reason that we all know why. And you
know, again, I'll elaborate, you know,
into that, you know, later on because I
want to do another video. But, you know,
you're sat there saying that no wonder
no one respects your word. Mate, I've
shown more money than anyone on here.
I've shown more women than anyone on
here. I've shown more life experiences
than anyone on here. And you still
continuously sit back and talk [ __ ] over
and over and over and over and over and
over and over again. That's why people
do not show you people anything anymore.
We we do not [ __ ] wake up out of bed
every morning having to prove ourselves
to fat ugly little self projectors, you
know. That that's not the way that
works, you know. At the end of the day,
um you know, I mean, I went to Mark's
area twice. No one ever said anything. I
went to meet Trevor Dawson 5 hours away.
No one ever said anything. I [ __ ]
What was the other one? I went to um
what was it? Another thing, uh,
uh, even the train situation, you know,
someone spoke [ __ ] to me, I spoke [ __ ]
back. Apparently, they owned me. Um, all
because I didn't do anything that you
people could get the police involved
for. And that's what that's what you
hate. Um, and so that's why you try to
wind people up. Um, it is jealousy on
here 100%. Um, you know, I've come to
the conclusion today that is generally
generally what it is with these sad act
people on here. Um, that ain't got no
life. Um, and and that's that, you know,
and that's why I don't even show I I I
put that I said to Grievous, "You can
put that video up cuz you wanted to put
it up, so I just put it up." But that
you people have you proven that you're
biased time and time and time and time
and time and time and time and time
again. You're biased. Little jealous
little low-life people. If you've got
such a problem with people apparently
lying, Joseph Ferrar, why do you keep
going on LJ J's channel? That is the
biggest liar going, you know, since
you've got this big problem of liars.
because it doesn't because it because it
doesn't suit your agenda. Is Is that
what it is? Like you're you're a [ __ ]
idiot. You're a [ __ ] absolute idiot.
You know, and you're non-sl
with with that nonsense thing as well. I
mean, you people have been proven wrong
multiple multiple times and you still
talk [ __ ] So, basically, anyone who's
watching this, if you're younger and
you're better looking than these people,
they will always find problems with you.
This is where the jealousy stems from.
Um, don't they will sit there and and
and swear blue in their face that
they're not jealous, but bro, people
that are living their best life that are
better looking than you that ain't they
wouldn't be on here doing this. They
they generally would not be on here
doing this. And yeah, that's that's
that. They are definitely definitely
it's cuz you're younger and better
looking than them. Simple. And how they
can sit there and deny that knowing that
we know their ages is [ __ ]
ridiculous. So, I mean, it's jealousy is
a horrible horrible thing. Um, that
explains the biasness and whatever.
[snorts] It's because they're jealous.
They're jealous that you're not, excuse
me, they're jealous that you're not fat,
ugly, and hopeless like them. Um, and
that's what what it boils down to. Um,
it might be a tough pill to swallow, but
that is that is generally the truth. Um,
but yeah, it's it's you you you are
clearly biased, Joseph Ra, you know. So,
let's sum it up. You say that no one
respects my word, yet you go on LJ's
channel the biggest liar ever. Even
though I proved I've had money, I've had
money multiple times. I've proved I've
been with women multiple times. I've
proved I've had sex multiple times. And
you people just continuously talk a load
of [ __ ] and twist things. It's Come on,
bro. It's embarrassing. It's really,
really embarrassing. Uh, stop it.