Yo. Okay, so I'm just on my way to
Liverpool Street. Um I've not been to
this area for a while. Um I used to, you
know, come here quite a bit, but I
haven't. I normally go to like central,
but this time I'm going to Liverpool
Street. Um I was sat home bit bored. I
thought, you know what, let me go out
for a meal. Let me have a few beers. And
yeah, I've got nothing else to do. And
hopefully this time we'll be able to
land a date because the past three times
I have gone out, I am at I think 23
numbers now. and none of the numbers
showed any kind of level of interest. Um
I followed a couple up um you know
yesterday saying if they wanted to meet
Friday and they just weren't having none
of it at all. So yeah um basically 23
numbers in and not even a single day. So
it's it's really really bad. Um not to
you know mention how toxic it is and
whatever their you know their attitude
you know when you um approach them or
whatever. It's it's really really bad.
Um, and I was on Hinge um, yesterday and
I matched with this person and they
didn't reply to my message, which is
strange because if you like somebody on
a dating app, you know, you like the
way, you know, they look, you would have
thought these people would be willing to
talk, right? Um, but nope, just didn't um,
>> just just didn't reply. And then as soon
as I wrote a negative message, they
replied straight away, which is strange
because if it was, you know, um a uh
something you just randomly messaged,
then it would make more sense. But
they've actually liked you on a dating
app and they haven't replied to your
message. So the dating apps are no good
either. So I mean that's what we have to
go through in this country, you know,
trying to, you know, even find a date,
not even to find someone, to try to find
a date. I mean, it's terrible. It gets
worse and worse and worse and worse and
worse. Um, so yeah, 23 numbers, not a
single date. Um, dating apps not
working. Um, so back to approaching it
is. So yeah, I'm going to pause now and
when I get to Liverpool Street, I'm
going to resume and do a couple
approaches and show you because my
friends wanted to see a couple of
approaches. So I thought, why not? Why
not do a couple of sober approaches um
and show you um and then after that I'm
going to go for some food and then I'm
gonna drink and then yeah go clubbing.
So yeah, I'll pause on the zoom when I'm
in Liverpool Street and ready to
approach someone. Yeah,
>> right. So I have arrived.
There was some mad
but finally here. So find someone to approach. Jesus Christ
them stairs, man.
Okay, so I'm going to pause and
approach when I find someone. Anyone here? Sorry, boss. >> Okay. Well, she's
she's all right. A bit old.
I'm going to pause on the zoom cuz this take ages. Find someone
that I like
the look of.
We're going to do that one, but like the
look of it. Excuse
me. Excuse me. Sorry. I just wanted to
ask you, where did you get that beauty from?
>> Thank you.
>> What's your name? >> Mickey.
>> Where you from? America.
>> I'm heading off. Thank you.
>> There we go. That's one.
That wasn't too hard. I thought, you
know what? Let me use that pickup line
and just execute it.
But I just said it because I said it to
be honest. No one wanted to talk. No one
wanted to get to know my personality or
anything. I mean that's just
>> typical, isn't it? >> Sure.
I'm going to have to try to hold my
phone whilst I do it as well. four is the 60.
>> So, uh, right, pause, I'm assuming, and
I find another one.
>> I'm going to do her. I'm going to do her one.
>> Excuse me. Sorry. I just wanted to ask
you, where did you get that view from?
>> I've got I'm meeting my boyfriend. I
appreciate the good.
>> Have a good evening. Me too.
>> Boyfriend person walked away.
>> I mean, it's what do you what do you
actually what would you actually expect
other than that? Right. Pause again
because again, it could take a while
until you actually find someone that will
actually speak to you. Speak to you.
They're the ones you
Well, hold on a minute. What about her?
Let me give her Excuse
me. Sorry. I just wanted to ask you uh
where did you get that beauty from?
>> What's your name? >> Bri.
>> Peter, where you from?
>> East London.
>> Do something. Same. Where abouts? >> Ilford.
>> Ilford. Oh, I'm Stratford. >> Okay.
>> Yeah. What's your plans for today?
>> I think you were boyfriend.
>> Oh, you boyfriend. I best go then before
have a good evening. Yeah.
So that's two boyfriends and the one
person just walked away. >> Yep.
>> I don't mind doing it in this area. I
haven't done it in ages.
>> Ellie called me.
>> I need to be careful. These phone
snatches, bro. This is where I got my
phone snatched last time, bro.
Literally, I was hitting it.
>> I was actually Bro, you need to be
careful around here, man.
>> Let's go over there. I might go and
investigate. What's going on here then? Hold on. Oh Sorry.
Climb up here.
>> Excuse me. Sorry. Sorry to interrupt
your conversation, but I just wanted to
come over and say that I thought you look beautiful.
>> What's your name? >> Ariana.
>> Peter. Where you from?
>> I'm from Spain.
>> Spain. Ah, nice. You live in London now or?
No, we are in traveling.
>> Say again. >> Traveling.
>> Oh, traveling. Ah. How long are you here for?
>> How long are you here for?
>> How How long?
>> Not yet.
>> Two days.
>> Two days. Okay. And you go back to
Spain. Yeah. Whereabouts in Spain you from?
>> Whereabouts in Spain? Madrid?
>> Um, Barcelona.
>> Barcelona. Ah, I've never been to Spain,
but I should go. But
>> And when will you come back to London?
>> Say again.
>> I hope in a short time.
>> In a short time. Next time you come, we
should go for some food.
>> When you come back to London or I go to Spain.
>> We should go out. Yeah.
>> You have WhatsApp? >> Yeah.
>> I add you on WhatsApp.
>> Okay. Cool. Going to heart.