Yo. Okay, so I just wanted to show you
that this is indeed proof that um the
skint virgin in the bed is an absolute
copycat. Um and the only reason he was
saying that if you don't find Sher Co
attractive um you're gay, it's because
he he's copying people. Literally, this
is a um forum where people are asking
each you know, do you find Cheryl Co
attractive? Look, even this person knew
what was coming. Gay, you gay. Um, that
was the whole part of the the trend and
being a copycat and trying to fit
[clears throat] in is that they say that
if you don't find a certain um celebrity
attractive, uh, you know, you're gay.
That is being a copycat. Um, they used
to do it with Beyonce. Um, they've done
it with Cheryl Cole. And what I always
say is, so hold on a minute. If you don't find
one of them said celebrities attractive,
but you like big black women with big
boobs, would you still be gay and still
like dick? Or what if you preferred, you
know, blonde women with blue eyes,
freckles, and big boobs, and a big ass?
Would that still mean that you like
dick? Or would it still mean you like
women? I think it would still mean that
you like women. But again, it's a trend
um where they, you know, copy each
other. you know, even this person that's
commenting here even says in before your
gay comments. It it's a copycat trend. Um
um so yeah, and and they were only doing
this because the person's famous and it
was like I said, the trend. Um another
reason. So look, another way to ask OP's
question, are you gay? They're all
copycats. I told you back them years
ago. They're copycats. And Virgin Boy by
is nothing but a copycat. Um, just
because he wears some shitty, ugly
virgin clothes that no one else wears
does not mean that he's got a mind of
his [ __ ] own. This right here goes to
show that this virgin [ __ ] has never
ever had a mind of his own. Never has
and never will. Look, they all literally
copy each other. Um, you know, calling
each other gay because they don't find
some [ __ ] transgender looking woman
with no tits and no ass attractive. Um
because let's face it, she's she's she
looks like a transgender. She's got no
ass and she's got no tits. But
apparently if you find if you don't find
that attractive, you automatically like
dick. Really, mate? Really? [ __ ]
really? Yeah. If there was somebody
that's better looking than her, no one
would call you gay because their name is
not Sher Co. It's all to do with the
name and the trend. You see, it just
goes to show all along Virgin Boy was a
copycat. You know, it's it's that does
not mean you're like a dick because you
don't like some [ __ ] transgender
looking [ __ ] with no [ __ ] ass, no
tits attractive. It's called having a
[ __ ] mind of your own and um you know
uh having your own preference.
[ __ ] copycat. No mind of your [ __ ] home.