Virgin boy. Okay, so I've just ordered
myself a nice uh curry. Uh a nice
binderoo curry. Something that you you
can't afford cuz you your skin. Um
that's why you ran away for 18 months
when you were shown a 5.7 grand. You
literally can't even have this. M nice
lamb ticker vindaloo.
I got lamb ticker because I know that
you couldn't have it. A cuz it's hot and
b you got no teeth. You [ __ ] skin
burden [ __ ] in a bed [ __ ] And um
obviously you got no teeth.
You can't chew lamb ticker with no
[ __ ] teeth, mate. You a nice set of
teeth. Nice set of teeth with this. M.
They do it proper here in London. Very nice.
Not where you [ __ ] live. [ __ ] Kemp. Shitty area.
Stop going on about [ __ ] 14 grand.
You've never had 14 grand in your
[ __ ] life, mate.
I think you've been sucking your dad's
dick too much.
This is [ __ ] lovely. Guess what?
ain't even drunk a bit of Coke yet cuz
I'm a big strong Turkish man, you know,
that can take spice, that doesn't have
to date disabled girls, that's not skint like you.
M love r love it. [Music]