Yo. Okay, so this is going to be u my
reply to uh The Virgin. Um sorry for the
delay. Um I was supposed to um do this
video um last night, but I was a bit too
drunk. I had a few too many um
Guinnesses and um I just wasn't um in
the right state to uh do the video and
it just wasn't feasible to um do at that
precise moment. But I'm doing it now, so
that's all that counts. Um, so I just
wanted to say um I watched your video
and um you were saying about how um you
went to Amsterdam to watch a singer play
live. Um you know, a singer that you
liked and you wanted to watch them
perform live. Now that may be true. Um
there might have been a singer that you
liked um and you wanted to watch that,
you know, that could very well be the
case. It's not unbelievable. Um, bear
with me. But the only thing that I would
be wondering is wasn't that same singer
playing in, I don't know, uh, England or
Scotland or Wales or France or Belgium
or Germany or Switzerland or Greece or
Spain. At this point, I've just listed
other alternative places that you you
could have went. Um, but you ended up in
Amsterdam and you didn't even try to
make it uh believable that you wasn't
copying me because you literally went
there via the Euro store. I went to
Amsterdam via the Euro store as well. I
mean, I'm pretty sure most people that
um likes watching a singer that they
like play live um or an act play live,
don't they just wait for them to come to
whatever country they live in? I'm I'm
I'm sure that's what most people do. Um
not you though. No, you had to take the
Euro Star to Amsterdam just because I
went there. And it's so strange how you
also went via the Euro Star. Um,
considering you don't even live anywhere
near London, even though you tried to
tell people that you live in London, um,
to make yourself sound better. Um, you
literally don't live anywhere near
King's Cross. You got the Euro store all
the way to Amsterdam.
Smells a bit fishy, mate. It's the same
thing um, as the Cheryl Cole thing, like
I've said before. Um, you know, isn't it
funny how everyone um else has said to
each other, "Oh, if you don't find Sher
Co attractive, you're gay." They haven't
said it to me. They've said it to each
other. Um, I've seen it. Like, you can
even go online and look and you you'll
see people saying it to each other. And
then you started saying it to me. You're
nothing but a little copycat.
Nothing but a little copycat. That's
what you are. You're copying. You've got
no mind of your [ __ ] own. Um, that's
why next time I'm not going to tell you
or show you um what holiday I go on
because you're just going to copy me.
Um, you know, you'll be going [ __ ]
Thailand next. Jesus Christ. Um, I I
wouldn't be surprised if you [ __ ] end
up going Thailand just because I [ __ ]
went, you [ __ ] copycat. Um, so that's
that. Um, it doesn't really wash that
you went there to to to see a singer.
Um, you probably just thought for 24
hours of an excuse you could make um to
make it seem like why you went there
without copying me. You were copying me,
kid. You didn't just end up in Amsterdam
going there. Your first time abroad. No
[ __ ] way, you little copycat. Now,
what I wanted to say is um you what you
said at the start of your video, you
were accusing me of being jealous. Now,
why would I be jealous? I literally went to Amsterdam,
you know, seven.
No. Yeah. 8 years
um younger than you. So, I went at 23,
you're 31. Why would I be jealous? You
are literally copying things that I have
already done. So, how could I possibly
be jealous? Like, like I said, you're
copying things that I have already done
that I've done already. Like, you got
the ideas from me and you copied it. So,
why would I be jealous if I've already
done these things that you're copying?
That doesn't make any sense whatsoever.
And to be fair, um, I didn't really like
Amsterdam. I thought it was overpriced,
overrated. I thought it was dirty. I saw
Free Rats when I was there, by the way,
and I just didn't like it, to be fair.
Um, and I that's why I didn't go again.
And to be fair, you couldn't pay me to
go again. If I wanted to go, I could go
tomorrow if I wanted to. Um, you know,
it's it's something I've already done.
And to be fair, the Netherlands is nice.
You know, Holland is a lovely place, and
the people are very nice as well. Every
single Dutch person I've met are down to
earth. It is a nice country. There are
some nice places in in in the
Netherlands, but just Amsterdam isn't
nice. um when you compare it to like
Rotterdam and other places in the
Netherlands and stuff and now you know
when you're saying that I'm jealous now
what I want to say is anybody would
think that I'm the one that's got the
YouTube channel of you stalking you
every day and it not being the other way around.
Isn't that a madness? Anybody would
think it's me stalking you being
obsessed with you every day um not the
other way round. So, if I'm jealous of
you, why are you the one obsessed
stalking me every single day? That
doesn't really add up, does it? It's
like zero and zero. It doesn't add up.
So, I'm jealous of you because I told
you that you're copying things that I've
already done, yet you are the one that's
got a channel dedicated to stalking and
harassing me every day and being
obsessed with me every day. Huh? Yeah.
Well, I guess I'm the jealous one, and
you totally aren't, then. You learn
something new every day, don't you? Um,
and then you were saying about how um
I'm a virgin. Um, now here's the thing
is, you know, when you were saying about
how am I saying that you're a virgin to
um make other people believe it? Like,
the more I say it, the more um you know,
people will be inclined to believe that
uh you're a virgin. um or you know to
even convince myself things. You do a
pretty good job of convincing yourself
things. Um I saw your community post
where you're trying to call my clothes
ugly when you shop at the charity shop.
You're you have got the worst fashion
sense than anybody I have ever known. I
I would not be seen dead in your ugly
clothes. I mean you can't even [ __ ]
cor coordinate colors. You know what the
[ __ ] is that red shitty charity shop
jumper you're [ __ ] wearing? What the
[ __ ] You wouldn't see me dead in that,
mate. But cuz I actually know how to
dress and I don't shop in a charity shop
like you. Um, you know, you've got some
ugly creased up handme-down [ __ ] old
clothes and you're trying to talk about
my clothes just like you try to convince
yourself that I'm ugly when I'm better
looking than you, million times better
looking than you. You convince yourself
that I'm the incel yet you're the one
that's with a disabled girl and I've
been with plenty of normal women. you'd
just love to convince yourself loads of
loads of different things. Um because
deep down that
the facts is that you're the one that's
insecure. Um so um that's what it is I
think with you. I feel like it's a bit
with Pat Mustard. You're insecure. You
know you're ugly. Um and you project
that onto me every single day. It's like
what Pat Mustard used to do and a bomb
used to do. They're unhappy with their
own lives. So I mean that why else would
you have a channel harassing and
stalking someone every day if your
life's so perfect? I mean, make it make
sense. But anyways, so the thing with a
virgin, this is the last thing I'm going
to say, is um I've actually proved I've
had sex. I mean, I've put I've put a
poro out there. Um there's a video of me
getting a [ __ ] I've been in women's
beds. I've had women admit to you that
I've had sex with them, but yet you're
calling me the virgin. There's proof
that I've had sex. There's no proof that
you've had sex. Um, so I don't know
where you're getting at with that.
There's absolutely no proof that you've
had sex. And again, there's no proof
you've had sex, but there's proof that
I've had sex. That's the thing. As
immature and as ridiculous as it may
sound, that's where we're at, you know?
So, how can you call me a virgin when
I've proved I've had sex and there's no
proof that you've had sex? Again,
projection because you are the virgin,
you know? It has to be. It's always
projection with you. Um, that's what I'm
going to title this video projecting uh
copycat. Um, so and the other thing I
was going to say is for the last time
it's not about who stayed where, who
didn't stay where, how long someone
stayed. You went to the same place as
me. You went there just because I went
there. It doesn't matter who stayed
where, who spent more money. And stop
trying to make it seem like you're the
one that's got all of this money and I'm
the one that's poor. For [ __ ] sake,
you haven't even been on a plane. I've
been to more countries than you. I've
been to more restaurants than you. I
have more life experience than you. So
don't [ __ ] sit there in your skint
little ugly shitty little out of London
council bedset and try and [ __ ] act
like you got more [ __ ] money than me,
son, because you [ __ ] don't. Um, so
yeah, that's my response to you.