Yo. Okay, so this is how this um whole
thing uh went in case people was
wondering. So, I tried my hardest um to
get her to um you know, go for a steak
with me cuz I was absolutely going to
[ __ ] rinse her. Like, she got a lucky
escape. Um and yeah, I just thought, you
know what? Yeah, let me [ __ ] with this
[ __ ] because um you know they were [ __ ]
when I met them and they were still
being a [ __ ] um over you know WhatsApp
messages and I tried my best my hardest
to um get her to meet me for the steak
and she just she just weren't having it
at all. I tried to get her to you know
buy rounds. She wouldn't. So, I thought,
let me just give her the run around
and stand her up and make her go to like
two different places because I mean,
it's better than nothing, is it? So, I
basically told her that um I was in this
pub, which I wasn't. Got her sending me videos, making
her think herself was crazy. And yeah,
man, that's what they get for being
[ __ ] you know. Don't go around being
[ __ ] to people because you never know
when karma might uh get you right in the
ass. There we go. Lovely. A bit [ __ ] you
in the end, you know. And obviously my
WhatsApp number is uh not the same as um
my normal number. So yeah, my WhatsApp
number is not the same as my normal
number. So obviously they can't even SMS
me cuz I'm on a different number. So,
uh, yeah, it's lush. Absolutely lush. That [Music]
had enough of him, mate. Had enough of
him. She's so lucky she didn't come out
for the steak. I would have rinsed her.
I'm not even joking. I would have rinsed
up that meal, bro. Trust me. So, while
she was [ __ ] around,
I've just been in bed chilling, bro. I
mean, it's not what I wanted, but it's
better than nothing, can it?