Yo. Okay, so this is going to be another little
video about dating. So, I went out
yesterday, which was Sunday, because I
was lying in bed, and I thought, do you
know what? I've not been out for
3 weeks, and I want to go get a roast
dinner, go drink some beer, and do some
approaches because, yeah, I've I've not
gone out in 3 weeks. Took a break for 3
weeks. So, um yeah, let me let me go and
do that. So I said, "Don't mind if I
do." So I went into central London and I
approached 10 women like completely
sober, which is crazy cuz I've not done
it in about um
you know uh
3 week. I haven't done it. Yeah, I
haven't done it in about 3 weeks. So to
do 10 just like that sober is is is an
accomplishment. And it just really goes
to show that um approaching is in your
DNA and it never and it never leaves
you. um you know the whole cold
approaching thing. So yeah, I approached
10 women. Um three of them said they had
boyfriends and then the others were just
like some walked away, some spoke and
walked away as they were talking, some
said one thing and walked away. Um
so yeah, like a lot of people say, "Oh,
like why don't you record your
approaches anymore and put them up?"
Because honestly, it's just the same
thing, you know? It's the same beginning
and it's just the same ending, just
different women. So, I mean, I'm
surprised people would want to see more
of them because it's just always the
same thing. Um, so yeah, and it's crazy
how like every time you go out, you're
reminded how bad it is, but it's not
like you forget. Me of all people can
never forget how bad dating is in this
country, you know, and trying to meet
women or me of all people. But I don't
think forget is the right word. I feel
like you're just reminded um even though
you didn't forget, if that makes sense.
you know, I don't know what other way to
uh um to to um put it. So, yeah. And
it's just Yeah, it did. But surprised
me. It didn't wind me up at all. It
didn't annoy me. Normally, it would like
I'd go out like looking my best and you
know, you you'd get the same like I have
a boyfriend or people not willing to
speak and then you'd lose hope even more
and more and more and then it would just
become like a cycle. But, um yesterday
never. It didn't wind me up at all at
all. Um which um which is good. But like
I was saying before, you know, all of
the times where it did used to wind me
up, I still feel like it was it was
justified because obviously I've been
through it more than anyone in the
world, you know, trying to date and meet
women and the experiences I've had. So
it wasn't it wasn't like it wasn't
justified all the times where it did
annoy me, but it was just good that it
didn't annoy me this time. Um so yeah,
so um yeah, I got one number out of them
10 approaches and I went on a drink and
then um yeah, I got four numbers all in
all. And to be honest with you, even
though it didn't wind me up or annoy me,
it obviously would pop into my mind a
few times. Well, hey, look, you know,
you get these people that say, you know,
you're going to meet somebody one day.
You don't know what the future holds.
And then obviously when you try to speak
to someone, you can barely get a
conversation out of somebody at the best
of times. And whenever you do, it's I
have a boyfriend. Um, even though it
didn't annoy me, obviously it's
something that would pop into someone's
head because it's like, hold on, they're
saying one thing and you're experiencing
another thing. Um, which we're going to
get onto that back onto that in a
minute. But, um, yeah. So, that's the
only thing I was sort of thinking. It's
like, odd, isn't it? Odd, isn't it? So,
um, and yeah, like I got four numbers.
And here's the thing, right? Um, you
know, still with a lot of these women,
they have bad attitudes. Like there was
one literally um some of them were all
right obviously some of them were nice
but like there was one
and I sat down um and I tried speaking
to them and they literally just stood up
and walked away. They didn't even look
at me like they generally didn't even
like look at me and I was just thinking
in my head it's it's a bit rude you know
and obviously when you're getting
experiences like that and you know when
people are not really trying to talk how
are you suddenly just going to meet
someone like how is it that all of these
things have been happening for years but
somehow people are so optimistic to
think that one day it's suddenly not
going to happen. It just to me it just
seems delusional like like I was saying
on my other video, you know, there's
there's a difference between positivity
and just being delusional because
obviously the the number one question
would be why hasn't it already changed?
But it did wind me up. Um you know, I've
accepted it for what it is now. It
didn't wind me up at all. You know, I
had a fun time, but um and there was one
as well where um they said straight
away, I'm not interested. Um,
which um then I replied, "Oh, like okay,
that's fine. You know, you don't have to
be rude, but don't like moan when you're
like 30 and you can't find anyone."
Which I don't think that was me being
rude. I feel like that is the truth
because a lot of the time like a woman a
woman will get to like their 30s and
then they'll struggle to find somebody
that wants something serious. Um, so
it's not even being rude. It's just a
dose of reality, which I'm surprised
they don't learn off of each other. And
then she started saying, "Oh, like walk
on." And I was like, you don't talk to
me like that. Like, I'm not going to you
don't tell me what I do when I do it.
Um, so obviously you have to deal with
negatives like that, which you shouldn't
have to in my opinion. You shouldn't,
you shouldn't have to deal with with
that. You know, it's fair enough dealing
with people that don't want to talk and
people saying they've got boyfriends,
but I mean, why should anyone have to I
mean, like I've said before, God forbid
anybody else was in my shoes having to
deal with, you know, a lot of the women
I've been counting over the years. God
forbid what they would have done. I
wouldn't even like to think of it
because I don't think they would have
been as calm and patient as me. And to
be honest with you, yeah, it's just like
you always get reminded how bad it is
whenever you go out and you you try um
it's really really really bad. Which I
don't know why people make it seem like
it's so easy. Like you go on Reddit and
you get all of these people that say,
"Oh yeah, go on dating apps or try to
speak to women and ta." Now, I could
understand if they lived in somewhere
like Thailand or anywhere in Asia or
even South America. You know, I could be
like, "Okay, fair enough. It's it's but
most of these people, they live in
America." And America is probably even
worse than, you know, the UK for trying
to date. I mean, it's not set in stone
that it's worse, but one thing that is
set in stone is it's not any better.
Like, I've seen approaching videos. I've
seen how people act. You know, I've met
a lot of Americans and safe to say it's
not any better. So, I mean, I don't know
where they get the idea from that it's
it's just so easy. It's there's nothing
easy about it. I think like that's the
that's the that's the that's the way to
put it. Um there is nothing easy about
any of it. So,
that's just the way it is. Um but they
seem to make it seem like it's easy. And
it's weird how none of these people on
Reddit ever say that, oh yeah, you're
going to encounter a lot of stuckup
women or a lot of women are going to
give you attitude. Like, no one ever
says any of this stuff. They all go on
like you go out and it smells of like
pink roses and everything's fine and
everything's easy. It's It's strange. It
does make you wonder sometimes. It
really really does. Um, and again, it
hasn't annoyed me at all. It's just I
feel like it's just something that's
interesting to bring up. you know,
people that say, you know, you're going
to meet somebody one day and then when
you go out and you can barely get a
conversation out somebody or you're
dealing with somebody that's got
attitude, I mean, it doesn't look good,
does it? You know what I'm saying? So,
it's Yeah, I mean, that's how it is. So,
anyways, uh that's what I done yesterday
and um I'm going to go text these
numbers in a bit and um yeah, just go
from there. So, I don't think I done
bad, you know, getting four numbers on a
Sunday. after I did go out by myself and
I hadn't tried for three weeks. So yeah,
give myself a pat on the back. You know, credit
when credit where credit's due. And
that's one thing you can ever take away
from somebody is that when they've
tried, they've tried, you know. So yeah,
so proud of myself. Give myself a pat on the back.