Okay, so this is going to be a response
to Virgin Boy. Um, so I watched your
video. Oh my god. Let me just start by
saying it. Please sort your disabled
voice out. Like, oh well, how do you
know these women don't actually have
boyfriends? Like, you actually sound
like a simpleton. Like I'm surprised you
actually have the nerve yet to actually
do a video um and sound like that and
actually post it. So I was watching some
of your cringy
simpy virgin video that you that you
done and do you know what made me like
laugh is that how you think that you've
got the cheek in your skin virgin bedsit
with your fat ugly girlfriend to try to
call other people an incel. Like he
wasn't even he wasn't even referring to
me. He was referring to them people on
the video. Why Why are they an incel?
Cuz they can attract women that aren't
fat, ugly, and disabled like yours. Is
that Is that Is that what you refer to
as as being an incel? Cuz you call me an
incel as well, but I've had more women
than you, been with more women than you.
It's so bad that you literally stalked
every single sloppy second I had that
you actually could and they had to block
your ass. Um, but I'm the incel and
everyone else is an incel, but you're
the one with a fat, ugly, disabled
girlfriend, which is the only thing that
you can attract. Did you have you ever
heard the saying, look a bit closer to
home, virgin boy? You might actually
want to do that. Um, you know, now and
then. And you know, we was actually
speaking about this the other day on my
um live stream, how I find it so mad how
like you can say one thing about women.
Bear in mind, like I've had women, been
with plenty of normal women, had plenty
of women, and you'll say one thing
that's not even offensive. Yet, you get
these [ __ ] virgin simps, like [ __ ]
nonss or, you know, people that just
don't get women or women don't like
them, and they'll come to their rescue
like Superman and stop defending them.
Like, we already know that's autism, and
that's, you know, you're diagnosed with
autism. And they actually think by
defending women it's it's going to make
women like them. I mean, bro, think
about it. you're with a disabled girl
that can't even talk. The last thing I
would be doing is defending women and
trying to call other people in cells.
Like, look closer to home because I feel
like um you don't do that enough. Um you
know, it's uh it's it's very very very
strange. Um, and um, another thing I was
going to say is um, you were saying
about how you've never encountered any
of these problems and um, you've never
had these problems with women and you've
never had any problems attracting women.
And I had to like replay that about five
times. You've never had problems
attracting women. Uhhuh. That's why you
stalked to women in Canada for 3 years
when she rejected you. That's why every
single woman that I've been with that
you know you could get hold of, you
tried it on with them and they blocked
your ugly ass and you literally had to
go on five dating apps and pay for them
to get a disabled girl. Uh-huh. Yeah,
buddy. You've never had any problems
attracting women. Do you actually hear
yourself when you when you're saying
these things? like it got so bad that um
you know his jealousy with all of these
women that I used to get with he used to
generally stalk them and he used to
start like messaging them and then
they'd have to block him and reject him
and he done it with every single woman
he could and if he couldn't he would
like screenshot like in messages. Yeah,
you've never had problems attracting
women. You keep telling yourself that, buddy.
Honestly, that made me laugh for about
10 minutes. Yeah, because somebody that
that can attract women stalks other
people's sloppy seconds and tries on
with other people's sloppy seconds and
stalks a woman in Canada for 3 years
that he's never even met once. Yeah.
Uh-huh. Cuz people that can attract
women do all of them things. And bear in
mind, you was 19, 20, you was an adult
when you was doing it. Um, and then
you're trying to take the piss out of my
[ __ ] cold approaches. Bro, are you
serious? You're so disabled. You can't
even talk to a [ __ ] normal [ __ ]
woman. That's why you have to go to
these special need [ __ ] classes, you
know, with people that's got the same
[ __ ] condition as you and you're and
you're trying to do a [ __ ] video on
me in your virgin skin bedset. You're
you're trying to do a video video on me.
And listen, let me just end this video
right here. Yeah. Um is, you know, uh
when you're saying about how it's not
going to convince people this, I'm not
trying to convince anyone anything. I
don't give a [ __ ] what people people
think. I'm telling you that you are a
virgin. I am telling you that your
girlfriend is disabled. I don't care
what people think or what they don't
think. I'm telling you about you because
I know you. Which is how do you think
people know all of these stories about
your mommy starving you and all of this
[ __ ] It come from me knowing you. So I
don't care what anyone else thinks, you
[ __ ] virgin. You know, believe me,
don't believe me. I know you better than
you know yourself, virgin boy. And every
single time you would still call of
these women that I've been with, trying
it on with them, messaging them and
[ __ ] it proved even more so that you're
an insecure virgin, which is, you know,
when you sit here and you try and call
me big nose. I laugh at it. I laugh at
it, bro, because it just goes to show
how insecure and ugly you are. You're
the one, right, that stalked all like
think about what you're saying, right?
Let's just say that I'm all of these
things that you're trying to call me.
Big nose incel. Why is a big nose incel
had women that you wish you could get
that you probably still dream about to
this day that you probably still stalk
to this day? Genuinely, if you actually
was able to get your erectile
dysfunction little dick up and actually
stick it in that [ __ ] Sarah, I'm
guarantee you'd probably be screaming my
sloppy seconds out loud, bro. I'm not
even joking. So, yeah. I mean, think
before you start doing a video. I mean,
that that is a good question. If I'm so
ugly, why have I never had to resort to
a disabled girl? Why have I never had to
resort to disabled clubs? Why have I
been with all of these women that you
wish you could have got with that you
stalk that you tried it on with
yourself? Like, these questions need to
be asked, you know, if you're making if
you're making statements like this. But
trust me, listen, you need to stop this
singing [ __ ] now. It's getting really
low. It's getting really embarrassing.
It's never going to get you laid. It's
never going to get you a normal
girlfriend that can actually talk. I
mean, [ __ ] think of it, right? Okay,
look. Your girlfriend spoke once in four
[ __ ] years. Probably cuz she went to
[ __ ] speech therapy in all them four
years to be able to string a [ __ ]
sentence together. But guess what? We
never ever heard her talk since. Isn't
it funny how all of the women that I've
met, we all heard them talk. Every
single [ __ ] one of them. Even if I
only met him once. Get a grip, you
[ __ ] loser. Think before you do [ __ ] videos.