So, I'm just Ubering about. Yeah, I've
been doing it all day, mate. I made some
Wonga today, buddy.
Mate, I just wanted to show that view.
Yeah, look at that lovely view. If you
ever want to come to London and see
Westminister, here you go. Look at that view, man.
I've done some serious mileage today.
Serious mileage. That's not even a joke.
Need to make sure somebody doesn't uh
snatch my phone. But here we go. That's
the view of London. Yep. Oh man,
look at that. It's where I met uh it's
where I met Molden. It's got to be
somewhere near here.
I know it. It definitely was London
Bridge. I've been there a few times. Wa!
Look at that, man. Just chilling. We're
doing this all day. If I told you the
amount of miles I've done today, you
wouldn't even believe me. Like, you
wouldn't believe me, right? [Music]
Get in there, son. Yeah, man.