Here we go. Coming.
Yeah, it's the truth. That is a truth or honest truth.
Dude, if you want if you if you want if
you want an apology, you can come meet
me. She didn't like that pit smoker. She
didn't like it cuz she knows I'm right.
She knows she knows I'm right, bro.
Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ] I got three numbers,
but it was [ __ ] hard. And to be fair,
it weren't even that bad for one day. To
be fair, three numbers, bro. Almost got
into a fight with someone as well. But I
almost got into two fights,
bro. It's a M. I need to go back home
and get myself some nuggets. Some [ __ ] bro. Wave. Yeah,
I'm [ __ ] waving.
said to her this. I said to her this,
"Bear, listen, listen to me."
>> I said to her, "Listen, I'm near your
neck of the woods. Come and play games
to my face. I'll trouble to you. Come
on. It's a free stops. Let's talk. Come
on. Face to face in the five guys." She
don't want to do it. She don't want to
do it. She knows I'm right cuz she knows
I'm right. Poker, she knows they're
[ __ ] right. She knows I'm [ __ ]
right, bro. Mr. Bean, I said, "Listen,
I'll trouble you now." Mr. Be. >> Yeah.
this apology so badly. Yeah. Let's Hey,
Mr. B. So, you want this apology so
badly? Yeah. Come meet me to my face.
Yeah. Come on. We'll talk normally. In
front of everyone,
bro. I had it with this lesbian in this
bar, bro. You're going to laugh at this
[ __ ] You make jokes about this [ __ ]
bro. Yeah. She was trying to say, I
said, "Oh, why you being rude?"
I said to her, I said to her, "Mr. Bean,
why you being rude? Why you being rude?
Why you being rude? [ __ ] why you
being rude?" Say, "No, you want me to be
rude?" I said, "Listen, listen, listen.
Let's go outside." Yeah. Stop farting on
in a bar where there's loads of people
where you know people are going to get
involved. Let's do it good and proper.
Come on. Let's see how brave you are.
Yeah. Don't get rude if you're around
other people when you know it's going to
get broken up. You're bad. You got a big
mouth. Yeah. A big mouth in a place
where you know shit's going to get
broken up. You know, you know you're not
about that life. [ __ ] off.
Yeah, I was saying Mr. B [ __ ] you
laugh at it. You laugh at it, but it
ain't funny. It isn't funny.
This is my friend about as well. Mr. B,
listen. I said, yeah.
I said, if you want trouble, I'll give
you trouble in it. Hey, Mr. B, you heard that?
If you want trouble, I'll give you
trouble, bro. You get me? Yeah.
>> I knew she deleted my but I knew that
was the thing. Oh, Mr. Bean. I knew that
was the thing, bro. I said, "Listen,
let's meet now." I said to her, "Let's
meet up now." Yeah, let's meet up now.
Just talk one to one. Come on. Let's
talk one to one. Come on. I'll come to
you now. Come on. Let me let me hear me.
Let me come to Elen and we'll talk. Come
on. Yeah. Come on, let's do it. Let's do
it. Let's do it proper. Let's do it good and proper.
I said, "Let's do it good and proper."
Yeah. Yeah. You can be Yeah. You know
what I'm saying, bro? You know what? You
know this lesbian you play silent trying
to get rude. And I said to her, "Listen,
let's go outside. Come. Let's get rude
outside. Let's get rude outside. Come
on. You're not about that. Like, you'll
never be. You keep getting you keep
trying to be rude in a little car, but
you know that shit's going to get split
off. Trying to get rude." I said let's
go outside now. [ __ ] you. [ __ ] you. You
get me wrong.
>> You get me. Get me 100.
>> She the [ __ ] She the [ __ ] [ __ ]
Steven a proper [ __ ] Yeah. I said,
"Listen, I'll come to the evening area.
Let's talk. Come on. Let's talk. No
violence. Why is there going to be
violence? Let's just talk normally.
You know, it's [ __ ] bro. Steven, he is,
you know, we laugh at it. Yeah, he is,
man. I don't know how many approaches I
done today for three [ __ ] numbers.
God knows how many, bro. A lot of a lot
of approaches. A lot of
Got some extra money today, bro. I got
paid from somewhere. So,
it's a maza. It's a maza. Maza. Yeah,
it don't feel like a Monday night. >> Why?
>> Yeah, it's a madness, bro. It's a
madness. I knew she deleted my number. I knew it.
>> I knew it, man. I knew it. She's [ __ ]
in the head. She's mad in her head, bro.
Yeah. But yeah, I mean, what can I say,
bro? England's the same old England.
Maybe I got three numbers, but still
at least I add one of these numbers. Got
a couple of people Snapchats as well.
Oh, the maniacs. I went to waxies as
well. Went to waxies. No problem.
Went to wax is not a problem.
What we going to do, Stephen? Now, Jeff,
we'll do this proper.
We'll do this proper. We'll do this
Listen, we'll do it good and proper.
Yeah. We'll try We'll try one more day
this week. Get the haircut, do
everything. We'll go out again. And
after that, bro, we got to leave. We got
to leave, bro. It's as simple as that.
We We This bro has [ __ ] [ __ ]
everything up, bro. Like, we're leaving.
We're leaving. I've got to leave.
I got deal with attitude today. Like
seriously, bro. Serious serious. All
joking aside. All jokes aside, all
joking aside, like
it's leather, it's fun. I went on a
piss. I got some extra money. But
honestly, bro, we got to leave. We
really, really have got to leave, man.
Like it's fine. I have fun today
anyways, bro. But saying still, like you
got to get out of this country, bro.
It's like it's the only way it's going to change.
And the lesbian tried to get rude to me.
I told her to tell her about herself.
Like, who are you talking to? Let's go
outside. I said, let's go outside.
Before you say anything else, just go outside.
Yeah. All I drunk was good. To be fair,
I haven't even ate today, J.
Yeah, I told her, "Let's meet up." I
knew she I knew she deleted my number. I
knew it. See, I knew she did.
It was too obvious. It was too obvious
cuz the symbol
got removed, too.
Why am I scary? Why am I scary?
Why am I scary? Tell me. Why am I scary?
For what reason? Come on, let's meet up.
Let's talk. Come on. What? What's going
on? Let's talk. Let's meet up. Let's
Why not? Let's meet up.
He's like, "Oh, we don't allow track
suits. We don't allow track suits." I
had to change into my jeans. Change into
my jeans, brother. [ __ ] [ __ ] Um,
come and said, "Oh, we got a picture of
you. You're banned." I told him, "Fuck
off you." He said, "Oh, you understand.
You understand?" I said, "No, I don't
understand." "No, I don't understand.
If you're going to play games, at least
have the balls to play games in somebody's face.
That's it. Like, you know,
that's all I can say. I mean,
no, actually weren't Indian, but
I've done a lot of approaches today. and
a good couple of them sober
and then I moved on to a drink. But it
was kind of like
we need to we need to make a last day
for this hour.
>> We need to make a last day. We need to
make a last day for this, bro.
>> Yeah, she's crazy. She's crazy.
>> She's a mad bastard, bro. She's a crazy [ __ ]
Don't jump off. Get a blow jump from school. Nah.
I'm good, bro.
I'm good, bro. Don't need to do any of
that [ __ ] I need to go home, bro. I
need to get some food. All right. So,
Right. So, what I'm going to do, bro, is Okay.
So, we need to go out Thursday, then we
need to go out Saturday, then we need to leave, bro.
You could have had a perfect life. You
could have met me today. You could have
met me today. You could have met someone
that weren't going to cheat on you. I'm
not going to do this. I going to do
that. You could have had all of that
[ __ ] You understand now? You could have
had all of that [ __ ] Um,
you could have all you could have all of
that [ __ ] but you can't
all the gang on and everything.
I need to um
Yeah, I'm think I'm going to what I'm
going to do. I think I'm going to send
it Thursday. Take on Thursday
and then Saturday just go to a local
area and just leave. I need to leave. But
this has been going on. just been going
for too long now, bro. Um,
Saturday I'll just play local. I think
that's two that's two days.
>> Thank you, Captain.
like this cuz
>> it's Monday in it.
I can't just have one. Once I have one,
I'm out all day, bro. I can't just have one drink.
>> I can't just have one drink, man.
Yeah, that Christian Izzy thing annoyed
me, bro. I'm not going to lie. I knew
she deleted my number the other day. I
knew it. I knew it. As much as you tried
saying she didn't, I knew it. I knew
that was the thing.
>> There was no coincidence. >> What?
>> Why you going to give man your number?
Why are you going to say you're going to
meet someone and then you're not going
to do it? What's the point?
>> Can we get off? Should we? No.
I don't care about that [ __ ]
I can get some food.
like 50 60 pounds today.
I knew it. I knew it. Stephen Howard. I
So, time will tell. Stephen Howard. Time
will tell. Bro,
do you agree with me? We should do it.
We should do it this weekend one more
time and then get out of it. escape.
>> What do you think?
>> What do you think, bro? I think we should.
>> Yeah, I kind of just left it like this.
I had my bed cuz it would make a
difference. Anyways, you're still going
to get the same thing, same response.
>> I don't really think anything of it to be fair.
My next station is
>> we need to leave, bro. Serious.
Seriously, we need to leave, bro. And
I'm saying this in public. Seriously,
just getting worse. Getting seriously worse, bro.
Trust me. Like, even if I was like in
another even if I was in like another
westernized country, if I wasn't in like
another westernized country, I'll try,
bro. If I was in America, I'll try. If I
was in Canada, I'll try. But yeah, we
need to do two days and then we need to
get out of it, bro. Simple.
This is going to keep happening over and
over again. And it's getting worse. It's
getting worse, bro. I didn't I didn't go
to sleep till 6:00 yesterday. Yesterday.
6 or 7:00.
I was watching some gory [ __ ] Steen
Howard. I was watching some gory [ __ ] I
was going to send it to you on I was
going to send it to you on email by
email, but I didn't.
Yeah, I was going to send it to you via email that
I knew that was the thing. I knew it. I
just knew it.
I knew it, bro. I knew it.
I watched Three Guys One Hammer, bro.
Should even be saying it on the train,
but I'm sure you've heard of it. Have
you ever Have you watched it?
I was speaking to some guys today I met.
I said, "Have you watched it? Three guys, one disgusting."
I was saying it to you on email if you want.
I'm sure you've heard of it.
Hey Dusty, I got three numbers, bro.
[ __ ] which weren't bad for Monday.
They weren't bad for Monday, but bro,
it's getting harder. I said to Stephen,
"Yeah, we're going to go out Thursday.
We're going to go out Saturday, and then
we're done. We're leaving, bro. Done. Done." >> 100%.
Don't know how many bros on today, bro. So many.
>> I got three numbers and I got I got
Sorry, I got so many. I got three numbers. No,
>> some people's trying to get rude dust,
they have to stick it on him. They need
to know their place. All you got to say
to these people, if any, if any woman
tries to get rude to you in like a bar
club, all you got to say is, "Are you
going to say outside? Come outside. Come
outside and stay." They won't do it cuz
they know that it's not going to get
broken up. Stop [ __ ] running your
mouth to me, you [ __ ] chilly [ __ ]
And then some guy tried being a white
kn. He tried being a s. And I said to
him, "Listen, shut up, four eyes. You
specky four eyes [ __ ] You try to get a
man." I said, "Come on then." >> Yeah.
But yeah, so we got two days basically.
>> So we'll make do with
>> Yeah, she did. She deleted my number, bro.
She deleted my number, bro. She didn't
delete the picture. She deleted my
number. I know she did. She deleted it
again. I messaged her saying, "No, let's
meet up." I said, I said, "Dusty, I'll
go to Eden. Let's let me go to Eden.
Let's talk." She went, "Have it, bro.
Let's go to Eden. Let's talk." She won't
do it, bro.
She wouldn't do it. I said, "Come on,
let's go. You want an apology so bad?
I'll meet you with the five guys. Come
on." She would have it.
Yeah, she's mad. She's in her head, bro. Don't you?
She's match though. Trust me. Trust me.
Trust me. I didn't get her today, bro. I
got three numbers today. I didn't get
what I wanted today, but it was a
Monday. But trust me, I'll trust me.
>> All that time for nothing. Voice notes.
Waking up to 23 messages.
Well, I was waking up to 23 messages and everything.
23 messages and everything for nothing.
Then I tried to go into the bar and they
go, "Oh, we got your picture." You know
what, bro? I don't even like drinking in
this country. I don't even like going
out in this country. But, you know, I
was pissed off today cuz of yesterday. I
was pissed off. That's the only reason I
went out today.
I don't really like drinking. I don't
really like going out here. It's just
[ __ ] Everything about this country is
[ __ ] But yeah.
Yeah, it was a Monday, bro. Yeah,
hard it was. You don't know how many.
>> But it's not fair though, bro. Like the
whole Chris and Easy thing is not fair cuz
why do all of that, bro? Like, you get me?
I didn't go to bed till 7:00 in the
morning yesterday, bro. Man,
put my reaching number.
Trust me, we will send it on Thursday.
We send the B.
There'll be six, seven numbers. But I
approached a lot of people. I did. But
Lebanon was very like rude and [ __ ]
But you know, all of this anyways. Every
time you go out, it's the same.
>> Yeah, man.
Cakes, you just don't know. Yeah, she is
unfavorable. She's [ __ ] She's [ __ ]
She messaged me saying I'm delusional.
>> Come on.
>> We are now arriving there.
>> It's not funny. It isn't funny, bro.
It's [ __ ] It isn't funny, bro. Trust me.
It's not funny, bro. It isn't funny.
>> Nothing at all. So, I need to add one
and then message them. So, I got three
numbers on Monday and
>> it was still decent for Monday to be
fair. And waxies. Waxies was decent on a
Monday, bro. To be fair, it wasn't even that bad.
But yeah, they're just too stuck up and
[ __ ] in this country, bro. But we'll do
what we said Thursday. But um
obviously after that we need to really
consider what we're >> about
>> sending me all these messages and deleting them
cuz you know I'm right. You know I'm
[ __ ] right, bro.
Sunday the service will be part and
due to engineering work.
>> Even got the vapor on as well.
>> Got the vapors on. Yeah, I dodge a
bullet. Yeah, but still [ __ ] it ain't
nice, bro. It weren't nice. The whole
thing is not nice, bro. I tried to go
back to the same place and tell your B.
I said, "Fuck off, bro. You and your
little ego trip. Don't tell me what I
can and can't [ __ ] wear." You don't
give. [ __ ] off, bro.
Yeah, man. It is what it is. I need to
go home and
order some food, bro.
When I'm drunk, I like to message
people. I've been drinking. I like to message people.
I like to message people and I've been
drinking. I don't know about any of you chat
messaging people and I'm drunk, bro.
Yeah, I do need to get a haircut and
that. But obviously, I didn't care today
cuz it doesn't make a difference anyways.
So, you know, like
Well, nah, we need to get a burger, bro.
[ __ ] the nuggets, man. Where the [ __ ]
are we going?
>> We need to get a burger, man. We need to
get a burger, bro.
>> You're sick you are, Stephen Howard, for
knowing about that. Three, three guys
one hamburger. You're disgusted. You're
sick. How do you know about that? You're
sick. you are, bro.
>> Even knowing that you're [ __ ] sick.
>> I was going to show Laney it, but I never.
>> I was going to show Laney, but
I had to go out today, but I didn't
leave the house yesterday.
>> Good maze.
>> Yeah, I was too I had too much on my
mind yesterday, bro. I couldn't leave the house. Yeah.
You're sick, Stephen Howard, for knowing
about that. You're sick, man.
Extra money from somewhere.
Do you want me Do you actually want me
to send you it? Just remember that when
you get sent it, bro, you can't unsee
it. So, you sure you want me to send you
it? See me with Adman says, "Oh, it's bad.
the gap between the tra
>> you can't unsee it. See, Antman said to
me is [ __ ] up. It still gives him like
anxiety and [ __ ] but with me, I had
someone die in front of me, bro. So, I
mean, it's like not much not much bothers me.
Not much bothers me if that makes sense.
I'll send you it on the email, bro. Not
much bothers me, but it was a bit thick
to be honest.
If you see someone die in front of you
and you can still see the blood to this
day, then I don't think there's much of
a bobby. But
um I'll send you an email, bro. Disgusting.
But just remember, you can't unsee it.
So if you're screamish with blood and
stuff, you can't unsee it. Just remember that. >> Yeah.
>> Service, too.
>> Yeah. You just can't see it. No. Watch
it. Watch it, bro. Tell me what you
think of it. No, watch it, bro. Watch
I reckon you should watch it then.
I got some extra money today from
somewhere. So, I need to see.
Yeah, I'll do Thursday. I'll do
Saturday. I'll do I'll I'll [ __ ] send
it, bro. Don't worry.
And then we need to be done, lad. We do
seriously need to be done.
Um cuz I can't do this anymore, bro.
It's as simple as that. I can't [ __ ]
do it anymore. Where are we? Oh, [ __ ]
We won't stop. I need here to go, bro.
>> Really seen it. I think
I'm going to piss. I need to go piss. Go
home. I'm going to go back live when I
go home. Yeah. But Stephen, I say two
more days. We're in March now. Two more
days and then just [ __ ] it off, bro.
Just get out of it, bro.
Take your experiences to the grave of
you and just just stop being simple, isn't it?
>> It's really bad, bro.
[ __ ] Christian done the [ __ ] dirty
kind of on me, bro.
She's [ __ ] mad, bro.
>> I knew she'd leave my mind.
>> Knew it, lad.
>> Bye. Bye. Bye, bro.
>> Right. I'm going to come back. I'm going
to go back live when I go home, bro.
Yeah. You order some McDonald's and
[ __ ] starving, man. Yeah.