Imagine
getting happy over £800. Mad.
That's funny, bro. That's really,
really, really funny.
That would even last me [ __ ] two weeks, bro.
I'd win I'd want to win something like
30 like maybe 25 to 30,000. Maybe. Maybe, bro. to 30.
That's what I'm going for when I when I played roulette, you know. Yeah.
No, I didn't max the bar, bro.
No, it's not unrealistic. There's loads
of people that's won that. I know
someone that won 18 grand from £140.
Not really. It does. It does happen.
It's just unlikely. Yep. >> Yeah.
No, I didn't.
I was going to get like a coke. I was
going to get a Coke bottle, bro. Coke
can, fizz it up, and then just smack it
on the machine.
If it was any more than 20 pound, I
think I would have done it to be honest.
This [ __ ] is like, "Oh, you said you
were going to do this. You never." Bro,
that's the only time I've not done
something. Most of the time I spit all
over the machines. I spit all over them.
You done nothing. You know when you come
to London, you literally done nothing.
You knocked on someone's door and had a panic attack
about you didn't you didn't do nothing.
You little [ __ ] ass. You didn't even do
anything to [ __ ] You didn't do You
didn't even do anything to [ __ ] Timmy.
You [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] You know what I'm saying?
You know what I mean?
about what people do. You When the last
time you done anything to a [ __ ] betting shop,
I don't know why you're getting happy
over £800, but yeah. Mad.
You're getting happy over 800 quid.
That's funny, bro. That's hilarious. Very hilarious.
Oh, I didn't know thingy was life.
Not really, bro. £800 nothing.
And it wouldn't be anything to him as
well. Remember, he goes on like he's got
all this money. He goes on like he's
rich in that. Do you think £880 is something
to someone like that
that claims they own property? Claims
they've got all of this money, claim
they're not on benefits. You really
think £880 is anything to someone rich like him?
I mean, it's nothing. It's nothing to
me. So, it's definitely definitely not
something to someone that's rich.
Think about it, bro. The guy's the guy's rich
like minted. He owns property. Yeah.
He's on YouTube every single day. He's
got all this money. He sat on YouTube
every day. No life. So, I mean, that
kind of that money to someone who's
rich, bro, isn't anything. Think about it, you know?
You know what I'm saying, bro?
I'm waiting for Kieran and Jo
to be fair.
still cancelled. I'm not eating, bro.
I feel sick.
Yeah, but not if you're rich like him.
Not if you're rich like him.
>> Nah, bro. £880 is nothing. Not even to
win. Trust me, bro. That wouldn't even
make me happy. [ __ ] £880
would I [ __ ] celebrate, bro. It's not
even a,000 [ __ ] pound. Jesus.
I used to clean up more than that every
[ __ ] week when I used to go to the
casinos. [ __ ] hell, bro.
And especially when you're someone like
him that's rich, that's got all of this
money he claims he has. Yeah, right.
You're right, lad.
I don't need to lose any weight. I'm not fat anyways.
I'm not fat anyways. So yeah,
but yeah, I mean if you are fat.
So yeah, that's that, bro.
That's that in it.
I can't believe I'm not eating today,
bro. Jesus Christ.
I never go a day without eating, bro.
But that's just depressing as [ __ ]
That is, bro. Seeing that 25, seeing it
go next door.
Very lucky I didn't do anything to that
bookies today. Very, very, very, very
lucky. Very, very, very, very lucky. Cuz
all the other times I have spat all over
it, made a scene. I have every single time.
No, I'm not eating today, lad. I've been
put off my food
cuz of that roulette. I've been put off my food.
I went past my favorite chicken shop
today on the way back home. Didn't go in
it. Nah, I've been put off.
Puts you off your food. It puts you off
your mood, your vibe, everything. That's
what it does. It does me. Don't know
about anyone else, but it does me.
Definitely definitely does me. So, yeah.
Jesus Christ. Get a [ __ ] life. I
swear some of the people on here, bro,
I've blocked like [ __ ] 10 accounts.
You seriously, seriously, seriously need
to get a life.
[ __ ] me. Just come out the closet already.
Seriously, seriously. Just come out the
closet. It will do the world of good.
There's a lot of people in this
community, Stephen Hen, that need to
come out the closet. It's actually
getting pathetic now, bro.
They do this because they're gay and
they hate the fact that they're gay and
they want to take out on you because
they're gay and they don't know how to come out. Literally, bro,
I just messaged the army lad. Are you
out tonight? He says, nah.
unless he's one of the army lads.
There's a few people in here in the closet.
Jo, uh Redstone, Nunch Legs, Jamie
Thompson. They're all closeted gays.
They hate the fact that they're gay as well. Yeah,
just the way they stalk men on YouTube
every day, the way they've got a channel
dedicated to another man. It's just
clear. It's clear as as a blue sky that
they're just gay.
They're just gay. Only gay people do
that. Proper [ __ ]
That's what they are. Proper proper proper [ __ ]
Just come out the closet. [ __ ] me.
They've got channels dedicated to me.
They stalk me on here. They talk about
me all day.
Yeah, they're gay, bro.
Yeah. Anyways, we're not talking about that virgin.
We're not talking about these virgins
anyways anymore. So, yeah, until thingy
comes on later, we're not we're not
talking about we're not doing what they do. So, yeah.
We're not doing what they do, lad.
All right, moving on. Anyways,
[ __ ] get a life. The amount of people
in this community that need to come out.
And the only thing is, Stephen Hour is
that they say they do it for reaction,
but they're reacting to you and spending
more time on you than you could ever on them.
Nothing skint about me, bro. I got more
money than LJ will ever have
and £880 is nothing. So yeah, go back to
sucking your boyfriend's dick
because I've got more money than both of
you and £880 is nothing for someone like
me. So yeah, keep uh keep keep um
keep sucking your boyfriend's dick.
£880 is peanuts.
It's not a great mid. It's peanuts. I'm
I'm telling you, it's [ __ ] nothing.
£880 is nothing. It wouldn't even last
me two weeks. I'm I'm not even joking.
It really isn't a great win. It's nothing.
I'd say if it was, I honestly would. It's nothing.
£880 is nothing. And you know it. And
the only reason you're saying it is is
because it's L that won it.
I know they're they're gay. Joe does it
as well, Ben. They're gay,
bro. They're gay and jealous. I know
this, bro. They're gay and jealous. And
the thing is, bro, yeah, they say they
do it. They say they do it, Ben, for
reaction, but they're actually spending
more time reacting and talking about you
than you could ever on them. So again,
it's an autistic community that don't
make no sense, Ben. So, don't try to
figure it out cuz you just end up losing
brain cells. I I woke up earlier, Ben.
Yeah. Um, and my phone was dead cuz my
phone always dies. Um, I'm just lazy to
charge it. So, I made myself a tea, bro.
I went on LJ's channel, bro. I swear to
God. Yeah. I clicked on it. Jo was
talking about me. Every single comment
was about me, bro. He's gay. They're
[ __ ] They generally generally
generally are gay [ __ ] They are,
bro. Um, if 800 Sorry, I'll answer your
question now anyways, bro. Sorry, I was
talking to Ben. If £880 is peanuts, why
are you upset about losing 20?
Uh, bro, I answered this earlier. I
already answered the question earlier,
lad. Why are you asking me the same
question that I already answered?
Why Why am I angry over losing 20,
bro? I I already answered it. Because
it's not about the money.
I don't know how many times I have to
say the same thing. It's not about the
money. It's about losing on them dirty,
stinky, rigged machines to next door
numbers. It's not about the money. £10,
20, 2000, it doesn't matter.
It It doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter, bro. Because it's not
about the money.
Simple as that.
How's Thailand, Ben?
Go away you little law J simp. Go have a
[ __ ] wank over £880 peanut money.
Yeah, bro. Go and have a wank over £880
madness. If you actually think that's a
lot of money, mad. Mad.
So yeah, it's not about the money anyways.
How's Tyler, man?
Do you know what? I don't really go I
don't really go on LJ's channel. It's
only because it popped up today. I don't
really go on that channel. That's just
where all the disabled goes. All the
disabled people go there.
It's such a weird channel. And it's the
[ __ ] that people do on that channel is
so weird. A bunch of 40-year-old losers
sat on YouTube every day talking about
strangers. It gives me the ick.
It's so weird and gay. Like if you you
go on that live channel, Ben, yeah, it's
just a bunch of losers that talk about
the same [ __ ] The same people. They
bring up the same people and the same
[ __ ] It's a proper It's [ __ ] weird
as [ __ ] bro. No, I don't watch him. It
popped up earlier, so I clicked on it. I
don't watch him. No, I don't watch him.
And I'm not subscribed to him either. Go
look at all of the people that I'm
subscribed to. It is [ __ ] weird, bro.
What they do on that channel.
It doesn't matter what perspective it
is. It's It's not a lot of money.
It doesn't matter about perspective.
It's just not a lot of money. Simple as that. Oh, yeah.
That channel is so weird. And the people
that go on it is so weird as well. You
just bring up the same people and the
same [ __ ] Weirdos. Proper proper weirdos.
Just like that weirdo Jo. He's another weirdo.
We're just waiting for him to come on.
Another little closeted gay weirdo
that still trying to pretend he's going
to meet people when he's not.
£880 is not a lot of money, bro. Yeah, simple.
It's just a weird community, isn't it? So weird.
It's a disabled community.
That's what it is more than anything.
Just a disabled community.
This is the last day that
Chinese is open.
So until next week, Reezy,
they only open three days a week. I
ain't going. Simple as that. Yeah.
Guys talking about what people have done
and what they haven't done. Bro, you
come to London and you [ __ ] your pants.
You didn't do anything. You literally
had several chances to hit me and you
didn't do nothing. When was the last
time you smashed up a bookies after
losing what? More money than I done.
Usually when I lose in the bookies, I
spit all over the machine. You don't do
nothing. You're just a [ __ ] house.
You'll never do anything. You're a
[ __ ] disabled diabetic with a [ __ ] bad back.
You [ __ ] farey ginger little [ __ ]
Yeah, obviously. Who else am I [ __ ] referring to?
Talk some mad [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
Yeah. So, it won't be open till next
week. Grezy. So, yeah.
I think if I end up going out, bro, I'll
just beat someone up. If I go out now, I
think I'll just end up beating someone up, bro.
Yeah, trust me.
[ __ ] I will end up just beating someone up, bro.
That's what I'll do.
So, best to stay in. Best just to stay
in, you know.
I just lost 20 pound on a FBI earlier.
Depressing [ __ ] Food's cancelled today.
I didn't manage to do any food shopping.
I didn't manage to do any football bets
cuz when I lost, bro, I just had a tantrum
and had to go back home quickly before I
was going to end up doing some serious damage.
Serious damage with a cocaine.
With a coan, lad. Yeah.
Nope. It was actually going to be steak
today. Greavves. I was going to eat cuz
I was food cho. I was going to do food
chopping, but after that I couldn't keep still.
I was going People must have thought I
come out of [ __ ] mental asylum or something, bro.
Yeah, it drives me mad as well. It
It drives me [ __ ] mad as well, bro. I
withdrew 30 pound and I lost 20 and I
just put 10 pound back in the bank.
I just put the£10 back in the bank, bro.
Uh I've already got a woman, thank you
very much. And my stonies fit perfectly.
We're not all fat like you and Lavy,
lad. We're not all fat like you and your
boyfriend. I can fit a medium. Tell your
boyfriend L to put a medium on, brother.
I'm better looking than you. I'm [ __ ]
in more shape than you. I've got a woman
unlike you. People sat on YouTube 24/7.
Yeah, we have seen you people from the
time you wake up to the time you go to
bed on YouTube 24/7. Yeah, you [ __ ]
ugly fat bastards. Yeah, we've seen you,
bro. We've seen you people
on YouTube. You fat [ __ ] You
overweight little [ __ ] You think,
Listen, S. You really think if you had
anything in your life, you'd be on L J's
like a [ __ ] 24/7?
No woman, you fat you. Everything is
about you people. Ugly fat bastards.
That's you people, bro. No woman, no
life, overweight, ugly [ __ ] bullied
all your life before you even come on
YouTube, bro. It's you people, bro. It's
you people. I can fit in all of my
clothes. I'm not fat like your
boyfriend. I don't have to go on diets
like your boyfriend. I don't have to
[ __ ] I don't have to [ __ ] go on
the scale like your boyfriend because of
his weight problems. I'm not the one
that's going on diets and then stepping
on that scale, bro. And the numbers are
still coming on the same. We're not all
like your fat boyfriend. You need to
remember we're not like your fatty
boyfriend. Do you understand, lad?
We're not all like your fatty J boyfriend
on these diets, but he's still a fat
ugly [ __ ] with four eyes. Oh, exactly,
bro. You know I'm right as well. You
know I'm [ __ ] right. Skin. Like
again, I'll repeat myself. I've got more
money than you and your boyfriend. Bro,
these people are generally generally
disabled. Yeah. You tell them something
and it doesn't process in their mind.
Skin, brother. I've got more money than
you. I've said this like god knows how
many times. I've got more money than
you. If you people right, okay, let let
me ask let me ask you this question
here. If you people really had money and
a job, why you on YouTube 24/7? Let's
let just just chill, chill, chill. Stop.
Let's just stop typing over each other
now. Yeah. If you really had this money
in this life, why you sat on YouTube 24/7?
Exactly. I live in poverty, brother.
I've got more money than I'm not the one
with a 300 phone. Is that the same Joe
with the 300 phone? I've got more money
than all of you. You're on YouTube 24/7
because you got no money, no life. Bro,
if you people weren't living under
poverty and you weren't skinned, why are
you on YouTube 24/7? That you can never
ever you, bro. There's nothing you can
say about that. There's nothing you can
ever ever say about that. The evidence
is there. The proof and the evidence of
you people can't not being able to get
off of YouTube shows you're skinn, show
you're fat, show you're ugly, shows
you're lonely. The evidence is there,
brother. The evidence is there. Oh, a
bud mate. Have you seen you people? You
fat ugly bunters. We've never seen any.
And how comes we've never seen you
people with a woman as well?
You are fat ugly mters. You're the
muners yourselves. Have you Have you
looked at yourself recently? You fat
ugly [ __ ] Middle-aged wrinkly old men.
And you know the thing is about people
like you, Salted. You're too old to
change it. That's the thing. You're too
old in your full Egypt. You're too old.
You're too old now. Fat ugly skin
monties. And you can't change it cuz
you're too old. Whereas people in their
20s like me, nope. It's not speculation.
It's facts. Okay, I'll put the link up.
Right. If it's speculation, prove me
wrong then. I'll put the link up right
now. Right. If it's speculation, then
prove me wrong. Okay? You're not fat
ugly moners. Okay? Prove me wrong then.
Prove me wrong. Just like I'd be able to
prove people wrong if I went on a
community and I was slagging people off.
I could prove them wrong. If it's
speculation, prove me wrong. Prove me
wrong then. Prove that you're not fat
and ugly. But you can't do it. Exactly.
Cuz you are fat and ugly. There's a
reason why you people don't show your
faces through embarrassment of your m
looks. I'm not Bro, you can't. You
literally can't say I'm lying, bro.
Right. It's the same if I went on this
[ __ ] Savvy Boys right now. Yeah. And
I'm calling people everything. I'm
calling people all of these things. I
can prove my looks. You moners can't.
You're fat and ugly. And then you come
on here 24/7, right? Trying to talk
about people that are better than you in
life. You're [ __ ] retards. That's why
we call you lavy moms. That's the
reason, right? Yeah. We call you lavy
moms because of what you do.
Middle-aged, fat, ugly people talking
about people better than them. Talking
about people that are better than them.
That's why we call you the levery bombs. Yeah, exactly.
That's it, bro. Look, the link's up. Is
anyone going to join or what?
Is anyone going to join? Is anyone going
to prove that I'm speculating and I'm
wrong? I mean, I mean, you can say that
people are speculating, but if you're
not here to prove anyone wrong, then the
point still [ __ ] stands, mate. The
point still [ __ ] stands. Yeah, I've
got anxiety. Yeah, yeah, cool, bro.
You're the one not joining the hangouts,
lad. You're the one that can't show your
m ugly, fat, stinky, dirty face. Ugly
[ __ ] Go back to sucking your boyfriend's dick.
Go back to sucking your foreyed
boyfriend's cockr. You little low lives.
Literally everyone Steven Howard on that
Lavy channel are low lives. Anyone that
goes on that channel, they're just fat
bunters that ain't got nothing in life.
Not even a life to live, bro. Why do you
think they're sat talking about people
every day? Because they're fat little
wasters. And why do you think when I
said this, bro? Yeah. People started
using my words. They're fat wasters that
lie around in the house. No woman, no
money, no life, no looks. And they know
I'm right. They literally know I'm
correct. That's why they can't join and
show me what they look like. They're
just fat, stinky, dirty, ugly. No women
getting [ __ ] Why do you think they
they beg this Autumn Rose, bro? Why do
you, Bro, why do you think they Why do
you think they beg this Autumn Rose,
bro? Cuz they get [ __ ] Because they
get all these women. Why do you think as
soon as a woman comes on the community,
they want them like a bottlefly and [ __ ]
on the subs day cuz they're too ugly and
[ __ ] and disabled to go out and get
anything themselves? I can say it better
than my body man ever could, bro. Ever
could. Ever could. ever could. Ever
[ __ ] could. You get it? If people are
generally speculating, prove us wrong.
Prove us wrong. So, if you're not going
to prove us wrong, stop telling us that
we're speculating because you can't
prove us wrong.
Think about it, bro. If any If any of
you can come on here on here now and
prove me wrong, you'd get the last
laugh. I'd be a laughingtock. But you
can't cuz I'm right. I'm correct.
Just like I'm correct that Joe F is
never going to meet me and he's probably
just some rice looking [ __ ] ugly [ __ ]
that will never meet anyone. Just like
I'm right about him as well. Job done. Simple.
Simple. Simple dimple.
That's it, bro.
Is Rich May still alive?
Sorry about that. Um,
what's your face? I forget.
Fire stick. Just got a bit out of hand, bro.
Oh, Monty's on Vix's.
Yeah. See you later, lad. Anyways.
Okay. Well, if I'm wrong, why won't any
of you come on camera then? Okay, I'm
lying then. Okay, I'm I'm wrong. Okay,
bro. I'm wrong. Okay, I'm It's not just
bomb. It's multiple people that's been
doxed. I mean, it's been multiple
people, not just Bomb, but Okay.
>> It's multiple people. It's not just a
bomb. He's just one of them.
But if I'm wrong, bro, and I'm
speculating, then prove me wrong. Prove
you're not fat, ugly,
or ugly. Prove it then. If you're not
these things I'm saying, prove it. Simple.
But you can't do it. But you can't do it
because you know that you're fat and you
know that you're ugly and you know you
ain't got Yeah. You just got nothing
going for yourselves.
>> Yeah, that's nice, bro. Why don't you
come and show everyone your face? insulted.
You people, you know, the thing is, bro,
like you people don't bother no one
because everything that you do is just
self- projecting. Everything you do is
self projecting. Everything you say is self-p projecting.
It's just self- projecting with you
little lowife [ __ ] What you do on
here is so weird.
And the fact that you're older than me.
Yeah. And the [ __ ] that you do on here
is so weird, man. It's [ __ ]
freakified what you do on the on this community.
Very weird. Very very very [ __ ]
weird. So why won't any of you join then?
Why won't any of you join um the hangouts, man? H
why won't any of you join the hangouts?
You act like you got this better life
than everyone. Yeah. When you just sat
on YouTube 24 [ __ ] seven all day, every day
then do that, bro. Then do that. Do it
then. Is it? Yeah. Do it then. That's
fine, bro. Then do it. Then do it. Then
But then stop talking about other people
that are better than you in life. It's
as simple as that. You know, if you want
to do that, TJ, you have this amazing
life. Why? Uh why am I doing it? Because
I'm saving money. Um and I'm not going
out until probably next month. I'm
saving money. I've done a lot of [ __ ]
over the years. Why are you people on
YouTube every day, all day, every day?
Why are you not living your lives? So I
answered it. I've already lived the life
that more than most probably than more
than half of you people have. Yeah.
Already. So why are you people not
living your life?
Why are you people not living your life
every day? Sat on YouTube talking [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Why are you not living your lives?
Yeah. I'm skin. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. Yeah. So why Okay, fair enough. So
why are you people not out with your
mates? Why are you not living your
lives? Why are you not at work? See,
see, because what it seems to me by what
I'm one second, Grezy. By what the the
verdict has um come up, it's come
through the post,
you people must be skint. You people
must be skint. You people must be ugly.
You people must be alone. You must be
You really must be these things that
you're trying to call other people.
What? Which is why you sat on YouTube
all day, every day from the time your
eyes open to the time your eyes closed.
That's the verdict has come back. And it
must be you people. It must seriously
seriously be you people.
I've not stepped in other countries.
Well, I have been to other countries and
I have been on a plane. Anyways, we're
not Why are you talking about that? Why
are you people on YouTube 24/7
when you should be at work? When you
should be out with your mates living
this good life that you've got? I'm
asking you now, why are you not doing
it? I answered. I answered. I answered.
So, can you answer me then? Yeah.
Are you saving for something? Are you
depressed? Like, what's the There's got
to be a reason. Cuz there's no way you
people can have all this money and this
perfect life when you're sat on YouTube
all day, every day for years. I'm sorry.
I'm really, really, really, really,
really sorry, man. You know,
I'm not your [ __ ] mate. All him.
Yeah. Listen, listen all him. Listen,
listen, listen him. Yeah. One second.
You need to tell your friend. Yeah. That
you're not going to let him hit it. You
need to tell your little bumchum that
you you don't like him romantically. I
think he's starting to like he's
thinking that uh he's going to get in
your knickers. I I think you need to
tell him like and you need to stop
making posts about me. Um because it
might look to some that you know you've
got a crush on me and you know how the
virgin is uh the the the the proper
virgin one the one in the council beds
it sit he gets very very jealous and
then he starts sing. So I think you need
to tell him that um you know you're not
going to let him hit it.
Um he will know what that means.
You're not going to You're not going to [ __ ] him.
Yeah. You're not going to You're not
going to [ __ ] him.
Yeah. I think he thinks by like licking
your ass you're going to have sex with
him or something. Quite weird to be honest.
Rose great women. That proves my point
even more. You're calling somebody on
the internet a great woman when you
don't even know them. But yet you're the
good-looking person, yet you've got this
life. You give yourselves away. A lot of
you people with what you do on here, you
actually give yourselves away.
It's like you try to lie about [ __ ] and
then what you do just gives you away
completely. It's mad.
It's actually mad to be honest
when you give yourselves away.
It's [ __ ] weird.
Yeah, she can slag me off all she wants.
I don't care.
I don't care, bro, about some fat ugly
woman that uses filters. That's nice,
man. Good for you, bro.
Good for you.
You people are [ __ ] weird, lad.
You people are [ __ ] weird what you do
on here, man.
But yeah, anyways, um, just say to him
that you're not going to let him hit it
all him like really. No, like really really really Yeah.
Yeah, that's bad. Yeah.
Yeah. What you people are doing doing on
this community is so weird.
And look at all of these people singing
L over £800.
Mad. which is a good thing as well
because it also shows got the manta
ranting and raving. Yeah, bro. Like I
said, I put the link up for you people
to come on here and show your faces, but
none of you will do it. So, yeah, that
doesn't mean anything coming from you
fat ugly lives rejects. But yeah,
M. But everyone you're calling a M is
better looking than you in it.
The M that's better looking than you.
When are these people really going to
stop talking about themselves?
Never, bro. If they're not going to do
it in 2026, they're never going to do it.
And most of the people in this community
are [ __ ] fat as [ __ ] as well. You know,
most of the people in this community are
fat as [ __ ] Yeah.
I've never done the lottery, you know. Never.
Me. 100%. Me 100 million%.
And you're the one that's obese, lad.
You calling me right, hy is not going to
change the fact that you people are
really the fat and ugly ones. You can
you can project all of this all your
weight issues onto other people, but
it's not going to change what you people are.
Fat ugly bully victims, which is why
you're so obsessed with the word
bullying, because you people have been
bullied your whole life for being fat and ugly.
You people are [ __ ] fat and ugly. I
don't know how many times you people
need to look in a mirror.
You people are fat, ugly, life reject.
Most of these are probably virgins on
here as well. You know
who's not ugly?
That's why I used to get mad at losing
at the casinos and stuff because I'm
feeding their kids. That's what used to
piss me off. I don't like the fact that
they're feeding their kids with my money.
That's what used to Yeah, that's what
used to buy me up.
Who's not ugly? They They are ugly.
These people in this community, bro.
[ __ ] proper ugly.
proper proper proper ugly self projectors.
They [ __ ] are. That's why none of
them come on camera cuz they're ugly.
They're ashamed of what they look like.
[ __ ] fat and ugly bastards. That's
what they are. Yeah.
My head's feeling a bit sore now from not eating. Yeah. Yeah, bro. Yep.
That's why like whenever I'd lose like
online or the casino, I'm tempted to
beat the [ __ ] casino manager up.
Like give him a good [ __ ] heiden.
Give him a good [ __ ] hide him.
Yeah, I've had some real psychotic bad
thoughts in my head, bro. Trust me, I'm very psychotic.
Very, very, very psychotic. Trust me, bro.
Why do you think I'm not scared if
anyone ever came for me, bro? Because
they'll know what they'll get. Trust me, Yeah. Yeah, man. Some peanuts.
And people still are still telling me
that I'm skinn even though I told them
Stephen Howard multiple times I've got
more money than them.
And they're still saying that people are
skinn even when you've said to them
multiple times you've got more money
than them. Disabled community. That's
why we call it a disabled community.
It's not It's more of a disabled
community than a copycat community.
Autistic disabled community. Let's call it that.
It's an autistic disabled community.
That's what it is.
Does that sound a bit better, Grezy? Yeah,
I think that sounds better. What do you think? Yeah.
Still saying it's about the money and
and why is it an autistic community? Why
Look right. Look on look on LJ's 880
880 is peanuts but 20 quid loss has
caused him to starve himself again. This
will be the seventh time now that I've
explained the same thing. That's why
it's an autistic disabled community,
bro. Because even if you explain
something to them, it doesn't process in
their mind cuz they're [ __ ] disabled
on this community.
Yeah, I've explained it more than seven
times in the past. You can't explain
anything to them, bro. They're disabled.
They keep thinking it's about the money
when I've told them multiple times it's
not about the money. It's a disabled
community. That's why we call it that
disabled autistic community. So, yeah. Yeah, bro.
cuz you don't react the way they want
you to react greasy.
They don't you don't react the way they
want you to react. Do you understand? So
then they'll say that you are addicted
or your skin because you're not reacting
the way you want them to react. you know,
because you don't react. Oh, it's only £20. You know,
they seem to think that, oh, because you
still got money. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I
could have a billion pounds, bro, and I
could lose five pound and I'd still be the same.
Simple as that. Simple as that. So, yeah.
Psychotic Pete. I love that, bro. True
though. Is it?
Cuz I thought of that Coca-Cola thing. Is it
that LJ is still putting out the old
prime video. These people are so
embarrassing. That's why we call them disabled.
That's why we call it an autistic disabled community.
That's why we call this an autistic
disabled community, bro.
That's what it's going to be called from
now on. Greasy, the autistic disabled community.
Nah, there's no point joining a retards box.
That little [ __ ] box. Repeating
[ __ ] There's no point, bro. He's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
And you know what? They're so disabled.
They've got no new content. They just
talk about the same [ __ ] Have you gone
on it? Um, Steven Howard with LJ's
channel. It's just the same. It's just
the same repeating [ __ ] They got
nothing new. They'll talk about me, then
they'll talk about Monty, then they'll
talk about like Timmy. They've got
nothing new. That's why they've just life rejects.
All the life rejects going there, bro.
I think I tipped him over the edge when
I said the Stony didn't fit him and he
was gaining weight. No, you're just self projecting, bro.
No, you fat ugly people don't tip no one
off the edge. You little life losers. I
t I tipped you over the edge when I put
the link up and you couldn't show your
face. But yet you claim people are
speculating. You say that people are
speculating, right? These people were
saying that I'm speculating. Okay. Well,
prove it then. Prove you're not fat and
ugly. And they can't prove you're
speculating. So then they shouldn't be
telling you that you're speculating when
you're right. Cuz clearly, bro, if you
wasn't right about these people, they'd
prove you wrong. Do you not think they'd
prove you wrong, lad? If they weren't
really fat, ugly muners, do you not
think they'd show their face? Just like
if I would if I went to a new community,
bro, I would happily show my face cuz I
know I'm decent looking. I know I'm not
ugly like these people. You not find it
weird, bro. In 15 years, they will do
whatever they will to not show that ugly
face of theirs. And every time, bro. And
every time Yeah. Their faces get out
there, they're [ __ ] ugly. Does that
not tell you something, bro? Does that
really not tell you something, bro?
They don't come, they don't show their
faces. When their faces are out there,
they're always ugly. I mean, how much
evidence do you need, bro? Even the
people, bro, even the people that show
their faces, even the people that show
their faces, bro.
Even the people that show their faces,
these people that are on YouTube 24/7,
these ugly life rejects never show their
faces. And when their faces are out
there, they're always ugly. You're never
wrong about them, bro. That's why
they're on here. Why do you think
they're on here 24/7, bro?
Why do you think the fat losers are on
here 24/7? Cuz they got nothing. They
got no one. They got no money. They got
nothing. That's why they'd rather talk
about other people, bro.
You know what I mean? They would just
They just You know what I'm saying, bro?
Like, [ __ ] me.
Think about it, bro. Yeah. Where does
Where does the name calling come from?
Firstly, bro, where does the name
calling come from? It comes from that
channel, doesn't it? It comes from them, bro.
You know what I'm saying?
It comes from them, bro. So, why are
they on YouTube 24/7?
I just I just want I just want the
answer. You know, the name calling comes
from their channel, right? It comes from
them. So why are they on YouTube 24/7?
They're very hesitant to answer that question
because it's the truth.
It is literally literally What's the day
today, bro? Saturday, right? These
people are not depressed. These people
have got all of this money, right? So
why are they not out living their life?
It's a Saturday.
Why are they not out living their life, bro?
You know what I mean?
Sat in my house, Mrs. Waiting. Yeah. Is
that the same person that said that you
come on my door? You never come on my
door. I've got more money than you. And
I bet your MS is [ __ ] ugly. Just like
your kid's going to be [ __ ] ugly and
you're not going to come on anyone's
door. You're not going to do anything.
Nobody you ugly Mrs. you ugly child you
and you're not going to do anything
about it. Simple.
You should come on in now, bro. Simple.
Yeah. Listening to a broke a bloke who's
better looking. Never had to resort to
ugly. Got more money than you. This is
how many times I've said this now, bro.
Yeah. And I I don't pretend I've gone on
someone's [ __ ] door when I [ __ ]
haven't. Yeah. This is the same person,
right, that was saying to Red that he
covered the door. This little loser
would be fat. They'll never go on
anyone's door, bro.
You're going to come on my door, bro. I
would have split your [ __ ] face in
half if you come anywhere near me, bro.
Yeah. And this little [ __ ] loser with
his ugly pregnant woman is trying to
tell me he's come on my door. Trying to
lie on people's channel. Didn't you
didn't you see that when he was trying
to say that he's coming on my door?
Are you [ __ ] mad? You're coming on my
door. That's what he said, bro. He
[ __ ] randomly started saying he's
coming on people's doors.
Yeah, Christian Izzy. You don't know any
You don't know Christian Izzy. You don't
even know her [ __ ] name. V, you
[ __ ] [ __ ] knows everything about
Yeah, that's funny because you don't
know who that is. You know
you you don't even you don't [ __ ]
know who that is.
Christian Izzy, you don't even know who she is.
Christian is he? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You're retards, bro. You're retards.
pretending that you've come on someone's
bro door. Bro, I would have slapped your
pregnant misses in front of you if you
ever come on anyone's door. Do you know
what? I I will I will say that, bro. Do
you know what? I'll actually say that.
Yeah. Tell that PC. Yeah. If he comes on
the door, I'll slap up his pregnant
woman in front of him and smile at him
at the same time.
Tell him to do it, bro. Cuz he's saying
about how he's going to come on people's
doors and I will [ __ ] up your misses in
front of you. Manto man. I will do it. I
will. Tell him on the chat right now,
bro. Stop pretending that you're going
to go on someone's door, bro. Come with
your fat misses and I'll spit in her
face and give her a slap for you being a
little [ __ ] on YouTube. Yeah, simple.
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] You stupid
Yeah, stupid little [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah,
now they're saying that they got
people's money stopped. Yeah, this is
boring. We've already been over this.
But do you know what though? You control
these people's lives because every time
you go live they go you control them.
You literally control them, bro. Every
time you go live and stuff. Yeah. These
ugly fat moners go for you. You You
control their pathetic existence. You
actually do, bro. That's where they get
all of this [ __ ] from that people
control them. R Yeah, man. PC, join my
live, bro. Join I I want to know why
you're you say you're you're going to
come on people's doors. I would slap you
in your pregnant misses in front of you
and laugh about it if you ever went
anywhere near my any kind of door that
I'm living in. It's the truth, bro. It
is honestly the truth.
It's the truth. I'll give a one big slap
across that mouth and look at you and
smile at you like a dirty [ __ ] That's
why you don't go on people's doors. You
going on people's doors. You're going on
people's doors. Some little gay boy off
YouTube. The cheek of it, bro. The
[ __ ] cheek of it. The [ __ ] cheek
of it, bro.
The actual cheek of it.
The cheek of it, bro.
[ __ ] some disabled [ __ ] with a fat
ugly misses with no money, soon to be a
dad to an ugly child. Is is saying he's
going to come on people's doors? Did you
not see him say that the other day?
[ __ ] little [ __ ]
You [ __ ] ugly pregnant Mrs. carried
an ugly baby. And I'm talking about his
kids. And he's not going to do nothing
about it. Not going to do a damn thing
about it, bro.
It's as simple as that. Your [ __ ]
ugly misses carried an ugly kid. You
can't get as low as me, but you're not
going to do anything either, bro. You're
not going to do anything about it either. You know
you [ __ ] I'll slap your [ __ ] ugly
pregnant misses in front of you, you
silly [ __ ] And break your [ __ ] jaw
whilst I'm at it. You [ __ ] stupid
You [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Yeah.
Stupid idiot, bro. Mad.
Anyways, put the link up, bro.
Yeah. You don't know who Christian Izzy
is. You don't even know her name. You
don't even know the first letter to her name.
I can come to where you live. Yet you
said you was going to come on my door.
You're a little [ __ ] house. You're a
little [ __ ] house, bro. These people.
Hey, Steven B. They're just little [ __ ]
houses. That's what they are in this
community. Shitous, bro. They're just
little shitouses. That's what they are, bro.
Just absolute little shitouses.
Yeah. Anyways, bro, [ __ ] him off. Anyways, bro.
Yeah, that's it.
are you eating today anyway? Stephen
I almost lost brain cells there, bro.
Sorry, man. I almost lost brain cells.
That's how [ __ ] these people are.
They make you lose brain cells. They're so disabled.
Yeah. Do you know the thing is Stephen
Alij? No matter how many times they want
to try and call me a MTO, I'm better
looking than them, bro. I'm better
looking than all of these people. I'm
better looking. I'm in better shape than
them. I'm literally better than these
people in every way. Which confuses me
when they try to talk about you. They're
trying to talk about people that are
better than them. Better than these
middle-aged ugly O's. That's the only
thing that I found a bit like weird,
bro. Like people do what they do on
YouTube. Yeah. whatever people do, but
they're trying to talk about people that
are better than them in every single way
possible. Confidence, looks, more money,
more family. Uh you're just better than
them in in every way. And then they come
on here and then try to talk about you, bro.
Middle-aged ugly people trying to talk
about you. People that are better than
them, bro. Come on now. Pathetic.
Very, very, very pathetic.
Think about it, Steven Howard. Why are
none of these people out with their
mates? Why are they sat on YouTube on a
Saturday at 6:00
in the evening? Why are these people not
with their friends? Why are these people
not with their misses? Why are they sat
all alone on YouTube? Come on. They
didn't answer me, did they, bro? Why are
they sat on YouTube with nobody
typing with their shitty little
comments? Where's their friends? Where's
their misses? Where's their night out?
You get me, bro? Do you get the point
I'm trying to make? So, it's funny, bro.
It is funny.
It is funny to be honest with you, bro.
Kind of. But they're sat on YouTube.
They've got no friends. They got no
money. They got no misses. And they're
trying to talk about other people.
[ __ ] hell, son.
You need to get a life, lad.
Oh, look at that, bro. What a loser.
They're proper proper life losers, bro.
I'm not even ending the live stream,
bro. I'm not even ending it. That's how
much I give a [ __ ] about this community,
bro. I don't.
Oh, that's funny, bro.
No, I'm not even restarting. I can't be asked.
I literally can't be asked, bro.
No, I can't be asked.
I literally can't be asked, lad.
One second, bro.
Oh, if it goes, it goes. I don't give a [ __ ] bro. Yeah. Yeah, man.
There we go, bro.
[ __ ] damn so disabled, bro.
You know, hey, Steven Howard, you know
women that I speak to normally, I don't
speak to them on Instagram, you know
that? They don't know anyone that I
speak to, bro.
They don't know anybody that I speak to.
So don't let them try to trick you
saying they know people I speak to. They
don't know nothing, bro. I don't have
serious people on on my Instagram, bro. Uh uh.
Yeah, I don't, bro.
Stalking little gay little [ __ ] ugly
bastards. He just reeks of autism, bro.
If you ever wanted to know Yeah. what
autism is, just go on L J's channel.
Just autistic people with no life. How
many years have these people been on
this shitty ass community, bro?
Can you imagine how bad it feels to be
almost hurting your mom council,
bro? He's talking about himself, right?
Let me let me let Right. Let me see if
this guy's blocked.
I'm going to say some madness to him now.
One sec. I'm going to say some madness.
One second, bro.
I'm going to start talking about his kid
and everything as well, bro. Yeah.
Watch. One second, bro. I'll type it.
I'm going to get nasty, bro. Trust me.
Yeah. brings you likes when I'm like
this in it, bro. Yeah, I'm watching it. I'm typing.
Watch, bro. I can get nasty, bro. Trust me.
I'm going to talk I'm going to talk
about his kids as well, bro. Watch.
Yeah, I'm going to talk about his kids.
Your ugly fat is pregnant with a milk,
man. Actually, you're never going to
cover my [ __ ] door, bro.
Yeah. Let's see if he types back, bro.
Let's see if he types back.
Let's see if he types back, bro.
I'll get nasty, bro. Trust me, I'll get
nasty. Proper proper nasty, bro.
Proper proper nasty. Yeah, trust me.
Well, trust me. Yeah. One second. >> Yeah.
I'll I'll happily slap you up. One second. One sec.
It's not yours. It's the milkman's. One sec.
Yeah, bro. Did you see it? Yeah. chopped up.
I'll give her one little [ __ ] slap in
her little [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Told him I beat his pregnant
misses up in front of him. You know what
I'm saying, brother? Yeah. [ __ ]
Yeah, he's nowhere to be seen now, is
he? And trust me, bro, I can't imagine
someone saying that to me, bro, if I'm
expecting a child. And he won't do
nothing. That's the thing with these
people. You can say whatever you want to
them, but they'll never do anything.
They'll never ever ever do anything.
They'll never ever ever ever do
anything, lad. I don't know if I got
blocked, but I just said some madness.
I just said some madness, bro. Mad. Yeah,
you can say whatever you want to these
people, Greavesy, and they're never and
they're never going to say anything
back. They're never going to do anything
I said to him, I'm I'll kick the [ __ ]
out of these pregnant Mesy
[ __ ] like a dirty greasy [ __ ] master
whilst I do it. He ain't going to do
nothing to me, bro. Never in a million years.
Never in a million years. No one's
worried about these people.
And And I said, "It's the milkman's,
baby. It's not yours. Stop saying that
you're expecting a kid. It's the
milkman's baby." Yeah.
It's the It belongs to the milkman.
Isn't that right, Grezy? The milkman's
kid. It's not your kid. It's a milkman's.
Oh, some little [ __ ] fat [ __ ]
Well, it didn't show. I did say that.
I did say that. I don't know why I didn't.
Pretending that you've gone on someone's door.
Pretending that you go on people's doors
when you [ __ ] don't. You [ __ ] sab bastard. Mad little [ __ ]
I'll beat your pregnant woman up in
front of you and laugh about it whilst I
do it. You don't believe me, Grezy. You
really, really don't.
You really, really don't. And I'll give
him a cheeky smile. A cheeky lad smile
when I do it. Test me, bro. The guy
knows where I live. He said that he's He
told me, bro, he told everyone he was
coming on the door, bro.
He told everyone that he was coming on
the door and then he never He's a
[ __ ] What grown man, bro? Listen
listen to this. What grown men say
they're going to come on someone's door
and then don't do it?
You know what I'm saying? Who who who
does that, bro? You know,
[ __ ] little [ __ ] Yeah. Little low life.
Can you hear me? Yeah.
No. Can you hear me now? Yeah.
There we go. Bro,
where's that thingy gone?
When he was lying to people that he was
going to [ __ ] come on people's doors.
There we go. Is he blocked?
Yeah, he is blocked. I've unblocked him now. Anyways,
yeah. Yeah, he's unblocked now. So,
yeah. You didn't go in anyone's door,
you little [ __ ]
You didn't go in anyone's [ __ ] door.
You and your fat ugly pregnant misses.
Bring her as well and see what happens.
Simple as that. If you're if you're to
go to come on someone's door, bro, we
need to make it like proper. Know what I
mean? We need to make it good and proper.
I don't give a [ __ ] if your M is a liar.
She's a dirty [ __ ] carrying a milkman's
baby. Hey, listen. He's He's unblocked.
Yeah, he's unblocked. He's unblocked.
She's a lawyer. Tell her to suck my dick.
Yeah, man. Record everything I've said.
Yeah. Yeah. No one cares.
Yeah. You tell your lawyer to suck my
dick, the dirty pregnant [ __ ] How about
that one? She's a dirty little slapper.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Recall that as well.
Your MS is a dirty little slapper
carrying the milkman's baby. Yes. Yes.
Record that as well.
Yeah. She's a lawyer. A dirty little
slapper. Sleep about. And you're not
going to do nothing about it.
You're going to do nothing about it,
Giza. Nothing about it. Geyser. Yeah, it
is bad. Yeah. Your lawyer, Mrs. is
carrying the milkman's baby cuz you you
fire you fire blanks. You fire blanks
and she's carrying the milkman's baby.
So some [ __ ] baldy [ __ ] with no money
with someone carrying the milkman's baby
is coming on here talking [ __ ] about me
and you're not going to do nothing about
it. That's that's the worst thing about
it, bro. The worst thing about it is
you're not going to do anything about
it. She's carrying the milkman's baby. I
want to do the little dance that you
done. Cheeky cheek cheeky chappy. Like
you're going to come on anyone's door,
you little sad bastard. Slide to
redstone that you that you knocked on
people's door. I was waiting for you all
day that day, mate. Cuz I didn't go out,
you know. Bring your [ __ ] ugly lawyer
pregnant Mrs. Pregnant with a milkman's
baby. Come on, big man. Come on. It's
about time. In 2026, one of these people
start showing what they're about, bro.
You get it? I spoke about your ugly
misses. I spoke about a [ __ ] unborn
[ __ ] kid. For [ __ ] sake, what what
more are you supposed to [ __ ] say?
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
And this guy actually started on me, by
the way, cuz he was talking about going
on people's doors. So, okay. Yeah,
about like going on people's doors and [ __ ]
So I thought, "Okay, really, really,
really [ __ ] off, you stupid [ __ ]
You stupid little cunt."
And that's it, bro.
I don't give a [ __ ] if your [ __ ] Mrs.
is a lawyer. I couldn't give a [ __ ]
There's people on Reddit I argued with
that were police officers, Grievy. Some
of them work for the police.
Some of them actually work. I couldn't
give a monkeyy's [ __ ] If there was if
there was if there was a monkey in the
jungle, I wouldn't give a [ __ ] And he
wouldn't give a [ __ ] A [ __ ] liar.
A [ __ ] liar, mate.
Jesus Christ. [ __ ] hell, bro. Do you
think anyone gives a [ __ ]
You stupid [ __ ]
Don't tell people you're going to start
coming on people's [ __ ] doors.
[ __ ] stupid idiot.
You're never that brave. You're not a
[ __ ] You're not a mad [ __ ] Yeah,
stupid [ __ ] idiot.
Loser, bro. Proper loser.
Proper proper loser, bro.
[ __ ] carrying the milkman's, baby.
I'm carrying the milkman's. [ __ ] idiot.
Thinking of eating greasy, but I can't
really be asked.
I can't really be asked. Nah. Psychotic
Pete. That's [ __ ] funny, bro. Yep.
I only had one kind of Coke today, you
know. One kind of Coke.
I had one kind of coat, bro.
Yeah, I have a skin tragic mess. Come on
my door and say it to my face like you
said you was going to. Come on, big man.
Come on. Come on. Yeah, you are skin
just like your ugly lawyer Mrs. Skin. Go
and recall that as well. You stupid
little [ __ ] trying to say to [ __ ] Red
Star that you're coming on people.
You're never going on anyone. You're not
mad. You're not mad. There's not one
person on this community that's mad
enough to do that.
You're not mad, bro. [ __ ] going on
people's channels saying that you're
coming on people's door.
Really? Really, big man? Really? Get in
your dreams, bro.
I don't give a [ __ ] if she's a pregnant
lawyer. I don't give a [ __ ] She got
come in. She's a dirty [ __ ] Yeah. look
talking about police. That's fine, bro.
I've got your comments where you said
you're going to come on my door.
Yeah, you [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Don't act
like you're bad and then when somebody
tells you to come on the door, don't act
like you're a mad [ __ ] cuz you're
really, really, really, really, really,
really, really, really not. Yeah.
Shouldn't you as a man be protecting
what I'm saying?
What the police all you want, bro? I got
evidence where you're saying you're
coming on my [ __ ] door. You [ __ ]
stupid [ __ ] with your ugly pregnant
lawyer. I got [ __ ] up by the by the milkman.
You got [ __ ] in by the milkman.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Yeah, I've also got
it where you're saying you're going to
come on people's [ __ ] door, big man.
And your comments,
you [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. Yeah. Go call the police. You
little gay boy. Your little police boy.
Yeah. Little police boy. Exactly. See,
they give it, but they can't take it.
They say they're going to come on
people's door and stuff and then they
end up like a little police boy. [ __ ]
your pregnant ugly Mrs. who got [ __ ]
up by the milkman.
[ __ ] your ugly lawyer, Mrs. I don't give
a monkeys. [ __ ] Instead of [ __ ]
calling the police, police boy, should
you be on someone's door?
Yeah, bro. You're not blocked. You're
You're not blocked, you stupid [ __ ] And
[ __ ] your pregnant misses that got
[ __ ] [ __ ] up the dumpster by the by
the [ __ ] Yeah.
You wish. [ __ ] you and your ugly you and
your [ __ ] ugly pregnant misses. [ __ ]
you and your lawyer come dumpster misses. Yeah.
Dumpster misses. You little loser.
Dumpster baby. See, they can't get as
nasty as you. So then they get the
police involved. Run to the police cuz
you got owned. I love it, bro. Yeah.
It's the milkman's, baby. Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
There we go. I love it, bro. Woo!
Did you like that little meme?
Yeah. And you'll do nothing. Anyways,
see you later.
Guy's a [ __ ] clown, bro. Giving it
the big Steven Hour. Yeah. And then when
he gets called out, he's saying that
he's running to the police. What a
loser. [ __ ] you. And [ __ ] your pregnant
lawyer, Mrs. You got come in by the [ __ ] milkman.
who got [ __ ] up by the milkman. And no
one should be saying that about anyone.
She got [ __ ] up by the milkman and I'm
saying it and you know where I live and
you're not going to do nothing.
Simple. You [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] How's
about that one?
I [ __ ] love it.
You're going to come on
If this guy come, he would have got
humiliated, bro. Proper. You no job, no
mates, no life. What have I told you?
What have I stop projecting your gay
life onto me, bro? Yeah,
that is literally you. No job, no mate.
Stop talking about yourself. Go cry to
your pregnant lawyer, Mr. You got [ __ ]
up by the by the by the milkman.
Tinky diggy. [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
One second. I want to talk about the
baby now. One sec.
Well, probably one second.
Simple, right? Yeah.
Cheeky cheeky cheeky
cheeky cheeky. Go in the comments. Greasy. Cheeky cheeky.
I'm a cheeky cheeky chappie.
I'm a cheeky cheepy chucky chappie. Cheeky cheeky. [ __ ] idiot.
I love it, bro. I love it.
Am I psychotic, Greasy?
Grezy? Am I psychotic, lad?
It's funny, isn't it? Yeah.
No, it's funny, isn't it? Yeah. Yeah. Is
Stupid little [ __ ]
Yeah. Knock knock tomorrow PJ. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, bro. You keep telling
yourself that, bro. Knock knock. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. You wish, please, boy.
Yeah, you wish. You little police boy.
Police boy. He's known as the police by now, bro.
>> Yeah. Don't ever [ __ ] try and tell me
you're going to [ __ ] come on my door,
you stupid [ __ ] This was like a week
ago, bro. He was saying this. Don't
[ __ ] try and tell me you're going to
come on my [ __ ] door, you stupid little [ __ ]
Yeah. Or anywhere where I live, should I
say. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Lord have powerful people on their side,
do they? Oh. Oh, do they? Oh, I'm so
scared. Oh, I'm so scared.
I'm terrified. Oh.
Oh, I'm so terrified.
Oh, I'm so scared.
[ __ ] [ __ ] The wee little [ __ ]
Oh, I'm so scared. I'm [ __ ] myself.
Yeah. No, I don't think so.
Trying to give it the big man [ __ ] How
you're coming on people's [ __ ] door.
Yeah, you [ __ ] little fanny.
Yeah, little fanny. loser.
And then more self-reflecting on the
Lavry Mong's channel.
Projection upon projection upon
projection upon projection upon
projection. It's all it is with them,
bro. That don't bother me. their little self-reflecting comments.
But yeah, this guy said that he's going
to come on people's doors and [ __ ] [ __ ] that. Yeah,
that's that, bro.
So, you eating today, Greg getting a
takeaway or what?
I still feel agitated, bro, from earlier.
Yeah, I still feel agitated from earlier, bro.
Oh, yeah. Chicken and rice.
So, what are we like? So, we spoke about
a new channel. Um, Stephen Hour with me
and Greavvesy. We I've got a new I've
got a new channel, bro. I'm going to
send you the link. Yeah.
But we need Triple H to join as well
because it's only like six, five, six of
us anyways. We need Kieran to join too.
And then we could just go on that
channel and Yeah, bro.
I got your email. I got your Instagram.
But we need Triple H as well. Yeah.
Just leave these losers on this loser community.
These life's losers.
I tried to have a normal conversation.
They can't have a normal conversation.
Wasn't I trying to have a normal
conversation earlier, Steven Howard?
They can't have a normal conversation. I
say, "Why are you on YouTube 24/7?" They
can't answer it. "Why can't you come and
show your face?" They can't answer it.
You know, they're idiots, bro.
They're severely damaged goods. That's
what the people are in this community.
Just old fat
farts that's got nothing going for
themselves. Sat on here all day, every
day. It's their life, bro. It's their
life. They've been on here more than me today.
Mad, mad, mad, mad, mad.
Look at this all night mic trying to
trigger me. YouTube got got his money stopped.
Sad, sad, sad, bro. You really do. You
just feel sorry for people like that,
bro. I feel bad for them. Sometimes it's
funny, but then I kind of feel bad for them.
That's They hate themselves so much. You
can tell by the way they comment. It's
just a cry for help. I do feel bad for these people.
Sad, rejected, jealous losers. Nothing
going for themselves. You do have to
laugh at them, bro. You really, really
do. Bless them.
Bless, bless, bless them in life.
Bless them in life, bro.
Nothing going for themselves. These people
sad. I just want to know why these
people are not out with their mates. Steven Howard,
I just want to know why these people are
out with their little mates today.
No one else. We're all alone. We're all
skin. I know. I know. I know. I know. I
know. So, why are these people on YouTube?
They've been on YouTube for the past
[ __ ] god knows how long. They're
still on it, bro.
Why are these people on YouTube?
Why don't they out with their mates?
Steven Howard, they're just sat at home
fat nobodyies, bro. Believe you me, bro.
Anyways, enough about these retards.
Yeah, I think he's lying as well. You're
not on no [ __ ] diet, Grezy. Don't lie to us.
I actually haven't ate today. I've had
one can kind of coke. That's it.
One second. Let me go on my thingy. Who is
stop removing people? Yeah,
like I said, I won't be eating today.
No way. I'm too agitated, bro.
No, it's not good, bro. I'm hungry, bro.
I'm hungry. I haven't ate today.
It just push you off your food, didn't
it? the roulette and [ __ ] It just puts
you off your food.
It just completely puts you off your
food. Push me off my food.
I won't eat today, bro.
Yeah, bro. Look,
Peter Belly can put his camera on. These
people can't put their cameras on.
No, they can't cuz they're fat and ugly.
See, one thing you ask with these
people, just put your cameras on. They
can't do it. You say to them, just put
your cameras on. Put your cameras on.
Put your cameras on. And they can't do
it. They literally cannot put their
cameras on. Bro, look at this. I'm not
afraid to show my face.
I'm not show afraid to show any part of
me. Look at me, bro. I'm a sexy
[ __ ] Not fat, not ugly like
these people. Look. Look at me, bro.
These people can't show their faces.
They can't show what they look like.
They're ashamed of their looks, but they
want to try and criticize other people.
Isn't that funny? None of these people
could show their faces. None of these
people can put their cameras on.
You know what I mean, bro? I love that,
bro. I I love that, man.
Nothing ugly about me, lad. Nothing fat Yeah.
Sorry about that, lads. Oh, [ __ ] I need
to wipe this. >> Yeah. [ __ ]
Yeah, sorry about that, bro. [ __ ]
Nothing fat about me, lad. Nothing ugly
Not like these ugly people on YouTube,
bro. Had to wipe that camera, man.
Yeah. Sorry about that, bro. Look at
that, bro. Isn't it funny how Look, I
can show my face. These people can't
show their faces due to embarrassment.
Let's put the link up again, bro. See if
if any of these people want to join.
I haven't even had a shower today, bro. [ __ ]
Yeah, these people can't show their faces.
I don't know, bro.
It was just dark, so you didn't see anything. Yeah.
See, they call people stuff. Yeah. Look
at this, bro. Yeah, they call people
stuff, but you're they call you they try
to call you stuff, bro. Yeah, but you're
showing your face. They can't show their
Is it that you can show your face, they
can't they can't show their faces. You
know what I'm saying, bro? Due to embarrassment
of their looks
and they want to call other people.
They want to call other people that are
better than them. Yeah, right.
Look at me, bro. Look at my face. Yeah.
And then look at Not legs's face. Look, bro. Look.
[ __ ] way better looking than that
ugly [ __ ] My [ __ ] face don't look
like it's [ __ ] melting. These people
can't show their faces.
You know what I mean, bro?
Nothing fat about me. Nothing porky
about me. I'm still the one showing my
face. These people can't
know what I'm saying, bro. I'm the one
still showing my face. These people
can't show their faces. What does that
tell you about them, bro? What does that
tell you about them?
Is Rick still alive? Let me see.
It's not hard, bro.
Let me see. Oh,
have a look.
I need to go to the barbers, bro. Look
at my hair. [ __ ]
I need I need to go to the barbers, bro.
But look at me, bro. Look. No face fat,
nothing fat about me. You can even see
my cheekbones. Look, you can actually
see my cheekbones. Nothing fat about me,
lad. There's also nothing ugly about me.
Like these people that can't show their
faces that continue coming on here every
day talking about other people, bro.
Yeah, it's true though, isn't it, bro?
Look porky. Nothing porky about me.
Nothing fat about me. Nothing ugly about
me. Nothing bored about me. Nothing.
Nothing at all whatsoever.
I got my Simpsons top on. Yeah.
Well, you know this. Yeah. It's It's a
bit big. This is a medium, but it's a
It's a bit big. just T-shot. Yeah.
I want a battered sausage, Beezy.
I feel like a battered sausage.
Yeah, no one cares, bro. No one cares.
I fancy a little battered sausage.
No, I don't need to own him. I've
already owned him. Life owns him as well.
No, they need to get a life. I've
already owned all of these people today.
I said to them, "Come on camera." They
can't come on camera. They can't come on
camera and show their faces.
No, they can't come on camera and show
their faces, which is strange.
Do I have money? I've told you multiple
times I have money. Again, we autistic disabled community
I don't think I'm going to eat, bro. I
can't be asked.
Yeah, I can't be asked.
Nope. You're not seeing my money, mate.
You've already seen my money before.
Never show money again. Never ever show
money again to these self-reflectors. Never.
Not even £10. Not even one pence.
Never happening, lad. Yep.
>> Yeah. I didn't go on holiday, but I was
too busy [ __ ] [ __ ] I was too busy
going out three times. I was too busy
going out three uh days a week, three,
four days a week. And I didn't sp
thousands. I've never sp thousands. I
spent thousands on designer clothes and
meals and nights out. I didn't sp thousands.
Nope. I don't need to spawn any I don't
need to spawn any of my clothes. I'm not
skin. Thank you very much. Jesus Christ.
Yeah, because I don't go out drinking
much anymore. We I've never seen what
you people look like. Why don't you show
us what you people look like? I We
haven't seen what you people look like
despite going on about people's looks
every [ __ ] day.
Yeah, we haven't seen what you people
look like. Like you got something to hide.
Calling people monties when they're
better looking than you. Again, only on
this autistic disabled community would
that happen. No other community. Only this one.
Yeah. Why can't we see what you people look like?
You got something to hide?
To be fair, if I was as ugly as you
people, I probably wouldn't show my face
to be fair. To be fair,
I don't need to I don't need to prove
myself to any of you people.
You need to start owning me by showing
that you're not fat and ugly. You need
to own me, bro.
Prove to me that I'm speculating and
you're not fat and ugly. I'll put the
link up again.
Two seconds. Bear with me, dads. Own me.
Prove to me. Prove to me that I don't
know anything about you people. Prove to
me that I was wrong when I said that
you're fat and ugly.
Prove me wrong. Own me. I need a good
ownage. Come on. You can't do that now,
can you? You would never show your looks
cuz you know the truth, don't you? Just
like I do, mate.
Madness, bro. Madness. Absolute madness.
How long have you people been on this
shitty ass community? Huh?
How long, man? How long?
How [ __ ] long, man?
So, if I'm speculating, why can't you
prove me wrong then?
Yeah, I'm coming off this community
stream permanently. Greasy, we're going
to go on a new channel. Yeah,
we're going to go on the new channel. Yeah, bro. 100%.
Okay, captain. Okay.
Bro, I can't be bothered to eat, bro.
Need to eat, but I can't be bothered.
Can't order Savoa Grezy cuz the halal
thing isn't it?
Because of the halal problem. You can't
even order Coke from anywhere cuz it
just tastes like [ __ ]
not a fint.
I like Sublo. Fancy some chips,
you know. Some nice chips with salt and vinegar.
Salt and vinegar chips.
No, you can't order a Big Mac because
anytime you order McDonald's, it just comes cold.
It comes cold.
So, I don't order stuff like that.
Yeah, I might go get some chips.
I thought I didn't know who Donald Trump
was. UK asylum.
I thought I didn't know who Donald Trump was.
Oh, bro. I love it, man. It's funny, is it?
Very funny. E,
I didn't know who Donald Trump was.
No. No, I didn't know.
Not at all, bro.
I'm not a troll. I never troll UK asylum. Never.
I never ever troll.
Why would I troll, bro? What would I get
out of trolling?
No, I don't troll.
Be easy will tell you I'm serious about
everything. I'd never troll. Never ever
I just fancy a bag of chips
with salt and lots of vinegar, you know?
Just like a load of chips.
Just scoffing them all up.
Just a load of chips. Easy.
Yeah, one second. Be back later.