Yo. Okay. So, this is um my response to
Timmy. Yeah. So, yeah. The reason I
messaged your family is cuz, bro, I
literally went on your channel and you
keep going on about me over and over and
over again. And I had the same thing
with Monty the other day. I said, "Keep
my name out of your [ __ ] mouth. I
don't care what you're saying or how
you're saying it. Keep my name out of
your mouth. I'm away from this
community. I'm not involved with these
[ __ ] same repetitive regurgitated
arguments. Like I didn't go live
yesterday for a a [ __ ] reason. I
don't want nothing to do with this
disabled projecting community and you're
bringing me up to try to take the
[ __ ] to try to take the attention off
of you because I assume people are going
for you. Keep my name out your [ __ ]
mouth. We wasn't going back and forth. I
wasn't mentioning you. So stop
mentioning me. mention me again. Every
time you mention me, I'm just going to
keep messaging your family over and over
and over and over and over again. So,
you know, that should be a deterrent to
leave me the [ __ ] alone and stop [ __ ]
mentioning my [ __ ] name. It's as
simple as that. You're never going to
say anything to my face. You're never
going to come to London. You know, you
was even saying um earlier uh you know
um I'm going to meet this person. I'm
going to meet that one. And that didn't
annoy me because you're not talking
about me. And I'm just thinking, bro,
I'm losing brain cells watching this.
You're not going to meet anyone. You've
never ever won a fight against anyone on
here, Timmy. How many people have you
met on this community, Timmy? And you
have not won a fight against anyone. Am
I lying? Like, am I literally lying?
Like, how many L's have I took on this
community? And I've even had wins. And
I've even had wins. And you're still in 2026,
you're still acting the big man on
YouTube. Like, you've been you [ __ ]
millilated. Like literally the last time
you come to London with Tiger, bro, you
was running away. You was running up the
road and you left your mate to get
[ __ ] knocked on the floor and you're
still coming on YouTube giving it the
big self projecting and trying to get me
involved with your [ __ ] Okay, come to
London tomorrow. You can come to London
tomorrow and bring whoever the [ __ ] you
want. I don't give a [ __ ] And at the
end of the day, yeah, if no one from
Birmingham comes tomorrow, bring LT,
bring London Taylor and and that will
prove to you that I'm not scared of him
either because we all know he's going to
try and get involved. I'm not scared of
none of you. Yeah. Do you understand?
So, come tomorrow. Do go live tomorrow.
Bring whoever the [ __ ] you want and you
will see what will happen to you. Simple
as that. Watching your [ __ ] bro. Self
projecting your life onto me once again,
saying about how I lost my last 20 pound
and I'm skin and I am this and I'm that.
Timmy, you don't know how much money
people have. I've not been skinned for
about five or six years. You don't know
how much money people have. You don't
know what money people get. Yeah. So, if
you're bored and you want a bit of
drama, good for you. Don't bring my name
into your [ __ ] and start trying to get
me involved with your [ __ ] [ __ ]
You understand? Like, bro, and then
you're saying about how, you know, what
was it again? Um, about how I'm I've got
no woman. Ah, Timmy, listen, mate. I've
had more women than you've had hot
dinners, you're still a [ __ ] virgin.
You've never even kissed a [ __ ]
woman. The last time we saw women walk
past you, you're [ __ ] blushed. You're
a virgin. You're [ __ ] skint. You're a
gambling addict. I'm not even addicted
to gambling. You know, last month was
the first time I started gambling again
in a year. Like a whole year. I don't
even gamble that much. You are
self-projecting your life onto me. Stop
asking people to show you money, right?
So then people show you money again and
you run away just like you always do.
Which is why we call this an autistic
disabled community, which is why we
tried to get away from it. And stop for
crying out loud. Stop going on about
your nonsle's boyfriend having money. He
has not got no money. Just like you
ain't got no money. Because if you did
actually have money, mate, you would
have beat me at the money game a long
ass time ago. A long ass time ago. But
you two just couldn't because you don't
have it. Like you don't have money. E
don't have money. Just like you're both
virgins. So at the end of the day, bro,
like you've you've annoyed me today.
I've messaged your family because I've
asked you to keep my name out of your
mouth. I don't know how many times. Come
to London tomorrow like you said. Yeah.
I want somebody tore to screen record
that video where you're saying that
you're going to come to London tomorrow
cuz you've annoyed me now. You've
dragged me into your [ __ ] again. Right.
And if you do not come to London
tomorrow, I will be messaging your
family again. Yeah. Because this has got
to stop. Keep my name out of your
[ __ ] mouth. Yeah. At least certain
people would actually be able to say
stuff to, you know, to someone's [ __ ]
face. You understand? So it's like, bro,
you you come to London tomorrow, right?
If you mention my name one more time,
I'm being nice now. And you do not come
to London tomorrow, I'm going to be
messaging your family all day. It's as
simple as that. because I don't like you
keep involving me with your [ __ ] to try
to get the heat off of you. Same thing
with Monty Man the other day. I had to
tell him about his [ __ ] self on Rick
Mason's. Yeah. So, bro, you you saying
all of this [ __ ] Okay. Come and see me
tomorrow like you just said you was
going. Then bring your boyfriend money
with you. Bring whoever you want,
whenever you want, however you want. I
don't care. Yeah. Just make sure you
come tomorrow. Um, and if you don't and
I hear you mention my name one more
time, I'm messaging your family again.
It's as simple as that. So, you know,
you want to keep you want to annoy me.
You want to keep involving me with your
drama when I'm trying to get away from
this place. I'm I'm purposely trying to
get away from retards like you. You're
probably the biggest [ __ ] on here. I
mean, you started this whole community
and you keep dragging me into your [ __ ]
So, okay. Yeah. Come tomorrow, bro. Come
anywhere you want to in London tomorrow
and you go live. Yeah. And if you don't
do it, I'm messaging your family again
tomorrow. You mention my name one more
time after this video and you do not
come and see me tomorrow, I'm messaging
your family again. I don't give a [ __ ]
Right? And if you want to me and you
want to message Laney or whatever, I'll
simply explain to anyone who I need to
explain. I've told this guy, keep my
name out of your [ __ ] mouth. And he
has not done it. Yeah. Simple. Go
selfroject your gambling addict skint
life onto someone else and keep my name
out of it. Yeah. This isn't a back and
forth thing. I've not done videos on you
today. I've not mentioned you. I didn't
go live yesterday. You're bringing me up
now. Yeah. So, put your money where your
mouth is and come to London tomorrow.
Bring whoever you want. I don't care.
Try to set me up in any way. I don't
give a [ __ ] I'm not scared of no one.
Yeah. So, just make sure you come
tomorrow. Yeah. And if you don't and you
mention my name one more time and you
wind me up, I'll just message your
family again. It's as simple as that.
I'll keep messaging your family until
you learn Yeah. to stop doing this [ __ ]
You done this [ __ ] to Monty man as well.
Yeah, it always starts from you. Yeah.
So, make sure you show up to her
anyways. Like you said, you [ __ ]