Right, sorry about that. Um, I ended up
recording by accident, so this will be part two.
It's coming along nicely.
Look at that, mate. That's just pure mints.
People are going to call me boring
because I don't have anything but
bacon and like normally onions as well
in the burger, but
like I said, it's been marinated in
onions already. So,
This is so yummy.
So, you can put it here. Actually,
I bent this. Yeah.
I mean, you could put it here, but
if you try to close it here, then
if you try to close it here, then it
will get stuck there.
But it obviously cooks spare in the center. So [Music]
leave it like that for now. Yeah.
I don't like them too done, my burgers.
That's the thing with beef is if you
have it too done,
you sort of ruin it. [Music] Must
start waking up the neighbors with that
smell, mate. Smells lush. Okay. Close it. [Music] One second.
Yep. Put it back in. [Music]
Turn it again.
Might be too long now. Oops.
I feel like Spongebob cooking a Krabby Patty.
Turn this and then turn it back.
Yeah. Krabby Patty, mate. [Music]
Yeah. See it bent from last time. [Music]
I think I should start a [ __ ] um
cooking channel to be fair.
Well, I'll pause and resume.
Right, almost ready. [Music]
So, obviously got the cheese there
and the buns. So, I need to melt that. [Music] Bacon's ready.
I like my bacon very crispy. [Music]
Oh, look at that.
Oh, just need to be careful with this
hot cheese, eh?
[ __ ] Could be quite hot, man.
Damn, that's hot, bro. And
This is how you make
a homemade burger.
Hot cheese is hot, man.
There we go.
What you do? So, you put the bacon here.
I was going to have one, but I thought I
might as well two because the burger's so big. Jesus.
And you really want to push it down and
then just gobble it all up. So, that's
how you make a uh homemade burger.
Look at that. Jesus. I can't wait. Let
it cool down for a second.