Yo, so this is going to be a video to um
L J because I was watching your live
stream back yesterday. I was meant to
reply, but I didn't get time to. I was
busy. Um so anyways, um what is it with
you and Virgin Boy coming on here trying
to convince people that you've got
money? Like you're trying to convince
yourself and you're trying to convince
other people like that you've got money.
Like firstly, we've got some [ __ ]
idiot taking out of his taking out his
housing benefit trying to convince
people that he's got money when in
reality he lives in a bedsit. He's got
no bed. It took him to [ __ ] 30 to go
abroad and he's literally living below
the poverty line. Um, but somehow every
time he gets his housing benefit, he
needs to feel the need to withdraw all
of the money to act like he's got money,
then put it back in before the housing
benefit takes it and deduct it from his
account. I mean, Jesus Christ, I have
never seen so many£10
notes in my life. Who the [ __ ] gives out
that many10 notes? Like, you just know.
He actually thinks he's got money. like
he actually thinks he's got loads and
loads of money when in reality he has he
has nothing. And I don't understand why
these people are still trying to play
the whole money game when they've
literally lost over and over again. Like
I'm still waiting for somebody to show
me 10 grand. Um and all people seem to
be showing me is their housing benefit
or like £500 or whatever. I mean think
about it. living in a bedsit with no bed
in it. Like, it literally does not get
worse than that. Like, honestly, it
doesn't. Um, but I just can't believe
it, man. Like, if if you're actually
wanting to play the money game, you need
to show higher than the amount that
someone's already shown you, which I
showed five 5.7, but I was like, "Okay,
well, we we call it 10." But no one's
been able to show that. So all of this
like people showing their benefits, it's
just embarrassing. Um anyways, on to you
LJ. Um you was what was you saying? Um
excuse me. Um you were saying about um
how uh do why do I keep saying that I
have savings when I don't? Um I keep
saying I have savings because I do. I
mean that's a pretty normal thing to
have is savings. I should have a lot
more savings to be honest, but you know,
things happen. Um, and you're saying
that you doubt that I even have £500.
Bro, why would I have £500? We're not
all like you and your followers sat on
YouTube all day ain't got no money.
Like, bro, again, I I think part of your
disability, LJ, is getting um other
people uh mixed up with yourself. Why
the [ __ ] would I not have £500?
Like, do you hear yourself? Like I
literally bought a TV 2 days ago which
was near enough £500 now. Um yeah. So
why wouldn't somebody have £500? You're
also another person that got shown money
and you still haven't shown us anything.
Um so I don't understand. And we all
know that you really really are the ski
one as well. Just like Virgin Boy. Um
it's not that you you come on here
trying to convince people that you've
got money. It's it is that. And also
think about it, right? You claim,
excuse me, you claim that you've got all
this money, that you get a good income, ret.
Now, I was on your channel yesterday and
I noticed that you've got a store where
you're selling um merch. Now, here's
where none of it makes any sense. If you
get all of this money, why are you
swallowing up your pride just to make a
tiny tiny tiny bit extra? You see how it
makes no sense whatsoever? See, that all
started from big YouTubers. Like,
somebody would be a big YouTuber, they'd
get loads and loads of followers, and
then they would make Merts to make loads
and loads of loads and loads of money.
What makes no sense about you is you
claim that you get loads of money, you
have loads of money, but you're doing
everything possible, including
swallowing your pride just to get a bit
of extra money. It doesn't make any
sense considering like um you know uh
considering what's your followers don't
even buy your merch because they will
skin. Like you got 3,000 subscribers,
bro. All of the people that follow you
um you know it's uh you know they're
skin. So you're not even going to be
making money. And it's not that like
your design is [ __ ] It's not even about
that actually because if you had a huge
following and you was going to make a
lot a lot a lot of money from it then
fair play. I mean most of the YouTubers
the big YouTubers that make merch there
is no substance behind any of their
merch but it makes sense for them to do
it because they're going to be
accumulating millions. You are not going
to be barely getting an extra150
a month. You see how none of it makes
sense? Why somebody would swallow all
their pride, beg for donations, but they
claim that they've got all this money.
You see how it just points to you being
skinn. You see how it just points and
points and points. It it it's more like
you're on three, four, 500 a month doing
anything to get extra money because you
need that extra money. Not that you get
[ __ ] two and a half, three grand a
month or however much you get needing to
get an extra bit of money. It doesn't
make no sense whatsoever why somebody in
your in your boat, right, that claims
you get all this money, claims you own
property, um would do the most degrading
thing just to get a tiny bit extra
money. It doesn't make no sense. None of
it makes no sense whatsoever.
So, you're you're one to talk about
people being skinned, but bro, come on.
Let's let's look at let's look at the facts here.
You're on YouTube all day every day. You
don't leave your house. You literally
beg for money and you're doing and
you're looking through every single
avenue just to try and earn a tiny tiny
small amount of extra money. You see how
it all points to you being skinn? You
know, we can all like say this, that,
and the other, but you can't can you
understand how it all points to you? you
are the one that doesn't have money. You
understand that? That's how it looks.
All the evidence suggests that you
literally are the skin one, bro. Because
you wouldn't be doing that if you had money.
You know what I'm saying? It just it
doesn't it does not make any sense. Now,
if you was making thousands and
thousands a month, then fair play. You
know, that's that's you was making big
amounts of money. Why wouldn't you do
it? You're making huge amounts of money.
Probably money that you could even
invest. But come on, bro. Would anyone
really go through the struggle that
would really do all of that just to get1£150
extra a month? No. It just goes to show
even more that you you really really
really are are the skin one. But there's
nothing wrong with it. You know, you got
70 75% of people now they struggling
with money, bro. It's nothing to be
ashamed of. But I don't know why you and
Virgin Boy feels the need to come on
here and pretend that you got money.
It's just ridiculous. I never went on
about money. I just said that I had some
savings and I'm looking for something
else. But if you really had all of this
money, you wouldn't be on YouTube
begging. It's it's it's it's as simple
as that. You would not be on YouTube
begging to try and get a tiny extra bit
of money if you had all this money. It
just points to you being skinned. Like
if if if if actually like I'm missing
something here and I'm wrong, then you
know, tell me. But it it really does
point to to you being skin. You know,
it's the same as Virgin Boy. Like he can
show his benefits off as much as he
wants, but think about it. Bedsit, no
bed, couldn't afford to go abroad until
he was 30. Dresses like a complete and
utter [ __ ] It doesn't look good, does
it? Unless I'm Unless it's something I'm
missing. I would say that you both
[ __ ] skint yourselves if I didn't
know any better. I' I'd say you're both
[ __ ] big [ __ ] skin flints. But um
yeah, that's all I wanted to say. L it
doesn't make any sense how you claim
that you have all of this money, but you
would beg and do the most degrading
things just to try and get a little bit
more. Just does not make any sense at
all. Doesn't make no sense. How does
your brain actually work, man? Come on.