Yo. Okay, so time for a new video. Um, I
was supposed to do this video yesterday
to be fair, but yeah, I was tired and I
just fell asleep, so I didn't get around
to doing it, but I'm doing it now. So,
what I want to talk about in this video
is um what is it with these people in
this community seeming to think that
everybody shares the same life as them.
like they seem to think that their
reality, right, goes for everybody else,
you know? Be it them trying to call
people skint when they're the skint
ones. Be it they're trying to call
people ugly when they're the ugly ones.
Be it they try to say that no one's got
friends when they've got no friends.
Like just to name a few examples, like
they seem to generally think
their life and their reality goes for
everyone else. Like they generally
generally think that. So, I was on um
Virgin Boys um short um yesterday and I
saw Money Mike's comment saying about
how I can't show money. Um I mean, yeah,
I can't show money. It's not like I've
ever show money before. I made you all
run away multiple times, right? Nah,
that must have been another PJ. Wasn't
me. Must have been someone else. Um, but
anyways, he said about how um I've got
no money and and I've only got about 50
pound to last me until I get my
benefits. And I'm thinking, what the
[ __ ] is this guy going on about? You
know, that is so random and so specific
to say about someone that you don't even
know. You don't know how much money I
have. You don't know how much um money I
don't have. So, then it gets to my
point. It's self projecting. Fun fact,
Michael, when I went out last Friday, I
saw it through to the Sunday, I spent
over £500. Yeah, you don't know how much
money I have. You don't know how much
money I don't have. That is a clear sign
of self-p projection. Um, same as you
know what L J's followers do. You know,
they sit on YouTube from the time they
wake up to the time they go to bed all
alone trying to call other people skint
and lonely. It's just they they bounce
off of their own lives and think
everyone's got the same life as them.
Um, you know, it's like, and that's the
thing. It's like, you know, here's
another thing, Money Mikey. I know
you're watching this. I wish you done
all of this keyboard warrior freaky
snaky [ __ ] before I went to Birmingham
because I would have called you out. You
know, I generally would have called you
out when I went to Birmingham, but you
weren't doing none of this [ __ ] until I
come back. Typical with these people,
isn't it? They start their [ __ ] as soon
as you go back to London. Um, when you
know I would have called you out just
like I called Prime out, just like I
called Timmy out. Like listen, what is
it with people like [ __ ] nonss, you
know, Money Mike, [ __ ] Ricky
Milindon. Have you noticed that they're
all white, weak, leaky nerds that are as
weak as a newborn puppy. Nothing to look
at in real life. Little shitbags, but
you know, behind the keyboard, they've
got all this energy. It's mad. Like,
they actually are starting to give white
people a bad name. Like because it's
always white people that are doing it as
well. Like and it's like I've met you
literally money Mike and you're not
about anything at all. Like for [ __ ]
sake, how many times were you [ __ ]
arguing with [ __ ] Monty for how many
months and you never even went to his
[ __ ] address? Like you're not about
nothing. You're just like these little self-reflectors,
you know, freaks. That's literally all
you are. You know, you don't know how
much money people have. You don't know
how much money people don't have. But,
you know, if you do want to say
something to my face, um, I will be in
London. I'll be in central London on
Saturday. Um, because I'm going to go
out drinking and you go anywhere in
London and I'll meet you and I'll show
everybody what you're about in real
life. Yeah. I have more money than you
will ever ever have. Yeah. Like, live
with that. You do not know what people
have. You do not know what people don't
have. You stupid little albino dowy
looking [ __ ] Yeah. So, at the end of
the day, you do all of this YouTube
keyboard warrior [ __ ] like your
boyfriend. So, come to London on
Saturday. I'll be in central London.
I'll go anywhere you are cuz I'll be in
the center of London anyway. So, you
know, and if you're not willing to do
that, shut the [ __ ] up. And I was going
to do this privately, but um you know um
you deleted all your videos and I
couldn't comment on anything. So, I'm
doing a video like, "Trust me, I've met
you. You are about nothing." Yeah.
Simple. So, I don't know why you're
coming on here self-reflecting. You do
not know what people have, what people
don't have. I just told you how much I
spent in the past [ __ ] three days.
You don't know me. Yeah, simple. You
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] ugly bastard. So,
and even using [ __ ] Timmy as an example, right?
Uh Timmy, I watched uh Timmy's video
about an hour ago and he done a video to
Smokey Be saying, "Oh, Smokey Bee, you
can say that to the virgin. Um, but you
can't say that to me. And obviously when
he's saying virgin, he's trying to refer
to me. Again, I proved I've had sex. I
approved I've been with women. This is
what I'm saying with these people. They
seem to think their life is like
everyone else's. Same as Timmy. He's a
virgin. We've never seen Timmy with a
woman. We've never seen Timmy have sex.
We've seen me with a woman. We've seen
me have sex. It's self projection. This
is what all of these people do on here
is talk about their own lives. It's
[ __ ] ridiculous, you know? And it's
like I'll bring LJ into it as well. Like
he done a video the other day um showing
what he bought saying about, "Oh, it's
so nice to be able to afford um things
you want." And then he showed New
Balance trainers and a hoodie and jeans.
I mean, yeah, good way to show people
that you can afford anything you want by
spending no more than 200 pound on some
things that you bought. I mean, yeah,
that that will show them, though, Jay.
That will show them. And then it's like
again, even with that, I spent more than
double that the Friday to the Sunday
that I went out. But you still have
these self-reflectors trying to call me
skin. Again, self-p projectors. Um, and
there was a comment as well saying about
how um, this is probably given PJ
nostalgia knowing that, you know, when
he used to go out and buy trainers and
stuff and he can't do it anymore cuz he
doesn't have the sublet money. Um,
firstly, that would not give me
nostalgia because I would never be seen
dead in New Balance. I wouldn't be seen
dead in any of them trampy clothes um
that LJ bought. And secondly, I can go
out right now and buy myself trainers.
can go out right now by myself. Stone
Island jumpers, you don't know me. You
don't know how much money I have. Um,
this is the thing with these people in
this community. They seem to assume
things about people because it goes for
themselves. They seem to think because
their skin, everyone else's skin. Bit
like what I was saying earlier. They
seem to think that everyone's got the
same life as them. Bro, I can go out
literally right now and buy what I want.
You don't know how much money I have.
You don't know how much money I don't
have. Um, you know, this is what I mean.
I don't know what it is with these
people in this community. Um,
thinking that everyone's got the same
life as them. You know, it's like, what
the [ __ ] I can't go out and buy
trainers if I wanted to. I can't go buy
buy a Stone Island jumper. You don't
know how much money I have. Every single
time these people have tried to assume
in the past that I've got no money, I've
shown them money and they've run away.
every single time. Like every single
time, not even half the time, every
time. Like, it's I don't know what it is
with these people thinking that they
know people's lives is just because all
of these things apply to their own
lives. It's like that's what I'm going
to title this video is that what is it
with these people thinking that
everyone's got the same life as them?
Generally, it's it's [ __ ] It really
is [ __ ] They seem to think everyone
is skint like them. I don't know what it
is with these people. [ __ ] madness.