Right. So, this is a video to Joseph
Farra. Um, I've got a bone to pick with
you, right? I'm getting fed up with this
[ __ ] now. No one's bloody
interested. You know, you telling me to
go on these dating apps and these dating
apps, they don't even work, right? You
can't even get a match on these uh
dating apps. I was telling my friend
about this, which is a woman, and her
name is Jaden. And I go on these dating
apps and I can't even get a match.
And if I do get a match, they just troll
me and stuff. And there's like, "Oh,
well, why don't you go out and you
approach women?" And then when you go
out and you approach women, they just
say that they're not interested. Oh,
they've got boyfriends, Joe. Or if they
give me their number, they lead me on.
They lead me on and they play games. And
it's like, what the hell? You know,
people have been saying to me since I
was 13, "Oh, you're going to meet
somebody. Your time will come. You just
need to go out and speak to women." But
then when I speak to women, they all say
the same thing,
Joseph. Even though apparently they're
not the same. It's is I'm getting sick
of this [ __ ] now. Joseph Ferrar, I'm at
my bloody wits end. I bloody well am I?
I bloody well had enough of this, you
know. I'm getting sick and tired, you
know. How much more money and how much
more time do I have to spend looking for
someone? I'm 28 years of age. I should
be settled down by now, you know,
considering I've tried, you know, more
than anyone in the world. I'm getting
sick to death of this. You know, last
week with the GS and the going out, I
spent over a,000 pounds, Joseph. And I'm
not made of money, you know. I'm not I'm
not rich, you know. It's like, how much
more money and and time do I have to
spend trying to find someone in this
bloody country when no one's bloody well
interested? You know, I'm sick of it.
Absolutely bloody sick of it. You know,
the last day I went on was April and I
went out last week and the time before
that was six weeks ago and that was a
lot of effort as well. And even one of
them times I actually looked smack and
still no one's bloody well interested.
You know, it's ridiculous. When's it
going to be my turn, you know, to have a
family, to have love, to have a sex
life, to get my vitamins and my calcium,
you know? I'm I'm bloody well at my wits
end with this now. I'm sick of it. Sick
of it, I say. Got start it.