Indian restaurant. Yeah. And you know
what I love the most when you come in
and you eat as opposed to ordering it is
that the mint sauce is never ever
watery. Look how thick that is. Whereas
when you uh
order it, it's always watery. And a lot
of the time the curry is watery.
Yeah. So just get my vitamins. This is
such a better way to get your vitamins. Um,
you know, than, you know, trying to date
women. No mind games, no leading on, no
white knights making excuses, you know,
poor women just could date women. This
is such a better way to get your
vitamins and be happy. [clears throat]
No mind games, no being led on,
no attitude. This is a life, man.
This is a life, mate.
This is so yummy.
>> I'll pause and resume and the other look comes.
Look at that. Just come out. Oh, look
how red that is. What I call a lovely s.
What's a better way to get your veins?
[ __ ] better way to get your veins.
What I love is when you
when you get this Yeah. And it almost
gets stuck to it because it's so fresh.
A look at that. That is a lovely side, mate.
Pause and resume. Going to eat this and
pause it. Eat it and then resume when
the best comes.
Can't eat it.
Right. finish my starter.
Took me about 3 minutes to yam that now. Absolutely delicious.
Yeah, completely demolished the starter
and the papadoms.
Just waiting for the vindaloo now. The
rice and the non red delish.
Right, here we go. Here's the main now.
Oh, look at that.
Just you can never ever get bored of
[music] this. The naan bread is so hot.
Yeah. That if you touch it, it burns
your bloody fingers. It's lovely. Absolutely lush.
Look at that, matey.
No watery, no nothing.
I just say to the guy, it's the same guy
from last time
that when you come to the restaurant,
it's never ever ever watery.
Put that there. Lovely.
Right, enjoy this now. And yeah,
such a better way to get your vitamins.
Don't have to deal with women. Such a better way. [snorts]