Okay, so a little gambling story whilst
I'm still semi- agitated. So I went to
get the roast dinner and the place that
I get off the train station, there's a
bookies opposite the train station and I
thought, you know what, let me try some
roulette £50 because that's all I can
justify on the two pound roulette. And
I'm telling you, mate, it was [ __ ]
winding me up. Um, I was shouting the
whole shop down and everything and £50 I
can afford to lose £50. But it gets it
gets even better, right? It gets even
better. You literally any money that you
win, it takes it back trying to get the
next spin. Even though the the the bar
is on 30 40%. It will literally miss
about 12 times in a row and get that win
that gave you back off you. So, I'm
thinking you're not even getting a spin
and losing it on the spin. You're not
even getting a spin. When the when the
green is high enough to hit, you know,
one in three, one in four chances and it
would just keep continuously missing.
You know, I got the £50 to 80, back to
40, back to 70, back to 10, back to Oh
my god, I went back and forth about four
times. It got to the point where I just
took the money back. I literally just I
think I took I think I won £1. And this
is what I'm trying to say to you. There
was no such thing as gambling
responsibly because if I lost that £50,
I can afford it. I didn't even lose £50.
I won a [ __ ] quid. You know, like
obviously a pound was nothing, but
technically I actually won a pound. I
didn't lose any of my own money. And it
was [ __ ] annoying me, bro. [ __ ]
annoying me. Um, you don't understand.
So, this is why people like me shouldn't
really gamble. And that's why I don't
gamble. Not because I can't afford it.
Not because I'm living the high life
because of how it gets me. And if I kept
doing it and kept doing it and kept
doing it, I reckon I would have been in
jail by now. Um, it's like a demon
overtakes your body. Um, it's it's
horrible. It is really really bad. Like,
it might sound funny to people. And this
is why I don't do it. And it's not about
you being weak or anything. It's how
you're made and if you're like that, you
shouldn't do it. And that's that's
exactly why I don't do it. This was the
first time in months. I don't even know
why why I did. It's just, you know, I
mean, it's like it it generally feels
like it is a country designed to annoy
you. It literally literally does like
the women, the gambling, um the prices
of things. It literally feels like it's
a country designed to get under your
last nerve. Um this country, it really
really does. It's always a negative when
you're here. A negative in this country.
Um, you'll find that like the roast
dinner I just had, it cost me £44. I'm
thinking, what the [ __ ] £44 that roast
dinner cost me. And um, and the thing
is, I'm not even in central London. Then
I could be like, all right, we're in
central London. It cost me £44 and I'm
out of London. What the [ __ ] For a bit
of chicken, lamb. No, it wasn't even
lamb. It was chicken, pork, and beef.
There weren't even no lamb. Which lamb
is the most expensive. So you can get a
whole leg of lamb for like 40 quid. That
cost me 44 [ __ ] pound and it didn't
even have a bit of lamb on it. That is
insane, bro. That is insane. I couldn't
believe that, you know. £44. That is
really, really bad. It generally just
feels like it is a country designed to
annoy you and get under your last
nerves. I don't know if anyone else has
felt like that with the gambling even
just now like the prices, the women, the
people, like various different things.
It does generally feel like it is a
country designed to annoy us.
As as ridiculous as that may sound, it
generally generally does
feel that way. Like what you see, you
have to wait around for things.
[ __ ] trying to get bumped, gambling
[ __ ] you over. It's madness. And I
didn't even lose any money. I took my 50
back. [ __ ] that. [ __ ] that. It was
winding me up so badly, bro. And it
still annoyed me to the point where I
didn't really enjoy my dinner. That's
not They say gamble responsibly.
I could lose 150, 200, 300, 400 lb now
and I'd be comfortable.
I didn't even lose the 50 I put in today
and it's still making me like that. So
you you be the judge. I could lose 500
600 right now. would I would be able to
live. It wouldn't affect me. It wouldn't
affect me financially. It would affect
mentally obviously because it is now.
That just goes to show you if you're
anyone like me, you shouldn't gamble.
You shouldn't. God knows where I would
have end up now if I carried on gambling
the way I was gambling. Any kind of
amount £10, 20, 600. God know I reckon
I'd be in prison to be honest with you
for smashing up a machine or something.
It's not good. It's really really not
good. So there you have it people.
There's no such thing as gambling
responsibly because that should not make
you like that. The
>> next station is
>> What's the excuse now? You can afford to
lose £50 and you didn't even lose £50.
You You got the money back because I was
sick of going up, down, up, down.
[ __ ] give it a rest. You know, it's annoying. [music]
I won a pound, bro. I won a [ __ ]
pound. I didn't even lose anything. I
won a pound. [ __ ] me. [ __ ] annoying.
I was going to show the money cuz they
gave it in cash, but I don't show money
to self-reflectors. They call people
skin. They gave it in cash even though I
paid by card. Strange. But um yeah, I
don't show money to self
self-reflectors. But yeah, people, if
you're anything like me, do not gamble. Bad.