Yo. Okay, so I just finished watching
London Taylor's video um where he's
mentioning me and Rick Mace. Obviously
Rick Mace can defend himself if he
wants. Um now I want to start with this
right for somebody that says that um
I've got special needs and how uh people
need to make it make sense. God, I hate
that word. It sounds so common. London
Taylor, all you literally do is
contradict yourself. Like you're one of
the biggest hypocr hypocrites that I
have ever come across in my whole life.
Like you, nothing you say makes any
sense. So before like um telling people
that they're special needs and how they
need to make things make sense, you
might want to work on your IQ and maybe
go back into education so the next video
you do, it makes sense. Right? Let's
let's get into this. Right? So, what I
want to know firstly is you're making a
video claiming that you're superior to
this sector, this toxic sector, and how
like you try to get away from these
people and ret. Now, how does everybody
seem to know about your [ __ ] new
channel? That does not make any sense.
How the [ __ ] do you seem to know
everything and everything that's [ __ ]
going on? Because when somebody makes a
new channel, bro, no one finds it unless
you comment on someone's live stream
from that community, which is what you
have done and that's how people have
found you. Let me tell you something,
bro. Fun fact, the the new channel that
I've got, right, where I put all of my
approaches and everything, um, no one
knows about it and they will never know
about it because I'm not commenting on people's
uh, [ __ ] on this community, which is
what you have done. So, at the end of
the day, if you was really trying to get
away from this place, people wouldn't
know your channel and you wouldn't be
knowing what's going on. Like, it's it's
as simple as that. But the fact that you
know everything that's going on, yeah,
okay, fair enough. Some people might
have told you, but bro, how do they know
your new channel? If you made a new
channel to get away from this sector,
this community, how does everyone know
it? It doesn't make sense. Nothing you
say makes any [ __ ] sense. Right.
Second thing, right, you were saying
about how um uh I was trying to go you
the other day into coming to my mom's
and ret this is what you like to do. You
like to twist things and you like to
[ __ ] stir. No. What happened was right
sick of [ __ ] repeating this. I
emailed you two times asking you why do
you seem to have such a big problem with
me calling nonslegs a virgin because
he's got this spasticated girlfriend.
Meanwhile, he's calling me a virgin and
you've got no opinion on it. Even though
I've shown me getting my dick sucked,
shown me sleeping with multiple women,
proven to to [ __ ] healing back that
I've had sex, and you don't seem to have
a problem with that. Um, and it just
didn't make any sense because at the end
of the day, right, the the whole um, you
know, the the whole years of us like
talking and then arguing and then
madness then going back to being civil.
We was always a victim of these people's
biasness, you know, like when I went
somewhere, they said I didn't turn up.
When you went somewhere, they said you
didn't turn up. So, for you to then be
biased yourself, it doesn't make any
[ __ ] sense. And you are being biased.
Before you try and sit there and say,
"Oh, well, he's got a girlfriend. I I'm
only saying what's right." If you was
generally saying what was right, you
would have a lot to say about him
calling someone like me a virgin. You
know, someone like me. We all know what
that means. But you seem to let that
slide when we know you're on YouTube
constantly. We know that you probably go
on his channel. You've seen him call me
a virgin before. You must have done
once. Um, and you've got the opinion on
that. But every time I call him a
virgin, you're straight to his rescue. I
found it a bit odd and contradictory. I
I I must admit um especially when you
were a big crybaby about people being
biased um to you in the past um and then
you just coming out with these
ridiculous excuses. So you're very much
like these people in this community that
you're trying to slag off. Um you're
biased. There's no doubt in my mind that
you're biased. And then anyways, [ __ ]
all that. We know you're biased. There's
no if two ways about it. You're biased.
So then then you was emailing me a load
of [ __ ] Then I went live and then you
tried coming on here with your bully boy
tactics. Yeah. Trying to say, "Oh,
people spoke about your kid." And then
that that's not what happened. Yeah. And
then you tried to say that you're going
to come on my door and slap you. Sorry.
You was going to come on my mom's door
and slap my mom in her face. Are you
[ __ ] mad? And then I emailed you like
saying, "Oh, don't bother. There's
cameras." I was trying to stop it
because basically my mom um there's two
reasons. Basically, it's not my [ __ ]
house. And obviously my mom's quite old
and she's scared and I was scared what I
would do to you, bro. Like trust me.
Trust me. You don't know my temper.
Yeah. Right. Every single time you have
said in the past about oh your friend
doing this, I've already explained the
reason, bro. Trust me. If anyone come on
that door that day, they that would have
been the last thing they done. And
that's as simple as that. I'm not a
talker. And that's it. You started
coming on with your little bully boy
tactics. And then when I wasn't not
going to be like a victim to you, you
started saying, "Oh, I'm going to come
on your law. I'm going to come on your
door like I'm not having that. It's as
simple as that. Like and and that's it.
No one started going you to come on
people's door. Yeah. I asked you why
he's being [ __ ] biased cuz you are.
And then you started trying to do your
little bully boy [ __ ] Yeah. Which ain't
going to work with me, bro. Like Yeah.
Trust me. I was waiting that day as
well. I was waiting that day, bro. Yeah.
Trust me. You don't know what happens
behind the scenes. Um and then you know
that's it. And then and then that's it.
No one was bringing trouble. You started
your little bully boy tactics cuz you
know that you was being biased. You knew
I was right and then you tried like
threatening people as you always do. Um,
so yeah, and we all know if I had a if I
got a girlfriend tomorrow, you still
wouldn't say anything about people
calling me a virgin. You're a biased
[ __ ] So at the end of the day, stop
moaning and crying when people are doing
the same thing to you. Showing that
saying that you've not turned up here or
you're this, like you're you're you're
doing the same thing as you're bitching
about what they're doing. You don't make
no sense. is contradicting, right? And
then and then another thing is, right?
Um you were saying about how um
[clears throat] you were saying about
how um I went for Timmy the other day.
Okay, get your facts right. Right. I was
lying in bed. Timmy done a gambling
video because Timmy's the only person
that I'm subscribed to and I thought,
"Okay, let me just click on it. Let's
just see like cuz I find that kind of
stuff interesting. I gamble sometimes."
And this guy was mentioning my name,
mentioning my name, mentioning my
[ __ ] name, trying to draw me the [ __ ]
out. And it's the way he was trying to
do it as well because he's skinn and
he's a virgin and he's done his balls
in. He's trying to go for me and put me
in a bad mood. Yeah, I was lying in bed.
I'm thinking, Timmy, yeah, if you do not
stop, right, I'm going to message your
family. I didn't mention meeting him.
He's the one that started saying, "Oh,
I'm going to do this. I'm going to do
that. I'm going to do this." And we all
know know that Timmy was never going to
get in that cab. We all know that Timmy
was never going to come outside that
front uh that out that front door. So,
we test it. No one called him out, bro.
Nobody called him out. Yeah. This is
what you don't This is what you failed
to realize. I told him, "You The more
you mention my name, the more I'm going
to keep messaging your family cuz I'm
sick of this [ __ ] mentioning my [ __ ]
name." No one went on his channel and
started picking on him or trying to
bully him. Yeah. Like [ __ ] Nleegs,
the one that you love defending or you
know these other [ __ ] people. He was
trying to wind me up on purpose. So I
thought, "Okay, I'm going to message
your family." Yeah. And that's it. And
think about it, bro. If if I was really
going for the week at Target, LT, when
have I gone to Birmingham literally the
same day, bro? Like, this is what you
don't understand. You think that people
are really scared of you, but they're
not. They're really, really, really not,
bro. And another thing is, right, if I
was really going for the weaker target,
that's I I'm allowed to do that. You
don't dictate to me who I meet and who I
don't meet. who who are you to tell
people who they can and can't meet like
and and another thing is so that's that
and then with that Timmy with the Timmy
one right I think okay yeah you can kind
of say that he's a weaker target but at
the end of the day bro if he comes on on
this door on Wednesday I'm finishing him
that's it that is that is it not coming
back on this website um and that will be
his own fault he needs to stop
mentioning people's name he needs to
stop drawing people out yeah and I said
to him that's the only time I'm going to
do anything is if you actually come and
you knock on that front Not. So, no
one's trying to pick on weaker people,
bro. No one's trying to do that. And no
one's scared of you either. Yeah. And
another thing is, right, you talk about
So, that obviously you would never
attack Timmy. So, but bro, again, you're
being a hypocrite. You're mentioning non
legs. You have [ __ ] stirred um stuff
between me and Nles multiple multiple
multiple times. You yourself as has even
wanted to beat him up in the past
because you don't like what he was
doing. you fully. If you saw him on the
street, you would smack him up. But now
he's a weaker target because I've tried
to meet him because he tried getting my
money stopped. You're a hypocrite.
You're a hypocrite. You are a hypocrite.
People are not easy targets when it
suits you, bro. Yeah. All of these
people, right, that you say that I've
gone for in the past, you've tried
meeting half of the bastards yourself.
[ __ ] Terry. Um, you know, nonslegs,
not Timmy, but bro, Nonss, you have [ __ ]
stirred things between me and him
multiple multiple multiple multiple
times, and you wanted to catch him at
one point yourself, but now all of a
sudden he's a weaker target. Get the
[ __ ] out of here, bro. Like, you don't
even realize that. I don't even think
you actually realize that you are like a
lot of people on this sector. Like, no,
no, no. You really, really, really,
really, really are. Like, you need to
you need to get a grip, bro. If you was
generally done, not one person on this
community would know about your channel.
No one knows about my channel. The only
time they found out one of my channels
is when they was on Reddit pretending to
be a woman. That is literally the only
[ __ ] time. Yeah. Is when like they
pretending to be a woman and and and
[ __ ] like that. But bro, you really are
a raging hypocrite. Nothing you say
makes any sense [clears throat]
whatsoever. Like you're you're not done.
You're not superior to this to this
place. You made a new channel which was
pointless because everyone knows about
your channel. Why are you making a new
channel if [ __ ] people are just going
to know about it? Cuz you're not done
with this place, bro. This is it's as
simple as that. Stop acting like you're
not a part of this community when you
[ __ ] well are. Because if you wasn't,
you wouldn't be making video. People
wouldn't know. People wouldn't know your
channel. You'd be well away from this
place. Like, get a grip, bro. Get a
[ __ ] grip. You're the one that needs
to make it make sense when and truly.