Yo. Okay, so time for a new video. Um,
yeah, I was supposed to do this earlier,
but um had to go and replace my charger
because uh my previous one packed up.
So, apologies for um it being a bit
late, but better late than never. Um so,
yeah, I've got um a few things to talk
about because a lot has happened in the
past week. So, I thought, yeah, why not
do a video on it. So, the title of this
video is going to be um called to all
you white knight simps and feminists out
there. Um now, before I get into this
video, the most scary thing about this
is that there's more people in the world
that exists as one of those things as
opposed to somebody that's um completely
unbiased and none of them things, which
is what I which is what I class myself
as, you know, somebody that's completely
unbiased. Um, and yeah, and what I mean
by that is it's very, very rare that you
will go on the internet nowadays and,
you know, share your bad experiences
with women, you know, such as, you know,
them leading you on, them [ __ ] you
over, them playing games with you, or
simply, you know, you going over and
trying to speak to a woman normally and
her giving you attitude, which is
strange because how many times do we
hear that a man can't meet a woman or
get a girlfriend because he's got a bad
attitude or, you a negative attitude.
But, you know, if if you've watched
these videos where I've approached
women, a lot of them have got bad
attitude and they're rude and entitled,
but all of that stuff
gets dismissed. Um, which is strange.
It's like no matter what black and white
evidence um you show of women doing any
kind of wrongdoing, they completely make
up excuses for them um such as they've
changed their minds. um you don't know
um what they're going through or they
will be adamant that
said women has not led you on on purpose
um even when it's in black and white
evidence. Um and it's it's mad. It's
mad. And you know throughout the whole
sort of debate um that you're having
with with with somebody about this,
you're just thinking that me and you
both know if this was a man doing wrong,
we wouldn't be hearing any of these
excuses. So, it is very much because
they're a woman. And my whole problem is
not, you know, it's because they
completely dismiss people's struggles.
Um, I have shown these people black and
white evidence and they still nod their
head and deny it. Um, which I don't know
how somebody could possibly do that
unless they are by definition
delusional. Um, but they still do. Um,
you can show women having attitude
problems, leading you on. um and they
will just nod their head and be like,
"Nah, change their mind." um completely
dismiss it. So there's there's there's
no getting through to these people um
even though you have evidence of, you
know, what women um you know have done,
which is strange why they don't take
accountability. It's not the worst
thing, you know, it is pretty shitty,
you know, leading someone on and playing
games, but it's not the worst thing
ever. So, I don't know why they don't
disown it and and take accountability
because, you know, I I very much think
that if people wasn't um uh completely
if somebody was completely unbiased,
they would sit there and say, "You was
wrong on this one, you was right on this
one wrong, you was right on that one,
you was wrong on that one." But the fact
that they don't think women are ever
wrong in any of them screenshots um I
have showed is very, very, very, very,
very concerning. Um, and what's very
concerning is they've all got the same
excuses for them. Um, they've changed
their minds when me and you both know
that all of them women. Um, there was at
least a lot of them um that led me on on
purpose. It's clear as day. Um, you
know, I don't know why people keep
making excuses for them. Um, like you
know, for example, um, when I was on,
uh, Lex's podcast last week, I was
telling him about, um, you know, some
woman that I met last week and we was
talking and she had blatantly led me on.
Blatantly led me on and I had clear
black and white evidence and they were
like, "Nah, probably just changed their
mind." I was like, "Really, bro? Really?
Really?" like they wouldn't even admit
that the person just simply led you on.
So, I mean, it's very scary if they
can't even take such a small
accountability for doing something.
Yeah, the world's [ __ ] to be honest
with you. And like I said, me and you
both know that if it was a man doing
wrong, yeah, they'd just call him a
prick, wouldn't they? Um, quite simple.
Um, you know, they wouldn't be having
all of these excuses that he's changed
his mind and all of that. So, when you
actually, you know, think of it like
that, it is because it is a woman. It's
not because they're right or they're
wrong. Um, even if somebody said to me,
like I said, you're wrong seven times
out of 10 and they're wrong three times
out of 10, I'd be like, okay, that's an
opinion. But the fact that they never
think any of these women are wrong, um,
is mental. Um, absolutely mental. I
don't I don't know um what else to say.
And yeah, and then the thing about it is
is you just end up feeling like the boy
who cried wolf because anyone who's
thinking about having a debate or
jumping on a podcast when it comes to
like women and sharing your experiences,
I would strongly advise against it. Um
because all they're going to do is keep
dismissing your struggles no matter what
you tell them, what you show them, what
you prove. And in the end, you're just
going to come out the podcast thinking
to yourself, well, you might as well
just had an had an argument with a brick
wall because you would have just got
more sense out of a brick wall. It
generally feels like you you are the boy
who cried wolf because no matter what
you show them, how you try to make them
understand, they will still make excuses
for women. So, um, which is which is
very very very strange. Um, another
strange thing what they say is that, oh
well, people can't find a woman because
they're negative. And to that I always
say, this whole thing has been going for
years, is that people are not born
negative. People don't come into this
world negative for no reason. Because
that would make absolutely no sense
whatsoever. So, you think that people
are just going to be just come out and
be negative for no reason? I would
probably imagine that they're negative
after their bad experiences. And when
you keep going over the same thing over
and over and over and over again, it
does get quite annoying. Um, which is
why I say to people, just don't even
bother because there's no getting
through to these people. Um, they
clearly think women are angels. They
clearly think women can't do no wrong,
so leave them to it. Um, that's that
that's that's that. Um, weird. Very very
weird. Um, but that's just the way it
is. Um, very very strange. Um, you could
prove the world to these people. Um, but
they will never ever hold a woman
account. And it's not even about being
right or being wrong. It's not even it's
not even really about that. It's they
won't admit any wrongdoing that they do.
They will never ever have it as, "Oh,
women's led you on. Oh, women play games
with you." They will never in their
minds, they think that a woman possibly
can't do that. That men can do it. Men,
I can assure you men can do it, no
problems. But the fault of a woman
leading someone on, they can't have
that. It drives them mad. They're like,
"Well, no, they changed their mind. It's
it is it is mad." Um, and you know,
another thing that I find very very
strange is I I was talking to someone
and I said to them, um, yeah, I'm kind
of giving up with the whole dating
thing. Um, and you know, to be honest
with you, um, it's toxic and I'm I don't
want to deal with women's attitude
anymore and I shouldn't have to. And
anyone that any man that respects
themselves wouldn't have to because
yeah, it's it's toxic. I mean, and
that's obviously why I gave up. And then
he turned around and he said to me, um,
that's weak minded. Now bear in mind, I
need to make this clear as well.
Whenever I'm having like these debates
or whatever with people, um, what I
always think in my head is that
obviously I'm in the minority when it
comes to meeting women. I'm probably
women I'm probably in the 10 5 10% of
people that have met women. So, I'm very
very aware of what they're like. You
know, I've been up and down the country.
I've met thousands and thousands and
thousands of women. So, um, I thought
that was kind of offensive that he's
saying to me that I'm weak-minded
because I don't want to deal with toxic
women all my life. Um, I mean that's my
choice and like I said, any man that
just that respects themselves would do
the same thing. Why are you constantly
dealing with stuck up women with
attitude because you don't want to do
that? That's not weak-minded. That's
your choice. But then, hear me out,
right? This is we're getting into double
standards now. is that when a woman
chooses this the same man over and over
and over again, the the you know the
drug dealer or the man that beats them
up or the man that cheats on them and
they want to give up based on the men
that they choose. Oh, they're angels.
They're literally given that they they
get a silver spoon put in their mouth
with all different flavors of pages
saying, "Oh, you go girl. Men are bad.
Men are bad." So, a man that wants to,
you know, give up on dating for however
long it is because of toxic women, he's
considered weak-minded. But a woman
that, you know, will continuously choose
the same man over and over again, the
same deadbeat, the same drug dealer, and
then wants to generalize all men and
give up, she's considered she's
considered a legend. It's not entirely
fair, is it? Let's be real here. It's
not entirely fair. Now, I just wanted to
say right now, when these women go for
these kind of men, I don't think that
they know that they're going to beat
them up. Let's let's be adults about
this. I don't think, you know, the the
women that go with men that beat them up
know they're going to beat them up
because that's ridiculous. You know, I'm
I'm pretty sure that's not the case.
But, however, what I will say is these
women that go with these men, they know
they're no good. They know that they're
no good. you know, maybe a drug dealer,
maybe, you know, a [ __ ] maybe a bad
person. Again, bad and not abusive. They
are very, very, very aware of what these
men are like, you know, minus the
[ __ ] you know, um, physical abuse.
Of course, I don't think people just go,
"No, they're going to get beat up by
someone, but they're very they're
attracted to the same kind of [ __ ]
[ __ ] men. They all seem to go for the
same stereotypical man, but then they
moan and winge about it. This I've never
ever understood it. And then when they
want to give up on men, they literally
are called legends. Yet you'll get a man
that can't find any good women no matter
what he tries. Keep dealing with toxic
women that play the same games over and
over again. But when he wants to give
up, he's weakminded.
You know, just just just listen to that,
bro. that that is completely completely
completely insane. And you know, and all
of these women that try to say to you
that oh they they the men are nice at
first, it's complete rubbish. I can tell
you from my experience, right, the
amount of times that I have approached
women um and I'm probably the most down
to earth um person that they'll ever
come across and they will say the truth
in writing that, you know, you're this,
you're that, you're sweet, but they
still won't give you a chance, which
again, I don't mind. I don't expect them
to. If I was using this as an example in
comparison to what they're saying, it
doesn't make sense because if they were
really going for nice people, you'd be
getting women all the time giving you
the chance, at least giving you the
chance. But the fact that they keep
going for these same stereotypical men,
trust me, they these women know exactly
what these men are like. Um, you know,
they're not stupid. So, don't try and
tell you that, you know, yeah, like I
said, they might not beat them up. They
might not know that they're going to get
beaten up. Yeah, obviously not. But they
know that these men are no good. Um, so
don't So that's what makes me laugh is
when women moan about men being all the
same, it's all the men that they keep
going for. You understand? When I moan
about women, it's all the women I've
ever come across. Um, not women that I'm
choosing, men that they're choosing. Big
difference. Um, so that's that. And
another weird thing I find is that um
the oral thing again, I never ever
understand this and I don't think
anyone's ever gave an answer to it. Um
that when you say, for example, like I I
was having this conversation the other
day with someone and it's like, "Oh, you
didn't go down on that woman, that means
you're gay." But when they don't want to
give people [ __ ] completely fine.
That's just what they like. So again, if
a woman doesn't want to give somebody a
[ __ ] completely fine. completely,
oh, they just don't want to um, you
know, do that. Um, but if a man doesn't
want to eat a woman out, gay, completely
gay, that automatically means you like
dick. So, if you come across a woman
that you've met once and you don't want
to give her oral for whatever reason,
um, maybe you're just not into oral. I
don't know, maybe she smells or
whatever, you automatically like dick.
Um, their logic is that you
automatically like dick. But yet, if a
if a woman doesn't want to give a
[ __ ] well, maybe she just doesn't
doesn't feel like doing it, how they can
deny in this day and age that they're
not completely sexist and the double
standards is mad is is beyond me. It,
you know, it generally generally
generally generally is um beyond me how
they can sit there and and and deny the
[ __ ] You know, it's it is crazy, you
know, the amount of excuses that they
make for these these women. um is mad.
It is it's it's completely mad cuz let's
let's put it right here, right? Say that
I am wrong.
You know, nine times out of 10, but
you're telling me not one time any of
these women in the screenshot were
wrong. And then there was a woman that I
was speaking to um obviously that you
saw on Reddit, completely fine. And then
as as soon as I uh started showing the
women doing me over, leading me on, she
hated it. She started sending me voice
notes. She argued with me all day. And
then she said at the end, which is
funny, is that don't get me wrong, women
can do wrong.
I said, "Huh? You've literally just been
arguing with me for the past 45 minutes,
right? Saying how all of these women
have not led me on when I've literally
proved that they have led me on, but now
you're saying that all women can't be
wrong." So, uh, which one is it? Heads
or tails? What side of the coin are you?
It's it's it's mental. It is absolutely
mental. Why these people think that
women can't do no wrong and they can't
simply leave people on purpose or I
don't know why why they think that. Even
when they're shown evidence, even when
they're shown black and white evidence,
they still deny it. I I I I shall never
know. Um and yeah, it's it's mad. Like I
said, if you don't want to go down on a
woman, you're automatically gay. Um, you
automatically like dick. Um, but yet
when a woman doesn't want to give our
all, well, that's her choice. Sickening,
really, isn't it? Sickening how these
amount of um double standards exist, you
know? It's it's insane. But yeah, that's
all I wanted to say, man. So yeah.