I'm in my area. I'm just going to send
this approach. Hold on. Send it.
Solo approach success.
>> Excuse me. Sorry.
Wanted to say that. What's your name?
>> Me and your friend.
>> Me and a friend. Yeah. Well, just doing
a little bit of shopping.
>> Yeah. I'm going to Central.
>> Central? What's Central? Like a few
days. I'm always in Central. You live in Stratford?
>> Never in central. I live >> never.
>> I live in Essics. So
>> live in Essics. Oh, nice. Where else? >> Port. Okay. Yeah.
>> I live in Stratford.
>> Oh, I live.
>> Yeah. I'm like time. So whenever I go
out like even when I'm staying in
Stratford, I'll just like
>> Yeah, cuz it's close to you. I used to
be like that cuz I used to live in Tams.
>> Okay. Not anymore.
>> What nationality are you?
Do you know what that is?
>> Yeah, obviously I know what it is. I was
going to say [Music]
>> everyone always gets everyone always guess.
>> Yeah, I'm already
mine's weird. Like my mom's half Turkish,
>> but she doesn't speak the language.
She's western. My dad's like [Music]
>> guess I think I look more Turkish than I am.
>> How old are you? [Music]
>> I'm going to get going then. Can I get your number?
>> Okay. Yeah.
Oh man. Dumb one. Thought she was going
to give me her number.
[ __ ] me. That was woo. Got the old art
going there. Ain't drunk for 2 days.
Ain't drunk for 2 days. Literally ain't
That was like a workout, bro. I was
pounding, bro. That's what happens. You
You do this every day. Your heart starts
pounding. But yeah, I thought she was
going to give me a number, but no. Oh my
god. I thought that was going to be your
first number. Never mind.
No worries, man. On to the next. I'm
going to try to do free. Lovely. Back in
my old area.