So, I've just come out of the gym. Yeah,
for some reason I went on two channels
earlier. That Red Star channel and that
Jamie Thompson channel. They're still
stalking me. [ __ ] hell. These people
jealousy is a is a terrible, terrible,
terrible thing. It's a disease. It's not
even a terrible thing to be fair. It's a
disease. Like, they literally live to
hate and be jealous. Like any normal
person that's watching this, imagine
like waking up every morning and every
day living to be jealous of someone else
from the time you wake up to the time
you go to bed. It makes my skin crawl
even like the thought of it. But when I
was on like one of the um community
posts, I keep seeing this a few of these
keyboard warriors like All Night [ __ ]
who runs his mouth online, but when you
go to his country two times, he keeps
his mouth shut. Like we know them
spastics are never ever going to meet
anyone. But I keep seeing this Smokey B
time and time and time again. He's been
doing this for years, man. Like he's
he's done it to like LT. He's been doing
it to me. Like all he does is comment
and comment and comment and comment and
comment. Bro, listen. Yeah. This is a
video to you. Yeah. You have literally
had my address for years. Yeah. And and
and I know I've said this many many
times. This little Milton Keen little
gay boy who tries to be from London, but
he will never be from London. You can
tell my accent and his and he and his
accent. Like he tries to force it like,
"Bro, you're from Milton Kes. You're
from a dead ass area." And it's funny
how he's trying to talk about like how
much money people have and how much
money people earn. Bro, you live in
Milton Kes. Fix yourself up. You live in
a dead ass place where they all want to
be from London. And I'm seeing this
comment and you know when you click on
their comment, you see comment after
comment after comment after comment. And
you'd be thinking like, well, the guy's
only half an hour away from me. It's
like 20 minutes on the train from uh
Houston to Houston and then obviously
you can easily get to me. Listen, bro.
Yeah, you've been running your mouth
time and time and time again. Listen,
you little Milton Kees keyboard warrior
who sucks his mom little bacon. Yeah.
Why don't you do a video today in Milton
Keen? Prove you live there. Agree to the
time 6 7 8:00, whatever time suits you
and I will be there. I will get that
train since you obviously can't afford
it or your anxiety would not allow you
to come to London and we will see who
the real keyboard warrior bacon boy with
anxiety is. And I suspect that you're
going to shut your [ __ ] mouth like
you always [ __ ] do. What's the point,
bro? What's the point of being like
coming on the internet every single day
starting [ __ ] that you can't finish? I
don't understand. [ __ ] London
cyclists do it all the [ __ ] time. I
told the story earlier, don't start
something you can't finish. It makes you
look like such a [ __ ] [ __ ] Like
you really really don't know how
embarrassing. Obviously, you live in
Milton Kees, so everyone's soft there
when they're all [ __ ] And yes, I'm
saying that you're a [ __ ] and you're
from Milton Kees. And I will say it to
your face today. If you literally prove
where you live, prove you live in Milton
Kees. Just go by the station, prove you
live there. 6, 7, any time works for
you. You can say the time, just reply in
the video, and I will be there. It's not
a biggie. It's only 20 what 20 25
minutes away from Houston. Like you make
it this big thing, bro. Like you come on
the internet all the time bothering me,
bothering El. You You've done it to a
few people, but you would never ever say
boo to a goose. And I think you're the
perfect candidate because you live the
outskirts of London and you're still a
[ __ ] Like you still won't come to me.
Yeah. You're still not going to come to
me and you're still not going to show me
where you are cuz you're a [ __ ] So
listen, Smokeoky Bee, stop the whole,
"Oh, this person's got this. This
person's got that." Whilst you're like
40 years old living in Milton Kees, bro.
You I would not live in Milton Kees if
someone [ __ ] paid me. That is such a
what a bee area, bro. Like you get them
people. You get them a lot in London.
They say they're from Milton Kees and
they tried to put on like a London
accent and then they just sound like
inbred between [ __ ] the outskirts and
[ __ ] Essics. But listen, put your
money where your mouth is. You've
started and started and started. You're
still starting. Tell me, do a video in
response to me. Everyone's got your
channel. What time, where, and if you're
not, then I guess the person that's got
the crippling anxiety and who the little
bacon who sucks his mom in Milton Kees
is is you. Simple. Like that's it. I
will make I'll make another example of
somebody that can start something that
they can't finish. Yeah. I'm walking
home now. I'm going to upload this
video. like you've been running your
mouth for years. You've been doing it
for years as well, you little Milton
Kees keyboard warrior. That's going to
be your new name. Everyone's going to
know you as the Milton Kees keyboard
warrior now. And you've also joined
hangouts as well. But you're never going
to meet anyone. You're never going to
show where you are. You're never going
to come on someone's door cuz you've had
my address for years. And you can't even
say that, oh, he lives too far. Like as
in like the bomb used to make them
excuses. Just show me where you are in
Milton Kins and tell me the time and I
will come up there today and slap you up
in front of everyone on YouTube. We'll
see who the real crippling anxiety guy
is. We'll see who the real bacon is.
We'll see who the real skin [ __ ] is in
Milton Kees. And if you're not going to
agree to it, bro, just shut your mouth
and stop embarrassing yourself. And the
whole of YouTube will say as well.
All the like I'm not going to lie, I
went live today. Yeah. just to chill and
[ __ ] you know, but you get all the
spastics from LJ's come over. That's
where all the spastics come from. This
is why you don't see me on YouTube
anymore because it's the same people,
the same self projectors, the same
40year-olds, [ __ ] virgins that ain't
got a life. Anyway, Smokey Be not not
coming off topic now. Do the video on
Milton Kees. Set the time and I'll come
today and slap you up in front of
everyone on Hangouts. And if you're not
going to do it, just shut your [ __ ]
mouth and stop bothering people online
because we all know that you're the one
that hides your milk and kees probably
in your mommy's [ __ ] You probably go so
far up your mummy's [ __ ] in her belly.
That's where you do all your keyboard
warrior antics from. So if you're not
going to show where you are like, bro,
I'm telling you, you have my word. I
will come there today and I will slap
you up before I go on holiday tomorrow.
Simple. And if you're not going to do
it, you're a [ __ ] any response now you
not showing yourself in Milton Kees what
I've asked you to do or even doing a
response video you're a [ __ ] buff but
to be honest with you I don't even think
you're going to do a video because your
accent is so inbred and so forced it's
so embarrassing like you really think
you're from London but you're not but
bro anyways do that video today and I
will come and I'll happily slap you up
and you can bring whoever you want so
chop chop I'm going to upload this video
we know you're on YouTube all day every
Okay. Do the video showing where you
are, setting the time, agreeing to it,
and I'm going to come there and I'll
slap you up, bro, as soon as I come up
that off that train. Yeah, that's that's
my that's what I'm saying. So, I'll be
looking forward to this video. Don't
make excuses, please, like you always
do, you [ __ ] idiot.