Yo. Okay. So, I've got a bone to pick
with you, Ricky Millington. I am not
happy with you at all at all. Right. I
done that video partly dedicated to you
to show the bad experiences that I've
had with women over the years. you know,
them leading me on, playing games,
agreeing to meet them, back out, or
simply just not even replying to, you
know, the first message I've sent them
because they've got unrealistic
standards. And at the end of the day, I
left the comment section open for you to
have your opinion and everyone else to
have their opinion for that matter. You
know, they can agree, they can disagree,
they can just write what they like. As
long as they don't project and spam
hate, they're nothing's going to be
getting deleted. So, I made it fair. And
also, you know, I I've seen you talk
[ __ ] behind my back, you know, multiple
times. I've seen you on the Virgin
channel saying about how, oh, it's not
women, it's it's it's me and, you know,
I talk about babies and having babies
with them and that's what puts them off.
I can guarantee you there's no baby
talking any of those messages where them
women were wasting my time and leading
me on. So, if you are going to say
something a white knight, you know, get
your facts a little bit straight first,
mate. I would say um and it's it's it's
crazy. You've got a lot to say behind
people's back. But I don't see you on my
channel, even when the comments are
enabled, you know. That's that's a bit
strange, isn't it? I mean, what can you
actually say really? Your argument's
been completely ruined, you know. Um,
and at the end of the day, right, um,
it's weird. It's like you live in Hull,
right, which is, if anyone doesn't know,
uh, is probably the worst place to live
in the whole of the UK. Like, I'm not
even joking. And you're white knighting
women, do you not know how pathetic that
is in in somewhere
as bad as Hull? You know, I I could go
to Hull and I'd probably look like a
model. It's that deprived. Like, it's
bad bad. If you gave a woman£10, she'd
probably marry you. So, the fact that
you are happen to white night whilst
living in Hull means you really are down
bad, my [ __ ] son, you know, because
it should be very easy to be able to get
women there, get dates or whatever it
is. And and you know, I mean, I'm I'm
all I'm against white knighting and
singing. I'm allergic to that kind of
stuff. I don't agree with it at all. Um,
I don't think women are perfect. I don't
agree with what they do. That's just me.
Everyone's entitled to their own
opinion. But, I mean, if I was going to
agree with somebody doing it, I mean,
maybe do it more in a highmaintenance
area like [ __ ] London where, you
know, it's it's harder to meet people.
And it's it's [ __ ] weird. Why have
you not commented on my [ __ ]
video, Rickster? you know, it took me a
while to compile them uh messages
together, you know, it took a while and
yeah, that's not even 5% of what I put
up with with these women over the years.
So, don't try and blame me, mate. You
know, do not try and blame me. There's
no hidden gems in any of their messages
either, my good sir. Um, and what I
don't understand is, so you're not going
to comment on my video yet. I've enabled
the comments. You're not going to go on
my channel, but you will go on the
Virgin's channel and talk the most
[ __ ] shite. Should we Should we go
over a few of the things that you've
said? You've said about how Oh, how can
PJ call you a virgin when you've got a
girlfriend? Well, I can answer that
because he is a [ __ ] virgin. Just
because somebody shows a disabled the
wolf, right, a couple of times does not
mean he's had sex. He literally would
not even be able to have sex with her
without that being considered [ __ ]
rape because she can't [ __ ] consent
because she's not all there in the
[ __ ] head. Now the the the real
question is is how can I be a virgin
because I proved I've had sex. I've
shown me in bed with women. I mean
that's the real question is how can
anyone call me a virgin when I have
physically proven I've had sex. So, and
then you sit there and say about how I'm
jealous because um you know he has sex.
I would not want to have sex with a
disabled girl if my life depended on it.
Um and then you talk about
he has money. Yeah, bro. He has so much
money that it took him eight years after my holiday
to be able to copy it because before
that he couldn't [ __ ] afford it. Yes,
he's got so much [ __ ] money and I'm
so [ __ ] jealous. Very [ __ ] jealous
indeed. Ricky Milling, you say that in
your bedsitting [ __ ] hull. You've got
me to a [ __ ] tea. [ __ ] guilty. Do
you know what I'm saying? And then you
come out with the most uh ridiculous
[ __ ] And then you talk about money. How
much money do I have? You don't know
anything about me, bro. You don't know
how much money I have. You don't know
how much money I don't have. And again,
you say that I'm jealous of people being
able to go on holiday when that holiday
that he copied of mine is eight years
after I went. So I assure you, mate, I'm
not jealous of anybody. Never have been,
never will be. But the point is, you're
trying to you go on the the the Skint
Virgin channel and talk a load of [ __ ] right?
ridiculous stuff coming out your [ __ ]
ass about, you know, how people generous
or someone it. But then when I'm
literally telling you to come on my
channel and I make a video dedicated to
you, you you don't want to know. I mean,
Ricky, why would somebody be jealous of
somebody that's gone on a holiday eight
years after that person that's supposed
to be jealous? I mean, you said that
they've got money. If they have got
[ __ ] money, it would not have took
them till 31 years of age to [ __ ] go
and [ __ ] broad. [ __ ] would it? You
know, get your [ __ ] facts right. I
don't know if you're [ __ ] low IQ is
um clearly because you're from Khan and
you know what they say about
northerners, they're a bit slow, but I
don't understand it, mate. I really
really [ __ ] don't. You are really
nutting me off. You are, mate. You
really, really [ __ ] are, you know.
Comment on my video. I made a video
dedicated to you. Tell us where we what
we're doing wrong in their messages. You
don't need to talk [ __ ] behind my back,
mate. Be a man. Be a man. Be a man in
the bedsit in your bedsitting hole. In
that bedsitting hole. Got a pair of
[ __ ] balls then because it's [ __ ] ridiculous now.