Creepsy 9:00 in the morning. Got a knock
on the door and my little Simpsons top
come with some more good news. Look. Oh
gosh, it fell over.
Making some good progress with the Lego.
This bit got undone. So I have to um do
it all over again and I just don't have
the patience. But this is pretty cool.
Look, Yoda can actually sit now
without any problems. Look.
And then Mr. Robot gets involved. So
whilst people was out yesterday damaging their liver,
[ __ ] wasting money in the cold,
getting [ __ ] around with by women.
I I I was building Lego, you know, in
the warm, you know. I I know which one
I'd rather pick, to be honest. I know
which one I'd rather pick.
Yeah. I've still got one more t-shirt
coming. I don't know when that's going to come.
Um, but yeah, at 9:00 in the morning, I
was thinking, who the [ __ ] is on the
door? See, look. There's my little Simpsons top. Yep.