Right. So, um, normally I don't get on
with Timmy and like we're not friends,
but I've just watched this video that
the great guys put up where he's
sticking it on this woman.
>> Let's have a sex. Okay. Bring your
[ __ ] boyfriend. Bring your boyfriend.
No, no, no, no. Bring your boyfriend.
You call me sexist. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. I will not come. You call
>> Why am I No, no, no, no, no. Gone from
me. Go for me. Go for [laughter] me.
>> I mean, it is funny that it's the same
website. You can watch Harry Potter and
Mickey Mouse. But yeah, big up to me.
Um, I loved watching this. This was an
absolutely lovely site. Um, I watched
all of the video and yeah, good on you.
Um, if it was me though, I I I would
have done it bad. I would have done it a
lot better than you. But um, yeah, big
up to me. Um, and yeah, I might come to
Birmingham today and and go for a pint
with you. Um, why not, you know, might
wear them jeans and and come to
Birmingham to see her because that is an
absolutely lovely site, you know. Show
them who's boss, you know. Don't take no
[ __ ] [ __ ] for no [ __ ] white
knight, [ __ ] You know what a lovely
site to me. What a lovely site. I'm glad
you stuck it on her. Um, she didn't seem
scared though to be honest. But she
would have been scared if it was me.
Trust me. [ __ ] [ __ ] Good on you
though, Timmy. Good on you, son. Ignore
all of these white knights, you know,
saying, "What the [ __ ] are you doing?"
They're They're just jealous. That's
what they are. They're just They're just
jealous, Timmy. You know, they're just
little white knights. They're probably
still live with their mummy in their
40s, still virgins. But no, that was
lovely, mate. Yeah, I might come to
Birmingham today or tomorrow to see you.
Big up Timmy sticking it on this woman.
What a lovely site.