Yo. Okay, so quick video uh to Timmy
before I go to bed. Oh, my adrenaline is
going, bro. I can't wait until tomorrow,
bro. I'm excited. Timmy, seriously, bro,
you don't scare anybody. Like, no one is
scared of you at all. But I just wanted
to say, yeah, um before like I get into
this. Yeah. Like, please, if you do by
some miracle have the balls to come
tomorrow, just don't do one thing and
try to play the mole high ground. Oh,
he's brought me to your door. No, no,
no, no, no. He said this about women and
tried to like make it seem like, bro,
no, no, no. You started it and I will
finish it. Yeah, that you started it. I
was literally chilling on my live
stream, like was in a good mood,
whatever. Gambling vlog comes out from
Timmy. I thought, okay, let me click it,
right? Uh cuz I'm subbed to Mont I was
subbed to Monty and Timmy, but I've
unsubed from Timmy now cuz I liked a bit
of the gambling stuff like when I was
still gambling. PJ this, PJ that. Not
legs has got a couple of quid, you know,
like heard it over and over and over
again. This guy is clearly trying to
draw me out because he's done his balls
in because he knows that he's a virgin.
But why do you think everyone who's
watching this? Yeah.
Why do you think this guy constantly
calls me a virgin, bro? Me out of
everyone. Cuz he's a virgin himself.
Like I have been with more women than
this fat [ __ ] has ever had hot dinners.
He's seen it. still calls me a virgin.
Showed more money than this [ __ ] Still
calls me skin. I'm not a gambling
addict. He is. So, do you not see how
and why this guy always tries to draw me
out when someone, you know, is trying to
bully him on YouTube or going at him or
he's done his balls and it's jealousy
with this [ __ ] And at the end of the
day, bro, people can't even say that
it's speculating because we know him. We
know what he's about. And, bro, he's
look at just look at the guy, bro. Like,
no offense. So, he tries to draw me out,
put me in a bad mood. I told a guy
multiple times, "Keep my name out of
your mouth. Keep my name out of your
mouth. Keep my name out of your mouth."
And he would not do it. He tried to [ __ ]
sleeves. And I said, "Listen, if you
don't keep mentioning my name, I'm going
to message your family." Yeah. Because
nothing else teaches you. So I was like,
"Whatever." Then he says, "Oh, I'm going
to come to London. Oh, the big man talk
again." I said, "Okay, I'll order your
cab." So do not try tomorrow and make it
seem like you didn't start on me. Yeah,
you started it and I guarantee you I
will finish it. Okay, [ __ ] You listen
to me? Yeah, you little [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] Yeah, I'm going to give you
enough knuckle sandwiches tomorrow to
last you a [ __ ] lifetime. Yeah, try
and shout in my face and tell me you're
going to knock me out, you little
[ __ ] Yeah, don't forget, bro. I'm
bigger than Monty. I'm taller than Monty
and I've had enough of your [ __ ] and the
cheek of it as well, thinking that
you're going to travel from Birmingham
with you little broom and then going to
start banging on someone's door. Oh,
bro, just if you are brave, yeah, you
will do it. Like, if you are brave, you
will do it, bro. I'm not even going to
tell you what I'm going to be doing
tomorrow, bro. But trust me, you you are
just not doing it. Timmy, you tried it
four years ago and you and you ran away
and you left me and Tiger and you're
still on YouTube trying to act the big
man because you've done your balls and
trying to bother people. Yeah. It's the
same thing with Monty Man. Yeah. Every
time it's been you, you you you starting
[ __ ] with people. Timmy, you're a
[ __ ] You can't fight no one. Why are
you still on YouTube trying to draw
people out when all eyes are on you or
you've done your balls in, bro? Like,
allow it, bro. Like you're not you're
not going anywhere. Like trust me with
your this is what I highly recommend you
do tomorrow. Yeah. Your London tickets
just go to London and sightsee bro you
know cuz you are not coming on this door
and leaving in one piece. I I am telling
you right now bro I am [ __ ] telling
you right now. Yeah. Last time you can
bro you struggle to even kick. And
here's another thing bro please do not
tell me I'm backing out because bro like
you do what you want to do tomorrow. I
know exactly what I'm going to be doing
to you if you come anywhere near the
start and that is a promise. But bro,
have you got nothing better to do than
try to [ __ ] meet people on YouTube
for fights because you're jealous of
them? Like trying to, I don't know, make
more money, trying to see [ __ ]
friends or a hobby. Like, do you
generally not have anything better to do
than to like come and and and and try to
act good for women that's never going to
sleep with you? Like, really? Like, do
you you're trying to act good for women
to me? You're the perfect example of a
white night virgin. Yeah, you're an
actual virgin that is nothing but a
white knight, bro. They're not going to
let you hit it. They're not They're not
going to [ __ ] you. Doesn't matter how
many doors you thump on. Don't know like
Well, you're not going on my door, bro.
You're not going on where I'm living,
period. But no matter who you try to
meet, whatever, bro. They're not going
to let you hit it. They're not going to
[ __ ] you. They're You're a virgin. I'm
not, bro. Does that not tell you it
doesn't work? You know what I'm saying?
But yeah, Timmy, seriously, it's not
worth your energy, bro. We don't need
that energy tomorrow. You'll get
yourself seriously seriously seriously
seriously seriously seriously [ __ ]
hurt. Um, but I want to make sure that
you're not going to try and play the
mole high ground when you get beat. Uh,
we brought trouble. No, you started
mentioning my name, [ __ ] over and
over and over again. Yeah. So, yeah,
we'll see what you're about tomorrow.
You little [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] I'm
going to Bro, just just we'll wait until
tomorrow, bro. Yeah. Simple.