Right. So, this is going to be a video
to Timmy. Yeah. Listen. Right. I don't
know why the [ __ ] Yeah. You're still
doing videos to Monty saying, "Oh, I'm
going to meet you here. I'm going to
meet you there." Nah.
Timmy, you got called out. Yeah. But me
and Monty was in Birmingham. You got
called out. Prime got called out. And
none of you was anywhere to be seen. I
didn't call out [ __ ] Money Mike
because I didn't [ __ ] know that he
was still doing his [ __ ] on YouTube. If
I knew that then, bro, I swear to God, I
I would have called him out as well, you
know? And yeah, like I was so close
today to going to Birmingham. Like, you
don't even understand. Like, before
going to the cinema today, I was going
to drop the whole thing and just come to
Birmingham and just call out you and
that [ __ ] [ __ ] mic cuz I've caught
him snaking me on Virgin Boy channel.
But then I just thought, you know what?
It's a waste of time, isn't it? Because
every single time somebody does try to
[ __ ] meet you, you know, or you know,
you go to people's areas, you know, it's
happened multiple times, you will
pretend it never happened and then you
will just go back to licking each
other's asses. But listen to me. Come to
London tomorrow. Yeah. Bring [ __ ]
Mike with you. I'll even pay for your
train ticket. Yeah. And I'll meet you
and do you both in simple like it's and
and don't try and say that, oh, I'm not
going to meet you and No, no, no, no,
no. Timmy, when you came to London last
time, I was there before you could say
Jack Robinson. So, I mean, you can't
even [ __ ] use that excuse. Yeah. So,
listen, Timmy, you and that [ __ ]
mate, come to London tomorrow. Just come
to London tomorrow. Yeah. I'll deal with
you both myself. You know what I'm
saying? Like, you're [ __ ] annoying,
mate. Like, at the end of the day, if
that mic's got anything to say, come say
it to my face. You're only an hour and
20 minutes away. You [ __ ] stupid
snake. I swear down, bro. If I if this
was 2 years ago and I didn't know what
you little clowns do, you know, licking
each other's ass, then I I I fully would
have wasted my time and money. I'm not
even joking. But we all know what you
do, you know, from [ __ ] Mark Samson's
from my experience with Mark Samson,
[ __ ] Bomb, even Virgin Boy. You know,
you take L's and then you act like you
never and you forget it. So that's why
people don't waste the time. But listen,
Timmy, come to London tomorrow. Yeah.
And bring that [ __ ] mic with you as well. Yeah,
simple. I'll meet you 100%. I swear on
anything, I'll meet you anywhere in London.