Yo. Okay. So, I just wanted to do this
video to um Joseph Ferrar um because I
haven't actually seen this um until now.
So, I wanted to uh reply to it. So,
yeah. Joseph Ferrar, you really are a
little uh self-reflector, aren't you? Or
should I say a fat self-reflector going
by your hands, your fingers. I mean,
your Mrs. fingers, your M's hands. I
mean, let's face it, you you're both not
in shape, you know, to put it politely.
Um, I just don't understand why you
don't get on with your own life and, you
know, worry about yourself and how much
money um, you know, you have and you're
getting. I don't know what it is with
with these people. Um,
worried about what other people get. And
it's it's it's it's weird. But anyways,
um, I'm going to I'm going to, um, set
you straight on a couple of things here.
Um, so getting Jay, top fella,
consistent family man. I mean, yeah,
he's a family man. All right. Is it
being on YouTube all day every day? Um,
don't have a job. You tell him Joseph
Fro. He's going to bloody win father of
the year award. You know, I I can see
it. I can see it. I mean, Joseph Far, we
already know that you're you're biased.
Um, you know, when it comes to Nons,
your boyfriend, and L your boyfriend, at
this point, I think you three should
just have a [ __ ] threesome and, you
know, get out of the way. Um, you know,
just just get it because because you're
all obviously bent for each other. Um,
so ju just just get out of the way at
this point, honestly. Um, so yeah. Um,
doesn't have a job, spends all day on
YouTube talking to strangers, can't take
a day off of YouTube. Yeah, that that's
some father that is, mate. That is that
is some father. You tell him, Joseph,
for real. You tell him, son. Um, you
give back to the community and are d and
are the driving force on the tube. So,
get in there. I don't know about that
one. I've got to disagree. I mean,
there's people that are sub to him and
is a member that gives him money every
month and he couldn't even do a decent
vindaloo challenge. I mean, he he went
to Iceland and and got a microwave
vindaloo as opposed to, you know, just
going to a to a normal curry house and,
you know, given giving some content and
giving some back considering people are
giving him money every month. And this
is the same guy that calls other people
skin. Yeah. Let let that sink in,
people. The guy that got a microwaved um vindaloo
from curries, which mind you, I've never
had in my life. it is calling other
people skin. Just just remember that
when uh he uh he he comes and tries to
call you skin that he he got a
microwaved Iceland vindaloo.
Seems pretty skint
one to judge. Anyways, so
he now he's talking about me, right?
He's gambling days and the high life is
over. Bro, you're not wrong. Yeah, my
gambling days are over. You're correct
because I chose them to be over. Um
because I realized that in the end
you're just going to lose. It gives you
mood swings. It's just [ __ ] and I don't
want to carry on doing it forever. Done
it and I'm young enough to quit and
yeah, I don't want that to be a part of
my life anymore, which is pretty
sensible. Yeah, I chose them days to be
over Joseph. Not because I can't afford
it. I can gamble right now if I want to.
I can, you know, go out and gamble right
now if I want to. I can go to the
bookies first thing in the morning if I
want to. You do not know how much money
I have. Um, and you know, I can back up
what I'm saying here. Even when I had
the house and I was living in the house,
I'd gamble maybe once a month. Um, and
you know, I'd there there's multiple
times even when I had the house, maybe
three times a year where I'd stopped
going out for like 6 weeks. So, it's not
because of money, mate. And I'm telling
you, it's not because even when I had
the house, I still the same thing. I've
got money. You do not know how much
money I have. I can go out whenever I
want. I can do whatever I want. You
know, if I wanted to leave London on,
you know, this Saturday, I could do it.
You don't know how much money I have.
Um, so I assume you you're saying that
because um I I've stayed in for a little
bit. Um, Joseph, you're saying that the
high life is over. But here's the thing.
My jeans cost more than your phone,
right? My trainers cost more than your
phone. People got so jealous they
started accusing me of using CLA. I
wouldn't really say the high life is
over just yet. But my gambling days,
yeah, they're over because I didn't want
to keep gambling. I can gamble right now
if I want to. You're in your 40s and
you're gambling every day. It's a losing
game. It's a loser game. Um and yeah, I
just didn't like the mood swings and the
way it made me felt. So, I thought, let
me just stop it. Um and I stopped even
when I had the house. So, um I don't
understand what your point is. You don't
know how much money I have. So, and
again, I do not need to prove myself to
you. You're lucky that you got that
just, you know, I didn't even need to
justify myself to you, but you're lucky
you you even got that justification in
the first place cuz I don't need to
justify myself to you. If I want to
gamble, trust me, I'd bloody [ __ ]
gamble, right? If I want to go out
drinking, trust me, I'd bloody go out
[ __ ] drinking. Yeah, to be fair, I'm
going outside. E, but yeah. Um, anyways,
1.1k or let's be conservative, 1.2K a
month ain't cutting it. That's absolute
poverty anywhere in England, never mind London.
Now, here's the thing, right? You're
talking about 1.2K,
right? How do you know that I ain't got
£60,000 in one of my bank accounts? Bro,
this is what I'm saying about you
talking about people that you don't
know. And everyone else that's done this
in the past that says, "Oh, you can't
afford this. You can't afford that."
This gets proven wrong. How do you know
that I don't have £60,000 in my bank
account? You don't know me. So, mate,
there's somebody could be getting £500 a
month and they could have £80,000 in
their account. You don't know me. You
don't know what I have. That's that's
just an example of you do not know what
I have. And let me make you clear on a
on a few things. Because you work, you
wouldn't understand this. Now, here's
the thing. £1.2,000
disposable money is not bad at all.
Anybody that works, right, I would say
very very few of them are left with more
than 1.2,000 a month. You know, there
there's people that's left with500, 600,
700. I I I used to know I I I know
people that literally work and they're
left with about £200 for the month. So
£1.2,000 a month disposable.
It's not bad at all. I would actually
say it's it's above good. So it's that's
not even bad. So I don't even know what
what you're talking about. £1.2,000 off
the bills just for yourself. I mean,
it's hardly £2300 a month, is it, mate?
So at the end of the day, when you're
looking that up and it's saying it's
poverty, that's probably because they're
expecting people to pay rent and bills.
If you've got £1.2,000
after bills and after you've paid
everything, you're probably doing better
than probably most of the [ __ ]
country to be honest, considering most
people are skin. So to say that £1.2,000
£2,000 a month after everything is paid,
right? That is that is not poverty, bro.
That is not poverty. And I'm telling you
right now, you you do not know what
poverty is if it was to slap you around
in your [ __ ] face. Yeah. I went to a
chicken shop the other day. This guy was
paying with 5 Ps and 10 P's, bro. Yeah.
You don't know what skin is. You don't
know what [ __ ] poverty [ __ ] is.
Because if you've got £1.2,000 £2,000 a
month after you've paid everything just
for yourself. That is pretty [ __ ]
good to be fair, you know. So that is
definitely definitely not poverty. And
then you said, right, anywhere in
England? Okay, so let's go let's go by
your logic then. So if you're a single
guy, right, and you lived in Sheffield
and you had 1.2,000 a month, you really
think that's poverty, bro? So you had
your own apartment, right? Which was by
the council or whatever. you live with
someone, got a partner, whatever, and
you've got over a grand a month just for
yourself, over a grand a month. You
really think that, you know, you're
going to starve or you can't go out
drinking? Really, bro? Really? Do you
even hear what you're saying? Now,
here's the thing, Joe.
Somebody that gets £2.5,000
a month from working is more than likely
going to be having less than £1.2,000
£2,000 a month disposable by the time
they've paid rent by the time they've
paid bills. 2.5K 3K. There's people that
earn 3K a month and they're paying
15,600 rent. They're almost left with
£1,200 just on the first bill, mate. So,
at the end of the day, you wouldn't know
any of this stuff because you are an
idiot. You know, £1.2,000 a month after
everything paid. That is not even poor,
bro. What the [ __ ] are you talking
about? And it's very very easy to adjust
to as well, you know, like at the you
know, at the end of the day, you that is
not even poverty. 1.2,000 a month after
everything's paid. Really, bro? Really,
that that is not bad at all. Um, you
know, at the start it might be if
someone's getting five grand a month and
they have to drop to that, but bro,
you're going on like it's 200 pound a
month. Stop it. Really, really, really
stop it. And another thing is I wanted
to say to you, why are you talking about
what people have and what people don't
have, bro? All you have got to your name
to brag about is a pension that you
can't even touch. Like, you're probably
not even going to be alive when you can
finally access it. Like, that's the only
thing you have is, "Oh, I've got a
pension. Oh, I've got a pension." Bro,
if you actually had money, Yeah. then
you wouldn't be going on about this
[ __ ] pension. You know, a pension is
is something that you can't even touch
yet until you're a certain age. So
you're on here, bro, banging about
£1,200, £1,000, whatever. What people
have, what people don't have. But but
the only thing you've got to brag about
is a [ __ ] pension that you can't even
touch. Like you you might want to really
really really worry about yourself and
not worry about how somebody can live
off [ __ ] over £1,000 a month off the
bills. Do you know how ridiculous that
sounds? That that that that is even a
question. If somebody can live off over
a,000 pounds after everything is paid
for, like it's [ __ ] it's [ __ ]
mental. You're an absolute cloud, man.
And and the only thing that you've got
to brag about is a pension that you
can't even touch. So maybe, Joseph
Ferrar, you need to look a bit closer to
home before judging people. And yes, it
might say on the internet that £1.2,000
is poverty. Yes. Yes. Yes. for people
that need to pay rent, for people that
need to pay bills, not disposable. Look
up, right? I'll tell you right now,
right? And I already know the answer to
this uh because I've searched it up. You
go on Google right now and you type up
is £,200 a month disposable money
poverty and you'll find your answer. You
disposable means money that's all yours,
which is anyone that's on benefits,
their money is all theirs because they
don't have to pay anything. So you go on
Googles right now and you type is
£1.2,000 a month disposable enough and
you will find your answer pretty
quickly. So there you go. You're you're
typing, you know, and to that they
probably mean people that work that earn
that. So therefore, it's poverty. It's
poverty if someone is getting £1,200 a
month and have to pay, you know, £1,500
rent. Obviously, it's [ __ ] poverty.
If someone has to [ __ ] pay rent, how
are they going to pay rent for £1,200 a
month? But if they don't have anything
to pay and they've got £1,200 a month,
them [ __ ] ain't a ain't
starving in a hurry, mate. Trust me. So,
again, worry about yourself. Stop
bragging. Stop thinking that you're
better than everyone. You Your only
thing that you've got to your name is a
pension that you can't even touch. Stop
it. It's embarrassing now, Joseph. You
know, you're better than that. [ __ ] me.