Okay. So, yeah, I wasn't going to come
on YouTube. I'm not going live or
anything because all these people do is
self-reflect and they've got absolutely
no life whatsoever. But, um, I thought,
you know what? Yeah. I wanted to show
Grevy this. You can't beat a nice pork sablo
and the rib closed in London. Now, most
of the sabo now are chicken because most
of the places are halo and obviously
Muslim people can't eat pork. So they
substitute it with a chicken subloin,
but this is a pork subl. It is [ __ ] gorgeous. [Music]
I just fancied a nice subloin chips
today. And sabloin chips.
Can't beat it. When you know, you know.
And you're in the mood for it. [Music]
So yeah, this is to you.
Only to you, poor [ __ ] I didn't want
to leave you without content completely. M lovely.
Hopefully this doesn't ruin your diet now, weebs.