Okay, so this is going to be my reply to
um London Taylor. I saw a couple of your
comments on my video and yeah, I'm going
to reply to you. Um now, this isn't me
trying to wind you up or annoy you or
trying to troll you or aggravate you
like most of these people have done to
you in the past. I'm going to tell you
how it is. [ __ ] straight, you know,
simple as that. Right. So, you were
saying about how um you know that guy
couldn't fight me because he's at work
and no. Isn't it funny how you claim
that you're not on YouTube, right? But
as soon as it's to do with me
confronting a black man and he
absolutely shat it, right, you're like,
"Oh, uh, yeah, you're there straight
away. Oh, he can't do anything because
he's at work." And no, no, no. Like,
that's not what you generally think,
London Taylor, right? Because remember
when I went to Kenji's area and I went
to his workplace and he shot it. Oh, big
up PJ. Big up PJ. But then when it's to
do with a [ __ ] black bouncer, oh,
they can't hit you because they're at
work and no.
Now the thing is LT, I didn't go around
London going to nightclubs and pubs and
suddenly started on a black bouncer for
no reason because I was bored. The guy
obviously done something. Yeah. He was
asking me for ID to show off and then he
started kissing his teeth at me and gave
me a dirty look. Right. And I was like,
I'm not having that. Like you're not
going to kiss your teeth up at me, bro.
Yeah. You know, I'm from the I'm from
the ends. I know what it is. Yeah. And
then, you know, I started telling him
about himself and that's it. Like, bro,
like, if you can't fight people, you
can't say anything, stop [ __ ] kissing
up your [ __ ] teeth then, bro. Cuz
that's even more cowardly. If you're
going to be doing all of these things
knowing damn well no one can do anything
to you because you can't fight them
back. Furthermore, right, it's not the
fact that he didn't fight me. He didn't
hit me. He said nothing. He literally
stood there and done nothing. When me
and you both know, mate, if they wanted
to do something and if they wanted to
say something, they [ __ ] could. Why
don't you tell everyone, London Taylor,
about that uh bouncer that smashed your
friend's [ __ ] teeth down his uh down
his throat in McDonald's in my land?
Yeah, you you didn't tell anyone that,
did you, bro? The guy stood there like a
pedigree pet dog, bro. He didn't say
nothing. So, it's not it's nothing to do
with fighting or not fighting. It's it's
because the guy was black. if the guy
was white, right? Because you've got
this thing about black people being
better than white people and every black
person is stronger than white people. I
don't know why you think that is. You
know, some white people can beat me,
some black people can beat me. It's it's
not to do with skin color. I assure you
that, but it's it's cuz the guy was
black. Like, bro, it's okay. So, okay,
that guy can't hit me because he's at
work and ret there. Um, okay. Well, what
about them four What about them four
people that was mouthing off and I
mouththed off back to them. I stood in
the same place and they done nothing.
Yeah, it's not what they said was right,
Ali. It's none of their [ __ ]
business. It's none of their business to
butt in other people's [ __ ] business.
Right. I was arguing with the bouncer. I
was talking to the bouncer. It's not for
for [ __ ] to suddenly get involved
and then when they're told about
themselves then shy away like the little
cowards that they [ __ ] are. You know,
like, bro, they're not. It's It's You're
constantly making excuses. I mean, I'm
pretty sure in that video I said to the
guy, "Give me your number. I will meet
you outside of work." Like, you you're
always going to come out with these
excuses, Bob. It's pathetic. It's pathetic,
bro. The guy had nothing to say. Like,
trust me, I've been to a lot of cities.
I've been to a lot of different places
and I know exactly how bouncers can act
if they want. You're just full of
excuses, lad. Time and time again. And
you want to keep bringing up L J how I
keep using that as an excuse. Okay,
sorry, bro. I'll rephrase it, you know,
so I don't hurt your fragile ego. He
didn't hide behind the gate. He stood
behind the gate and he argued and he
done nothing. Is that better for you,
bro? Yeah. Okay. He flew here. Yeah. He
stood behind the gate and he done
nothing. And what, bro? Yeah. And
[ __ ] what? He had several chances to
kick the door in my face. He never He
had another chance to meet me, right,
when I was um, you know, 20 minutes
after he went on the door, I tried to
meet him again. Stop using excuses, bro.
My man stood behind the gate and he done
nothing but argue. Is that not facts?
Yeah, cuz you don't like the word
hiding. Yeah. So, how about he stood
behind the gate and he done nothing.
Like, that's literally
what he done, bro.
Whether you like it or not. Like, so I
don't know why you keep trying to use,
"Oh, we can't eat you cuz he's at work."
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's always excuses with you
[ __ ] you know? It's the same
thing with [ __ ] you know, they sit
on here, they call you a virgin. You
literally prove that you've had sex,
they still call you a virgin. Like, bro,
what the actual [ __ ] Yeah, if it really
was, "Oh, we couldn't hit you because uh
he's at work." Why didn't the guy give
me his number, bro? I would have happily
met him after work. Like, I had said, I
mean, I literally stated that in my
video. You're full of [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
And And you want to say, "Oh, well, why
didn't you start on people that had
nothing to do with working?" I did. Them
four people. I I continuously told them
about themselves and they sat there and
done nothing. And if you mean other
black people, uh, because other random
black people didn't start kissing up
their teeth, [ __ ] idiot. So, you
might want to get your facts right
before saying stuff. Yeah, [ __ ] fool.