Yo, so I just wanted to get into these
um little self-reflectors um quickly and
I wanted to go on one of their videos.
Subzero games alone just like old Peter.
Oh, you know about being alone because
you are Mr. Lonely. Um sat on YouTube
all day every day. Can't get off it. Do
you know what's so bad with these
people? Yeah. Is that they claim that
everyone's lonely, everyone's skin,
everyone's this, everyone's that. But
they're the ones that sat on YouTube Mr.
Lonely all day every day by themsel for
years. I think they're so disabled that
they don't even realize that they're
talking about themselves. Like I
generally think like their disability
gets them confused with other people.
Like that they're sat on YouTube all day
every day for years alone, no friends,
no money, can't get off of YouTube, and
they barely can't even leave their
[ __ ] house. They I think generally
their their disability
confuses themsel with you cuz man like
you you got to ask yourself the question
why are they sat on YouTube all day
every day? If they're not alone, if
they're not skin, if they've got all of
this money, they've got all of these
friends, why are they on here every day?
Because they don't have nothing. They're
lonely little 40-year-old self
projectors. But anyways, I just clicked
from this channel. Um, and yeah, he's
got a picture of me. I know you wish you
could be that good-looking in it. You
would never show your face cuz you're a
big fat ugly bastard, which is like most
of you people. You tried to take the
piss out of the way people look, but in
reality, you can't show what you look
like because you are literally the
ugliest of the ugly banger. So that's
why you try to take the piss out of the
way other people look. You've put here,
Tim. I waited for you at Birmingham
airport and you didn't show you [ __ ]
Now get life. Well, you can't even spell
properly, you absolute [ __ ] [ __ ]
And don't put my name PJ2. PJ2 what,
[ __ ] I don't live in [ __ ]
Birmingham, you [ __ ] bongo. So, I
don't know how you're going to
Birmingham trying to call me out when I
don't live in Birmingham. Bro, listen.
Come to London anytime you want and
we'll see who the [ __ ] is. I will show
you who the real real [ __ ] is. Yeah.
So, don't do these stupid little stick
to your little stupid little soft
cities. Yeah. Where you're pretending to
call people out. Don't go to some random
city trying to mention my name. Bro, go
live in London anytime and we'll see who
the [ __ ] is. We will literally see who
the [ __ ] is. Yeah. Come to London
anytime and go live and try to take the
piss in London. Not when you're four and
four and four and four and four and four
far away. Do you know what? Like, do you
know what I'm saying? I'd love to get my
hands on one of you little [ __ ]
40-year-old loners. Anyways, bro, so
it's not a problem. But yeah, if you're
ever going to do videos again mentioning
my name, come to London and see how far
you get. [ __ ] Birmingham. You're Who
the [ __ ] meets somebody at an airport?
You [ __ ] [ __ ] When there's
security, where there's police? Who the
[ __ ] goes to a Birmingham airport to try
to meet people and then pretend to call
somebody out that's not even from there?
Mate, listen, bro. Stop doing your
stupid little videos. If you really are
about it, come to London. End of
[ __ ] Birmingham airport. Yeah, try
that [ __ ] when you're in London and see
how far you get with your big [ __ ]
fat ugly legs. You [ __ ] loner. Look
at you sat there all by yourself. All by
yourself, Mr. Lonely. Listen, bro. Come
to London and then start mentioning my
name and see what happens. Simple.
[ __ ] weasel. Come to London and we'll
see how big you are, big man. Simple.
[ __ ] Birmingham airport. [ __ ] the
[ __ ] beat at an airport. Come to London
anytime, bro, and we'll see who the big
[ __ ] is. Simple. Until then, keep
mentioning spastics like Timmy. Keep
mentioning all of these other [ __ ]
vulnerable people. But, bro, don't
mention my name unless you're actually
willing to actually pull up to London.
Don't embarrass yourself now, please.