Yo. Okay, so this is going to be a video
to Joe F. I said I was going to do it
just before I um ended my live stream,
so I'm doing it now. So
yeah, Joe, this YouTube just gets
weirder and weirder and weirder. Like I
genuinely got stalked the [ __ ] out of
like all day, bro. Like they were even
doing it on Reddit. like they were
literally waiting all day for me um to
post something so they could respond.
And I've got like four channels on
YouTube dedicated to stalking me. Um and
you know, like I've been getting emails
and what's funny is um you don't
actually get it. Like you generally
don't get how none of it makes any sense
whatsoever. So let me let me break it
down slowly to you, right?
So, these people like Virgin Boy, uh,
Red Star, Jamie Fatson, um, that's my
new name for him, which I'll get on to
in a minute. Um, they come on YouTube
every day saying that you're skin, that
you're a ma, that you're this, and
you're that, like just trying to put you
down every day. And basically,
if you was all of these things, they
wouldn't waste their life stalking you
every day, talking about you every day.
Like, bro, your life, and by your, I mean mine,
my life, sorry, their their life
literally revolves around me. Now, from
my understanding is how I was brought up
that if you knew you was better than
someone and there was a waste of space
and they were this, they were that, you
wouldn't waste your life on them. You
live your life. You wouldn't give them
any time a day because why would you why
would you waste your time on someone
that's all of these things that you're
much better than? It's like, you know,
it's same kind of thing goes with like a
woman. You know, if a woman's like a
waste of time and she's no good, what
would you do? you'd you'd go and you'd
find a new woman and you wouldn't give
her any time of day. But the fact that
these people waste every second of every
millisecond of their life of every day
stalking you will not leave you alone.
It comes to jealousy. That's the only
possible thing it could come down to.
And obviously I'm going to um you know
take on board some of the things you've
said cuz obviously on a video you can't
defend yourself. And I'll just go over
how it's just completing up [ __ ] Now
you will turn around and say that they
come on here and they do this for a
reaction and they're trying to get a
reaction from you which is I never react
to these people. It's I'm reacting to
them because I'm trying to explain to
you why they're doing it which is
obviously jealousy. Um, so the thing is
is that, okay, let's just say that they
do it for a reaction. Again, if you are
a skint ugly ma and you're all of these
things that they're not, why would they
want a reaction from you? Why would they
be spending all of their and and also
it's not that it's that they get a they
want a reaction out of you or they don't
want a reaction out of you. What are
they doing to get a reaction from you?
stalking you, reacting to you, making
videos of you, stalking you all day,
every day to what? Get a tiny reaction
from you. That doesn't make any sense.
Reaction reacting to get a reaction
doesn't make any sense. Now, you've got
the wrong end of the stick. Now,
somebody doing stuff for a reaction is
Timmy's going live. You're gonna say to
Timmy, "Listen, you stole off a
hyperlinks and it's gonna take you 10
seconds to write that because we all
know that Timmy's gonna react that it's
funny." This is pure obsession and
jealousy what these people do every
single day and they don't leave me
alone. Um, so it goes beyond them
wanting a reaction because so what?
They're spending all of their life,
every second of every day of their life
wanting a reaction from somebody that's
a skin m. It doesn't make any sense,
Joe. It really does not make any sense
whatsoever. And also another thing is is
that even if you don't react to them,
they will still do it. they genuinely
will still do it. Um because like if you
don't react to them, you don't go on any
of their channel, they literally will
still do it, which also goes to show
that it is jealousy, which is like with
Timmy, right? Like there'd be a point
where he'd always react. And then when
he stopped reacting, people would stop.
But with me, I could be on YouTube for 3
years, go on a channel, and they'd still
be doing it even if I didn't react to
them. So, this whole like they want a
reaction doesn't make any sense because
it's like even if they wanted a
reaction, why would they want a
reaction? Why are they wasting all of
their life trying to get a reaction from
a skin m? It doesn't make any sense. Um,
which obviously they they are the skin
monters, um, which we'll get on to in a
minute. They're talking about
themselves, but that those are the
things that they come online and they
try to call you. So, this is why I'm
trying to make you understand how it doesn't make
any sense whatsoever. Um, and then you
claim that it's it's it's not jealousy
and retire. Now,
let me give you some fun facts right
now. Virgin boy, listen.
I am younger than him. I'm better
looking than him. I've got teeth in my
mouth. Got more money than him, better
clothes than him. Been with way better
women than him. Had had a better life.
I've got more life. Like I've got more
life experience than him. He is still
obsessed with my sloppy seconds to this
day because I mean if I was really the
ugly mun, why have I got all of these
women that he can't get out of his head?
Um it's literally facts that I am
younger than him and I'm better than him
in every way. Like I said, better
looking, a been starved by my mom. I've
actually got a bed. I've actually been
with good-looking women. Um you know,
the list just goes on and on. I've been
abroad more times. I've been everywhere
in England and I'm younger.
It is actual proof that you have a
better life than him. Um, so
I know that which is why I don't waste
my time on this virgin. Um, you know
what I'm saying? This is why I don't
waste my time making videos, having a
channel dedicated, because I know that
I'm better than that virgin in every
single way possible.
but he's the one online stalking me
every single day. So this is where it
makes absolutely no sense. And then if
you look on the other one, Jamie
Thompson, fat, ugly, he looks like Peter Griffin. So
it all suggests by the evidence
that you you're better than them in
every way. Like just them two people
like like look at it, bro. Like I'm only
27. I'm not 31. I'm better looking.
more money, had more women, been to more
places, got better clothes, got better
[ __ ] family. The evidence is there.
Like, it's in literally, it's like cold,
hard evidence that the evidence is there.
But the thing is, I don't contradict
myself because I don't waste my time on
YouTube every day obsessing over them.
They're the ones that are obsessing over
me. And it goes to show that the ones
that the ones that are obsessing are the
ones that are jealous. It's as simple as
that. Like it's it it is what it is. And
let me tell you another fact. Uh Joe,
people can show me £800. People can show
me £1,000. People can show me £1,500.
That doesn't bother me and it doesn't
trigger me because I don't think you
understand how the money game works,
right? The money game works
where somebody shows money and the other
person is supposed to double said money.
Right? I showed £6,000.
I asked to be shown £10,000.
No one can do it. So, it's not that you
show money, they don't show you
anything, and then they come back months
later and then show half of what you
have shown. I am literally waiting for
somebody to show me 10 grand. Now, we
all hear this every single day on
YouTube that this person's skin, that person's skin.
I'm still waiting for somebody to show
me 10 grand. You know, I'm not
interested in one grand, two grand,
[ __ ] two and a half grand, or
whatever it is people are trying to show
me. I want to see 10 grand because, you
know, I was showing the same six grand
for like over a month in cash. 50s, 10,
20s, there were some fives there. So it
the whole money game works as you show
money and they have to double it. Virgin
by ain't doubled it. All of the people
that stalk me haven't doubled it. So I'm
not interested in any money shown that's
not 10 grand. Um, and it's also proven
I've got more money than him. So, my
point is, Joe, that all of these things,
it just points to jealousy. Nothing
else. It really, really, really doesn't
point to anything else but jealousy. So,
um, yeah, I hope you uh I hope you
understand that. I try to explain it to
you the best I possibly can. But um if
you if they generally had a better life
than you and you was this and you was
that, they genuinely would just live
their life and leave you alone. But the
fact that they can't and the fact that
they spend all their life stalking you
and they won't leave you alone,
they're jealous of you. There's nothing
else. It it it can generally genuinely
be but jealousy or they're in love with
you and they want to [ __ ] you. I mean,
that's also a possibility. They either
want your ass um or it's jealousy.
There's there's literally nothing else
because logically would not make any
sense for somebody
that they deem in a worse position than
them that they would waste so much time
being obsessed with them. and um
spending all their life stalking and
stalking and harassing and stalking and
harassing if they weren't jealous of
you. They'd be like, "Fuck you." and
just get on with their life. And the
fact that they can't do that, it just
goes to show they're jealous of you. Um
and yeah, accents speak louder than
words, and that's what they do every day
on YouTube. So, it must be jealousy,
which is what I was trying to explain to
you uh the other day, but you didn't
really understand. So, yeah.