Right. Okay. So, this is going to be a
video to um to non legs and I've got a
couple of questions. Um this isn't a
slating video or whatever. It's just
simply a video of me asking you a um
couple of questions. Now, why did you
copy my holiday? Now, I know you're
going to sit there and say about how,
you know, you didn't and how where you
stayed was much better than where I
stayed. It doesn't matter where
someone stayed or where someone didn't
stay. You ended up in the exact same
country and the exact same city that I went.
I also went to Amsterdam as well. It
doesn't matter if I stayed in a hostel,
a hotel, I stayed on the street, you
stayed in a mansion there. How did you
end up in exactly the same country? Not
only exactly the same country, but the
exact same city.
That's a bit dodge. I mean, I'm pretty
sure there's over 300 countries. So, I
mean, what's the chances
um that you just miraculously ended up
in the Netherlands in Amsterdam, your
first time abroad?
Cuz I also went Amsterdam as well. Um,
obviously like I like I like I've said
there was a delay, but that's simply
because your skin and it took you years
to save up to be able to go. Um, you
know, uh, and how did you miraculously
end up? Now, I know you say that you
like Amsterdam and Amsterdam's a nice
place and all of this [ __ ] that that
you're trying to convince people to make
it not seem like you copied me, which
you did. But, I mean, yeah, that could
generally be true. But I mean there's
over 300 countries
and more than 300 different cities, but
you ended up in Amsterdam where I went
the first time you went abroad. That's a
bit dodgy, mate. I mean, that is that is
that is pretty dodge. It doesn't matter
who had the the the the the
best um hotel or whatever. You ended up
in the same place as I went first. your
your holiday could be a5 million pound
holiday. It you ended up where I was in
the same place because I went there cuz
you're a copycat. Just like when you say
that Shle's attractive, you say to fit
in cuz you don't want to feel left out.
Little copycat. Um I remember um meeting
you before. You told me that you liked
cats and obviously you don't like dogs
because of um the the history between
you and Tilly and your mom used to throw
the dog on you and you was always a cat
person and uh it makes sense really cuz
you're a big copycat. Little copycat you
are. I could just pick you up you little
copycat. Copying people's holidays. Copy
the Cheryl Cole trend because you want
to feel left out. Funny enough, other
people was um
other people was calling each other gay
as well when they didn't find Sher
attractive and somehow you started
saying it. I mean, what's the chances? I
mean, the holiday thing is ridiculous. I
mean, imagine putting a football on,
putting a pound on a 350 to1 odds. The
chances are you'd lose. But you ended up in Amsterdam,
the the same place I went. First time.
Unbelievable, mate. What's the chances?
Um and then um what I've got to ask you
as well is um you know how you say that
you've got all of this money and ret and
you know Peter Bennett skin and
whatever. Um may I ask you um how comes
it took you until 31 to go abroad? How
comes you've got no bed? How comes you
live in a bedset? You don't have any
designer clothes. And how comes you've
never been to any nice restaurants,
you know, been to multiple places,
multiple countries like I have? If
you've got all of this money, why have
you lived the worse life than me? I'm
sure it should be the other way around.
People that progress with money, people
that have money is supposed to have a
better life. But you literally didn't go
abroad until you was 31. You don't even
have a bed. You've got no designer
clothes. You've got no life experience
because obviously I I understand that it
is one or the other with a lot of people
and a lot of people are not into
designer clothes. I get that. And then
they then replace it with something
else, i.e. traveling, i.e. assets, but
you have absolutely nothing. So, if you
generally had more money than me and
you've been having more money for me for
years, how comes I've had a better life
and luxurious life experiences and you
have nothing? I'll be I'll be um looking
forward to your reply. But, mate, that
Amsterdam thing is proper proper dodge
because I went to Amsterdam before you
and then somehow you just ended up there.
You went to Amsterdam even though you've
got a girlfriend where most people go to
Amsterdam to smoke weed and [ __ ]
prostitutes. That's literally the number
one reason why people go there. You've
got a girlfriend and you somehow ended
up in Amsterdam.
Yeah. It wasn't cuz I went, was it? No.
No. And again, it doesn't matter where
you stayed. It doesn't matter if the It
doesn't matter if you spent 10 years
there and you spent a billion pounds.
You ended up in the same country and the
same city as me. All because I went. You little copycat.
That's what I'm going to title this. Few
questions for the copycat.