Yo. Okay. So, I'm going to reply to this
little keyboard warrior and I'm going to
make him write on a good couple of
things here. I'm going to make him
correct on on some things. But, um
before I do, um this isn't going to be a
video of me insulting you or anything.
I'm actually going to cut you some
slack. I mean, you would embarrassed
yourself 3 weeks ago when you put that
photo up of you tensing your skinny,
twiggy, weak little arms, um, thinking
that you got muscle and then 2 days
after then deleted a photo due to pure
shame and embarrassment. Now, Ricky,
manto man, uh, you have not got one
ounce of muscle in any part of your
body. You are very, very, very weak.
Like I was actually concerned. Like I
was thinking, bro, if this guy tenses
for any longer, his body's going to
shatter in pieces. He's that weak. Like
you are very, very weak. Which is which
makes me laugh because it's always like
it's always people like Ricky Milindon
and Ngle, Scrawny, weak, no muscle
cowards that are the biggest keyboard
warriors on the internet. Like, I swear
to God, these two, geeky nerds would
never even look at anybody funny in real
life, let alone say anything to anyone's
face. Like, there's nothing to them.
They're both skinny, no muscle, weak.
Like, there's literally nothing to them.
But on the internet, they're the biggest
keyboard warrior cowards going. Um, but
I guess that's just the internet and
nothing's going to um change that. So,
it is what it is, huh? But anyways, on
to this um [ __ ] that you've um
wrote here. I thought this is gonna make
a really good video. Um so here we go.
Okay, so he's utterly jealous and
envious of your life. Now the thing is
Ricky, I'm not going to make it out that
it's the worst um thing to accuse
somebody of um being jealous, but to me
it's always been a big thing. I mean, I
hate the word, you know, same when
people say I'm jealous of them, when I
say that you people are jealous of me,
which you actually are jealous of me.
Um, because in the end, you left me know
of a choice where it had to be jealousy
what you people do every day. Um, which
I will actually back up my claim. I will
back up my statement. Um, in a bit,
unlike you, you can't do that. You're
just writing [ __ ] for the sake of
writing [ __ ] But um yeah, like even
when I'm saying about how you people are
jealous or how you're trying to say that
I'm jealous, it just seems like an easy
attempt out of any kind of argument
encounter um debate sort of thing. So I
just don't like the word jealousy. Now
the thing is Ricky um I have never been
jealous of anybody. Never have. And I
don't think I ever will. But if one day
I woke up and I suddenly wanted to be um
jealous of somebody, it would not be
somebody that has no teeth, less money
than me, and less life experiences than
me. It would have to be somebody that's
that's got a better life than me.
Because in order to be jealous of
somebody, Ricky, the person has to have
a better life than you. I mean, even if
someone had more money than you, I don't
think that's enough. I mean, they have
to have a better life, better looks,
better money. bit like what I've got and
why you people are the ones that are
actually jealous of me. Um, which is
what I'll explain, you know, in a
minute. Um, it's not just one thing. And
in order for you to uh be jealous,
Ricky, the person has to have a better
life than you. I generally don't think
you could be jealous of somebody that's
got no teeth. Even if you tried,
even if they were the last person on
Earth, even. I don't think you could be
jealous of somebody that's got no teeth.
I mean, think about it. Anyone who's
watching this, anyone you you envy or
you look up to even or you idolize even,
I'm pretty sure they've all got teeth in
their mouth. Correct me if I'm wrong. I
don't think you could be jealous of
somebody that don't have any teeth. That
does not even make any sense. How could
you be jealous of someone that doesn't
even have basic dental hygiene? Make it
make sense. Now, another thing I'm going
to ask you, um,
uh, Ricky, is what gives you the
impression that I'm jealous? Is it
anything I've done? Is it anything I
said? Is it, uh, a community post I
made? Like, tell us what what it is,
what the problem is. Um, because you're
claiming that I'm jealous, but you've
got absolutely no evidence to back any
of it up. um you've got no evidence to
back that claim up that you've just
made. Now, when I say that you people
are jealous of me, I can explain it. You
harass me every single day. You stalk me
every day. You will not leave me alone.
Um you've been doing this for years.
You're at me constantly despite the fact
you try to call me what you are
yourselves, you know, skint ugly. And
then you think, hold on a minute, you
have to put two and two together. If
you're really all of these things that
these people are trying to paint you as,
they would leave you alone and live
their life. And then the fact that they
don't do that and they won't leave you
alone every day, it says something
completely different. Um it's jealousy.
Um that's how I knew that like what you
people do every single day. And it's not
just that. I'll get into other things in
a minute. Um how you claim I'm this that
you won't leave me alone. You stalk me.
You harass me every single day. People
that are not jealous of people don't do
that. They just live their life. And
then you'll always get people on here
say, "Oh, well, there's nothing to be
jealous of." Well, you need to tell
yourself that because you're the ones
that are showing yourselves to be
jealous every single day when you're
doing this [ __ ] on YouTube. You don't
need to tell me or convince me that
you're not jealous of anything. You need
to tell yourself that um that there's
nothing to be jealous of because that is
not actions of a man who is not jealous
of someone. It's the complete opposite.
Because like I said, I'm adult enough to
be able to put myself in other people's
shoes. And yeah, if somebody was really
skin ugly and all of these things,
uh, they would leave you alone, but they
don't leave you alone, which
only points to jealousy. So, that's
that's the whole point I'm trying to
make. Now, and another thing is it's not
just the fact that it's the fact that,
have you noticed that they don't do this
to anybody else on here?
like no one else. Have you noticed that
it's only Peterbelly? Um probably
because you're younger than them and
better looking than them. Oh, sorry. I
shouldn't have said that, but it's the
[ __ ] truth. So, I'll leave it in
there. Um if you notice, they don't do
this to anyone else. They only go for
me. You only get these stranger danger
men um only going for me, lining up to
have their say every day. Will not leave
me alone. I don't know, man. That looks
like jealousy to me. Um, and I think it
would look like jealousy to anybody
else. Um, that's not biased. Um, that
they don't go for anyone else. They
claim they you're all of these things,
but they won't leave you alone. And then
I thought, okay, maybe there was a
chance that they aren't jealous and
they're doing this because you've done
something drastic. But then they can't
even blame that. I mean, you haven't
even done anything that they that that
warrants this whole obsession and this
hatred other than being better looking
than them. Um, that's one thing they
can't stand that I am better looking
than them even though they'll never
admit it. But at the end of the day,
they never um, you know, it's not like
you've raped somebody or you've killed
someone um, or you've done something
drastic. There's no real reason why they
do this every day, which points even
more to it being jealousy. Only the
arrows only point to jealousy, Ricky,
with you people towards me. I've never
shown any actions of jealousy towards
anyone else. I mean, for [ __ ] sake,
you are the ones going on all day, every
day about me. So, when we put when we
when we do a summary of this all, right,
let's think about it. You say that I'm
skinn and I'm ugly, yet you stalk me
every day. You harass me every day. You
talk about me every day. Um, you don't
do it to anyone else. And there's no
real reason why you do this other than
me being better looking than all of you.
Sounds like jealousy to me. So, what at
the end of the day, mate, you've got it
the wrong way round. Um, you are the
ones that were jealous of me and I've
just backed up my claim on how I know it
is jealousy. Um, which is why I don't
waste my time on you people most of the
time because it's just jealousy. Simple.
And like I said, you can, like I said a
million times, you can claim it's not,
but your actions show it is. And that's
the main thing. So, um, because if it
wasn't, you would just not waste your
time and leave someone alone. Simple.
So, you need to tell yourself that. So
you say that um you have everything that
he wants. Um
does he? News to me. I've got designer
clothes. I've got teeth. Better hair.
More life experiences. Been to more
countries. Been on more holidays. Ah,
strange. I I didn't know he had
everything that I wanted. Well, that's
strange then. Well, if he's got
everything that I want and he's better
than me, then why is he on YouTube all
day every day talking about me,
obsessing over me, stalking me? Make it
make sense, Ricky, if you're going to
make a statement. So, he's got
everything I want, but yet he's sat on
YouTube all day stalking me, and it's
not the other way around.
Strange. Again, in order to be jealous
of somebody, they have to have a better
life than you, and they have to have um
teeth in their mouth. If they don't have
any of them things, I don't think you
could be jealous of them. I don't think
it's possible. And then you're saying
about um girlfriend. Now, here's the
thing. Um I've had a girlfriend. Um I
have been with multiple different women.
Um all of which has never had special
needs. Um let me let me let me put this
into perspective for you. Um all of the
women that I have been with has never
been as ugly as his girlfriend.
So, how could I be jealous of somebody
having an ugly girlfriend? Let me repeat
that. You're saying that I'm jealous of
somebody that's got a girlfriend. Now, I
have been with I have been with not the
nicest looking women in my time due to,
you know, me being drunk or just why
not? You take what you can get. And I
can hand on my heart say that I have
never been with anyone as ugly as his
girlfriend. So again, how could you
possibly be jealous? What you're saying
on here doesn't make any sense. And
again, is there anything to back up your
statement of me apparently being jealous
of him having a girlfriend? Um, I've had
a girlfriend and I've had multiple
chances to be in rel other
relationships. Um, and again, it's not
even about going back and forth and
that. It's about evidence to back up
your statement. Now, you're saying that
I'm jealous of him because he's got a
disabled girlfriend who looks worse than
any other woman that I've ever been
with. And that's what you've said. So,
where's the evidence? So, so when I say
that he's jealous of all of the women
that I've been with, all of the, you
know, USA Izzy and all of the women that
I pulled cuz I'm better looking than him
and he can't cuz he's an ugly bastard.
My evidence is that he has stalked them.
He has tried to get with them. Um, he
has literally spent so much of his time
convincing himself that I have not slept
with said women that he doesn't even
know. That's my evidence on how he's
jealous of the women that I've been
with. So, if you're just going to throw
stuff out there for the sake of throwing
stuff out there, um, you know, it
doesn't make any sense. And then, um,
cuz I've got evidence to back up how you
people are jealous of me, and I've got
evidence to back up how he's jealous of
all of the women that I've been with.
I've actually got evidence. So, you can
say what you like, but without any
evidence, you can't back up anything
you're saying. Um, you just make
yourself look silly. So then you said
about sex. Um, let me tell you
something, Ricky. I have had sex more
times than you and him ever will. I have
been with I made a [ __ ] porno for
[ __ ] sake. Um, I have been with
multiple women um, time and time again,
which you have seen yourself. I've been
seen in bed with women. I've [ __ ] put
a porno out there on [ __ ] YouTube.
Trust me, you two combined will never
have sex as many times as I have. Um,
and to be honest with you, that just
sounds like such an immature thing to
say. Um, oh yeah, well, you get sex and
he doesn't. That sounds like what a
5-year-old would say. I swear now, bro,
that sounds like something somebody
would say like as a 5-year-old kid. Uh,
you get more sex.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. Oh my god, that made
me laugh. The thing is, Ricky, um, I
don't want to have sex with a disabled
girl. I don't find her attractive. So,
if you are going to try and tell
somebody that they're jealous of
somebody having sex, the woman has to at
least be attractive and not disabled,
you don't, like I keep saying, Ricky,
you need to make it make sense. Now,
this is a good one, right? So,
this is a good one that you wrote here.
Um, money. Now, money. Let's get on to
the money point. Okay. So, you're trying
to say that I'm jealous that uh he's got
money. Okay. Let me put this into
perspective for you. If I'm so jealous
that he apparently has more money than
me, how comes I'm the one with the bed?
How comes I'm the one with the designer
clothes? How comes I'm the one that's
been to more countries than him, been to
more restaurants than him, been with
more women than him, stayed in more
hotels than him, and have a lot more
life experience than him. Surely to God,
if he's got more money than me, it would
be the other way round. Again, zero and
zero is not adding up because it doesn't
tend to. If you're jealous of somebody
that's got more money than you, they
would have a better life than you. I
mean, let me put this into perspective.
The holiday that he's going on, I done
that when I was 23. I mean, I've been to
more countries. I've been abroad more
times. I've been to countries he's not
been. He's only been to one country.
I've been to multiple different
countries. So, again, make it make
sense. And another thing is if he has
more money than me, um, then what was I
saying? If he's got more money than me,
how comes I've beat him at the money
game a million times and he's only just
showing money? You said that I'm jealous
of somebody that's that's got money.
Now, hate to break it to you, Rickster.
Um £13,000 is not a lot of money um to
have saved for 3 years. Now, let me put
this into perspective. That is just over
£4,000 a year saved, bro. I used to go
through about £4,000 in a month, maybe
even £6,000 in a month when I used to do
gambling, when I used to go out
approaching. Bro, I've lived the life.
And you can't put a price on, you know,
life experiences. You can have all the
money in the world. Um, but you can't
take that to the grave with you. And
your life experiences, you can because
you'll never ever regret that on your
deathbed. Now, at the end of the day,
mate, I used to go through four, five,
6,000 a month. A lot of the times I did.
Trust me, I did. So, why would I be
jealous of somebody that's showing £13,000?
That took them 3 years to save and they,
you know, and in them 3 years, they
sacrificed living the life. They
sacrificed living how life should be
lived in your prime. again, make it make
sense. Um, you know, £4,000, just over
£4,000 a year to save is not a lot of
money. And again, in order to be better,
in order to be jealous of someone, they
need to have a better life. I'll I'll
stick to my guns. I've been to more
countries. I've been to more places.
I've been to more restaurants. I've been
with more women. Um, he was sitting at
home for 3 years saving money. Why would
anybody be jealous of that? Make it make
sense. And then you say holidays. Um, now
again, I've been on more holidays than
him. I've been to more locations than
him. I've been to more places than him.
Make it make sense. Um, and then you're
saying deep down that will destroy him.
No. Nothing you people do destroy me.
Not one little thing. But what I Well,
me being younger and better looking than
you people destroy you. That's why you
won't leave me alone every single day on
YouTube. So, make it make sense. And I'm
not even joking, you know, when I had
that six grand, I got back payments and
stuff. Trust me, I mean, I was spending
four five 6,000 a month. Trust me,
£13,000 in 3 years is Mickey Mouse
money. To save for 3 years is is is
terrible. Um, you know, I could probably
save probably £13,000 in a year if I
really wanted to, if you know, if I
really put my mind to it. So, I mean,
there's literally nothing to be jealous
of, and there's nothing that backs up
your statement or your claim that I'm
jealous, but everything backs up what I
say about you people. So, you want to
you want to get a grip, Ricky. You really do.