Yo. Okay, so this is going to be my last
response to um LT. I've just gone on
your community post. I don't want to
keep going back and forth with you
either, and you're trying to take the
piss out of the way I look on my body.
Nice 2-year-old picture, by the way. At
least I don't catfish and put up
pictures that are not me, and I'm not
scared to show my face like you. Um,
that's the first thing, right? Secondly,
you're still making excuses for that
bouncer trying to say, "Oh, he couldn't
uh do anything because he was going to
lose his job." Ret? Okay then. Well, let
me ask you this question because I've
been thinking about this. How comes
right last uh I think it was November or
December when I was slabbering at that
man in Patty Power, the gay man. You
didn't say any of these things about,
oh, you didn't do anything because uh uh
he was going to lose his job when he had
more chance of losing his job than a
[ __ ] bouncer. We know bouncers can
get away with stuff and you're just
making excuses because it was the black
guy that backed down and not the white
guy, right? So why did you not use that
same analogy, right, when I was
slabbering at that white man in Patty
Power? Yeah. Nonstop.
You didn't say anything about, oh well,
we didn't want to hit you because he was
going to lose his job because you know
what you're saying is [ __ ] and it's
because the guy was black and not white.
That's what it is. because you've been
coming on here for years saying, "Oh,
oh, black guys are superior. They're the
alpha males." Well, guess what? That guy
weren't no alpha male and he happened to
be black, bro. And he shattered. So
what? You know, like you're you're only
using these excuses, right? Because
the guy's uh uh because the guy was
black. If the guy was white, you'd be
calling him a [ __ ] Yeah. And let's go
by your logic then. If you're trying to
use the excuse says, "Oh, I I can't go
for anyone that's working." Right. in
case they I quote lose their job and
they have to be professional. So that
must mean that that guy right do you
remember um the bus scenario when I was
on the bus to Wolfento and I was going
to Admiral's uh arcade and the guy was
giving it l I was a bit younger then
couple years ago right and the old black
man was slabbering to me right so that
must mean then he didn't win then did he
because going by your logic then if I
was to argue back with him um he
wouldn't be able to do anything to me
anyways because he would lose his job so
you're contradicting yourself which one
is it you know you have no problem when
the black guy is [ __ ] uh you know um
slabbing about me when he's a [ __ ]
bus driver or you have no problem when
I'm [ __ ] um taking the absolute piss
out of a gay white man in the bookies.
But as soon as it's to do with me
slabbing about a black guy and he ain't
got nothing to say. Oh well, he can't do
anything because he uh uh doesn't want
to lose his job. Bro, do you think that
guy would have done anything? Period.
Like like do you really really really
think if he didn't have that badge he
would he would have done anything? No.
Like bro, you know you're full of [ __ ]
That's why on that community post that
you uh put up it's basically just
repeating what you've said because you
know I've got you by the bollocks bro
cuz I know what you're about. It's all
to do with race. It's ridiculous. I
don't know what it is with you obsessed
with [ __ ] race. I don't know what it
is. Like you seem to think black people
are stronger than every white person. It
doesn't work like that. It's not to do
with skin color, you [ __ ] idiot. Um,
but anyways, um, yeah, that's that. And
then you were saying about how I was
shaking my tits off. Bro, maybe if I was
shaking, I might have been cold. I only
had a jumper on. I can assure you I
wasn't scared of any of them five
people. Yeah, I can tell you that for
[ __ ] nothing. Um, and I slapped my
mouth and I stood at the exact same
place. Bro, the guy was shaking his leg.
If you watch the video properly, right,
that guy was nonstop shaking his [ __ ]
leg and I was by myself and I stood in
the same place and I was slabing off
about them. Yeah. So, what about them
four people then? What about them four
people and I told them to [ __ ] off and
call them an ugly [ __ ] What was the
excuse then? What was the excuse then?
Because you're full of [ __ ] excuses.
What about the Weather Spoons when I was
telling that woman about herself cuz she
was [ __ ] cop blocking me, right, and
starting [ __ ] and then there was three
guys to the left of me and they done
absolutely nothing about it. What about
that? What about were they working?
You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] house, mate. It's
excuse after excuse after excuse with
you. Yeah, cuz we all know, right? If
that bouncer was a white guy and I and
and I done what I'd done to him, right,
as the same as black guy, you would have
no problem with it. You'd big me up cuz
why did you not have any problem with me
owning that white guy in the bookies?
You laughed at it. You found it funny.
You said, "Oh yeah, he's he's a puff.
He's got [ __ ] he paints his nails."
You had absolutely no problem with that.
But then when it's to do with a black
guy Yeah. who you would deem would be
about it, but he ain't about [ __ ]
right? Oh, well,
he can't lose his job yet. You literally
have told me that a bouncer smashed one
of your teeth friend your one of your
friends teeth in. So, which one is it?
You need to make up your mind, you know.
[ __ ] hell, bro. You really really
have got this thing about race, you
know. So that guy on the bus then didn't
win then when he was mouthing off about
me years ago and I didn't do anything
then then going by your logic then he's
a coward then isn't he? Because he knew
that he could mouth off about me and if
I say anything back or do anything back
then the argument is going to be oh well
uh he's going to lose his job if he says
or does anything. You're an idiot mate.
bouncers can get away with more stuff than
any kind of workplace, you know, like
it's not like a bookies. If you if you
go to a bookies and [ __ ] someone
starts fighting you, one of the members
of the staff, then there's a good chance
that they'll lose their job. And I had a
guy in a bookies before and he was ready
to fight and everything. He was ready,
more than ready to fight, bro. Yeah. But
yeah, when it's to do a black bouncer
who could easily have got away with, you
know, at least saying something. Oh, he
doesn't want to lose his job. Yeah, he's
the one that started it. You're an
absolute tool. That's what you are.