So, the jeans have just come. Um, sorry
it was a bit delayed. Um, I was waiting
for Postman Pat and his black and white
cat to deliver and he did. Um, so yeah,
I just wanted to uh start off with
Joseph Farra aka Joe's Joe F. Um, how
does it feel that these jeans are worth
more than your mobile phone? Literally,
what I'll be wearing on my little legs
are worth more than your mobile phone. I
bet that I bet that annoys you. So, when
you're when you think about coming
online again trying to troll me or take
the piss, just remember what I'm
probably wearing that day is worth more
than your uh [sighs] shitty little 200
pound phone. Just just throw it at you
like a bit of saliva. Um just making
friends, guys. And um another thing,
Joseph F, is you always talk about life
experiences and you you probably do have
more life experiences than me because
you know you're older than me and you
know you whether you're in your 40s or
your 50s, however old you are. Um but
there's one thing I do have that you
don't. I have experience wearing
expensive gums, expensive jeans. Have
you ever owned a 200 pair of jeans? No.
Didn't think so. I mean, it's so lush.
It generally feels like you're you're um
you're in heaven when you wear them. So,
just remember, Joseph, that with all the
life experience, you claim to have more
than me. You've never had jeans as
expensive as I have. Just just remember
that and let that let that stay in your
mind. Now, on to Virgin Boy. Um
obviously, I had to add Joseph Ferrar in
there because of the mobile. Onto Virgin
Boy, skint in the bed suit with no bed,
no money in it. Um, so I just wanted to
start by saying [laughter]
I need to calm down because obviously
the noise I don't want to disturb
people. I'm going for a meal with my mom
later. Um, when was the last time you
went for a meal with your mom? Oh,
never because she [ __ ] starved you
and disowned you and you know absolutely
nothing about it. So you got starved by
your mom. I don't think you went for a
meal with your [ __ ] mom. Um, so and I
was actually thinking that you need to
you've copied a lot of my stuff. Like
you've copied my holidays. You've went
to Amsterdam just because I went to
Amsterdam. You [ __ ] ugly ratfaced
[ __ ] virgin [ __ ] Um, you've copied
places that I've gone to, but you've
never you've always like to copy me with
a lot of things, but you've never copied
me with the designer clothes.
Wonder why that is. Cuz you can't afford
it. This these pair of jeans right now
cost more than anything you've got in
that shitty little virgin wardrobe of
yours in that outer London bedsit. Um
generally generally generally [ __ ]
is. Now I just I could just imagine you
well I say I could imagine you. I could
imagine you in waxies um with your skint
little virgin charity shop ugly clothes
with your ugly face trying to order a
pint and trying to chat to a woman when
she can smell the virgin a mile off. But
then I thought it is hypothetical at the
end of the day because a you can't
afford to go to waxies and b you're too
scared to talk to women because you've
got anxiety. So I don't know where the
[ __ ] I was going with that. They have
certain um places where disabled virgins
such as yourself can function cuz you
can't function in normal [ __ ]
environments. Can you [ __ ] virgin?
Now I was generally thinking of going
out Saturday because I've got 200 pound
pair of jeans here. Well, I was going to
get a new pair of trainers. Um, because
I'm not skinned like you, you skinned
virgin. Um, but Greavvesy said that I
can't and he locked the door, so I can't
go to JD and and buy the trainers. I was
going to go and buy them, but yeah,
Grievousy said, "No, just just just wear
them." Um, the ones you got cuz they
still look new. So, yeah, you would
never be able to afford a 200 pound pair
of jeans, will you, Virgin Boy? I mean,
think about it, mate. It took you eight years
older than me to copy my holiday because
you were that [ __ ] skinn. I don't
think you're going to be getting a 200
pound pair of jeans anytime [ __ ]
soon. You know, I generally think cuz
obviously we're different skin
complexion and obviously we got
different hair color. I'm much better
looking than you. Oh, by a long shot I'm
much better looking than you, Virgin
Boy. And I've never had to resort to
disabled. Even though you say that I've
never struggled with women in my life
and I've never had any of these problems
that PJ has. Yeah, you tell him, my son.
You only dating disabled women and going
on six different dating apps that are
paid for cuz you're scared to talk to
women shows that you've never had any
problems with women. You tell him, my
son, I'm right by your side. I'm being
sarcastic if you if you didn't figure it
out cuz obviously you've got autism, you
got asperes. Some people with asperes uh
they can't they can't tell or read
sarcasm. So I was thinking virgin boy if
you were this
and that got some nice after shave over
there and you went down to waxes
hypothetically cuz obviously you're skin
and you can't function in normal
environments. You might lose that vcard.
I I think that you might actually lose
that virginity, mate.
I generally think you might actually no
longer be a virgin and you will get to
your 31st birthday and you would finally
have lost it. Look, look at that, mate.
Talking about my clothes. I'm not some
[ __ ] skint virgin that has to shop at
the charity shop cuz I'm low on [ __ ]
funds like [ __ ] you, son. Now, if you
[ __ ] don't mind, I'm going to pop in
the [ __ ] shower now, get changed into
these lovely designer clothes that's
worth more than your whole life, and go
for a meal that my mom wants to take me
to because my mom didn't starve me like
[ __ ] yours. Goodbye now.