Okay, so I had ordered myself a lovely
takeaway. Nice chicken um turkey mane.
Um this time I got a lamb foul instead
of a lamb vindaloo. Sometimes I get
madress, sometimes I get vindaloo. This
time I wanted to get myself, as you can
see, lamb foul. Um so there's no funny
business. Everyone thinks I'm trying to
have a vindaloo.
Trying to think I'm having a vindaloo
and then claiming it's a foul. But I
must say before I start, a certain
virgin wouldn't dare go anywhere near
that, mate. That is very, very [ __ ]
hot. Look at that. Actually looks
beautiful. That looks yummy. No. Um, no.
Um, just going to have this whilst um talking. No. Um,
it doesn't watery or anything. It looks
perfect. Normally when you order it, it's um
it's um watery for some reason. So I'm
going to pause, put it on a plate, and
see if I can have this lamb foul, or
will it defeat me? Got my kind of coke
here, and I'll pause and resume. Right,
here we go. So I've whisked it up
nicely. What I don't understand with
these Indians is they always give you so
much curry and rice, which is the
cheapest thing that's made, they give
you so little of. They don't give you
the same rice as they do the curry. But anyways, right
that is um considerably a lot hotter
than the vindaloo.
My coke still closed.
This is beautiful. I might start having
to have lamb foul.
Oh, that's lovely.
M. Now, we know a certain person right
now would be opening that [ __ ] can
and [ __ ] yumming it down their
[ __ ] virgin throat. M.
No, that is lush. That's actually a lot
better than the bindu. I think I'm going
to start having this in future.
Here we go. M
just yaming it. Mhm.
They don't call me the big strong
Turkish man for no reason, lads.
They really really don't.
M. Don't see me [ __ ]
I can't take it.
Don't see me doing any of that [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] cuz I'm
a big strong Turkish man, mate.
So, there we go. Completed it. M. Lovely.
Just got me my new favorite one now, I reckon.
There we go. Look, coke's still there. Not frozen, no nothing. M m. Yummy.