Yo. Okay, so this is going to be a new
video on dating. I feel like I've got
some stuff to get off of my chest and
yeah, I was thinking out loud earlier
and a lot of the stuff that I was
thinking out loud was very logical. It
made a lot of sense and I thought to
myself, do you know what? Why not
compile it all into one video and yeah,
just make a banging video. Um because
why not? So, I thought, yeah, let's
let's do it. So,
I have completely given up on dating um
approaching women, trying to find Mrs.
Wright, if uh if you will, if that's
like a better way to word it, because I
figured in the end, you know, I have
tried more than anybody in the world. Um
you know, to try to meet somebody, you
know, I've been up and down the country.
I've been to various different cities
multiple times. God knows how many women
I have approached in all of these cities
in London. Like I have honestly tried so
much that I couldn't even explain it to
you and make you understand even if I
tried. Like it's it's you'd actually
have to see it actually all have to be
put on an hard drive and you'd have to
watch the whole thing and it probably
would be never ending. So I mean that
that wouldn't even really really solve
the issue to be honest with you. I I I
can safely say that I have tried more
than anybody in the world. And
it's clear now that I'm never going to
meet a woman that doesn't pretend that
she's got a boyfriend when I try to
speak to her. I'm not going to find a
woman that when I approach her, she's
not going to say that she's not
interested straight away before even
getting to know my personality or, you
know, find a woman that's not going to
give me her number. and you know um you
know doesn't reply when I message her or
reply once and stop or trolls me or
agrees to meet me then on the day you
know she says that she can't get over
her ex and she's in love with her ex or
something similar to what you know
they've been doing for years. I can
safely say with confidence now I don't
think I'm ever going to find a woman
that doesn't do any of the below. So,
I've completely completely lost hope.
Um, you know, and it's it's crazy to be
honest with you because, you know, I
don't know. I think a lot of people
knew that I had given up or I was on the
verge of giving up because, you know,
like I'd win a football bet and I would
just go to the cinema. I wouldn't even
go out drinking, trying with women. I'd
maybe do it like two weeks after. And it
just Yeah. it just it you you know when
you've lost hope. Um you know obviously
people have um different sort of
tolerance uh levels and obviously I'm
surprised I didn't give up a long time
ago with the amount of [ __ ] that I've
had to put up with with these women. I
found out that I had a lot of patience
and I never ever thought that I had
patience. Like I always saw myself as
somebody that never had patience. you
know, you're you're somebody that can't
wait because I always, you know, um
associated patience with laidback people
and not outgoing people and people like
with crazy personalities, like crazy in
a good way, obviously. Um so I I had
patience that I didn't even realize I
had because to have dealt with all of
this [ __ ] for as many years as I have,
that must have took some patience. and
you know and a lot of the stuff that I
had to deal with when I used to go out
and deal with these women and they'd be
rude for no reason like that how I never
ended up in a mental hospital or killing
someone I shall never know. Um like I I
generally don't know um because at the
end of the day um like I'm not going to
lie, right? I know that I've been OTT,
right, with a lot of things before and a
lot of my reactions to things have been
irrational, like if I've lost a bet or
if I've lost a game. And I realize that
the general population is not going to
act in that way. But I feel like with
this, I feel like it's very justified. I
feel like a lot of it is. I feel
generally like at the end of the day,
right? How would these people feel if
they were in your shoes? It could be a
man, it could be a woman, and they've
gone up and down the country and they've
tried to find love or they've tried to
get laid or whatever it is. They have
legitimately tried and they've
legitimately put their effort into and,
you know, they've they've done what most
people are scared of. Um, and they are
in my position. How would they feel? I
generally feel like they would have
ended up killing themselves, ending up
in a mental warden or they would have
gave up a long long long time ago. Like
I generally don't think there is
somebody like me that have that has gone
through all of this [ __ ] that would
still be even
even even here. Like I I think that's
like something that I should actually do
like seek out people that have actually
really really tried as hard as I have
and see where they are in life because
it would be quite interesting. I mean
even last month right when I went to see
Monty and I wanted to see if he was okay
cuz you know he had you know he was um
going through a breakup and I wanted to
be a friend. Like even then I spoke to a
couple of women and I got free numbers
and the chat was going good and you know um
you know and and we was talking back and
forth and then when it come to actually
meeting you know they used distance as
an excuse one did and one then all of a
sudden said oh well I'm not interested
in dating right now yet she was in a
club gave me her number messaged me back
and forth for 2 weeks yet she didn't
even give me a chance and it's it's
crazy. I mean, as it stands now, I don't
even have any new numbers on my phone.
Like, all of the numbers I had, you
know, it's gone now. You know, they
either weren't interested or they
replied and stopped replying or they
trolled me. And then as soon as I would
write something negative, they'd reply
straight away, which is very strange how
you get these people that sit there and
say, "Oh, all women aren't the same." And ret
similar things to each other. Do you not
find that very very sus? How like you
get a lot of women that say, "Oh, I'm in
love with my ex. I'm not over my ex." Or
they'll do things like have the same
attitude like reply to negativity or use
the word mate. Or, you know, use the
same excuses. Like, it's very very hard
to explain what I mean unless you've
dealt with them. But they're all very
similar to each other for people that
are apparently not all the same. Um it's
very very weird how they end up doing so
many they have so many simil sim similarities.
Um that's dodgy cuz I know that not one
man in the world is anything like me in
any way, shape or form. No man is the
same as me. Um and they would never ever
do or say the same things that I do. So
I mean but that it's not this is not a
video about them being the same or not
the same or any of this. It's that
that's not that's not what it is. So
obviously that's the reason why I didn't
go out tomorrow yesterday because it's
kind of like okay well
why would you go out and try again? You
know the result. You know you're going
to approach a woman and she's going to
say that she's got a boyfriend or she's
not interested or she's going to give
you her number and then just [ __ ] you
around. You know it's been this way for
many many many years. You know, and it
gets to the point where it's like you
thinking anything but
that happening is delusional. Like it's
not even being positive. Like any thing
that you say now like, oh, you're going
to go out and none of this stuff's going
to happen and all of it's going to
change and all of the things that's been
happening for years is no longer going
to happen. That is straight delusional.
And there's like a cuz because obviously
the the number one question would
obviously be is why haven't you already
found Mrs. Right? You know you've been
up and down the country. You've tried
with loads and loads of different women.
You've tried to make it work. You know
as much as which we'll get on to in a
minute. People like to say you're this
and you're that. You know you generally
have tried. So why have you not already
found Mrs. Wright? You've tried more
than everybody in the world. It's not
like you're somebody that's just been
off and on dating apps and you've not
really tried and four years have gone
past. You you legitimately have tried
with these women, you know, more than
anybody in the world. And why haven't
you already found her? I think that's
that's that's a that's a good question. Now,
this is the thing that I don't get.
Obviously, a lot of people will
disagree. Some people will agree. Some
people might even feel sorry for me,
which I don't want anyone to feel sorry
for me. That's not what this video is
about. But it's a figure of speech. But
one thing that they can't take from you,
even even if they generally wanted to,
is you tried. You put the effort in. You
went out, you approached so many
different women, you went on dating
apps, you tried dating apps in different
cities. Like, you generally generally
gave it your best. And I feel like
anyone in life that has given it, this
is getting a bit deep now, anyone in
life that has given it their best is a
winner in my book, which is where the
whole saying goes, God loves a try.
Think of it right now. Anyone who's
watching this, if you've got an enemy,
right, and you know, uh, they try their
best to change their situation for the
better. You can't knock anyone for doing
that. You can't knock a tryer that's
generally tried to change their
situation. This is what a lot of people
seem to forget. I feel like over the
years I never ever got any credit for
this. It weren't even enough credit. I
don't think I generally got any credit
for the amount I genuinely tried, you
know, going up and down the country
approaching women trying to find
somebody. And I know this is going to
sound very, very hard for a lot of
people surprisingly, but I didn't go all
over the country wasting my time,
wasting my money to come back, putting
my fingers in my earlobes, flapping my
hands around, sticking my tongue out,
saying that I told you so, laughing. I
was generally trying to find someone,
you know? I was genuinely trying to meet
somebody. When I was recording these
approaches, it weren't to say I told you
so. it was generally to um
uh spread awareness and what I'm going
through and my struggles. Um you know
what I'm saying? So at the end of the
day that's sort of uh how it is. It's
it's it's insane. It really really
really really is. And you know at the
end of the day right it's like even when
I have been on dates this is another
thing like the rare time you do get
dates. Now, another thing is it seems to
have gotten worse. So, two years ago,
you could get dates and
you could, you know, get kisses or you
could get the odd one night stand or
things was actually which is why I feel
like I had more hope back then. I don't
know if it was that or because I was
younger and I was living in the moment.
When I got stung by the reality be and I
realized, okay, I'm not no longer living
in the moment. I'm back to reality. I
look back on all of what I've tried and
even though this was only 20% of my
struggles at the time, it was still a
thing to remember, hold on, you have
tried, you have tried to meet women and
nothing has worked for you. Um, and you
know, it was possible, you know, to to
get dates and it, you know, and then it
was very good one year and then the
second year it was okay, okay, it's
getting a bit harder now and now the
third year it seems to be impossible. I
don't know what it is. Maybe people have
just gone on to Tik Tok more or Tik Tok
to become more famous, but there has
definitely been some changes in the past
couple of years because I remember a
couple of years ago it was easier and
you did get some sort of chances, but
now you just can't get anything. You
know, you try to get a conversation out
of a woman, all you're ever going to get
is I've got a boyfriend if you're lucky.
So, I mean, it's changed a lot in many,
many years. And I think also another
thing that was very depressing about it
is the fact that you know you're not
fat. You know you're not ugly. You know
a lot of what these trolls try to call
you on the internet. You know deep down
that you're not. And when you're not and
obviously you've got the history of
trying as much as you actually have. It
can [ __ ] with someone's brain, you know,
especially when like reality kicks in,
you know, cuz there's no reason for it.
You you should be with someone. You
know, you've approached good. You know,
you've been confident. You've tried.
You've took advice. And you know at the
end of the day you should be with
someone. Um but a lot of the things that
I also found um that I discovered that
even when you go on dates I remember I
had this foot injury. Um I forced myself
to go on a date and you know a few other
dates I went on is you can generally do
your best. You know they like the way
you look. You can be normal. You can do
your best. You can legitimately try all
you can on the date and they'll still
find some reason why. you know, they
won't meet you again. They'll say they
don't feel the vibe. And when it
happens, and then I've heard it happen
to a lot of people, I put it down to
they must have unrealistic expectations.
They must have in their head before
going on these dates that they want some
sort of Romeo and Juliet type [ __ ] And
if it's anything less than, you know,
they claim that they don't feel the
vibe, they're looking for
an unrealist like they're looking for
something like Romeo and Juliet. got
unrealistic expectations and if you
don't live up to them expectations,
they'll just say, you know, they don't
like you or they don't feel the vibe,
which to put it bluntly, what what else
can you do? You turn up to a date, you
do your best, you tell them your
hobbies. You know, there's been dates
I've gone on as well and I've tried my
legitimate best and they still it's been
so bad. I've actually kissed people
before and they've ghosted. Like, like
imagine that. Like then I think, okay,
what is it? And then you've actually
I've actually realized I've actually
gone on dates with people before, kissed
people like legitimately kissed people
and then they've still ghosted. So I
mean what's that all about? You know
what I'm trying to say? So um and that's
and that's you know what it is. But I I
feel like a lot of people never gave me
credit for all of the years of me
trying. And I generally feel like you
have every right to be pissed off. You
know you have tried. You've gone through
so much so much [ __ ] you know with these
women. You know, I generally feel like
I've gone through hell and back and then
gone back to hell to finish it off.
Like, I'm I'm not even joking. Like,
it's it's really really really bad.
Like, it's like, what does somebody even
do now if they want a relationship or
they want to get laid, you know? The
dating apps don't work. It's what you
going to do? Just keep trying for the
rest of your life and keep going through
this year in year out, year in, year
out. You know, don't don't you think
people have already been through enough
with it, you know, to to to last them a lifetime?
Um, so that's one of the reasons why I
can safely say I've completely given up trying to
trying to find Mrs. Wright cuz I don't
think she exists. At least not in Peter
Bell's world. So that's my story, man. Yeah.