Right. So Joe F made me do this and I
just wanted to show you that uh being a
bouncer is absolutely no excuse uh not
to defend yourself. Here you go. I've
got some videos here.
>> As you can see, the bouncers hit him
first. But you can't hit. They're at
work, says Jo. Look at this bouncer.
>> But they're at work. They're at work.
They can't hit you when you're at work. [clears throat]
And this bouncer literally hit him
first. Say what now, Jo? What? What are
you saying about people being at work
now, bro? What are you saying about
people being at work, not being able to
hit people? There's some even juicier ones here.
>> What are you saying, bro? Oh, but
they're at work. They're at work. [ __ ]
>> Say what now, Jo? Say what?
>> Oh, but they were at work. You're
picking your targets. I've just shown
you two bouncers that literally [ __ ]
hit people first. But you still use
their being at work as an excuse. You're
never going to win with these biased
jealous people. I need to realize that.
And then the better. Look, there that's
two bouncers that just smack people in
the face for no reason. But when I stick
it on a bouncer, well, they know they're
at work. The oldest excuse in the book. [ __ ] idiot.