What a [ __ ] day I've had.
I don't like you, UK asylum. I don't
like you. You always say I'm trolling.
You're a nasty fellow.
You always say that I'm trolling and I'm
never trolled in my life.
What I What do I get out of trolling?
Nothing. I don't get anything out of trolling.
Never trolled in my life, lad.
How am I trolling, bro?
You're a nasty fellow.
Oh, I spoke to her, by the way. She
messaged me back. So yeah, she just
deleted her photo and that Yeah, I spoke
to uh Christian Izzy.
You're not honest though cuz you're
saying that I'm trolling and I've never
trolled. See, this is what I'm saying.
They all lie on here. People like B and
[ __ ] They're [ __ ] liars, bro. Oh,
I've been speaking to people. They don't
know anyone I speak to, bro.
I told you they don't know. I've spoke
to I've already spoke to them this morning.
See, V such a stinking liar, bro. He's
such a stinking liar.
He's such a stinking liar. But my point
still stands on that video anyways. Regardless, lads.
No, she's not. No, she's not. She just
deleted her profile picture.
No, she isn't.
I suppose try, bro.
But it doesn't matter. Like I said, my
point still my point still stands
anyways on that video for the most part. So yeah.
Yeah, that was a piss take yesterday
with that [ __ ] with that gambling, bro. That
you say that you're honest. If you're
honest, why do you call me a troll then?
I never troll, lad. Never troll.
I should have won yesterday that football bet.
Don't know why it never
I don't know why it never won.
Fire sticks. I don't know why.
I think they're all [ __ ]
That's what I think. They're all [ __ ]
Yeah, that's what I'm going to have. I'm
going to have a curry today, I think.
Yeah, I'm going to have a curry today. Say Wednesday.
No, I thought they deleted my number,
but they never. No,
that's all right then. It
people saying that they spoke to her.
They never find her. How are they
finding people on WhatsApp that only
have WhatsApp? Good luck with that, lad.
Good luck with that, lad. Yeah. Right.
Yeah. takeaway core. Yeah.
I can't believe they scammed me. I have
100 pound, bro.
That's not good, is it?
Yeah. [ __ ] hell, bro.
What a [ __ ] day I've had.
That's what I said yesterday before I
went to sleep. Fire stick. What a
[ __ ] day I've had.
It's true though, isn't it?
What a [ __ ] day I had.
I don't know, bro.
He'll be here soon.
I don't know how they can do that. Scam
me, bro. And [ __ ]
What have you done, Fire Stick? What
have you done if you put £500 in, you
won,600, and they wouldn't give you it?
What would you do?
What have you actually done?
Oh, I was speaking to Christian is uh
this morning. Greasy.
Yep. She's still on the cards. Greasy.
Yeah, she just deleted her profile
picture. I was like, "Oh gosh."
Well, I'm just going to get a curry
later and that's it, bro.
Pretty much. Yeah,
Grezy, before I went to sleep yesterday,
I said, "What a [ __ ] day I've had."
You remember like Zip, do you remember
when Zippy said that on on the rainbow,
Greavvesy? What a [ __ ] day I've had.
It's true though, isn't it? Oh, bless. Yeah,
that's enough Tik Tok for today. Greavvesy,
that's enough tick tock for today.
I've actually got her saved as Christian Izzy now
cuz I didn't want her name to be put out
there in it. Christian Izzy.
So when they message me now, that's what
it comes up as. That's greasy. Oh,
that Brazilian food was nice yesterday,
Greasy. Is it? Oh, man.
£24 for all that.
I couldn't finish the gaming at the end,
Grezy. I was too I was too I was too full. No.
I heard from my mama today, didn't I,
Greavvesy? So, I feel better.
Have I found a new mama, Greavvesy?
Have I found a new mama, Grevy?
Uh, a Mackey's. Have a Macky's.
Yeah, the gambling yesterday pissed me
off cuz I got scammed, bro.
Cuz I got scammed.
That's the reason it pissed me off cuz I've been
Don't worry. When my lads account opens
again, I'll I'll I'll win some money,
bro. Don't worry.
I'll win some money, bro. Don't worry.
Can do a post about me. Oh, no one
cares, bro. No one cares about Timmy
after the other day, right? He needs to
be starved of attention. Isn't that right, Greavvesy?
He needs to be starved of attention, lad.
Yeah, it's true, isn't it? If someone
hasn't stepped in a taxi, bro, after
giving it all that big talk, all that
mouth, don't bother with them.
Simple as that, ain't it?
Why do you think I don't go back and
forth with non legs? Because they've
shown what they're about, bro. So why
why I might make the odd funny comment
here and there about the fact that he's
a [ __ ] virgin at 31, but you know,
for the most part, bro, like
this guy, all he had to do was step in
in a taxi.
There's no point, Mr. B. Arguing.
Arguing with Timmy is like playing chess
with a pigeon. Even if you beat the ch
the pigeon, it will just strut around
the table and [ __ ] all over it, acting
like it's one.
Pointless. It's like playing chess with a pigeon.
Arguing with Timmy is like playing chess
with a pigeon. Tom Wood gave me that quote.
Oh, that's just someone on Facebook.
That was just someone on Facebook, bro.
On PlayStation years ago. Yeah.
Why can't I get attached anymore? Greavves.
I had a go at a lane yesterday. I said,
"You're so selfish. You are." He said,
"What can I do, son? What can I do,
son?" I said, "I've just been [ __ ] scammed."
Yeah. I said, "I've just been [ __ ] scammed. No.
Yeah. I told um Christian Izzy about the
cinema and stuff.
She said, "What the hell? That's so
weird." I said, "Yeah." So weird.
That makes me laugh.
That makes me laugh. Boozy.
That's funny, Grezy. Ha, that's funny.
Do you remember that, Grezy?
Ha, that's funny.
Yeah, you love mocking me, in it. Oh gosh.
Oh gosh. Greasy. Oh [ __ ] Yep.
They were laughing at you. Who's they
mocking you? You forgot that saying.
I agree with you. You forgot that saying
to be fair.
Yeah, you forgot that saying. They were
They were laughing at you, mocking you.
laughing at you. [ __ ] you
that account is such a copycat, bro. I
swear to God.
I'm going to have a shower in a minute, bro.
Oh, getting some clean clothes, you know.
Could have done with this 150 yesterday.
scam and [ __ ]
You can see the westernity in their
eyes. I think that's got to be my
favorite. I think that's got to be my favorite saying.
You can see the westernity in their eyes.
That is [ __ ] hilarious, bro.
Yeah, he can go on about me as much as
he wants, lad.
I'm not asked.
Yeah, he can go on about me all he
wants. I'm not asked. He didn't step in
the cab. That's it. Simple.
I'm not giving him attention. If he
actually wanted to meet someone, he
would have he would have stepped on the
He would have stepped in the cab. Did
you get me? Yep.
Yeah. I don't even have his other channel.
I don't even I don't even have his other channel.
He can get he can go on about me all he
wants. I'm not entertaining him. Bro, he
showed what he's about. So why are we
going to keep arguing with someone
that's shown what they're about?
I don't know what the other channel is.
I'm not sub to it. Yeah.
I don't know, bro. Like just like a lot
of these people do.
Just jealous losers in it. Fire stick.
Just jealous losers. Yeah.
Give it a while, lad.
Give it a whirl.
No, I'm not doing a football bet. I've
retired from gambling now. Fire stick. I'm retired.
Retired like Ali Law.
Yeah, of course he did. He's He's a liar, bro.
Stop talking about these people, bro.
They're irrelevant, man.
No, another another saying, Grezy, is
they saw the white man coming.
They saw the white man coming, Grezy.
That's another one as well. Yep.
They saw a white man coming. Greasy.
The bookies. The bookies are the white man coming. Poor [ __ ]
Did you lose all Did you lose all your
money last month?
Buy a stick, you poor [ __ ]
No, I didn't, man. To be fair, I can't be asked.
Talking to my mama this morning.
No more collection.
I actually did think they deleted my
number. I thought they deleted my number. music
start to get a bit worried.
I said, "What are you doing, mama?
Deleting my number, mama.
Look for this person.
Uh there's this person on WhatsApp
Greavesy. You can see the westernity in their eyes.
Do you remember what Antman said? He
said, "Yeah, that's what stands out. Westernized.
That's what stands out."
But how do It's like they look dead in
the eyes, isn't it? That's the west
That's the western eyes. That's the
westernity in their eyes. It's just like
dead in it.
They just look dead in the eyes. Like I
can't explain it.
Mary Jane don't have uh uh westernized eyes. Grezy. Nope.
Yeah, that they only started becoming
westernized. So what you're saying,
Grez, is they they got it from watching
too much Tik Tok, isn't it?
It's too much Tik Tok, isn't it?
That's enough Tik Tok for today.
I hate that westernized look, bro. It's annoying. Hey, man. Antman
says to these women in Asia when they're
westernized and stuck up, you know what
he says to them, Greavvesy? He says,
"There's nothing Asian about you.
There's nothing Asian about you."
That's what he says. There's nothing Asian about you.
What other sayings is there?
I need to make sure you've got all the
all the right sayings. I need to double
check. Waves there.
Yeah. One second.
Oh, I'm banned from texting on Instagram
for a week, by the way, Grezy. Yeah.
Right. What sayings have you wrote down?
No, there's one you're missing here.
See you later, lad.
You don't bully anyone. People, you bully yourselves.
Uh oh. No, you did add it. Oh, I was
about to say you didn't add. What a lovely site.
Yeah, pretty much. Um,
I'm trying to think of any more.
I think that's it. Yeah.
Yeah, I think that's all the sayings to
be fair. Trying to think.
What a lovely site.
That's my favorite. What a lovely site.
I don't know where I used to come up
with these [ __ ] sayings, bro. I just
come up with them. Greasy.
What a lovely sign.
I'm crazy, aren't I?
We like pick We're going to like pick a mix.
Lovely. Here's it. Oh [ __ ]
What are you meeting?
Who the [ __ ] what you all about? Are you meeting Sho?
What the [ __ ] are you on about, kid?
What are you on about, kid?
Them [ __ ] were laughing at you by a
stick. They were mocking you when you
when you used to go into that own hills.
Laughing at you.
Them army [ __ ] were laughing at you, lad.
Them army [ __ ] are still laughing at
you, lad. You need to go there and sort him out.
Oh, what a lovely site. Grezy,
they didn't let me get the picker mix yesterday, Grezy.
They didn't let me get
They didn't let me They didn't let me
They didn't let me get a bigger mix in it.
They just didn't. No, they just didn't.
Well, if I was a black guy, Grezy, would
they let me up
if I was a black dude, [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. And like I have to sneak into a
screaming, but like I can't afford a £7 ticket.
Like I can't afford a £7 ticket. Greasy. [ __ ] hell.
Jesus Christ. I can understand if it was
like £50 a ticket. Do you get me?
There's nothing to watch until tomorrow.
Maybe the screams on today. I doubt it
though. It's Thursday it comes out. But
sometimes it comes out a day early. Sorry about
tomorrow is the housemmaid is still in
the cinema. You know that's been in the cinema months.
Grievy that's been in the cinema months that Housemaid.
No, I'm not a fan of Toby Carver. To be fair,
I would have tipped that um guy in a
restaurant yesterday, but I didn't have
any money on me.
I didn't have any money on me.
like cuz I didn't have any cash on me in it. So
he cut me some like some long slices of
meat greeny. I was stuffed.
But I don't like there was these guys on
a bus yesterday talking to each other.
They met on they met on the bus. Grezy.
Yeah. And you know when someone drinks
like cheap cans of beer and it lingers
and you can smell it
like it's like a cheap beer smell. I
can't I'm I'm sure you know what I'm talking about.
I don't know how people drink them kinds
of beers. I can't drink cans of beers.
I can't drink that [ __ ] bro. It has to
be in a glass bottle.
I don't know how people can drink cans
of beers. It's [ __ ] mad.
Yeah, he wasn't a cracker though, but he
was just um they were just talking on
the bus. I think they just met. Do Nah,
they're just talking about life and stuff.
I want to have this curry, but it
doesn't open for a couple of hours. Grezy.
What's Timmy's new channel?
Monty would know it in it. I don't know
their [ __ ] names. I wasn't [ __ ]
talking to them, was I? You [ __ ] Oh, [ __ ]
You poor [ __ ]
Fire stick. Are you a poor [ __ ]
Because he's already found his mama.
Peter Belly's already found his mama.
You know, LT. Yeah. I I've had him
saved. I have had his number saved as
[ __ ] for the past two years. Fun fact.
I always had him as [ __ ] Yeah, [ __ ]
Don't know why, but that's what he was always
um saved as. Yeah, right.
I'm [ __ ] hungry. Greasy.
Yeah, less you greasy with your little Stockport accent,
with your little David Dickinson accent.
Bless you with your little Stockport accent. Bless you.
Never said I went to this cinema with
Christian. And see you later, lad. Bye-bye now. One. Yeah.
Yeah. 10 messages.
No, bey. There's another saying, lad.
There's another saying.
There's another saying you're missing. A
wild s appears.
That's another saying that I made up. I
put it on Instagram sometimes as well.
When there's a simp, I reply to a
comment saying, "A wild s appears."
Did I say G?
That's a cute little saying, is it?
So many simps, bro. All
right, make myself. I think
uh I think I know this.
He got diagnosed when he was in
university, didn't he?
I swear he said he went to uni or
something and he got diagnosed. Yeah,
I knew it was something like that. I remember that.
No, there's another saying, Greavvesy. I
love you all.
I love you all. You see
that one? I love you all. When people
come knocking on the door. I love you
all. I love all of you. Oh, Grezy.
What? Oh, [ __ ] You almost saw my Pekka there.
You almost saw my Pekka.
Weey, what do you think of this? Who's this? Squeezy. Who's that?
He's cute, isn't he? Oh, man.
Look, I'm having a little pee. Yep. Groovy,
what was what was the funniest meme
you've been sent? Grey,
I like that Spongebob one. So I can go in.
I like these little beans.
Oh, there's some clowns at Tokia. You absolute.
Oh, I got some smiles here. Lane got me
some smiles. I can't type. Cheers, Lane.
Uh, one second, Chad.
Got some Tanzac here.
Uh, mom, what happened to the other swirl?
Are you having a [ __ ] [ __ ] You know,
so I can go in.
All them tic tacs yours.
What? You got me chubby tic tacs. Why?
So I can go in.
Did you get it?
Don't mess with me. You come. Would
you like a cup of tea?
All right, mate.
What's the mint for?
Really, mate? You put the You put the
Tic Tacs in the fridge.
Mom, are you all right? Why? What?
You need to stay off the tablets, lady.
She's fit on the X factor.
She's so fit.
She's so fit on the ex
you do you do a better meow than me. You do.
Are you going to find Are you going to
find Christian? Is he a messenger? No. Cinnamon.
That messes my mama.
Oh, Reddit banned me. It makes you wonder
why they'd keep banning someone that's
never going to stop making accounts.
Like I'm never going to stop.
What do you mean our name?
You know, you know Christian is his
name, don't you? No.
I'll never let anyone even know anyone
I'm speaking to. They're not going to know anything
cuz you know what this community is
like, bro. And they're not going to be
on no social media.
I don't have people on social media.
It's all right if I speak to someone on
social media, but I don't I wouldn't
approach someone and get their social
media. [ __ ] that.
these little birds.
So, what did you say this community is again, Grezy?
I think this community is just disabled.
I think it's very disabled.
I'm just on Lord J. Now PJ kept saying
Tim brought back up. I mean it was Tiger
though. How how wimpy are you if you
can't take two at the same time? No,
you're missing the point. Timmy will
never meet anyone by himself.
It doesn't matter what the other person looks like.
He will never ever meet anyone by himself.
Do you understand Gregy? He will never
meet anyone by himself.
Never. Never. Ever. Ever. Ever. Ever. Yeah.
My dating video got two thumbs up.
Soon to be about five or six cuz what
I'm saying is true. What I'm saying is facts.
Is that right?
I was pretending to be a woman the other
day on Reddit and this woman said, "Oh,
no one owes you anything."
That's got to be the first, isn't it?
You never let someone say to a woman
that they don't owe him anything. So,
you might get the odd impartial person.
You might get the odd impartial person, but
95% of them are just biased and sexist.
Yeah, but what's the point of banning me
when I'm just going to keep coming back
with you? I'm never going to stop coming
back, am I?
I'm never going to stop coming back.
I think I enjoy the power. Grezy,
I'm never going to stop ever coming
back. You can't get rid of me.
I'm not jockeying. You can't get rid of
the [ __ ] in a movie.
Can't get rid of the [ __ ] Yep. Boom. Boom. Boo.
What do we say to copycat squeezy? Boo.
Oh, bro. I'm going to show you the kind
of the goose um the goose coats when I
go out again. Groovy. I'm going to show
you how many people wear them.
I'm going to show you how many people
wear them. Little copycats.
I'll show you. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. I'll show you in a row. This
person's wearing it. This person's
wearing it. This person's wearing it.
It's a little trend, lad. It's a little trend.
Yeah. Some people just like to follow
the crowd for an easy life. Boozy. Isn't that right?
They like to follow the crowd for an easy life.
Some people are like that. It me I'm
asked to be fair. What anyone's got to
say about me they can say. I don't I
don't follow the crowd.
Does nonslegs like to follow the crowd? Greavvesy?
Does he like to follow the angry mob?
You know, like the Simpsons angry mob.
He likes to follow the crowd, doesn't he?
For an easy life, isn't it? But for some
people, it's just easy just to fit in.
You know what I mean? Crazy. It's just
easy. It's easy for some people just to
do stuff to fit in, to not get teased.
Is that right, Grezy? Mad.
The X Factor.
Greasy. The X Factor.
Grezy. Back in 2010, 2011. The X Factor.
There was a cat yesterday when I went
out. It was on top of the bin.
Greavvesy. What was it sat there waiting for?
It was just sat there. It was just on
the bin looking.
Yeah, was sat there on the bin looking.
Well, I saw you put that thing of Donald
Trump up, Grezy.
We just gone on your little channel.
Uh, I've got a bone to pick with you, Greavvesy.
Uh, why have you removed Ali Law from your channel?
You removed Ali from your channel. I've
just noticed that, Grezy.
I think you might have to have a five
minute timeout and in that five minutes
you can put Ali Law back cuz I'm sorry
I'm not having that Grezy.
You've been a naughty boy.
You've been a naughty fellow.
You naughty fellow.
Uh Grey put it back.
You've got until
Nope. It has to be Ali. Nope. You got 3 minutes.
Nope. You have to be retired like him.
Do you know what? I can't wait.
Greavves. Yeah. You know what I'm going
to do? I'm go I'm going to go to the gym
for a year and a half. Yeah. I'm not
going to come on YouTube for a year and
a half and see where life takes me. And
then I'm going to come back on here to
see who's who's on here. Greasy,
what do you think of that? Greasy,
what do you think of that? Grezy,
come back in a year and a half.
Hopefully, we'll be different folks. No, Timmy. Okay, captain.
You and your bloody mackies.
You removed it thinking I would notice. Cheeky [ __ ] Bless you.
You a little copycat.
My name's not greasy. I'm a little copycat.
Right, let me finish this code. I need
to jump in the shower.
I'm not My name's not greasy. I'm a little copycat.
You can't compete against mental health,
Tim. And Pete, I don't have mental health.
I don't have mental health, lad. Gosh.
Well, Joe's making a comment about me.
Another gay obsessed one.
Nice try, lad. You're not going to get a reaction.
Oh, I've just seen uh LJ's um
Oh, I just see that, bro. And this is
I've already covered this in the video.
Oh, I've already I've already covered
this in the video. And this is the kind
of people that I was talking about, the white knights.
that would just defend women for any any
re for anything and everything.
They just love defending women. It's
part of their autism. It's part of their
It's part of their illness.
That's other people you can't win with.
Even though they've had less women than
you, a lot of them probably are virgins,
they will still defend women even when
the evidence is there. You can't win
with people like that either. Bit like
bit like with Timmy. Oh, and I've
actually got to me. Oh, yeah. Molly's
video now. Yeah.
Look, look into Virgin Hotels. Huh?
What the [ __ ] I've just seen this now, bro.
Going to South End. Oh, this guy's a [ __ ] bro.
Timmy still calling me a virgin even
though I prove I've had sex. Interesting.
Right, we'll go on this video. Oh, ew. A simp. Ew.
Ew. A s
e. He scumed him and danger to women. He
has a muscle problem with femas. E. Ew. E,
this is what I'm saying, bro. It's bad,
bad, bad. Autism.
I'm just reading these comments, bro. Yeah.
This is what I'm saying with these
people. They these people either don't
get women, never been with a woman, and
they still defend them. It's autism. I'm
I I think it is definitely autism, bro.
I think it's definitely definitely
autism or something that their dad has
put into their head at a very young age.
At like a very uh at a very young age.
Proper proper autism.
I'd love a debate about this. You know
when we had them nice debates before
Greavvesy couple months ago. I would
love somebody to join my panel and have
a debate. No talking over but they can't
do it because them them themselves they
can't answer it
cuz they know that they they know it
doesn't make sense.
They literally know it doesn't make sense.
why they sit there and defend women and
women don't like them. They know like
what could they say? There's nothing.
There's no way they could they could justify it.
So that's why no one ever really says
anything. They just keep on doing it
because they know I'm right.
They know you're right. That's why they
can't answer it. Like think about it,
bro. And I'm saying this, why are all of
these people defending women and they
can't answer it? Because they know that
you're correct. They know what you're
saying is right. They know them trying
to trying to justify it. They'll make
themselves look stupid.
They don't get women. Women don't like
them, but they still lick their asses.
I I'll pay good money, Greasy, for want
somebody one day to join the panel
um and explain it to me, but they can't
explain it to me because what what can
they say? What realistically can they
say? You know,
so many simps in this world. It's
unbelievable. There's so many white
knights and simps. It's embarrassing at
this point. I just read the comments on
Timmy's, bro. I just read his channel.
Danger to women and a problem with
females. coming from someone that's a
virgin that's never been with a woman.
But it doesn't matter what you say to
them, bro. It doesn't m It doesn't
matter what you say to them. It's one
ear and out the other.
They defend women, but women don't like them.
They women hate these people and they
still defend them. They've left them
single. They've left them a virgin.
They've had they bro, they're finished.
They're like, "They've had worse luck
than you would ever have, Grezy." And
they'd still sit there. They'll still
sit there and defend him. Tell me what
sense it makes, Grezy. Like, tell me
what sense it it possibly can make.
You tell me what sense it can possibly possibly make.
And then even when you provide proof,
you provide evidence, they still defend
them. You can't win with them.
It's like trying to trying to meet Timmy
for a fight. You will never win with
them. White Knights, simps
that women hate them. I think what it
is, Do you know what I I think it also
could be a possibility is where they're
virgins, where they've never been with a
woman and they don't have no life
experience. They think what they're they
think doing this is going to get them a
woman. I think it's going to they think
they're going to lose their virginity by
keep licking their ass.
It's it's mad. Like I would have thought
Grezy, right? No, come on. Let's talk
about this. I would have thought Grezy
that once you provided the evidence
then surely some of them must have been
the problem that was leading you on. No.
Surely. But there's like nope no. You
can show black and white evidence. Nope.
Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Retards.
Yeah, look at all of these look at all
of these simp white knight comments.
They can sense this. They can sense that.
[ __ ] white knight simps. There's no
winning with them, bro. You can't win
with white knights. It's it's it's a
waste of time getting into it with them, lad.
They think defending women is going to
get them laid. And no matter how many
times you tell them, they still defend them.
They have no women, no girlfriend. And
they think defended them women are going
to hop on their dick. And women hate
white nights. I don't know how many
times you have to say to these people,
right? Women do not like white nights.
Women are not going to sleep with you.
It doesn't It doesn't process in their brain.
Like they're still going to sit there
and try and say you're the issue when
you when you've provided evidence. How
is that possible? Like how to how in
hell is that possible?
How in hell is that possible, bro? The
mo the mo the moment someone someone
provides evidence of what they've done clearly like
proves the whole thing. No. If someone provides evidence,
right, then how are they still going to
try and blame you? That's why you can't
win with them. In their autistic minds,
they think defending women, women are
going to sleep with them. It doesn't
matter how many times um you
you you say this, how many times you you
know, you try to get into their head,
they they they don't understand that
women hate them. They think by defending
them, they think they're going to get women.
It's embarrassing as [ __ ] I swear to
God, Greasy, bro. I I swear to God, bro,
the people that do this. Yeah, I not
saying all of them are virgin. Yeah, a
lot of them are virgins. They can't all
be virgins. But I'm telling you straight
for a fact. I've been with more women
than these people.
And I don't I can't understand why they
do it. We'll have to do some kind of
debate, bro. We have We'll have to do
some kind of debate and see if somebody
can actually explain it. cuz I do
generally want to understand.
There's nothing wrong in in wanting to
learn things and understand
why people that don't get women that
women don't like them will sit there and
defend them like they're babies like
they're newborn babies.
Like I want I want to I want to I want
to be learned this. I want to understand it, bro.
why they keep being sexist and keep
defending them even when they're shown evidence.
I'd love to know, man. It'd be
interesting. It would be a good debate,
lad. We'll have to host like a proper
like, you know, panel and stuff, bro.
But I think it stems from like lack of
life experience as well at the same time.
Yeah, I think it stems from lack of life
experience as well
because what what what would the what
else would the reason be? I've been with
more women than these people and I'm not
even just saying that. You don't see me
[ __ ] licking their asses.
You don't see me defending them and
making excuses for them when they're in the wrong.
You don't ever see that, Grezy. You
don't ever ever ever see that. And you
will never see it either.
They defend women but women don't like
them. It's the same thing with that Jo
that Jo nons legs random accounts people
kick streams people on the street.
You know, let's have a proper proper debate.
You can't just make stuff up when you're
shown evidence. It's not me that's the
issue at all. I provided messages. I
provided cold approaches. I proved up I
have proved everything
um to back up my claims. I've backed up
my claims. Everything I've said, I've backed up.
So you trying to say that it's me, you
just look silly. That's all you do. You
Yeah, they're they're just Yeah. Well,
yeah. We're never going to get
explained, I don't think, lad.
Women don't sleep. Women are not going
to get with them. Women are not going to [ __ ] them.
generally generally generally love to
understand why they do it. And I'm not
trolling. I'm genuinely serious, bro.
Because I feel like every time you've
said this, no one's ever tried to
explain why they've done it. No one's
ever come up and said, "Oh, we do this
because of this or we do that because of
that." No one has ever ever tried to um
to justify it.
Um because they can't because they know
I'm right. With this particular com,
they know I'm right. It's like this Jo.
Yeah. And these other accounts trying to
say, "Oh, the issue is you. The issue is
you." How is that possible when you have
provided evidence of what they've done?
You've literally provided evidence of
people leading you to [ __ ] on.
You've you've provided evidence of you
not even being able to say two words and
someone giving attitude. They don't like
the truth. That's the thing with these
people. They don't like the truth. And
when they're shown the truth, the truth,
it gets them it gets them worse. Like
this comment saying, "Oh, they sense
this. They sense that." Do you genuinely
believe that? Does that is that really
how your little mind works?
They're they're simps. They're white lights.
They don't get women. Women don't sleep
with them. They're never going to find
the love of their life by sing. But they
still simp. But they still white night.
No simp has ever got a woman from sing.
Ever. Ever. You know, the only reason it
worked with Monty man is because he was
already with the person
and he just kind of begged her back. No
person that has defended women right the
way that these people do has ever got
with a woman, has ever got laid. There's
no there's no pros. There's no pros to
it, you know.
It's got to be autism. When stuff like
that gives you doesn't make sense. It's
got to be It's got to be autism.
It's got to be very very very It's got
to be some disability. No, I'm being
serious, bro. It's got to be some disability.
It's got to be some disability where
someone is shown the truth and then they
still point blank deny it. That's got to
be some disability, bro. Come on now. It
has to be.
It's got to be some disability.
How can I argue with evidence? It's like
going It's like going to court, right?
It's like going to court. Yeah.
And you being shown you killing someone
on camera, right? And then you choose to
plead not guilty, right? What's going to
happen when you're on when you're on
camera stabbing someone up?
If you've if you've murdered someone on
camera, how are you getting out of it?
You see, without evidence, people can
say this and say that without evidence,
but you can't argue with evidence. It's
like going to court and saying you ain't
done something when you're on camera. It
doesn't make sense. It literally does
not make any sense. It's like
shoplifting, right? It's like going to
Primark and shoplifting on camera and
you'll be like, "Nah, never happened."
And then you and then you saying to the
judge, "Oh, it never happened." When
when it's on camera, how is that possible, bro?
Yeah. It's got to be that deep rooted autism.
And don't forget the people in this
community, grievy, they don't leave
their house. They've got no life
experiences with women. So maybe it's
like where they've got no life
experience and they're scared to speak
to women. They think that this is what's
going to get them laid or this is what's
it just to me it just doesn't it's one
of the things that just make absolutely no sense.
Please someone come in and explain it to
me. Even if you need to type, you don't
have to join the link. Just explain to
me how you can argue with evidence.
That's the thing with these people,
Grevy. Most of these people are born with um
um they're born with simp brains. So no
matter what you tell them, they will
still simp. No matter what you show
them, they will still simp. How are you
saying that I'm the issue and you're
getting two thumbs up when I've already
shown what they're like.
And just because this person's talking
to me and they've replied, I don't take
back anything I've said because I cover
90% of the stuff I had to cover in that
video. So, it's like, how are you going
to sit there and try and put the blame
back onto me when I've shown exactly
what they've done? How is that even making sense?
Oh, you trying to beat them too fast?
you see what I'm trying to say, bro?
They always all have these excuses for
women. They're simps. But I will do a
live stream. I will title it. I'll title
How they can argue. Do you understand
what I'm saying? Oo, Grezy. How could
they argue with evidence?
That is very very scary and dangerous.
How they can argue against evidence? How
they can be shown messages where people
have willingly agreed to meet you then
wasted your time and then come back and
try and blame you? How they can still
try and dig for things behind the scenes
when something is in front of them.
That's very, very scary, bro. Very, very
scary. That scares me. You know, it actually does.
simp. And they're never going to get
women. They're never going to get sex.
They're never going to get in a
relationship by doing this.
Jesus Christ. Women do not like simps.
They never have and they never will.
It's never worked and it will never work.
Very strange individuals, lad. Would
they be saying that I'm an issue? Would
they be saying that I was the issue if I
was gay grievy? Let's let's let's say it
right here now. Yeah.
Let's just say you was lusting over men
and you was and you was having these
problems with men. Would people start
trying to say that you're this, you're
that, you're this, you're that,
especially after you've provided
evidence? No. No.
I'm pretty sure they wouldn't. So, does
that not tell you everything? Same
person, same problem, different gender.
Would that not tell you that if you was
lusting o after men, right, and you was
gay or even bisexual,
how no one would be doing what they're
doing with these with with with with how
they're trying to get women out of doing
the [ __ ] How they're trying to not
blame them for doing the things that they do?
Does that not tell you everything? It
tells me absolutely everything. here.
So many white knights. So many simps.
It's embarrassing. It actually is
embarrassing, bro. Like imagine waking
up every day knowing that knowing that
you have to be a s grezy. Knowing that
you have to make excuses for women.
[ __ ] is so autistic. They're so
They actually are, bro. It's autism to the maximum.
Mad. It is a madness.
And all of these people that do this
have had less women than you and will
continue having less women than you. Oh, this
it's madness. Like, you see,
cuz I'm honestly like gobsmacked. I
don't know what it possibly could be.
I honestly don't know why.
Yeah, but these people on this community
are sing because how are you going to
try and blame someone when they've
literally shown that it is women on
loads and loads and loads of occasions?
I mean, what more do they want? Blood
out of a sp a stone?
How can they say that you're the problem
when you've shown people have blatantly
led you on? I mean, how is that even
possible? But you can't reason with
simps with white knights and simps. They
they have it in their mind that they're
going to defend women and women are
going to sleep with them. Same as non
legs, same as, you know, Jo, same as all
of these other people. Women don't like
them. You can say in the most southern
accent, um, women are not going to sleep
with you. Simp does not work. You can
tell them and they will still do it.
They will still do it. people in real
life, people on Instagram, people on this community,
you know, I think it's because where
they've not had women, they think that
this is the way forward. I think because
they've got no life experience, they
think this is the way forward
cuz they just lick women's asses because
they don't get women and they think that
by some miracle a woman's going to sleep
with them. That's the only thing I can I
I can think
That's the only thing I can think of.
That's the only thing I reckon it could
be, bro. To be fair, you know,
it's madness. And why is this joke going
on about me again? The little gay boy,
the little gay loner.
Proper proper [ __ ] troll. But yeah, all
of this, oh, they can sense this, they
can sense that, they can sense this,
they can sense that. It's the same thing
with the recording, Greezy.
Um, you record a conversation. Oh, don't
record people. Don't record people.
Don't record people. Don't record. You
don't have um consent to record. Well, I
don't have consent to record a
conversation with someone. Okay. What if
I was recording me having a conversation with men?
You know, they wouldn't have a problem
with that, would they, Grezy? Anything
that shows a woman in a bad light, they
they go insane. They literally go they
go [ __ ] mad. Like that cat, you know
that cat on Tik Tok when the phone got
took away from it. Any woman that's
shown in a bad light, they will go
through so many hoops and go through so
many rages just to admit that the
woman's a bit of a [ __ ] That is like
they'd rather swallow needles than than
admit that. That's a serious serious
problem, bro. That's a serious serious
serious problem. Think about it, bro.
When that when that Ali When that Ali
Law was doing all of them videos. No,
cuz I'm not gay like you, you little
[ __ ] Think about it. When Ali Law was
doing all of them videos, Greavvesy. Or
other people that do these videos. You
ever see people saying, "Oh, you
shouldn't record people. You shouldn't
record people. You shouldn't record
people. Oh, don't record people. You
can't do this. You can't do that. you
can't do this, you can't do that. Or
when people are walking around, but as
soon as it's to do with women being
women being a [ __ ] you can't record
people, you didn't have their consent,
they go mad, they lose their [ __ ] These
white knights and these simps will be
like, "No, no, they'll start having like
an autistic." No, they don't owe you
anything. They go mad, bro. They go on
this like autistic rage or some [ __ ]
They would have no problem with you
talking to men. If you was approaching
men, they'd have no problem with you
approaching men. No excuses would be
heard. You you you
know what you you know what you'd be
doing, Grezy? You'd be waiting longer
than that guy in the shop for an excuse
to be made.
You'd be sat there waiting for an excuse
to be made. And you'd be waiting a very,
very, very long time.
It's clear they're sexist. It's clear
they're biased. It's clear they're simps.
And that's it.
You'd be waiting longer than the awkward shopper.
And no excuse would ever be made.
[ __ ] pathetic, bro. Absolutely
pathetic. Nothing. I can't think of
anything more pathetic than a white knight.
Than a than a white knight simp. I can't
think of anything more pathetic in my life.
I don't think I can. They're really really pathetic.
Mad. Absolutely mad.
Yeah. One's got a disabled girlfriend
and there's no proof that Joe's got a
girlfriend. Women don't like simps.
Women don't like simps. I've had more
women than Joe. I've had more women than
nonslegs. They've never been fat.
They've never been disabled. And I've
never had to simp. Never ever defended a
woman for the sake of her being a woman.
Never ever ever would I lick a woman's
ass. I've got I've got more I've got
more pride than that. And yeah, one has
a girlfriend, a disabled girlfriend,
which no one would go near. Nothing
normal, nothing. And it shows that sing
don't work. They're not They don't like
you. They're not going to let you [ __ ] them.
How many How many How many offers have
these people had from doing it?
Yeah. Yeah. A [ __ ] disabled
girlfriend that no one would go near.
I'd rather have random hookups with
normal women than disabled girlfriends.
I would never get with a disabled girl.
Never. Ever. Ever. If I was [ __ ] 31
and I had a disabled girlfriend, I'd
think, bro, sing don't work. But let let
them let them let them be 90 in their in
their deathbed, bro. That's that's
that's on them.
Women are not going to [ __ ] you. They
don't like you. You can defend them all
you want. They're not going to jump in
your bed. They don't like you. There's
absolute evidence that they don't like
simps and white lights,
but they still defend them. It's autism.
It's got to be autism. We Let's get Lex
back on this [ __ ] panel, bro. Maybe
he can Maybe he can um Maybe he can explain it.
>> Maybe he could explain it, bro. What do
you think of that, Grezy? Someone needs
to explain this.
Yeah. Yeah. Internally. Yeah, that's
self projecting, lad. Yeah, that's self
projecting. You people are single and
you're also virgins.
You people on here are internally
virgins, lad. Don't self-reflect your
[ __ ] onto me, bro.
Don't reflect your internally single
virgin life onto me.
You do. Listen, listen. You little
clowns on here. Yeah, you don't bother
no one. Everything that you say is self projecting.
It's self-reflecting your own life. You
want to try to make people feel low like
you. Just like when you tell people that
their skin, your skin, your everything
that you're trying to put other people
down for. That's what you are.
No one hurt me at all. I'm just stating facts.
And you're saying, um, oh, so you want
to debate, but you just insert your
virgins. Yeah, you are virgins.
You are single virgins.
Yeah, you're virgins. You're internally
virgins. You're internally single.
Everything that you say is just about
your own lives. Think about it. Yeah.
You are the ones that are on YouTube
from the time you wake up to the time
you go to bed. You got no girlfriend, no
money. Yet you try to talk about other
people. Everything you do is self-reflecting.
You're single, you skit, you got no
girlfriend. Even when people prove stuff
to you, you still continuously come on
here and talk [ __ ] You jealous people
will pick at anything when you're single
yourselves. And you think that bothers
anyone projecting your loneliness onto
other people? Well, it doesn't.
But it doesn't.
It literally doesn't because all you're
doing is just talking about your life,
your own selves, mister, internally on YouTube 24/7.
I've already had a [ __ ] girlfriend.
I've had a girlfriend. I've had more
women than you. And you still project
your lonely life onto people. If you
people had all of these things, you
wouldn't be sat on YouTube 24/7. And you
know I'm right. You can't even say
anything cuz you know I'm [ __ ] right. Yeah. Anyway.
Well, I don't go on Reddit every day,
but yeah, I'll put the link up anyways.
So, that's that.
You people don't have a girlfriend,
brother. Listen, like I said, this
self-p projecting bollocks is not going
to work. So, just if you're not going to
have a debate, then it's pointless. You
don't have a girlfriend. You're a
virgin. Non-legg has got a disabled
girlfriend. You're not going to bring me
down to your level, you ugly people.
You're not going to bring You're not
even going to try and make me feel the
way you depressed people do sat on YouTube 24/7.
And you get the ump when I say that
because you know I'm right. You know I'm
right. What could you actually say?
You ugly people have been doing this for
years. Get a [ __ ] grip of yourselves,
bro. It's boring now. I want an actual debate.
I want a [ __ ] debate.
Why these people keep defending women?
They don't like you. Women are not going
to sleep with you. The evidence is
there. Every single person that has simple
s that I've come across, I've been with
more women than them. Way more women.
More women. had a girlfriend and like
them and they still simp. It's autism.
It's the same as It's like [ __ ] Timmy, bro.
It's like [ __ ] Timmy.
We don't call it the disabled community for nothing. Maybe.
>> Yeah, that's weird, bro. It's weird.
You people are [ __ ] weird, lad.
You people are [ __ ] weird.
Defending women, but women don't like
them. And half of the people that simp
are virgins as well. I would say, bro,
bro, half the people that do this white
night and sing and [ __ ] are actual virgins,
but they'll still defend women. [ __ ]
pathetic. We just call them losers. I
think them kind of people would call them losers.
They don't get women. Women don't like
them, but they still defend women when
they're in the wrong [ __ ] pathetic. Maybe
Yeah, it's weird, bro. It's weird.
You people are [ __ ] weird, lad.
You people are [ __ ] weird.
Defending women, but women don't like
them. And half of the people that simp
are virgins as well, I would say, bro,
bro, half of the people that do this
white knight and simp [ __ ] are actual virgins,
but they will still defend women.
[ __ ] pathetic. We just call them
losers. I think them kind of people
would call them losers.
They don't get women. Women don't like
them, but they still defend women when
they're in the wrong [ __ ] pathetic.
That's what you call [ __ ] pathetic, bro.
And then you try to project your
loneliness and your singleness onto
other people when you have always been
single. We've never seen any. None of
you have even been with a [ __ ] woman
ever in your life. Come to think of it. Self projection.
And it would always be self-reflective
of you little idiots on this community.
Jealous ass people sat on YouTube
talking about people 24/7. I done a
video yesterday. Yeah. Cuz I wanted to
do a video about dating. Done my own
thing. Somebody wanted to see it. You
don't see me going on about these people
24/7. That's what jealous people do.
That's what jealous deeprooted jealous
people do. Going on about people on
YouTube 24/7. It's obviously jealousy.
If people can sit on there every day
talking about you, it's got to be deep
rooted jealousy. Don't let them try and
tell you it's for this or for that. It's
deeprooted jealousy that they don't even
know about. You're better looking than
them. You got more money than them.
You've been with more women than them.
You're younger than them. You're more
confident than them. You're not sat on
YouTube 247 like them. It's all all the
evidence is there. What you people do on
here. You little sad losers. Well, you
sad little pricks do on here. You can't
even [ __ ] deny it. It's that sad. You know,
you try to make people feel the way that you do.
Single, alone, unhappy. That's why
you're on there 24/7.
[ __ ] you do on this community is so
disabled. The [ __ ] you do on there, the
[ __ ] you do, No, it's not assumptions,
it's facts. The [ __ ] you people do on
here is so disabled. You know, you know,
there's some communities, Greavesy.
Yeah. Where they talk about um like
religion and [ __ ] They'll be live for
about 10 hours and they're just talking
about religion. I don't even come across
communities. This is a proper proper
proper disabled community.
They sit on here and talk about people
every day that they don't even know.
They obsess over people that they don't
even know. It's a disabled community.
Bunch of [ __ ] 40year-olds jealous of
people that they don't know every day.
There's other community. No, there's
different communities. There's all
different kinds of communities.
This is a disabled, jealous, copycat
community. It's what they do on here as
well. Also, another thing with this
community, it's what they do on here.
Now, we're just talking about white
knights and simps
trying to get to the bottom of why
people defend women just for being
women. They're not going to get laid.
Women are not going to sleep with them.
Narcissistic. Oh, that's self
projecting, lad. Yeah. It it it takes
one to no one.
Yeah. Yeah. You'd know all about that
because that's the condition that you
suffer with. You suffer with that condition.
Takes one to no one, lad.
You're the one sat on YouTube for 10
years being jealous of people you don't
know, lad. Not me. [ __ ] loser.
There we go. Yeah.
>> Don't you ever get bored of talking
about women every day?
>> Can't hear any.
See you later.
>> I thought that was Timmy. See you later.
Yeah, you people are narcissists.
But no, there's no point anyways with
this whole thing. We're not getting into
you people. You people do what you do
cuz you're jealous. I was just trying to
talk about white knights and and simps
and stuff. You've got proper issues. The
people in this community's got proper
issues. They're clearly gay. They're
clearly jealous. Um they don't admit to
themselves. We're not even talking about
you people. You brought it up. We're
talking about why people white knight and simp.
Now you people are just like jealous
little closeted gay people that hate yourself.
So we don't we don't we don't really
care about you people. You just got
serious serious issues. That's that.
Yeah. You people are not. Like I said,
anyone that's younger and better looking
than these people, they won't leave you alone.
Yeah. You know, uh, everyone is jealous
of you. Yeah, you are jealous when
you're sat on YouTube for 10 years
speaking about someone every day. Yeah.
You're jealous. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You're jealous when you're on YouTube.
When you're coming on someone's channel,
when you're on someone's channel and
every single comment is about you, yes,
you are jealous. And I will put money on
that. Yes. Because, bro, you don't see
me coming on here talking about these
people every day. I do my own thing. So,
the fact that they go for you, it shows
jealousy. It's clear as a rainbow.
They're not on this community doing
their own thing. They're stalking you.
They're bothering you. It's clear
jealousy. Someone that's better than
someone doesn't waste their time on
another person. No person that's better
than you would waste their life on you.
It's jealousy. Everything about it is
jealousy. We have seen what these people
have looked like on this community.
We've seen what these people in this
community look like and they're [ __ ]
ugly. Which makes it pro which proves
the point even more. The people that are
doing this are [ __ ] uglier than you.
Always remember that. It's jealousy with
these people. It is hardcard jealousy.
There's no way someone would ever sit on
YouTube all day stalking someone they
weren't jealous of. They would never
ever do it for any reaction for no
reaction. You couldn't pay me a million
pound to do it. And then when you start
putting yourself in these people's
shoes, bro, they're jealous of you.
They're jealous. It's it's as simple as
that. We don't bother with you people.
We don't have channels. We I'm not the
one that's got channels dedicated to
men. I'm not the one I'm not the one I'm
not the one I am not the one that's got
channels dedicated to men like you
people do. Do you understand?
So, oh, how many dates, brother? It
doesn't matter how many dates. How many
dates have I been on in in my whole
lifetime? How many women have I been on
this whole lifetime? You're not going to
bring me down to your level. Stop
trying, bro. It's not going to work.
You people are fat. You people are ugly.
Stop trying to bounce off of other
people's lives, bro. How many women have
you been with in the past 10 years?
None. None. Yeah. Let alone a year.
None. You're not going to make me feel
like you ugly alone on YouTube 24/7.
You're not going to do it. You're not
going to bring me to your ugly levels,
lad. Trust me. You have never been seen
with a woman. You've never been seen
with money. Get the [ __ ] out of here.
You can't question anyone about their life.
Simple, bro. No, it didn't, bro. I
couldn't be bothered. Well, like I said,
bro, if it's assumptions, then you can
prove me wrong then, can't you? If I'm
making assumptions about you, then you
can prove me wrong.
Then you can prove me wrong then, can't
you? If I if it's speculation and it's
assumptions, lad, prove me wrong.
There's no point saying that people are
um speculating and they're assuming
things if you can't prove otherwise cuz
then the other person will never look
stupid then will they? Simple.
Trust me, bro. Just if it's assumptions
and it's speculating, then prove it.
Prove me wrong then. It's as simple as that.
Prove me wrong. And you're jealous of
other things. It's not just looks as
well. It's not just looks and stuff like
that. It's you're jealous of loads of things.
You're jealous. Uh, you're jealous. Uh,
oh, I'll answer that one with Timmy. One
second. I'll answer that. Yeah, that's
actually a good question. I'll answer
that. Um, and I'll tell you the
difference. Um, it's not even just
looks. It's not even about that. It's
the fact that you've got family. These
people don't. You're more confident than
them. You're younger than them. You can
actually go out and make friends. You
actually go out and have a life. And if
you don't have a life, that's your own
choice. You understand what I'm saying?
Whereas these people on here, they're
sat on YouTube 24/7. They don't even
leave their [ __ ] house. They ain't
even got a life. So, it doesn't take
much for these people to be jealous of. So, yeah.
Um, people say the same about Yeah. But
you know what the difference is? Uh, Dr.
Eko, we're back on this now. Um, the
difference with Slug is people don't
have channels dedicated to Slug. I do. I
do. People don't have channels dedicated
to Slug. People are more obsessed with
me than they are with Slug. people just
go on Timmy's chat and just try to wind
him up. There's a big difference. These
people in this community actually stalk
me. And there's more people doing it.
Um, and there's more people doing it
than not doing it. There's more people
doing it to me than they're doing it to Timmy,
you know? I know like Timmy's got Mr. B
and stuff. People are just typing stuff,
but these people are like
dedicated to me, bro.
like from the time they wake up to the
time they go to bed. Um, and if they if
there are channels that are doing it to
Timmy, um, if there were channels that
are doing it to Timmy the way they are
to me, then they've got to be jealous of
him as well. Like there's they have to be.
I don't know what they would be to be
jealous of, but that's the only thing
that it would it would make sense.
But there's not channels dedicated to
him anyways. There's not channels
dedicated to him.
There might be people that post videos
about him, but there's not channels
dedicated to him. No, no, no. There
there's not people No, no, no, no.
There there's not channels ded I can
tell you about five people that's got
channels dedicated to me, lad.
Mine's different. My situation's
Nlex is jealous. Red Star's jealous.
Jamie Thompson's jealous and other
people I don't know
but they are definitely definitely
definitely definitely jealous and you're
better looking than all of them as well
which is the funny thing as well. It's
funny how you're better looking than
these people isn't it? It's it's funny
how you're younger than these people,
isn't it? You know, the list just goes
on and on and on and on and on and on
with these sad acts.
But I don't know any channels that are
dedicated to Timmy.
I don't know any channels that are
I've already shown women multiple
multiple multiple times. We're not going
into this buy [ __ ] again, lad.
Oh, I know it's jealousy. It does help
me sleep at night. Yeah, because it is
jealousy. Yeah, it is definitely
definitely jealousy. I'm better looking
than you people. I've had more women
than you people. Oh, it's definitely
jealousy. And I'll say it until I'm blue
in the face.
It is 100% jealousy. I mean, okay, I'll
give you an example. Nonss. I'm better
looking, got more money. I've got a
mother. I live in a house with my mother
who didn't starve me. I've been with
multiple women that never had
disabilities, never had to go with a
disabled girl. And you know, it's
jealousy. You are better than him. You
are better looking than him. You've been
with more women than him. You have
family unlike him. You've got teeth that
are not missing. Unlike him, it is 100%
jealousy. 100 million% jealousy. And
I'll say it until I'm blue in the face.
It is jealousy. Because if it wasn't
jealousy, you wouldn't do it. If it
wasn't jealousy, you wouldn't do it.
It's as simple as that. If it wasn't
jealousy, you wouldn't do it.
You know, you know, simple as that.
Why are you saying that people have got
no Yeah, he's got missing teeth. Why are
you saying that people have got no dates
and stuff? What about all of the women
that I have been with? You don't speak
about them women. All of the women that
I [ __ ] Does it matter if I've been on
zero dates in a year? Does it matter if
I've been in a 100 dates in a year?
Overall, Overall, I've been with more
women than all of the people in this community. Overall,
doesn't matter if I've been on one date,
zero dates, a million dates. I've been
with more women than you. And that is
that is the truth. That is the good
honest truth. more girls, more women
than you will ever and I have been in a
relationship. Even though you say I
haven't been in a relationship, I
[ __ ] well have. So, does it really
matter? You talk [ __ ] regardless. Just
like when you got beat at the money
game, you still talk [ __ ] regardless.
This is why no one bothers with you people.
Yeah, it's seven women more than you.
And I've been with more than seven
women. I've been with more than seven
women. It's just women I didn't say.
Anyways, we're not talking about my life
anyways. We're not talking about my
life, lad. You people would always talk
[ __ ] I could be a millionaire with
jealous people. You'll never win. People
like you, Red Star, and launch legs.
You're bet. You could be a millionaire,
right? You could be married with kids
and they they'd still be like, "Nope,
you can't win with these people." Same
thing with the money game. You can't win
with these people. They're jealous of
you. They hate you cuz you're better
looking than them. So, their whole goal
and other things as well as looks, their
whole goal is to try to bring you to
their level, their ugly, alone, YouTube
24/7 life level. Cuz don't forget, these
people have always been bullied. The
people in this community have always
been bullied. So, they see someone
younger, better looking, hope that they
don't have and will never have, and they
don't like it. And that's why we call it
a disabled community, you know. That's
why it's a disabled community.
[ __ ] copycat community. Call it a
[ __ ] disabled community.
And that's that.
See you later, lad.
But I've not seen any channels dedicated
to Timmy. You could never pay me to
[ __ ] obsess over a man on YouTube
every day. Jesus Christ.
You could never pay me to be obsessed
with a man on YouTube every day. See,
that's me. See, when you look at it like
that, you know that they're just
weirdos. When you look at it like that,
bro. No, they're they're weirdos. They
definitely are weirdos.
No, it didn't answer my question. Are
they escorts? No, they weren't escorts.
And we're stopping with this biasness
[ __ ] anyways. We're getting into biased
territory again. We're getting into the
biasness again. We're not getting into
this conversation with this biasness
because it's coming into a biased
territory again where no matter what
you're showing and saying you can't win
with these people. Beat him at the money
game, they still think they got more
money than you. Show more women than
them, they still say you've never had a
girlfriend. You can't win with them. So
any kind of arguments like that, I'm I'm
away from. I'm not getting into them. I
don't get into argu biased arguments
with biased people.
Waste of everyone's time. So yeah,
and and that's another thing is like
when I was going at Timmy the other day,
have you noticed everyone was liking was
was giving me thumbs up. Everybody was
loving it. That's the biasness. You see,
it's the same thing what what they do with nodlexs,
you know. It's the same thing with what
they do with uh non legs. I was like,
"Oh, this makes sense now." Yeah, people
liking my thumbs up because I'm going
for Timmy. So, if I went for Timmy every
day, obviously people would come up
would would come off me
and no matter what I'd say, people would
defend me. Yeah. It's biasless. It's the
same as what they do with Nodlex.
Yeah. Yeah. You can't win with him.
I could go at Timmy every day. I've
never had a decent relationship. You
keep thinking that, lad. Okay. You keep
telling yourself that.
>> Yep. Okay. Yeah. I haven't. Okay. You
keep telling yourself that, lad.
And why? And if I've never had a decent
relationship with someone,
uh, what's that got to do with you?
That's another thing with you people.
You're you're you're so focused on other
people's lives but your own. You're too
busy trying to talk about other people's
lives and [ __ ] Why don't you focus on
your own life?
That's what normal people do in in in in
in in in the real world. They focus on
their own life. You actually like obsess
over other people's lives because you
ain't got one yourselves. I think this
is what you do. Yeah. Because you know
you ain't got lives. You bounce off of other people's
cuz it makes you forget about your [ __ ]
lonely lives and that's why you obsess
over other people. That's what you do on
here. It doesn't matter what my longest
relationship was. It's none of your business.
Simple as that. Worry about your own life.
They go for you because you're better
looking than them on here. It's
something I learned like I learned that
ages ago. You're you're be Why are you
better looking than these people that
are doing this? And it shows jealousy.
They want to bring you down to their
level. These ugly fat people want to
bring you down to their level. And
before you say that people are
speculating, then prove me wrong then.
Prove you're not all of these things
because that's the first thing I would
do. That's the first thing I would do, bro.
Channels dedicated to men that you don't even know.
Yeah. Only on this disabled community.
Only on [ __ ] It's madness. You
wouldn't even stalk a woman online
you've never met, let alone a [ __ ] man.
Gay. They're [ __ ] gay on here, bro.
Gay little jealous weasel bastards.
That's what they are. Anyways, enough
about these people. Now, we was talking
about white knights and simps. Yeah,
such a weird community. The way they
talk about people every day. Like, I've
seen it on on L JS as well, like where
they talk about people every day. It's so disabled.
It's so weird what they do on here.
It's not even just the fact that they're
on it. It's It's what they actually do.
It's actually what they do on here. A
bunch of middle-aged people that don't
know anyone going on about people every
day. It's so weird.
And you say that you're not jealous.
Really? Yeah. Okay, bro.
Give me a million pounds right now and I
wouldn't stalk a man for three years on the internet.
How about that one?
Give me1 million pound right now and I
wouldn't st I wouldn't have channels
dedicated to men.
Tells you everything you need. And these
people are willingly doing it for free every day.
They're stalking men every day for free.
They're [ __ ] gay.
Yeah, you're defin
Why do you people never come on camera?
Because so many communities that we go
on, you see so many people come on
camera. Like a lot of people show their
faces. I can never I've never come
across a community where like so many
people haven't shown their face. That
tells me something as well when you come
on here and you try to talk about other
people's looks. Um but none of you you
people big yourselves up. Yeah. That
you're this and you're that. You big
yourselves up. But none of you people
will come on camera.
You know, even the incel community, the
religion community, pretty much everyone
shows their faces.
Everyone shows their faces.
Um, but you people, it's weird that
there's so many people on here, they
don't join the hangouts and they don't
show their face. Why is it? Cuz they're [ __ ] stinking.
Stinking fat and ugly. Why else would
they show their faces? Most people do on
different communities and stuff. And
don't say it's because you're going to
get docks because that's [ __ ]
No, I'm talking about communities that
I've come across. It's weird how this
community, right, there's so many people
on here. Most people don't show their faces.
So many people on here don't show their faces.
Why is that, bro? Everyone else does it
on different communities. It's cuz
you're [ __ ] fat and ugly. And you
know, by showing your faces, you can
never come back on here and do what you
do anymore. It's just a disabled
community where peop where loser failures
um come on in their 40s.
Hey bro, you good man?
We're just talking about these losers on
here that got no life.
I said I just said it's a bit weird how
most of these people don't show their
faces on L's.
Most of them don't show their faces.
That's a bit strange, isn't it, lad? But
every other community you come on,
you'll see so many people show their
face. You not find that a bit strange,
lad? It's cuz they're [ __ ] fat and ugly. That's why. Yep. Proper.
All right. Timmy's [ __ ] having a
mental breakdown. Cory, have you seen
the madness the past couple of days?
Oh, bro. He's a [ __ ] He's a He's a clown, man.
It is a bit strange how no one on here
shows their faces like they do in other communities.
You know I'm right, isn't it? Yeah, you
know I'm [ __ ] right. Hello.
That's self projection lad. You people
in this community are lonely. Lonely forever.
Anyways, uh right.
But yeah, it's strange how um not many
people join the panels and not many
people show their faces
for such a big audience.
Why? You can't say you're going to get doxed.
You can't even use that excuse cuz Bomb
never got doxed. Bomb never got doxed.
Bomb never got doxed as well. That's his
excuses, bro. They don't show their
faces cuz they're [ __ ] ugly, bro.
And once they're outed, they're [ __ ]
They can't talk about no one else.
So that's why
I would safely say there's not one
person on this community that's better
looking than me.
I can safely say that. Lide rare.
Um I can safely say, bro, that there's
not one person
that's better looking than me, lad.
I've not seen it.
I've not seen it at all.
I haven't seen one person that's better
looking than me on this community, lad.
And you know what? It's not even better
looking than me. No, no, no, no, no. You
know what? It's not even better looking.
It's just someone. It's just people that look normal.
There's no There's no one on this
community that just looks normal.
You get what I'm trying to say? There's
Yeah. There's not one person in this
community that even looks normal.
If I look like some of these people on
this community, bro, I would actually
kill myself. Like, imagine looking like
[ __ ] Money Mike or looking like L J.
I would actually kill myself, bro. I
would actually kill myself. I'm not even
joking. If I look like that, bro, I
would [ __ ] kill myself. If I had four
eyes and a ginger beard, bro, I'd kill
myself. And fat as well, I'd kill
myself, bro. Definitely killing myself.
I'm I if I look like these people on
this community, bro,
that's it, lad.
Not like you, Cory. You know, we're just
we're just normal looking people, you
know? We're just like normal looking people.
Even Timmy, like Timmy, Albino, LJ, have
you seen? Do you know what's so bad is
you go out in public and you don't see
people as ugly as this. You don't see
people as ugly as these people in this
community, bro. They are [ __ ]
stinking, bro. They don't even look normal.
They don't even look normal. Even if,
bro, even if you was like a five out of
10. Yeah, just an average looking
person, bro. You know, that's enough.
You know, it doesn't matter. You know,
you just look normal. You just go gym or
whatever. But these people, they're beyond help.
That money Mike is [ __ ] ugly as [ __ ]
He is ugly as [ __ ] bro. He's ugly, bro.
They can't even help themselves. The
thing is, it's not like they're ginger.
It's not like they're ginger, but
they're not. It's not even like they're
ginger, but they're not ugly. They're
ginger and they're ugly. Cuz the thing
is, yeah, Cory, if you was ginger and
you was normal looking, then you're just
a normal looking ginger person. You can
you can work with it, isn't it? There's
certain things you get, bro. Yeah.
There's certain cards you dealt in life.
Yeah. You could actually work with it.
But these people, nah. Nah. They're
beyond they're beyond they're beyond help lad.
You could actually work with it.
I don't know man. I think that L J is
almost just as bad as albino. You know,
think about it. Fat, four eyes, ugly
beard, ugly ginger beard, can't lose
weight. Yeah, it's over.
It was over before it even began, little fellow.
It was over before it began.
It was over before it began,
bro. It was over before it even began,
He's telling me that LJ is telling me he
lost his hair at 14.
Lost your hair at [ __ ] 14. Oh,
lost his air at 14. What a [ __ ] What a
waste. What a waste. You [ __ ]
Women on here. I don't I don't know,
bro. I don't care about women on here.
And to answer your question, yeah, they
do. Natalie G said I was good-looking.
Um, but I don't care about women on this
community, but yeah, they have.
But it doesn't matter to me anyways. I
don't care. I don't care about women on this community.
And I think Autumn fancies me as well.
She's so obsessed with me. That's what
Knobs Legs is scared of cuz he's still a
[ __ ] virgin. Is that right, [ __ ] Cory?
Yeah, there have been people. There's
actually been two people.
And why does it matter? I don't care
about women on this community, bro.
Why you why why are you asking about
women on this community? Who cares about
women on this community, lad?
Yeah, but that L J to be fair, bro.
Could you imagine L J in a pub approaching someone?
Could you imagine? Like, think about it.
He's got glasses, he's got four eyes,
and he's got a ginger beard, and he's obese. Jesus,
bro. Jesus. And And like what? And he he
looks even worse if he takes the glasses off.
I think we've been underestimating these
people's ugliness for a very long time
now. Um, Cory, we've been
underestimating their ugliness for a
very long time,
come to think of it. Yeah.
And if he takes his glasses off, he
looks worse. Oh, yeah. He's finished,
bro. He's actually finished
over before it began.
And then you got Tiger who's 5' three,
5'2, and then he's ugly. Yeah.
It's funny though, isn't it? This is why
these people are [ __ ] virgins.
This is why these people are virgins. Cory. Yeah.
Yeah. Nons is scared that Autumn Rose
fancies me because he knows he can't get
anything uh normal himself because he's a virgin.
Because he's a because he's a virgin in it.
And because he's a [ __ ] virgin
in it, bro. I wonder you're a [ __ ] virgin.
And you see them [ __ ] weird glasses
he [ __ ] wears. No wonder he's a [ __ ] virgin.
O Hey, listen. Cory, you missed all the
madness with Timmy. Yeah. I ordered him
a taxi and it was a 200 taxi. Yeah. And
he wouldn't get in it. He wouldn't get
in the taxi, bro. I ordered him a taxi
from Birmingham. And then I like when he
didn't go in, I cancelled it cuz he
didn't go in.
You missed all the madness, bro.
Yeah, I ordered him a um
I ordered him a [ __ ] I ordered him a
cab. I'm done with Timmy, bro. I'm done
with Timmy. It's just like playing chess
with a pigeon. Even if you beat the
pigeon at chess, it's just going to
strut around the board and [ __ ] all over
and pretend that it's one.
It's pointless. It's point It's like
playing chess with a pigeon. Cory.
It's like playing chess with a pigeon.
Arguing with Timmy is like playing chess
with a pigeon.
Ew. No. I'll get [ __ ] locked up. She
can't consent to sex.
She can't consent.
What I [ __ ] Ew. Dude, even if I was 50
[ __ ] Guinnesses deep, even if I was
50 Guinnesses bloody deep, mate, I would
never go near that. That's [ __ ] disgusting.
No, he must be a proper proper incel.
That's what an incel would do. Start
targeting disabled, vulnerable girls
that can't consent. That to me
is a proper incel.
Yeah, he's a pro. That's That's what you
That's what you call a proper incel.
You look at me. I look normal. I need to
have a shower. I got nice eyebrows. I
got a nice beard.
Could do with a haircut, but you know,
who cares? It is what it is for now.
Nice beard. Nice little eyebrows. Look,
I have my eyebrows specially done. I'm
looking quite cool,
you know, but these people can't show
their faces cuz they're [ __ ] baggy. Yeah, that's what [ __ ] tants.
Right, I'm going to jump in the shower.
I'll be about
approximately 10 hours.
Approximately 10 hours.
So, you're going to have to wait.
No, seriously. I need to book a hotel,
man. I need a bath. I want to have a
bath, man. Whilst the weather's still cold.
I'd love a nice bath.
We don't have a bath. We might need to
get one installed. You a nasty fellow.
You're a nasty fellow.
Like, Cory, you're a nasty fellow.
You're a nasty fellow. Anyways, I'm
going to have a shower here.