Yo. Okay, so it is about 5:00 in the
morning. Um, just made myself a lovely
cup of [ __ ] Um, with three sugars this
time and not two sugars. Um, so yeah.
Um, somebody was saying to me earlier on
the live stream that you should go to
sleep and um, set your alarm to make
sure like you're the first person in the
bookies. Um, so that no one else um, you
know, cashes in the winnings. And it's
like, mate, I'm not even going to sleep.
Are you mad? like I am not even going to
sleep at all. I am telling you right
now, I am going to be that first person
in that bookies. Um, 100%. And
yeah, um, don't underestimate Peter
Belly. And I just wanted to say that I
don't need £110. You know, £110 doesn't
mean anything to me. It's just I don't
want these people having the last laugh.
You know, I don't like most of the
people in this community. Um, I'd go as
far as saying I hate them. um where you
know a lot of people on here might not
know that um because you know I always
joke around on my live streams and stuff
but you know like people like V and um
Fantasy Stories which is what his real
name is. You give me 20 seconds with
either one of them and there's plenty of
others mate I would absolutely [ __ ]
annihilate them. Um, so you know, the
last thing I want is one of these people
having the last laugh out of me and
getting £110 because £110 is £110
whether you need it or not. So, I mean,
to put this into perspective, um, if the
winners was £30, I would spend £70 in an
Uber to collect that £30 just so they
don't get it. Yeah. That's how much I
hate like a lot of people in this
community. Um, it's really, really bad.
and they're fat, narcissistic, little
self-projected little [ __ ] So, at
the end of the day, if it means me
staying up um you know,
all all day um to go to these bookies, I
have absolutely no problem. It will be
my absolute pleasure. Um you know, if I
had some of these people's addresses on
here, mate, [sighs and gasps] they would
be laughing. Put it that way. So, this
is a minor to be honest. It might seem
crazy to you, but it is. Um it is a
minor. So, yeah, the bookies around here
opens at 8:30,
but the one where I used to live opens
at 7:30. So, I'm going to go to um my
other area and go um to the 7:30 one
just in case these people are thinking
the same thing. So, I'm going to go to
uh yeah, the bookies that opens at 7:30.
I'll get the train at around 6:00 back
to where I used to live and go to that
book. Not a problem at all. Not a So yeah,
I guarantee you I'm going to be the
first person in that [ __ ] bookies,
mate. Trust me. In in in the whole of
the country, I bet you I'm the first one
to set foot in in that company bookie
today, mate. I'm telling you that. So
yeah. So yeah, and I'm going to do a
video when I'm there to see. And that's
that. So yeah.