Right. So, just a quick one to this Jo
because I was going to add him on this
LT video, but I forgot. So, I just went
on your um channel. Um and a lot of the
stuff that you're saying is is actually
projection. Like you're you're saying
that LT is a [ __ ] stoer. Bro, he's done
the same thing as what you're you've
done. You've done the same thing with
Nlex. You've gone straight to his rescue
every time I've called him a virgin
talking about this fat ugly girlfriend
that he's got. Um and then, you know,
you're talking about me bottling it.
Bottling it. Bro, I offered to meet you
two weeks ago in Nottingham, right? Fair
is fair. Everyone on the chat saw it and
you didn't want any of it and and and
you're telling me that I bottled it,
brother. Everybody knows that you're a
[ __ ] house, right? And you're never ever
going to meet anyone. You're talking
You're saying that I'm all talk. Okay,
bro. I'm all talk. I'm a I'm a talker.
Something that you can't do. You can't
talk. Yeah. You're just some fat ugly
melt that puts up fake gambling wins.
You're not even worth anyone's time.
This is why I'm only doing this video to
you. And this is the last one because
I'm not going back and forth with fat,
ugly, disabled people. So, um, at the
end of the day, bro, you're talking
about people bottling it and people
needing to grow a pair. Grow a pair,
bro. Like I said, you can't even talk on
a panel. You can't be took serious. I
think all of the things that you're
saying, you're actually talking about
yourself when someone someone's word
means nothing. Bro, words, what's a word
that comes out your mouth when you're
talking? You can't even talk. So, just
just stop it now. Anyways, what I will
be doing is um I'll be going to
Nottingham soon, not this week. Um I
don't know when. Obviously, you're in
Leeds this week. I know that much. And
I'm just going to let you know four five
days prior. Um there's not going to be
no back and forth videos. There's not
going to be live streams. I'm not going
live anyways. When I go to Nottingham,
four or five days prior, I will be
letting you know. So, if you really are
this big hard man calling people this
cuz you've got a big mouth, a very big
mouth. People have sent me what you've
um you know, said on you know, laws and
whatever. That's fine, bro. You can say
it to my face. So, I'll be letting you
know four or five days prior to me going
to Nottingham when I go to Nottingham.
And if you really are this big, hard
man, you'll be there. And I'll be
killing two birds with one stone because
I want to go Nottingham anyways. Uh I
said this to my mom earlier. Um you
know, going all the way to Leeds and
going all the way to Newcastle. All you
want people to do is waste their time,
waste their money, so you can sit there
and say, "Oh, we control you." This way,
me going to Nottingham proves that you
have a [ __ ] house. I want to go because
I want to go and you're not going to
show up just like you bottled out two
weeks ago. So that's all I wanted to say
to you anyways. You're not worth any
more time. Um you chubby fingered fat
ugly [ __ ] who's scared to talk. So when
I go to Nottingham four or five days
prior, I'll be letting you know and
that's it. So you will not be hearing
the next time you hear from me is when
I'm announcing that I'm going to
Nottingham 5 days after. Um so yeah,
until then you're I'm not going to be
entertaining you. So you'll be talking
to yourself. So anyways, big man. Um
I'll let you know four or five days um
before I go to Nottingham. So we'll see
what you're what you're about in real
life. And that's it. I'm not going back
and forth. So yeah, see you now.