Hey, Smokey B replied to me. Now, I
literally did not even know that he done
a reply to me. Um, so I wasn't ignoring
you or it's not like I got owned and I
shied away. Like, when I start
something, boy, better believe I will
finish it, Milton Keen, boy. Because,
um, where I'm from, which is not Milton
Kees. We tend to finish things down this
way. You understand? But, you know, I I
must say thanks for um showing something
and you know, I will give you credit
when credit is due and I won't pretend
that you uh didn't show what you just
shown, but there's a few problems with
what you shown, right? So, you wrote,
"Hey, Smelly Wool PJ, this is just an
account I used to gamble." Now, here's
the thing, right? I have been showing
thousands and thousands and thousands of
pounds for so long, right? And all I
have asked people to do is show me 10
grand. Here's a question to you. Why
would you show me a I quote gambling
account, which we'll get on to, that has
slightly less than what I have asked you
to show because you don't have it.
That's your main account. Trying to act
like it's your gambling account, bro.
That does not make any sense. Right? If
I had a gambling account that had
considerably less than my main account,
wouldn't you just show your main account
that has more and then you would just
own someone that way and show over the
10 grand? You're full of [ __ ] bro.
Like, I know people do have, you know, uh
uh money in their gambling accounts,
like a couple of hundred or whatever,
and they use it to like bet over the
weekend. There is people that do that,
but bro, you don't just have over £9,000
as a gambling account. That is your
account. Yeah. your main account, which
there's nothing wrong with that being
your main account, bro. Like, it's still
good you showed something. But even
then, you that skin that even all of the
pennies that you put together, you still
couldn't show 10 grand. And then to
brush it off, you say, "Oh, well, whoa,
whoa. It's my uh uh it's my gambling
account." Which, bro, it doesn't look
right. nothing what you're saying looks
looks right in the slightest because bro
listen you would not show the whole
point of it is to show as much money as
you possibly can. That's the whole
point. Why would you show less than what
I've asked when if you have a main
account that's not your gambling account
that has a lot more? Surely to God you
would own me. You really really are a
try hard. So even when you've put this
up you just owned yourself and um so
we'll carry on. But if you can show me
1% of their stats 9, bro, listen,
listen. Right. This is how the game
works again. Let me explain it to you
because um you're asking me to show you
money again. Right? Remember how the
game works. Someone shows money,
someone doubles the money. So you're
probably wondering, why am I asking
people to show 10 grand? Brother, I've
shown £6,000 in cash. Double that. I
said just show me 10. Even though it is
theoretically 12, I said, "Just show me
10." You're showing me less than 10
grand, which is what all you've got, and
you're trying to brush it off as a
gambling account, and then you're asking
me to show you £933.
Brother, when you show me that 10 grand,
and this goes to anyone else who's
watching this, then come back to me and
start asking me to show money. That's
that's the way the game work. It's it's
not it's not me showing money time and
time again. you don't show nothing and
then you show less and then asking me to
show you money. That's not the way the
game works. So, if you really want me to show you,
you know, uh, you know, um, one one out
of 1% of what you're showing me, okay,
show me my 10 grand. I didn't go
anywhere. This is not 10 grand. This is
less than 10 grand. So, yeah. Try again,
bro. I'll show you another account with
three time three times as much as this.
Really? Well, why haven't you already
think Think about that, right? Let's
just let's just read what you've just
said. I'll show you another account with
three times as much as this. When have
you already done that? If you generally
had an account that had three times as
much as what you're showing, which is
less than my 10 grand, which I've been
asking you to show, why haven't you
showed it to me yet?
These people don't they don't help
themselves. Think think about it, right?
If you had three different accounts,
right, and somebody was saying, "Oh,
your skin, you're this, you're that,
you're this." And somebody was asking
you to show 10 grand,
would you show an account that had less
than 10 grand, or would you show an
account that you have the most money on?
You'd show the account that has the most
money on. So, you don't make any sense.
And not everyone on here is broke as
joke, and pathetic as you, nearly 30,
living in your mom's. Okay, now you're
saying I'm nearly 30, but let's just put
this into perspective. You have said
that I'm almost 30 for the past 4 years.
And 4 years has gone by and I'm still
not 30. But you, you're in your 40s. You
spend all your life on YouTube all day
every day being a keyboard warrior
projecting, you know, and then like when
people call you out, call you out, you
shy away. Yeah, bro. I'm almost 30.
You've been saying I'm almost 30 for the
past 4 years and I'm still nowhere near
30. So I mean, bro, like you don't need
to hate the fact that you're the one
that's in your 40s and and and you've
reach I generally think, yeah, this
whole you're almost 30. It it it stems
from the fact that you know that you are
in your 40s, you're old and wrinkly and
your life is over. Um that's why you do
all of this. But yeah, it the the the
the the point is is that I don't
understand if you had three different accounts, right?
Why you would show an account that has
the least on because you don't even have
10 grand. Even when you put all your
pennies together like here, you still
couldn't get to that 10 grand. And that
explains why I'm undefeated. A year and
a half later, I'm undefeated. So, if you
are actually going to do a video um or
do a you know a community post next time
or whatever, actually sew £10,000 or
show more because that way you won't
embarrass yourself just like you just
did now. So, yeah. See you later, man.