Yo. Okay. So, I just wanted to do a
video basically uh to basically put into
perspective on how bad the jealousy is
towards me and the stalking is towards
me. And this is basically why I figured
that there's just no point coming on
here anymore because these jealous
people will never ever stop. You know,
people have told me before like you're
better looking than them, you got more
money than them, you got a better life
than them, and it kills them and just to
get off of YouTube. But back then, bro,
I wasn't really
listening cuz I just thought it was a
wind up. But no, these people are
clearly clearly jealous of something.
Like, I'm not going to start making
accusations of what it is or whatever,
but it's like if they're just put it
this way, right? If they're coming on
YouTube every day trying to say that
you're skin and you're ugly and you're
this and you're that, why are they
wasting every second of their life every
single day on you and not getting paid
for it? Then your mind will be like, uh,
this kind of will go like to a fog. Then
you'll actually realize that they are
the skinned ugly montas. This is why
they do exactly what they do every day.
There's there's no there's no other way
that can justify it but jealousy. Like
if you look right at all of what these
this is exa every single time I come on
YouTube this happens right this
literally the same thing happens and it
doesn't happen to anybody else like no
one like not even Timmy which it's it's
crazy and before I get into this video
right reply to these fat ugly insecure losers right
bro this is not your 20,000 yeah how
many people have come on
and showed fake bank accounts and fake
bank statements and they've been caught
out on it. If you are going to show
money, at least show cash because like
there's been a history of people um you
know [ __ ] showing fake bank
statements and fake [ __ ] bank
accounts. Now here's the thing, right?
You got all of these 40-year-old
disabled ugly people coming on here
every second of every day talking about
you and talking about your looks. But
isn't it funny how not one of them can
show their face due to them the ones
being ugly and not you? Isn't Isn't that
the madness? Like they're coming here
saying that you're this and you're that
and you're this. Yeah, they're the ones
that can't show their face due to them
being so very insecure and so very ugly.
I mean, I'm not trying to say I'm funny
here, but I mean, that is the truth of
it. Like, so I'll respond to some
comments, right? Yeah. If I showed him
what I have in my account, he'd be
joining his bro and dad. Yeah, bro.
Whatever. I believe it. Yeah, man. Cool.
You got all this money. You got this
life. I'm the m you waste every second
of every day on YouTube obsessed and
stalking me. Yeah, I know, bro. because
I'm the one that's skin and I'm the one
that's the ma. You see how none of it
makes sense. And then you wrote, "Keep
up with the good work in destroying the
ma." Believe you me, right? Hand on my
heart. Like, I'm putting my hand right
on my heart here and I'm saying this to
you. You fat, ugly 40year-old rejects
don't destroy no one but yourselves.
Right? You've been on here for years
doing this. Year in year out, day in day
out, talking about yourselves, calling
yourself a ma, you know, calling
yourselves skin. You've been doing this
for years. And how does it feel in them
years? You've got nothing out of it.
You've not ruined my life. You've not
destroyed me. You've not done anything.
You've just wasted your own life and you
ain't got paid for it. Think about it.
If all the time you spent projecting
your ugliness and your skinnness and
whatever onto me, you actually got a job
yourself, bro, you you'd probably be set
for life, you know, just to put into
perspective of how many hours that
you've actually put into this. And bro,
you actually would be um you'd actually
be rich. But what have you achieved in
four or five years projecting your [ __ ]
life onto me every single day? Nothing
but made your life even more [ __ ]
So, at the end of the day, I mean, it's
not even just that. I mean, you people
have been destroyed, bro. You're like,
most of you have probably been bullied
in school for being so fat and ugly.
That's why you come on here every day to
feel special. And, bro, listen. Listen,
you're really going to try and call me a
M. Okay, but if you are going to do
that, can you at least show your face?
But nah, you're never going to do that,
are you? Because remember when Bomb and
Pat used to call people Ma every single
day, just like you did? What do they
turn out looking like? A million times
worse than the other person that they
were calling. I've noticed that with you
people on here. You're all the same with
your projecting comments, with your
cowardness. Like, I've I've I've
actually noticed it, bro. You have never
ever destroyed me and you will never
ever destroy me. You're just weirdo skin
ugly 40-year-old weirdos that ain't got
a life, low lives, aka. And then,
right, you got [ __ ] Chase, right?
Hold on, bro. You're really, really
going to try and call me a M with your
patchy ass beard. With your patchy ass
beard and your rat face, you're really
going to try and call me the M. Am I
really the M, bro? Okay, show your face.
Show everybody your face. I've seen your
face, but not everyone. Um, I wonder if
all of these people that are trying to
call me the manta is actually going to
show their face and own me because they
like to say that they show money by, you
know, fake bank statements and bank
accounts. Let's see if any of them could
actually prove that they're better
looking than me. Nah, never in a million
years. That's when you always have one
over on these 40-year-old ugly disabled people,
right? So, here's one, right? He will
never understand. This is all man money
for adults to have in a savings account.
Obsession. And then here's another
thing. This screams projection. PJ is
too addicted to gambling to ever have
money. Not addicted to gambling. I don't
even gamble much anymore. So, you must
be talking about yourself. I don't play
slots. I don't play roulette. He will
never see that six grand again as as he
lives in reality. Bro, listen. These
people that are commenting, like I said,
they're 40year-old fat, ugly, sorry ass
losers that ain't got a pot to piss in.
It's clear as day. What they do on
YouTube, like this guy and all of these
comments, it's so obvious, bro. It's so
obvious why they do what they do. And um
here we go. Right. So
I like it when he says he's shown
thousands. He's shown it once only
because he won on roulette. He will
never have that money to ever show again
and acts like he does. He's on benefits.
Everyone on benefits is skin. Okay, hold
on. Hold on a minute.
>> So, I don't actually know what this
guy's problem is. I caught you being a
snake, right? And then I called you out
on it saying like, "If you got anything
to say, [ __ ] come and say it to my
face. Don't [ __ ] start writing [ __ ]
and then come on my YouTube channel
licking my ass." Like, that that is what
I don't one thing I don't understand. I
I can't get is when someone's licking
your ass and then uh
um you know what I'm saying? Uh yeah.
And then try and lick your ass. Sorry, I
just read that comment. And I like it
when he says he's shown thousand. He's
shown it once. No, no, no. You as in you
people, you got shown thousands and
thousands multiple multiple times,
right? and you got shown it on different
occasions for the period of about three
or four months. In them three or four
months, you showed me nothing, which was
the evidence that I needed to show that
you people are the ones that don't have
anything. And it's not even just
thousands. Like, you've been shown 700,
800, 1,000, 2,000, 3,000. And none of
you people in any of them occasion shown
me anything. So it doesn't matter if it
was shown a million times once. I mean,
I think you're you're actually
uh you're trying to uh show you're
actually trying to uh talk about the
time when I showed that six grand. This
the same six grand that was shown for 4
months. And in them 4 months, none of
you can ever show me anything, which was
the evidence that I needed that whatever
all this skin talk on YouTube is self-p projection.
That's what came to like. Yeah. He will
be absolutely fuming inside. Now you've
shown 20 grand. I bet he can't show 200
right now. Never mind 20K.
I can't show 200 right now. Why would I
show you £200, bro? Come on. You've got
all of this money, right?
You've got all of this money. Why would
you want me to show you £200? If you've
got all of this money, why would you be
telling me to show you £200? It's
because you don't have £200. You want
people to show you the money that you
don't have, that you wish you had. Yeah,
that's what it is. But bro, you've been
shown 200s, 300s, 400s, 500s, thousands.
You don't show nothing. Why would you
want me to show you £200 so you can run
away again like you always do, like all
of you people do? You sit there and you
ask people to show you money. And then
when people show you money, what do you
do? You run away because you ain't got
no money. It's a part of your self
projecting ways, you know, like
someone's ugly and someone's got no
friends, you know, all of this self-
projecting [ __ ] that you do. That's part
of it. Show me money. Show me money. And
as soon as someone shows you money, you
run away. Think about it, bro. You got
shown thousands for months and months
and months. Why couldn't you show me
anything if you truly weren't skin?
Exactly. Cuz you are the ones that are
skin. And then I've gone on your [ __ ]
thing here right now. He walks up to
them like he's got a great life he can
offer them. This is complete jealousy
right here. You just know that this
little [ __ ] 40year-old little loser
living in hole. I do remember this guy
by the way just wishes he could have
cold approached women and he could do
all of this and do all of that but I can
but he can't. He's just sat in hole skin
probably in [ __ ] shared
accommodation. And then he then goes and
then projects his life onto you saying
that you got no job, no money, no house,
no car, no future. But the funny thing
is is you've been shown all of these
things. You're telling me that I don't
have this, I don't have that, brother.
The only one that don't have those
things is your sorry ugly ass in whole.
That's the only pe person that doesn't
have these things. And do you know what
makes this the most funniest? Now
obviously Milton Kees is not London but
bro you you live in the the worst place
voted by Britain hole is worse than
Middlesbrough and you're going to sit
there and try and tell me in your little
[ __ ] beds sitting hole with your sorry
ass what I have and what I don't have.
Bro, come on now. No job. You've seen me
work. No money. show more money than any
of you. And guess what? All of the money
I shown, there was proof it was actually
mine. There's not been proof on here
that everyone that show money is
actually theirs because of the bank
statements and the bank accounts. No
house, no car, no future.
>> Bro, every single person's got a future
in their 20ies. You know where I'm
getting at with this now? Everybody with
a f everybody in their 20ies has a
future. You don't have a future. You
live in a hole. You are in your 40s.
That's where you get all of this [ __ ]
No car, no money, no future because
that's yourself, bro. Hull. The v it is
literally voted the worst place and
you're in your 40s. Think about it, bro.
I'm 27 and I don't Let's just say I
didn't have a penny to my name. I'm in
London. There's always a future when
you're in your 20s and you're in London.
You're in your 40s and you're in the
most deprived area in Britain. It's even
worse than Middlesbrough. If that's not self-p projecting,
I will never know what is. Um, so yeah,
and it's crazy. So, this is one of the
main reasons why I am coming off of this
YouTube uh, you know, for a very, very
long time, if not ever, bro. Um because
these people's obsession and their
jealousy towards me ain't ever going to
stop. So um yeah, that's just to put in
perspective of basically what I've been
dealing with for years with these
people. Clear as day jealousy. I've
never known so many people in their 40s
be jealous of somebody that they don't
even know. I just I just it's it's it's
mad. It's probably mad to most normal
people that's watching this as well.
It's crazy, man.