Y. Okay. So, this is going to be a
video. Yeah. To Rick's Mace, I'm going
to show you how you uh use a washing
machine because I was quite surprised. I
went on your live stream the other day
and you said you don't know how to use a
washing machine. So, you want you want
to use a Heaen's washing machine to
start with if you're um going to know if
you don't have a washing machine, which
I don't think you have. So, you buy one
of these. Could be any any um any any
any any model. And what you want to do
is you want to put your clothes in um
Rick's mace. But you want to put them
inside out. I mean, you don't have to,
but it's the best way. I've always
washed my clothes inside out, no matter
um you know what what they are. So, I'll
pause and resume when they're all inside
out, and then I'll go through the next
steps. One second. Right. So, it's all
inside out, right? So, obviously, this
is a dark wash rick. So, you can either
put it on a 20, 30, or a 40, but I
normally just put bedding in on a 40.
Um, or if there's loads and loads of
blacks or if there's a stain. But
anyways, everything's inside out. Throw, throw, throw.
And yeah, here we go. The washing's in.
Now, second part, Rex is
you need to buy some bombs or gel or
powder, whatever. And you put one in the
machine. Oh, one second.
One in the machine. Now, you don't need
more than one, but this is what I like
to do. So, I put one in the machine. I
get another one, right?
And I dissolve it so it's all nice and fluffy. One second.
Um, oh my gosh, there's that one here.
Right. So, just wait a moment. So, what
you do is uh
dark wash. I'm going to put on a 30. So,
this is for like really expensive dark
stuff. This is for some blacks. This is
for blacks and whites. And that is just
for whites, nets, whatever. So, we're
going to put it on a 30 Ricks. This only
goes to a th00and spin. Depends on the
program. If you can only spin it to
a,000, just respin it when it finishes.
And then you press start. Right.
So, obviously, if you're washing docks,
just follow the way that I done it and
it'll be grand. And then what I do is
I bo You have to boil the kettle, by the
way. Get a little spoon.
Again, you don't have to do this, but I
I like my clothes to be extra clean. You see?
Just mix it. Let it dissolve.
It's dissolving nicely.
All right. So, this is like I said, you
can use gel, you can use powder. If you
use powder, you have to dissolve it.
Fist bombs. I would say I would say you
still uh dissolve it. And obviously, if
it's gel, you don't have to. Just whisk
it like that. I'm extra with the
washing, by the way. But if you follow
my tips, you'll be grand. I done a bed
in yesterday, but I had to quickly go to
the cinema, so didn't have time to record it.
So what you do is
there we go.
And then this one second is to make the
clove soft, to make the clove smell
nice. Um I would highly recommend this.
Um people say you don't need it, but you
definitely do. There's so many ones to
choose from. Um these are my washed
stuff. I bought them myself. So just
wait. as you can see.
And if you need any more tips, Ricks, on
how to cook food or how to brush your
teeth or well, in your case, even to
wipe your own [ __ ] ass, um, you know,
just just just let your boy know and
he's here for you for absolutely free,
you know, even if even if you need a
guide on how to wipe your backside,
you know. So anyways, look, as you can see,
so what you do is wait about 20 seconds.
It's going to start moving now. So this
is what it does. It washes, rinses,
that goes, and then it rinses again. As
you can see, you'll be able to see the
bubbles even though it's black and it's uh transparent,
I think, is the word you actually would
call it. Right.
As you can see the bubbles and it's black.
It's black and you can still see the
bubbles. You see? That's what we like.
We like to see bubbles mix. That's yummy. Right.
Let me pause one sec.
Right. Here we go. So, you can see
lovely bubbles. That's what I love to see.
And then Rick one second.
Have to tip that cuz it's got a bit flooded.
So obviously you might get water in the
middle bit now. Rips. So basically
you can if you wanted to get powder.
They say that you're supposed to put
powder here, Rick. I wouldn't recommend
it because cold water don't dissolve
powder. And if you put cold water with
powder, it comes out with a powder still
on it. Hence the dissolving. Same same
the reason same reason with the bombs.
Um so if you're getting powder, make
sure you dissolve it with boiling water.
And this is where you put this. And this
is what will that's what your clothes
will come out smelling like. Uh Ricks.
Absolutely lovely. And like I said,
there's many of these to choose from.
Um, you just look for fabric uh
conditioner and just pick the one that's
smells to your taste basically. And um,
yeah, and then you just close it and you
wait. And then Bob's your uncle. There.
There you go, Rick. You've got a new
uncle with the name Bob. Not that hard
at all, as you can see. Lovely washing.
And Bob's your uncle. Thank me later, boss.