do this once she's working.
>> Excuse me. Yeah, sorry. Um, I just
walked past you and I noticed you and I
thought you look nice in it. So, I
wanted to um come and say hi. Like I
know you're working really nice of you.
>> I know you're working at
say hi. Anyways, where you from?
>> From Lithuania.
>> Lithuania. Oh, okay. So, you come here
for work or
>> working studying?
>> Studying. How How are you finding it?
>> You like it? Okay, cool. Nice. Yeah. So,
any time for today?
>> Just working for the rest of the day.
>> Working and then what? Just going home.
>> Going home. Go gym.
>> Go to the gym. Yeah. I need to get back
in the gym. I was at the gym for like
over a month. Then I just stopped going.
I need to need to get back on it. But um
yeah. What's your name? >> Eveina.
>> Eveina. Oh, I I used to know somebody
called me Eveina.
You know, my name is Peter. Peter.
>> Yeah. I was going to say maybe wanted to
do something another time.
>> Think about it. I mean, I'm still going
to be here, so you're going to be
passing through. Just remind me next time.
>> Remind you next time.
>> Next time. I mean, I'm going to add
>> Have you got Instagram? >> Instagram? >> Yeah.
>> What's that?
>> I do WhatsApp, but
>> you know what? I have a really busy
schedule. Yeah, but we can make time for >> Yeah.
>> Can I write Can I give you mine number?
>> Yeah, I'll write mine over there. Where?