Okay, I'm going to do this one here. [ __ ] it. [Music]
>> Is this
amazing thing? We do it. He's going to
say you were married. >> No.
>> Where you from?
>> Uh London.
>> Oh, nice. Yeah. Love it.
>> Yeah, they're really friendly. It
>> was fine. You live in London?
>> I do.
>> I love how
>> they are. Do you know it's like a thing?
Yeah, I know.
>> What's your name? Bronty. Nice to meet
you. Thank you.
She was nice to be fair. At least she
was nice though. I think I actually
think she was open. I was like, "Mate,
I'm sending this. I have to." Do you
know what I'm saying? Like, yeah, she
was actually really nice to be fair
though. That's probably one of Well,
that American was all right.
Um, so that American need to try and get
an Australian. I think if you got an
an Australian would
>> I don't think I think I have done a new but
>> all right now I need to do one more [Music]
>> right so we need to do
one more and then we need to hit the
bars and I need a drink cuz I am
tired man I've been walking around for May literally
And now we're trying to send these. But
yeah, bear in mind people, this is
really difficult like doing it on the
street. You get you're lucky to get one
number. What happened there that time? I
was lucky, man.
>> I got [ __ ] over the end anyway.
>> it was good whilst it lasted. Right. I
need to do one more.
Hopefully this last one is uh
Hopefully this last one Let me Let me
set that back a little bit.
>> Hopefully this last one will be sick.
>> Uh, she's all right.
>> Hopefully the last one is the one we get
the number from which is
>> which is we're still thinking. I am aware.
>> Is she waving? >> Okay,
I'm trying to assess the situation.
I am assessing the situation.
>> I need to start targeting people that
are the same ethnicity as me as well,
>> which I keep forgetting to do. I want to do [ __ ] [Music]
>> I'm going to guess Germany. Maybe [Music]
I want to go to Germany. I was supposed
to go last year on train. [Music]
>> What are you doing in London?
So, how long were you in? [Music]
>> Been here before.
>> What's your name? >> Pizza.
And how old are you?
Huh? What do I think? Hold on. I've always
guessed Germany. I'm like,
yeah. Like, you know, like
a lot of them were like German. So, like [Music]
I was going to say I do Instagram [Music] relationships.
They don't take anywhere.
>> That's very strange because
they tell people to approach them and
then when you approach them they say
they're not interested, which I am literally like
70% sober. So they tell people to
approach them and be brave on the street
and then when you do it they say they're not interested.
But I'm not negative cuz we still got the bars.
Very strange though. It is very very
strange cuz they literally they
literally tell people to approach them
like if you actually go on any forum and
then I ask them why so then I can see
what I can do better. But yeah, I don't
know man. It's very strange. Very
strange indeed. But anyways, moving on.
One more. I feel like I'm going to say
one more. One more and then one more
after. Okay, I'm going to do one more.
Uh, this time I'm not going to record
any ring. Um, yeah.