So, I said I was going to do these approaches.
>> The next station is >> doach.
So, I was just about to walk past you
and I wanted to say that I thought you
>> This is an line service to your name [Music]
>> via Heathro terminal.
like a greeting.
>> There you go. Where you from?
>> The next station is
>> I'm going to go back to my seat anyways.
I was going to say how's your WhatsApp? >> Um
I have that guy.
>> You have a guy? Yeah. Take
>> [ __ ] bro. This how you know you're
troing on the train.
Oh my god. Did I even feel I don't even
feel that nervous to be honest. I
haven't even started drinking yet. But yeah,
I'm I think I'm mad, bro. That is mad.
That is actually mad, bro.
I was fist bumping her and she didn't
know what it was. It's sort of like a greeting.
>> We are now arriving at
>> A lot of people don't want to shake
people's hands nowadays, but uh there
you go. Must say I'm going to do
something, mate. I'll do it.