Let me do this one. [Music]
>> Excuse me. I had to say
I had to say that beautiful.
>> Hi. What's your name?
>> Where you from, J? >> Cypress.
>> Cypress. Oh, you actually I'm actually
>> Oh, fair enough. I'm caught up.
>> Yeah. So, what are you like? Half full or
>> Well, I'm My parents are British, but
I'm born and raised in
>> Oh, see. Fair. Fair.
>> Oh, my dad's really English. And then my
mom's half, so I'm caught up, but like
she was born here, so she's very like westernized.
>> So, yeah.
>> But what's life?
>> It's really nice, but I'm
>> You're in a rush? Yeah,
>> I'm not late.
>> Okay. I don't know. Take your time.
>> Can I take your number? Take and take
you to Lando sometime.
>> You do? Yeah. Anyways, nice to meet you.
>> Nice to meet you. Thank you.
>> There we go. Another one down the drain.
[ __ ] me, man. We need to absolutely
>> I'm not even supposed to be really doing
it in this place.
Um because she's not keeping up.
>> Not not supposed to be doing in this
place, but uh >> yeah,
I was supposed to in another place, but
anyways, we'll do like one more here and
then we'll go to where we actually
really wanted to go and we'll keep sitting. There.