It's going to be the last one I'm
recording, so hopefully it's a good one.
>> All right, let me pause and resume when
I found someone.
I'm going to do this one. [ __ ] it.
>> What's up, man?
>> Excuse me. Sorry. I just wanted to come over.
>> Oh, thank you so much. What's your name?
>> Uh, Bella.
>> Where you from?
>> Uh, Canada. just visiting. >> Yeah.
>> How long are you here for?
>> Um, couple more days. >> Yeah.
>> What about my boyfriend?
>> Yeah. Well, thank you.
>> What's up?
>> Uh, I have a boyfriend.
>> You have a boyfriend? >> Yeah.
>> Take care.
>> Why? I have done about
five of these approaches. Six of these
approaches now sober. And every single
one of them have told me they have a
boyfriend. It's never this bad, bro.
Never this bad. It will never change. I
think like there was hope before two
years ago that maybe, maybe, but now
I've never had that in a row before.
Like you get it, but no, it will never change.
>> What the press in life, eh?