Here's one here.
>> Excuse me. Sorry. Just before you walk
past me, I just wanted to say that I
thought you looked really beautiful.
>> What's your name?
>> Have a lovely day. Oh, wow. She didn't
even ask for my name.
How the hell are we supposed to get into
a relationship when I can barely get two
words out of someone? I can't even get
them interested enough to even go beyond
the first word. It's crazy. But this
this is an indication, right, of what
it's actually like in this area
particularly. They're all because the
thing is here, most of them are just
from England. So, they're all snobs.
They all just think they're better than
everyone. That's why when you go to
central London, it's a tiny bit better.
People are more open to sort of talking
a little bit more. But this is
horrendous, mate. And this this is my
area as well. I can't even get a word
out of anyone.
I'm actually kind of wanting to hear the
boyfriend now, bro, cuz at least they're
actually paying attention to what you're
[ __ ] saying. You know what I'm
saying, bro? It's a madness.
All I've been getting is two words. It's
crazy. What the [ __ ]