Let me do this one. Hold on. I'm going
to do this. [Music]
>> Excuse me. Excuse me. Sorry. I just
wanted to come over and say that.
>> Oh, thanks.
>> What's your name?
>> It's Chloe, but I've got a boyfriend. I do.
>> There we go.
>> Don't even give me the chance.
Stone cold sober.
Haven't even drunk yet. Oh no,
that sounded like a lead accent to me.
And this is all you ever get in England.
Doesn't matter what you look like,
what you're I mean, I'm wearing a hat.
I'm rocking a hat nowadays, but you just
don't get nothing. Not even not even a
conversation, man. When you do get a
conversation, it's I have a boyfriend.
So, yep. But people still tell you that
you're going to meet someone.
It's not looking great, is it?