Gonna do one here. Yeah. Smack [ __ ] public.
Um, I was standing over there and I see
you and I think you look nice, so I want
to come and say hello.
>> Well, what what country are you from? >> Sorry.
>> Okay. I've heard of it, but I'm not
really familiar. But I've heard back
where it is.
>> Yeah. Where was it?
>> Yeah. Where you from?
>> I'm from London. I I live in East
London. I've been in London my whole life.
>> Oh, okay. I didn't think that. I've heard.
>> So, what what do you do in London?
>> How are you finding?
I don't think I did.
>> It's your first time or
>> living here?
>> Uh, just being here. >> No,
you've been here a few times.
>> Yeah. And then I >> Okay.
>> To me, I I live in London, but I
normally when I go out, I travel out of
London because when you live in London,
you've been here so long, you sort of
get bored. So you want to go to like
other places. Yeah. Like I was in
Sheffield last week, then two weeks
before that I was in Cardiff. Like I
just I just I just go all around the country.
There's so many places to go. People from
out of London think Oh, London's like
all of England.
Not too much.
>> Yeah. So, so what what cities have you
been to when you've
gone to the Midlands? >> Yeah.
>> So, like >> Okay.
>> I've also gone to um
>> Okay. Yeah. Raspberry.
>> I've heard of that. Yeah.
>> Yeah, I've heard of that.
>> Oh, okay. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Lake district.
>> Yeah. Lake district. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. >> Windsor.
>> Windsor. Yeah. >> Cambridge.
>> Oh, nice. Nice.
So, not not too far from London, but out of London.
>> No, that's not
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah.
>> That That's crazy because I went to
Scotland two times before I went to
Wales. So, I went to like two three
weeks ago, but before that, I went to
Scotland two times. Scotland.
>> Yeah. I've always been I've been to
Belgium and Amsterdam, but I've always like
>> Why Why do you ask that? places.
>> You want me to tell you all the place
I've been to?
>> Well, no. It just sounds like you've been to
>> Okay, name me some place. I'll tell you.
>> Say it.
>> Been there.
>> I've been to Bristol.
>> I've been to I've been to Manchester, Newcastle.
Birmingham. I've been to about
I don't really know where else I can go to that.
>> How old are you?
>> I'm really bad at uh maybe 23. >> Younger.
>> How old are you? >> Yes.
No, I'm really
>> No, just I I will not take advantage of
if you if you if you if you guess my age.
>> No, no, no. If you if you I won't take
>> 25. What would you say?
>> I think I would have
just it was a little bit shorter.
>> 25. Okay. When when's your birthday?
>> You're older than me. >> October.
>> Cuz I met somebody before. They have
exactly the same date of birth. Exactly
the same. 27%. >> It
What are you doing after? You just go
I don't know what I'm going to do,
>> but hey, I'm going to go anyway. But
maybe another time for like [Music]
You want to London London is so big like
loads of people every day. One day every
>> But I listen I take your number. [Music]
>> I don't know. I don't I like don't give my number.
>> I know you're not involved. You're not
No, but listen. I I said your number.
I don't know. I don't never give my number out
cuz I come so high. How How many people
do you get that come and say hello to you? [Music]
Oh, another guy you [Music]
>> have Instagram, >> huh?
>> You have Instagram? >> Yeah.
>> Follow me.
>> I I type my Instagram. You follow me?
>> I follow you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I follow you back. [Music]
My phone back.
>> Nice to meet you. Take care. Enjoy your night. Hello.