[Music]
Right. So, I'm off the train now. Really are sweating. Absolutely sweating.
Right. Let me go simple approach.
This person here [ __ ] [Music] Thank you.
>> The US [Music]
>> um uni, but now I'm living here working.
Oh, nice. So, how long have you been here?
>> 2 and a2 years.
>> 2 and 12 years. >> Yes.
>> You like it? Yeah.
>> Yeah. I love it. I'm not going back anytime soon.
>> Mad. I applied for
>> visa like book or accepted in 2 hours. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. At some point like either late
this year or next year somewhere like
>> Yeah, do it. I mean,
>> what's your name? >> Kylie.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> So, what do you do for work then? Uh, digital marketing.
>> Digital marketing.
>> So, I actually market a lot of theater
shows around here.
>> New York.
>> Going to go meet my boyfriend. >> Yeah.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> Thank you so much.
>> It's fine. It's fine. Hopefully you hopefully.
>> Of course. Have a good day. >> Killer.
I knew as soon as she stopped she was
American because there's no way someone
that's British has stopped like that. No
way. No bloody way. I would have bagged
that. I 100% would have bad that if it
weren't for my heart was [ __ ] beating
out my chest, bro. I would have bad that
she had a boyfriend. [ __ ]
I'm going to get a number. Don't worry.
I'll lick one, bro. Trust [Music]
now. I feel like I'm over that sort of
Jesus Christ. My heart's beating up my
chest, mate. Literally. [Music]
>> Can't believe that. I thought I had that
bloody boy. Why? Why talk to me for like
2 minutes then? What's up, man?
>> Yeah, man. >> Uh,
now I need to try and pull one off where
one actually gives me a number. [ __ ]
America, man. [ __ ] hell.
I thought she was going to say she was
from somewhere else, mate. I'm not going
to say where, but back in. All right. So, I'll try
>> a few more. And uh yeah, m I have to I'm
going to do about four or five.
About four or five. Yeah, I think after
four or five,
>> I feel like that's it.
>> On the street, of course. I'm sure that bars
H [ __ ] sake.